<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./AAAHH!!! Real Monsters.zip</path>
		<name>Aaahh!!! Real Monsters</name>
		<desc>Greetings, terror-trainees! Ickis, Krumm, and Oblina will have to prove themselves on the Monster midterm exams if they want to call themselves real monsters! They must work together as a team to receive a single gruesome grade on their frightful performance. So...go out and petrify someone!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/AAAHH!!! Real Monsters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ActRaiser 2.zip</path>
		<name>ActRaiser 2</name>
		<desc>The Destroyer is back... Amazing graphics, spellbinding music, 100% action adventure, all taking place in a universe of ghouls and furies! Dive into the dream... or the nightmare!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/ActRaiser 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero Fighters.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters is an Action game, developed and published by Video System,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Aero Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero the Acro-Bat.zip</path>
		<name>Aero the Acro-Bat</name>
		<desc>Step right up to the acro-batiest show on earth! The madman industrialist Edgar Ektor has siezed control of the World of Amusement. He and a deranged cast of fairground freaks threaten the circus. The only hope for survival is the high-flying, death-defying Aero the Acro-Bat! Spine-tingling terror unfolds as Aero tackles Ektor's wicked henchmen. Bungee jump into a battle with evil! Skydive in mode 7 toward the danger below. Hang on for the ride of your life as you rise and plunge on a roaring roller coaster! Tiptoe across a terrifying tightrope! Then power drill and twist Aero right through every sinister circus enemy imaginable. And all the while, the show must go on!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Aero the Acro-Bat-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero the Acro-Bat 2.zip</path>
		<name>Aero the Acro-Bat 2</name>
		<desc>The aerialist extreme, Aero the Acro-Bat bounds back into the spotlight once again to stop the wicked industrialist, Edgar Ektor! Aero has entered a new realm of enchantment and must now use all his acrobatic prowess to foil a criminal plot known only as 'Plan B!' Join Aero as he discovers new friends (and enemies) in a world custom built for his high-flying adventures.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Aero the Acro-Bat 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin.zip</path>
		<name>Aladdin</name>
		<desc>For years, Jafar, the Sultan's evil advisor has sought a magic treasure - a single lamp that holds the key to the greatest power in the world. With this goal in sight, Jafar learns that only one person in the world can claim the magic lamp from the dreaded Cave of Wonders - one whose rags hide a heart that is pure - a diamond in the rough!Join Aladdin and his pet monkey Abu, as they race through the marketplace toward their date with destiny. Watch as Jafar tricks our hero and his friend into retrieving the lamp from the dangerous Cave of Wonders. But Aladding and Abu outwit Jafar, releading the power of a wacky blue Genie! Aladding will have the chance to spoil Jafar's devious plans and win the hand of the beautiful princess Jasmine. But it will take more than magic to make his wishes come true...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Aladdin-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alcahest.zip</path>
		<name>Alcahest</name>
		<desc>Alcahest is an action role-playing game with a top-down perspective that plays similar to The Legend of Zelda. It is divided into 8 stages that are progressed by finding items that aid the protagonist Alen on his quest, and end with a boss battle. After specific boss fights, the player will gain the abilities of one of the four elemental Guardians. Alen will also find five allies that will join him at predetermined points of some levels. They are the young wizard Garstein, the princess Elikshil, the knight Sirius, the android Magna and the shape-shifter dragon goddess Nevis. Though they cannot be controlled directly, allies will attack and use special moves when the corresponding button is pressed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Alcahest-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Labs</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien 3.zip</path>
		<name>Alien 3</name>
		<desc>The ALIENS are fast, spit acid and are right behind you! The motion tracker is your only warning. No time to think, no time to catch your breath... RUN! Can't see very far ahead in these air ducts. Hard to breathe. Face-huggers can be anywhere. You have the firepower... blast the ALIENS with your machine gun, flame thrower and grenade launcher. You know what you have to do... rescue the trapped prisoners and end this nightmare! Just keep telling yourself, 'This isn't really happening. It's only a game!!!'</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Alien 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment Limited</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./American Tail, An - Fievel Goes West.zip</path>
		<name>An American Tail: Fievel Goes West</name>
		<desc>An American Tail: Fievel Goes West is an Action game, developed by Shimada Kikaku and published by Hudson,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/American Tail, An - Fievel Goes West-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shimada Kikaku</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arabian Nights.zip</path>
		<name>Arabian Nights: Sabaku no Seirei-ou</name>
		<desc>In this Japan-exclusive Super Famicom game, the player assumes the role of an orphan named Shukran, who is accompanied by the djinn Ifrit on her adventures to bring peace to her desert homeland.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Arabian Nights-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19960614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandora Box</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ardy Lightfoot.zip</path>
		<name>Ardy Lightfoot</name>
		<desc>The rainbow has been broken into 7 pieces! Ardy, our young and brave adventurer, with Pec, his friend-for-ever, are ready to sacrifice their lives to gather the 7 gems containing the colors of the rainbow, then their wishes will come true and they will finally save Nina from the clutches of Visconty.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ardy Lightfoot-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Axelay.zip</path>
		<name>Axelay</name>
		<desc>Mysterious aliens have invaded the Earth-like planet of Corliss, slowly draining the planet's resources. Take control of the prototype Axelay ship and use its wide range of advanced weaponry to battle enemy forces. Play through multiple stages of action --from other planets to space stations -- all on your way to destroying the alien headquarters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Axelay-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman Returns.zip</path>
		<name>Batman Returns</name>
		<desc>One oversized bird and one stinky cat are out to take control of this urban jungle. Only you, as Batman, possess the power to stop the sinister plots of The Penguin and Catwoman!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Batman Returns-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Clash.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Clash</name>
		<desc>The time is the 21st century. In the wake of natural disasters and social unrest, human society has collapsed. The only amusement left for the inhabitants of this grim Earth of the future is the Battle Game. This contest of advanced arena combat pits giant, armored riot suits known as Standing Tanks (ST's) against each other in a fight to the finish. The winner gains power and prestige, while the lower faces humiliation, dishonor and low class citizenship.You are the gunner of the ST Falcon. You friend's father experience defeat in the Battle Game and now you must help him get revenge. Your Super NES Super Scope&amp;trade; gives you complete control of all the Falcon's weapons systems.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Battle Clash-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads in Battlemaniacs.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads in Battlemaniacs</name>
		<desc>Battletoads in Battlemaniacs is an Action game, developed by Rare Ltd. and published by Tradewest,which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Battletoads in Battlemaniacs-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon - The Ultimate Team.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads-Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>When a battle-cruiser the size of a city called the Colossus smashes out of the moon, its laser cannon glowing menacingly, you can bet it ain't gonna be makin' no socian calls...You can bet it's gonna be creating some bad n' crazy mayhem on good ol' planet Earth - 'specially when you know that the dreaded Dark Queen and the shady Shadow Boss are on board just rarin' to rock n' roll...The dastardly duo are about to unleash their most monstrous play yet - from their secret lunar base they intend to launch an invasion that'll make them masters of the world...Neutralized by deadly glooming rays, Earth's forces are powerless... that is, until the Dragons join the Toads!Take a 'toadacious trip with the dream ticket as those terrific twins Billy and Jimmy Lee team up with Zitz, Rash and Pimple against the combined might of the gruesome twosome and their mindless minions, Big Blag, Abobo, Robo-Manus and Roper, in a 'toadally terminal new adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon - The Ultimate Team-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beauty and the Beast.zip</path>
		<name>Beauty and the Beast</name>
		<desc>A self-centered prince is transformed into a hideous beast by the magic of an enchantress. What's more, all his servants have been turned into household objects.Before departing, the enchantress leaves a rose in the hands of his Prince, 'This rose will bloom until your twenty-first birthday. You have until then to find the one you truly love and to earn that person's love in return. If you don't, you will be doomed to remain a beast forever.'</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Beauty and the Beast-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment Limited</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonkers.zip</path>
		<name>Bonkers</name>
		<desc>Bonkers is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Bonkers-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire.zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire</name>
		<desc>In a distant land, peace was maintained for thousands of years by a fearful dragon clan who could transform into powerful monsters. One day they discovered a goddess who could fulfill their every wish. Greed split the clan into Dark and Light Dragons, each battling the other to win her magic.One member of the Light Dragons, along with seven of his companions, emerged to keep the opposing forces from destroying their world. Using six magical keys, they sealed the goddess into another realm.Centuries have passed. The Dark Dragons are destroying the land in search of the keys. When they find the keys, they will once again release the magic goddess. Light Dragon... the time has come to draw your sword and fight for the future of your people.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Breath of Fire-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire II.zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire II</name>
		<desc>The incredible sequel to the best-selling RPG hit Breath of Fire is here! You are the last member of the Dragon clan, fighting to rid the world of a growing evil. A cast of unusual and exciting companions joins you in your adventures across a wondrous land full of magic and mystery. You'll find strange mystic items, memorable monsters and exotic locations in your quest to conquer evil. There's strategy and spellcasting galore in the hours of compelling action and adventure that awaits you. Breath of Fire II is the ultimate in RPG excitement!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Breath of Fire II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capcom's Soccer Shootout.zip</path>
		<name>Capcom's Soccer Shootout</name>
		<desc>Capcom's Soccer Shootout is a Sports game, developed by A-Max and published by Epoch,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Capcom's Soccer Shootout-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A-Max</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger.zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>The millennium. A portal is opened. The chain of time is broken. A young man is transported into the past, altering the course of history and the outcome of the future. He has to find his way home, but first he must travel to the outer edges of time to repair the world's chronology. On the way he encounters strange friends and foes, utilizes incredible devices and vehicles, and penetrates and neutralizes the fortresses of the past, present, and future. A paradox has been created. If he does not restore the order of time, nothing will ever be the same. He is the one who will become a hero. He is Crono.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chrono Trigger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Clock Tower.zip</path>
		<name>Clock Tower</name>
		<desc>Jennifer Simpson and her friends are from Granite Orphanage in Romsdalen, Norway. Adopted by a wealthy recluse named Mr. Barrows, they have come to live in the mansion known as "Clock Tower".

Though, this mansion is not what it seems. Strange experiments are taking place in the shadows, and horrific creatures prowl through the night. Jennifer's friends have gone missing, and now she must rescue them and  try to escape with their lives.

Clock Tower is a haunting adventure with over 10 different endings, and will stick with you long after you've stopped playing. Players beware.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Clock Tower-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Human Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Congo's Caper.zip</path>
		<name>Congo's Caper</name>
		<desc>Congo the monkey and his girl, Congette, were in the jungle minding their own business when a magic ruby dropped out of the sky and turned them both into half-humans. To make matters worse, the ruby also spawned a demon-kid who grabbed Congette and took off. Now you've got to hunt down the kid and find your girl, while adapting to your new form. You'll make your way through ghost towns, pirate ships, ninja castles, and the belly of a Tyrannosaurus on your search. There are 35 levels of side-scrolling action in all, and you'll have your hands full with tons of wild animals that will try to stand in your way. As you run, jump, swim, attack, and dive your way through the game, keep your eyes open for special gems that will give you special powers and open secret levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Congo's Caper-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra III - The Alien Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Contra III: The Alien Wars</name>
		<desc>Welcome to 2636, the year the Notorious One gets even, with an unprecendented alien onsalught orchestrated to push 16-bit technology and its commandos to their ultimate reaches.Plunge through a molten hot massacre on a high speed voyage to the guts of the archenemy alien. Scope out the side and top perspectives and backgrounds that do a 360 to engulf you in 3-D sensation. Pick off solar slimedogs like the Mutant Megasquitos and the Psycho Cyclers while you scale over walls, swing from girders and ropes, hitch rides on a missile, whatever it takes. Sweat through six gut splitting stages, including the Battle of the Blazing Sky and the Mucho Grande Badlands.The graphics are so real the explosions will nearly knock you off your feet. And the Boss Enemies are so gigantic, your screen can hardly hold them. You'll need to wrap both hands around artillery powerful enough to make today's weapons look like squirt guns. The Contra legacy is alive and dangerous!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Contra III - The Alien Wars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T021913</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cool Spot.zip</path>
		<name>Cool Spot</name>
		<desc>NO WAY! Your Cool SPOT chums are locked away! YES WAY! You, as Cool SPOT are here to save the day! Quit gawping over the dreamy scenery, the awesome animation and most savory sound around. Play! Man, this is the hairiest...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Cool Spot-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyborg 009.zip</path>
		<name>Cyborg 009</name>
		<desc>Cyborg 009 is an Action game, published by Bec, which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Cyborg 009-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bec</developer>
		<publisher>Bec</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daffy Duck - The Marvin Missions.zip</path>
		<name>Daffy Duck: The Marvin Missions</name>
		<desc>Get ready to duck and cover. Because the fate of the planets rests squarely on Duck Dodgers--alias Daffy Duck--the fearless space crusader from the cartoon adventure series.Marvin Martian, the extra-fiendish extraterrestrial, is poised to obliterate the galaxy! So choose your weapon. Then help Daffy race from planet to planet in hot pursuit of the outrageous alien.Search secret chambers and caverns for mystery bonuses! Help Daffy shield himself from needles fired by crazed cactus! Block an onsalught of enemy space mines! Battle an undersea army of Instant Martia's (just add water). Finally, look down the barrel of Marvin Martian's P-38 Space Modulator--with its destructive sights set on Earth!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Daffy Duck - The Marvin Missions-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daikaijuu Monogatari.zip</path>
		<name>Daikaijū Monogatari</name>
		<desc>In this clone of Dragon Quest, there are a series of natural disasters that are devastating the planet; causing the great Demon King Fattobajah to emerge from his elemental shell-induced slumber. A hero who carries a fire shell must save the world from a series of truly bad events. Up to ten playable characters can be used as allies in order to stop villains like Dr. Doan, Jalamar, Jodan, and Darkness Knight. The people who inhabit the land of Shelldorado are very smart despite looking like savage monsters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Daikaijuu Monogatari-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19941222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Birthday</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demon's Crest.zip</path>
		<name>Demon's Crest</name>
		<desc>The demon realm is peaceful until six wondrous stones fall from the sky. Each stone represents a portion of the Demon's Crest. When united, the stones of the Demon's Crest bring the user ultimate power over demons and humans.These stones were so highly sought that civil war broke out in the realm. The fight led to much bloodshed until one gargoyle emerged victorious: the red demon known as Firebrand.After Firebrand's final battle, his evil nemesis Phalanx ambushed Firebrand and stole the stones. Now Firebrand must recover the stones and unite the power of the Demon's Crest before both realms fall into the hands of the sinister Phalanx!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Demon's Crest-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Do-Re-Mi Fantasy.zip</path>
		<name>Do Re Mi Fantasy: Milon no DokiDoki Daibouken</name>
		<desc>A young boy named Milon sets off to save Alis, his fairy friend, after she was captured by the evil sorcerer Amon. He later learns that the only way to defeat Amon is by collecting five legendary instruments which Amon has stolen.  The sorcerer placed a curse on these instruments so that their true powers cannot be used and then left them in the hands of his minions.  The only way to lift the curse is by collecting five stars.

Armed with only his bubble shooter, Milon must retrieve the legendary instruments, lift their curses and use their powers to defeat Amon and rescue Alis.

Traveling through many different worlds starting with the forest, Milon will be confronted by many enemies. Milon can either shoot bubbles to trap and send his enemies away, or he can jump and flatten his enemies temporarily turning them into a platform for him to walk across.  

Milon has three different "outfits": red, blue, and green.  With the green outfit, Milon can withstand three hits.  Each time he gets hit, he will be downgraded a color - green to blue, blue to red.  If he gets hit with the red outfit, he will die and have to start the level over.

By collecting 100 music notes, Milon will get an extra life.  There are also other useful items to get like bubble gum that will save Milon once if he were to fall, a special bubble shooter that let's him shoot multiple bubbles at once and a star that makes Milon temporarily invincible so that he can defeat enemies simply by running at them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Do-Re-Mi Fantasy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft Company, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170212T160118</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donald Duck no Mahou no Boushi.zip</path>
		<name>Donald Duck no Mahō no Bōshi</name>
		<desc>Donald gets transported into a world of dreams through the use of a Magic Cap, and must stop the evil Magician Pete to save this unknown land.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donald Duck no Mahou no Boushi-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SAS Sakata</developer>
		<publisher>Epoch</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong is back with a new sidekick, Diddy Kong, in a crazy island adventure! Challenged by the crazed tribe of reptilian Kremlings, they endeavor to get back their stolen banana horde! Armed with lightning-quick moves, chest-pounding muscle and awesome aerial acrobatics, our duo is ready to face their cunning adversaries. With the help of Donkey Kong's quirky family and his wild animal mounts, they squabble and scamper their way through the unending monkey mayhem.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donkey Kong Country-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 2: Diddy's Kong Quest</name>
		<desc>Okay kid, wipe that drool off your chin and listen up if you really want to learn something about this game. Sure, it's got newfangled computer graphics and what Diddy calls stereo sound that 'rocks heavily and with little resistance!' BUT, the game play? Well, they FINALLY added some proper challenge to the game - a snap for me of course. AND THE STORY? You sure ask a lot of questions, kid! Kaptain K. Rool and his cruelest cut-throat Kremlings have kidnapped that flea-bitten ape Donkey Kong. I figured I'd rescue him when the little pip-squeak DIDDY pops up along with his girlfriend, and they head off fixin' to prove themselves heroes or something. Come to think of it, I haven't laid eyes on those two for quite a while. I just may have to help them out after all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<desc>Revisit Donkey Kong Island and join the Kong family for their latest adventure. The Kremlings have a mysterious new leader named KAOS and are up to their usual mischief, even capturing Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong. Now it's up to Dixie Kong and the newest Kong, a giant infant named Kiddy, to rescue the two missing apes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest VI.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VI: Maboroshi no Daichi</name>
		<desc>You and two of your friends decide to attack the Archenemy - the evil Mudo - in his castle. But as you reach his throne, he attacks you and send the three friends into three different places...

Was this just a dream? You have just fallen out of your bed dreaming! It's time to go to the village elder, to get a seemingly simple assignment - to sell some goods at a bazaar in the nearest town. But soon the hero will discover his dream was not so far away from reality...

"Dragon Quest VI" is the last SNES game of the Dragon Quest series (called "Dragon Warrior" in US). It is a party RPG with turn-based combat and battles viewed from 1st person perspective. Not much has changed since the NES days of Dragon Quest - gameplay style, setting, and even menu layout seem almost identical to those of the early classics. Like its immediate predecessor  Dragon Quest V, this game was never released outside Japan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dragon Quest VI-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./EarthBound.zip</path>
		<name>EarthBound</name>
		<desc>Intergalactic terror stikes the small town of Onett as a blazing extraterrestrial object crashes in the night! The earth now faces imminent destruction by the universal evil threat known as Giygas!Armed with a cracked baseball bat, a cookie and an ATM card, a courageous boy named Ness vows to save the planet from hideous destruction. He must first find his heroic companions, Paula, Jeff and Poo. Will Ness succeed in his attempts to ambush countless frightening monsters as he travels? The ultimate test lies in the impending encounter with the all powerful Giygas!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/EarthBound-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Ape Studios</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Energy Breaker.zip</path>
		<name>Energy Breaker</name>
		<desc>A tactical RPG by Neverland for the SNES featuring character designs by Yasuhiro Nightow of Trigun fame. It utilizes a Tactics Ogre-style battle system but also allows the player to freely explore the world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Energy Breaker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy III.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>Ages ago, evil beings created powerful creatures called Espers, and unleashed them against each other.The resulting battles left their world a smoldering rubble.Legend has it, the Espers destroyed themselves and most of humanity.Magic disappeared forever.Centuries have passed and a rational world now exists with Espers living only in myths, until one frozen solid since the ancient wars is unearthed.Suddenly, there are reports of magical attacks on civilians.Imperial Commandos launch raids using magic-powered MagiTek weapons.Magic is obviously alive and the world is in danger again.Who or what is behind the rediscovery and redeployment of this legendary power?What chaotic plans exists that will wreak havoc on this orderly world?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>In the kingdom of Baron, powerful airships rule the skies. At the head of this elite fighting force is Cecil, Captain of the Red Wings, As our adventure begins, Cecil and his squadron are ordered to steal a powerful crystal from a rival kingdom. Upon their return, Cecil questions the King's orders and is stripped of his command. To prove his loyalty, he must slay a dreadful monster and deliver a mysterious package to a neighboring town. But when the package explodes, destroying everyone, Cecil and his friend Kain vow to fight the King's dark forces. Will you be able to save the world from their evil plan to control the crystals? Get ready for the most challenging role-playing adventure ever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy V.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy V</name>
		<desc>The Elemental Crystals...the life source of the planet. With them, gentle winds blow, the seas are active, fire burns bright, and the earth is full of life. All seems well in the world, until the wind suddenly stops, the sea begin to grow stagnant, the heat of fire becomes scarce, and the earth begins to wither. King Tycoon, sensing a premonition of evil, hurries off to check on the Wind Crystal, only to witness it destroy itself.

Meanwhile, a young traveler named Butz is camping in a field when a giant meteor strikes the planet. When he heads out to examine the meteor, he is shocked to find a young girl named Lenna, who is the princess of Tycoon, and a old man named Galuf, who is on a critical mission. Later, joined by Faris, a pirate captain, the foursome must travel the land in search of the destructor of the Crystals, and save the planet at any cost!

Final Fantasy V featured many new gameplay options and tactics, including an improved Job/Ability system (like in Final Fantasy Tactics), the return of the ATB (Active Time Battle) turn system, and all of the classic FF gameplay you've come to know and love!

Final Fantasy V was released as a stand-alone game in Japan, and again in Final Fantasy Collection. Its U.S. debut was as part of Final Fantasy Anthology. It was also later ported to the Gameboy Advance, adding 4 new Jobs, a new 30-floor dungeon, a bestiary, a music player, the ability to quick save anywhere, a few extra pieces of equipment, and a newly update translation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy V-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher>SquareSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VI.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VI</name>
		<desc>Ages ago, evil beings created powerful creatures called Espers, and unleashed them against each other. The resulting battles left their world a smoldering rubble. Legend has it, the Espers destroyed themselves and most of humanity. Magic disappeared forever. Centuries have passed and a rational world now exists with Espers living only in myths, until one frozen solid since the ancient wars is unearthed. Suddenly, there are reports of magical attacks on civilians. Imperial Commandos launch raids using magic-powered MagiTek weapons. Magic is obviously alive and the world is in danger again. Who or what is behind the rediscovery and redeployment of this legendary power? What chaotic plans exists that will wreak havoc on this orderly world?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy VI-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight 2.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight 2</name>
		<desc>It's Mad Gear Madness! They're back stronger than ever and they want revenge. With a new mysterious leader they plan to dominate the entire world. This time they've kidnapped Genryusai and his daughter Rena.Now Haggar must travel around the world to search for Genryusai and Rena. But he's not going alone. Carlos and Rena's sister, Maki, are joining the slam-fest to put the gang away for good. Search for numerous weapons such as knives, nightsticks and 2x4's or find food to recover your strength.Choose from Haggar, Carlos or Maki, each with their own style of fighting. Or have a friend join in for double the power and crush any punk that stands in your way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fight 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight 3.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight 3</name>
		<desc>Final Fight 3 is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in Japan in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fight 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission - Gun Hazard.zip</path>
		<name>Front Mission: Gun Hazard</name>
		<desc>The year is 2064, when the great solar power satellite, ATLAS is overshadowed by the invention of fusion power. The government alliance that had supported the building of ATLAS now find themselves facing economic crisis as the balance of power shifts. In this world of conflict and change, the Walking Panzer, or Wanzer, (a form of mecha) becomes the standard armored unit for wars and petty battles across the globe. For the small nation of Bergen, a coup d'etat is underway, staged by Colonel Ark. Seeking to establish complete control over the government and the NORAD units stationed there, Ark's first step involves the capture of President Orwen. Tipped off to the rebellion, Orwen seeks to flee from Bergen, looking for safe passage out of the seaport of Port Ertothal. A young Wanzer pilot, Albert Grabner, is assigned escort duty to the president by loyal elements of the army stationed there...

Gun Hazard is a side-scrolling version of the Front Mission series. Gameplay is more than a little similar to Cybernator or Metal Warriors. The player moves between different stages on an area map. Once inside a level, the player controls Albert and his wanzer as it moves left, right across the screen. The wanzer is able to jump, and attack with a primary and a special weapon. At any time during a level, Albert can eject from his heavily armed wanzer to explore. Although vulnerable when outside, Albert is able to reach areas the wanzer cannot, in addition to being a smaller target and being able to jetpack indefinitely.

Additionally, Albert can recruit other characters through the normal course of the story, some of whom can be designated to support roles. These support characters when set can provide a variety of different cover fire abilities for Albert during his missions. They too gain experience and levels. Different weapons and armor can be found or bought. Essential components include the Booster ability which allows the wanzer to hover and increase it's jumps, as well as the Dash ability which allows quick left-right movement by the wanzer. Money and experience are earned through the completion of level objectives as well as the kill count of enemy wanzers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Front Mission - Gun Hazard-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ganbare Goemon 2.zip</path>
		<name>Ganbare Goemon 2: Kiteretsu Shougun Magginesu</name>
		<desc>Ganbare Goemon 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Konami,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ganbare Goemon 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Go Go Ackman.zip</path>
		<name>Go Go Ackman</name>
		<desc>Ackman is not what one would call a good person. His job is to murder and steal souls for the Demon Lord. The angel Tenshi has taken it upon himself to put an end to Ackman's nefarious ways, and sends an army of angels and hired assassins to take out Ackman for good. It's just as well, because Ackman was getting bored without anyone to kill.

Go Go Ackman is a scrolling platformer starring the titular Ackman. Ackman can punch and charge up a ranged wave of energy, and he can also jump on some enemies to stun them before running into them and turning them into a sliding projectile. Ackman can hold up to three bombs that can clear the screen of enemies, and can also hold a weapon, either a sword, boomerang, or pistol, but it will be lost if Ackman is hit. Levels are linear, but do allow some exploration to find weapons and items hidden off the beaten road.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Go Go Ackman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Go Go Ackman 3.zip</path>
		<name>Go Go Ackman 3</name>
		<desc>Go Go Ackman 3 is an Action game, developed by Aspect and published by Banpresto,which was released in Japan in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Go Go Ackman 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goof Troop.zip</path>
		<name>Goof Troop</name>
		<desc>Disney's Goof Troop is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Goof Troop-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost Sweeper Mikami.zip</path>
		<name>GS Mikami: Joreishi wa Nice Body</name>
		<desc>GS Mikami: Joreishi wa Nice Body is an Action game, developed by Natsume and published by Banirex,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ghost Sweeper Mikami-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ganpuru - Gunman's Proof.zip</path>
		<name>Gunple: Gunman's Proof</name>
		<desc>The year is 1880. Two meteors fell on Earth on a small island near North American Pacific Coast. In the middle of the island there is a small town governed by a sheriff. At first, the town's inhabitants didn't pay attention to the meteors. But then, strange things started happening. Monsters attacked people, and left on the victims' bodies a mysterious crest with one word: demiseed. One day you, a young boy who lives in the town, are contacted by two aliens who came in a miniature space ship. One of the aliens introduces himself as Zero, the Space Sheriff, and explains that an intergalactic criminal named Demi has escaped from justice and is hiding somewhere on the island, being the cause of all the troubles lately. Zero then possesses your body, lends you his powers, and commands you on the quest to destroy Demi and to bring peace to your island and to the alien world alike!

The game is an action/adventure with slight RPG elements (buying and upgrading weapons, etc.) set in Wild West. While featuring traditional dungeon-crawling and many enemies to dispose of in real time combat, the game doesn't equip you with standard medieval swords, but with pistols, shotgun, machine gun, and even a flamethrower. Your weapons have infinite ammo. You can duck to avoid the alien monsters' fire, and perform special attacks with various types of weapons.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ganpuru - Gunman's Proof-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lenar</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hagane - The Final Conflict.zip</path>
		<name>Hagane: The Final Conflict</name>
		<desc>Hagane is an Action game, developed by CAProduction and published by Hudson,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Hagane - The Final Conflict-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAProduction</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hameln no Violin Hiki.zip</path>
		<name>Hamelin No Violin Hiki</name>
		<desc>Pandora's Box was a cursed existence. Through the curiosity of a woman, evil was unleashed and very nearly covered the world in darkness. Miraculously, humanity managed to seal Maou Kestra back into the box but with immense sacrifices. Even without their lord, the demons are still a formidable force that has only grown stronger with time, locked in the abandoned capital of the north, Hameln. 15 years have passed since that fateful battle...

Enter Hamel, a travelling minstrel who is so self-centered that he'd sooner cook his guardian crow Oboe, than go hungry for even a minute. Welcome to the world of music and hilarious insanity that is the Hamelin No Violin Hiki. Watch as Hamel takes cheap shots at his opponents or how he bashes pigeons with his giant violin and turn them into dinner.

How WILL the world be saved from Maou Kestra with a hero such as this?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Hameln no Violin Hiki-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daft</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper Iria.zip</path>
		<name>Hyper Iria</name>
		<desc>Iria is the story of a girl and the Alien being she loves to hate. The series begins with her brother, Gren, taking a job. He is a bounty hunter, and one well known for his incredible skill. Iria, being a skilled apprentice bounty hunter herself, tags along. What is the job, one might ask. It is to find out what has happened to the crew and cargo of a Space Station. Needless to say, nothing is as it seems, and the war between Iria and Zeiram begins in earnest.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Hyper Iria-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TamTam</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Illusion of Gaia.zip</path>
		<name>Illusion of Gaia</name>
		<desc>Journey into the dark side of an ancient civilization.Radiating an ominous light in its path, the Chaos Comet threatens the existence of the planet. Battles erupt and a tentative peace is returned to the lands. Danger lurks as the Chaos Comet orbits and dreadful beasts lie awaiting.In the Age of Exploration a boy named Will is born. Tragedy strikes during an expedition to the Tower of Babel separating Will from his father. Telekinetic forces awaken as Will returns to South Cape. Armed with his transformation abilities of two great warriors, Will must save the planet.Gaia, Will's guiding spirit bestows magical powers and advice along his journey. With the help of his friends Will must battle relentless enemies and solve the puzzles of the ancient ruins. Patience and knowledge are essential to reunite this father and son.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Illusion of Gaia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures.zip</path>
		<name>Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures</name>
		<desc>Grab your trusty whip and slash your way throughout all three Indy classics in this no-thrills-barred video game adventure! If it happens in the movies... it happens here... the giant boulder from Raiders of the Lost Ark, the mine cart chase from Temple of Doom, Three Trials from The Last Crusade. It's three times the Indy, all on one blockbuster game pak!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Inspector Gadget.zip</path>
		<name>Inspector Gadget</name>
		<desc>Inspector Gadget is an Action game, developed by AIM and published by Hudson Soft,which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Inspector Gadget-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AIM</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>If the movie shook you, Ocean's REAL 3-D graphics will blow you away!This is in-your-face, eyeball-to-eyeball, full-motion 3-D. Wa're going to put you closer to the main attractions than ever before possible. So close, that when you find yourself staring into the flared nostriles of a famished raptor, you can almost smell his breath.Play the greatest game of all time: Jurassic Park in 3-DEnjoy your stay!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park Part 2: The Chaos Continues</name>
		<desc>A year has passed. No one has set foot in Jurassic Park... until now. As Dr. Grant, you'll venture back to the island, where more dinosaurs than you could ever imagine await your return - including all-new species.It's a totally different game this time. You'll realize it once the nerve-snapping sounds &amp; graphics get a hold of you.Go it alone or team up for terrifying 2-player action. Only you have the power to send these prehistoric monsters back where they came from.Only you can close the doors on Jurassic Park... for another 65 million years!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killer Instinct.zip</path>
		<name>Killer Instinct</name>
		<desc>Don't wait in endless arcade lines to play--Killer Instinct comes to Super NES with action, graphics and sound that annihilates all other combat games!Fulgore, Jago, B.Orchid, Spinal and all your favorite warriors contend in the Ultratech KI Tournament. Each combatant engages in the KI Combo Theory of connected moves and finishing tactics to destroy their opponents. With incredible displays of eyelasers, ice lancers, wind kicks, and laser blades these fearless fighters prove their battle prowess. But remember, if you lose, it's hero to zero!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Killer Instinct-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T023048</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star</name>
		<desc>Dream Land is under siege again! Our hero, Kirby, returns to instigate a rescue. King Dedede is snatching up Dream Land's food supply, but he's not the only one! Dyna Blade, Meta Knight and a slew of other evil baddies are on the loose and wreaking havoc throughout the land.Use any of Kirby's amazing powers to create a 'helper' to assist you in battle. Or have a friend join you for some two-player action by taking control of Kirby's helper. Help Kirby work through EIGHT challenging games filled with action and adventure. Enter the fray in Spring Breeze, enter a foot race against King Dedede in Gourmet Race and tackle a winged warrior in Dyna Blade. Hone your reaction skills in Megaton Punch and Samurai Kirby, then battle your way through the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge of Meta Knight and Milky Way Wishes. Each game is different AND some extra-special surprises are in store for you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kirby Super Star-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hal</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land 3.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land 3</name>
		<desc>Kirby's Dream Land 3 is an Action game, developed by HAL Labs and published by Nintendo,which was released in 1997.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kirby's Dream Land 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Labs</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kishin Douji Zenki - Battle Raiden.zip</path>
		<name>Kishin Douji Zenki- Rettou Raiden</name>
		<desc>Once already Chiaki and her reluctant demon servant Zenki have saved the world from the forces of darkness, but apparently once is never enough. Chiaki has a vision of five cloaked figures and knows that only she and Zenki can stop them. At once they set off to track down the demon leaders.

In Kishin Douji ZENKI: Battle Raiden the player takes the role of Zenki. At first, and occasionally through the game, Zenki will be in his powered down form where he can only punch, jump, and dash. After Chiaki recovers her bracelet, or regains her concentration, or whatever she needs to do at the time, she can transform Zenki into his powered up form. In this form Zenki deals more damage and has a much longer list of attacks that get added to as the game progresses, such as a pillar of energy, an electrified punch, and a dashing attack. By picking up scrolls Zenki can do a powerful Rudora attack to all enemies on screen, but this attack damages Zenki as well.

To complete platforming levels Zenki will have to make it to the end of the level while occasionally finding hidden stone monuments that, when destroyed, will drop items as well as alter the level or remove obstacles, allowing Zenki to pass. After a stage's first platforming level is a midboss fight, and after the second platforming level is the boss fight proper.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kishin Douji Zenki - Battle Raiden-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CA Production</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Krusty's Super Fun House.zip</path>
		<name>Krusty's Super Fun House</name>
		<desc>Hey kids! Give a hoot! Help out your old pal Krusty the Clown! My official Krusty's Fen House is infested with rats! There are over 60 leverls in this game, and they're all crawling with the little varmints! I've got my loyal cadets, Bart and Home Simpson, Sideshow Mel, and Corporal Punishment to guard the rat traps, but I need you to lead the filthy rodents into those traps! Then we blow 'em up! We incinerate 'em! We laser-blast'em! We electrocute'em! We Krusterize the little stinkers!!! Hoo boy!Did I mention the snakes, aliens and the flying pigs? Well, watch out for those riffraff! If you can't Krusterize 'em, at least avoid 'em...they're worse than the #@!*%! rats! Making Krusty's Fun House vermin-free is not a pretty task, kiddy cadets--but someone's gotta do it!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Krusty's Super Fun House-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Audiogenic Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lagoon.zip</path>
		<name>Lagoon</name>
		<desc>Lakeland has a drinking problem. All the water has been fouled, and it's up to you to find out why. As Nasir, Child of Light, you will embark on a quest that demands great courage and fortitude. It's a journey that takes Nasir from childhood to manhood, played out against breathtaking, 16 bit backdrops. Along the way, you must negotiate a network of labyrinths filled with horrifying, 3-D creatures. Using weapons, magical items and 16 spells, you can turn the tide, defeating the forces of evil and restoring pure water to this once tranquil little town.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lagoon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zoom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend.zip</path>
		<name>Legend</name>
		<desc>Legend is an Action game, developed by Arcade Zone LTD and published by Seika Corp.,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Legend-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arcade Zone LTD</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lennus II.zip</path>
		<name>Lennus II: Fuuin no Shito</name>
		<desc>Japan only</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lennus II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Copya Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Asmik Ace Entertainment, Inc</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lethal Enforcers.zip</path>
		<name>Lethal Enforcers</name>
		<desc>Lethal Enforcers is an Action game, developed and published by Konami,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lethal Enforcers-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Majuu Ou (King of Demons).zip</path>
		<name>Majuu Ou</name>
		<desc>Abel's daughter has been kidnapped by his former friend, Bayer. Bayer has sold his soul to the devil, and sacrificed Abel's wife, in an attempt to resurrect the King of Demons. With no other choice, Abel vows to save his daughter, no matter what the cost - even if it is his own humanity... 

Majyuuou is a side-scrolling platformer for the Super Nintendo, taking influences from Castlevania and Contra. You play as Abel, intent on rescuing his daughter from the depths of Hell. As you defeat certain bosses, they will drop large, color changing gems. Pick up the gem, and you'll transform into either a red Harpy, a blue Dragon, or a green Lizard, depending on what color it is when you pick it up. Each demon type has its own special attacks</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Majuu Ou (King of Demons)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KSS</developer>
		<publisher>KSS</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Paint.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Paint</name>
		<desc>Mario Paint lets you draw, paint, animate and compose music! Creation! Imagination is your only limit with an amazing variety of drawing tools. Animation! Add exciting dimension by creating moving animation with up to 9 frame sequences. Orchestration! Compose your own songs by selecting from over 15 different musical sounds and the entire scale of notes. Coordination! Increase your Super NES Mouse dexterity by playing Gnat Attack, the clever fly swatter game included inside.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mario Paint-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel Super Heroes - War of the Gems.zip</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes in War of the Gems</name>
		<desc>The most powerful collection of MARVEL SUPER HEROES now unite to battle treacherous mobs of Super-Villians! A mysterious foe has kicked off his plan to rule the world by collecting the Infinity Gems. While each gem controls one force of nature, combined they command limitless power.The fate of the entire world depends on your ability to defeat this sinister scheme before the gems are combined. Master the brute strength of your favorite hero to take on this life and death challenge. You choose the hero best suited to each mission and control all the action, like breaking barriers with the Incredible Hulk or tackling challenges with Spider-Man's webs and climbing ability.It's an incredible action-adventure demanding skill, cunning and reflexes to defeat a diabolical plot and the most amazing assortment of corrupt Super-Villains ever assembled.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Marvel Super Heroes - War of the Gems-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvelous - Another Treasure Island.zip</path>
		<name>Marvelous - Mouhitotsu no Takara-jima</name>
		<desc>The great Captain Maverick was a pirate of legend who kept his treasure called "Marvelous" hidden that could only be found by those who were willing to solve puzzles that many deemed unsolvable. A group of children, however, will use their wits to prove them wrong when they go to the island where the treasure is said to be held. A group of pirates, however, have similar intentions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Marvelous - Another Treasure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19961026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman VII.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 7</name>
		<desc>Mega Man 7 is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in Japan in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Megaman VII-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman's Soccer.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Soccer</name>
		<desc>Dr. Wily will stop at nothing to control the world and who would have thought his next move would be to attack the world's most popular sport? Dr. Light is ready and he's preparing Mega Man for a new type of battle.As the two best soccer teams in the nation took the field for the championship, suddenly the stadium was pelted with blasts of fire and the field was engulfed in smoke. The smoke cleared and some very familiar robots replaced the players on the field. Dr. Wily had sent his greatest robot creations like Skull Man, Cut Man, Wood Man, Needle Man and Pharaoh Man to rule the soccer world.But Dr. Light was prepared for this new tactic. Almost instantly a reserve of Mega Man robots appeared to take on the evil forces in the strangest game of soccer ever seen. No matter where evil appears, Mega Man willbe there to kick one past Dr. Wily and hist robot master.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Megaman's Soccer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sun L</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X</name>
		<desc>Near the end of his life, Dr. Light succeeds in creating the first of a new series of robots which will change the world. Able to think and make decisions, this new robot holds great danger as well as great possibilities. Fearful of the possible consequences of unleashing his creation on the world, Dr. Light decides to seal him in a capsule and test his systems until they are totally reliable. The future will have to decide his fate...Released from the capsule by Dr. Cain, 'X' is born into the world of the future where the robot rebellions are a thing of the past. But when Dr. Cain tries to implement Dr. Light's designs into a new series of Reploids, something goes hideously wrong. Now the future lies on the brink of destruction and a new Mega Man must emerge to face Sigma and his forces before the human race is wiped from the planet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Megaman X-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X3.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X3</name>
		<desc>Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town?Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Megaman X3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Combat - Falcon's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Combat: Falcon's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Metal Combat: Falcon's Revenge is an Action game, developed by Intelligent Systems and published by Nintendo,which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Metal Combat - Falcon's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Warriors.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Warriors</name>
		<desc>Metal Warriors is an Action game, developed by LucasArts and published by Konami,which was released in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Metal Warriors-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey no Tokyo Disneyland Daibouken.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey no Tokyo Disneyland Daibouken</name>
		<desc>Mickey no Tokyo Disneyland Daibouken is an Action game, developed by Graphic Research and published by Tomy Corporation,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mickey no Tokyo Disneyland Daibouken-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graphic Research</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey to Donald - Magical Adventure 3.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey to Donald Magical Adventure 3</name>
		<desc>Donald’s mischievous nephews Huey, Dewey, and Louie have found a mysteriously old and dusty storybook while hiding in Donald’s attic. When reading the storybook, the three ducks are magically transported into Storybook Land by Evil Baron Pete. Evil Baron Pete rules over the Storybook Land and is plotting to take over the Outside World. With the Fairy of Storybook Land’s help, it’s up to Mickey and Donald to rescue Huey, Dewey, and Louie.

Features:

- Play as Mickey or Donald in this awesome action adventure
- Go on an adventure with your favorite Disney friends--Minnie, Daisy, Pluto, and friends
- New magical costumes with special abilities to master: Knight, Wood-Cutter, and the Magician
- Mini-games for players of all ages to enjoy</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mickey to Donald - Magical Adventure 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19951208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nangoku Shounen Papuwa-kun.zip</path>
		<name>Nangoku Shounen Papuwa-kun</name>
		<desc>Once, on an unknown southern island, a battle was waged over two mysterious stones, one red and one blue. The blue stone controls desire, and its power created the blue clan. And the red clan that inherited the power of the red stone was filled with the light of hope. Finally, the battle came to an end, and the young one who possessed the power of the blue stone fell into a deep sleep. The one with the power of the red stone flew off far across the sky. Desire and hope... until the day these two powers meet each other again...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Nangoku Shounen Papuwa-kun-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daft</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neugier - Umi to Kaze no Kodou.zip</path>
		<name>Neugier: Umi to Kaze no Koudou</name>
		<desc>Duke, the son of Count Wein of Neugier, was exiled from the country by his father a long time ago. Traveling in faraway lands, Duke heard that his homeland was under attack. He decided to return to Neugier. On the way his ship was attacked by pirates, lead by a mysterious demon named Ord. After he barely escaped the ship, Duke found his way into his father's castle. He realized now that the pirates' attack and the monsters roaming the castle are connected. Although his father doesn't trust him, Duke is determined to save Neugier.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Neugier - Umi to Kaze no Kodou-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantom 2040.zip</path>
		<name>Phantom 2040</name>
		<desc>You are the Phantom, searching for the evil Rebecca Madison in the vast city of Metropia. As head of Maximum, Inc., she will stop at nothing to fulfil her twisted plans to control the world... unless you can overpower her.Vicious bosses and hordes of biots, programmed to destroy you, relentlessly attack of every turn. But you strike back with an arsenal of heavy-duty weapons including a smart gun, inductance rope, homing missile, and many others. Use two weapons at once to double your chances of survival! Then control your destiny as you weave your way through more than 60 incredible levels!The danger is staggering. The fate of the city, the eco-system, and all of humanity rests on your abilities. You know what must be done to save Metropia and the world from certain doom.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Phantom 2040-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Viacom New Media</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinocchio.zip</path>
		<name>Pinocchio</name>
		<desc>Play as Pinocchio and Jiminy Cricket, through nine levels of remarkable gameplay and stunning animation from the Disney Interactive Studios. Choose the correct paths of truth, bravery and unselfishness to ensure that the Blue Fairy grants you your ultimate wish!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pinocchio-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Pitfall: The Mayan Adventure</name>
		<desc>A vast labyrinth of interconnected levels guards the fabulous secrets of the Mayans. Hollywood-produced sound effects and revolutionary animation technology create an intense journey of excitement and discovery. Dare you take it?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pitfall - The Mayan Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Redline Games</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Plok!.zip</path>
		<name>Plok</name>
		<desc>'Hey, you! Over here! It's me, Plok! Waddya mean, you don't know who I am? Here on the island of Akrillic, in the magic archipelago of Poly-Esta, my flags are all over the place. Here, they call me Top Banana, Head Honcho, Numero Uno, Big Cheese -- you know, King!'At least, some of them call me that. Would you believe there are still a few stubborn holdouts who refuse to recognize my supreme authority? But now they've gone too far -- they've stolen my favorite flag!'I know what you're thinking: who would do such a despicable thing? I'll tell you who -- the nastiest, foulest, most loathsome critters in all of Poly-Esta: Fleas! And I'll bet that rotten Flea Queen is behind it all! In fact, she's probably teamed up with the Shprouts, Rockyfella, Womack Spider, and every other troublemaker around here.'Well, they're really in for it now. Besides my amazing, stupendous ability to fire my arms and legs at will, I've got my nifty jetpack, off-road truck, 'copter, and secret supervehicle. By golly, we'll show 'em who's boss!'So c'mon, already -- let's go get 'em!'</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Plok!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky.zip</path>
		<name>Pocky &amp; Rocky</name>
		<desc>Pocky &amp; Rocky is an Action game, developed and published by Natsume,which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pocky &amp; Rocky-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky 2.zip</path>
		<name>Pocky &amp; Rocky 2</name>
		<desc>Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Natsume,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pocky &amp; Rocky 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Popful Mail.zip</path>
		<name>Popful Mail</name>
		<desc>Kazyr, Necros, Ulgar. Ghosts from the past that nearly once destroyed Popful Mail's world. Now, the Black Seal is about to be broken so they can return to wreak havoc on the world once again. Three ragtag adventurers become the only hope of stopping the second coming of Evil. Play as Mail, tomboy bounty-hunter wannabe who's handy with a blade, Tatt, the ultra-polite apprentice magician with a deadly staff, or Gaw, a winged blue blob with breath of fire, as you search for the manicial Muttonhead, who holds all the answers. During your quest, change characters at any time! You'll need to, because Nuts Cracker and the minions of Evil will stop at nothing to end your party before it starts! And, thanks to the storage power of CD, Popful Mail comes alive with over 2.5 hours of spoken dialogue and 20 minutes of heart-pounding animation. Face it, your butt's gonna be glued to the couch till the credits roll!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Popful Mail-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prehistorik Man.zip</path>
		<name>Prehistorik Man</name>
		<desc>Prehistorik Man is an Action game, developed by Titus Software and published by Kemco,which was released in Japan in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Prehistorik Man-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>The award winning computer software adventure that has people everywhere rattling their sabers is here for Super NES. And now the animation is more detailed, and the controls more responsive. There's even a five part training mode for sharpening your running, jumping, climbing and sword fighting skills.But the sands of time are against you. For you must survive 20 perilous stages, rescure the princess from the evil Grand Vizier Jaffar, and claim the royal residency all before the hourglass is empty.Beware the unpredictable floors and ceilings, gut splitting guillotines, hidden spikes, walls of flames and more. Jaffar's spells spell doom if you're not crafty and nimble. And a legion of savage servants, amazing amazons and immortal skeletons will do his barbaric bidding. Even your own alter ego is the enemy.Pass through invisible doors and walk through space portals. Find vessels of magic potions, but partake of them wisely. They may increase your life or just as easily poison you. So take each step with caution, young would-be prince, or the entire kingdom will suffer the darkest Arabian night ever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arsys Software Inc.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type III - The Third Lightning.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type III</name>
		<desc>It was believed on Earth that the deadly BYDO Empire had been destroyed--but now they've returned, as nasty as ever. Their ships and armies are more powerful than before, and Earth will surely be conquered unless the new R-90 ship can destroy them. Powered with engines that launch it into different dimensions, and armed with the Round, Shadow, and Cyclone Forces, R-90 has what it takes to wipe out the BYDO threat. Then, the BYDO mother ship must be found and destroyed to entirely erase the species from our galaxy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/R-Type III - The Third Lightning-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Realm.zip</path>
		<name>Realm</name>
		<desc>Realm is an Action game, developed by Flair Software and published by Titus Software,which was released in 1996.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Realm-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flair Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rendering Ranger R2.zip</path>
		<name>Rendering Ranger R2</name>
		<desc>Rendering Ranger: R2 is an Action game, developed by Rainbow Arts and published by Virgin Interactive,which was released in Japan in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Rendering Ranger R2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Road Runner's Death Valley Rally.zip</path>
		<name>Road Runner's Death Valley Rally</name>
		<desc>Road Runner's Death Valley Rally is an Action game, developed by ICOM Simulations and published by SunSoft,which was released in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Road Runner's Death Valley Rally-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocky Rodent.zip</path>
		<name>Rocky Rodent</name>
		<desc>Rocky Rodent is an Action game, developed and published by Irem,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Rocky Rodent-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Romancing Saga 3.zip</path>
		<name>Romancing Sa.Ga 3</name>
		<desc>Every 300 years the Death Eclipse kills all newly born creatures. Men, women, and children, animals and plants, even ferocious monsters - no one can survive the devastation caused by the Eclipse. No one except a child chosen by the destiny. 600 years ago, such a child survived the Death Eclipse, only to become a demon king. During the next Eclipse, a chosen child became a holy king, and he defeated the evil demon king. Now, when the next Eclipse is nearing, nobody knows who the next fortunate survivor will become - a demon or a holy man?

In "Romancing Sa・Ga 3", you can play through the story controling any one of the eight main characters - Julian, Monica, Mikhael, Harid, Katarina, Thomas, Elena, and Sarah. The story is common for all eight characters, and they often join together and share the same piece of a story. The princess Monica learns about a rebellion planned by a treacherous Baron to dethrone her brother, Marquis Mikhael. She goes to warn him, but on her way, she loses her horse, and has to stop in an inn of the town Shinnon. There, she meets travelers who agree to lend her a horse and accompany her to see her brother. When they finally reach Mikhael, a war begins...

"Romancing Sa・Ga 3" has a refined upgrading system: you can upgrade your weapons and your spells by using them continuously. The party combat is turn-based, and there are also strategic army-vs.-army battles you'll have to command.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Romancing Saga 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19951111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rudra no Hihou.zip</path>
		<name>Rudra no Hihou</name>
		<desc>In a fantasy world inspired by Indian folklore, the end of mankind draws nigh.  Can you break the cycle before humanity is doomed?  Up to four separate scenarios are available for players to enjoy, with a magic system that gives the player total creativity in combat!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Rudra no Hihou-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of Evermore.zip</path>
		<name>Secret of Evermore</name>
		<desc>In Dr. Sidney Ruffleberg's old, decaying mansion, a boy and his dog stumble upon a mysterious machine. By sheer accident they are propelled into Evermore, a one-time utopia that now has become a confounding and deadly world. A world of prehistoric jungles, ancient civilizations, medieval kingdoms and futuristic cities. During his odyssey, the boy must master a variety of weapons, learn to harness the forces of alchemy, and make powerful allies to battle Evermore's diabolical monsters. What's more, his dog masters shape-changing to aid the quest. But even if they can muster enough skill and courage, even if they can uncover the mysterious clues, they can only find their way home by discovering the Secret of Evermore&amp;trade;.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Secret of Evermore-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square USA</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of Mana.zip</path>
		<name>Secret of Mana</name>
		<desc>There is one force in the universe that keeps good and evil in perfect balance. It is called the tree of Mana. But a magic sword has tricked a young warrior into upsetting the balance, spreading evil throughout the land. Thus the warrior must undertake a dangerous journey to find the seeds of the Mana tree which has been hidden for centuries. Only then can perfect harmony be restored. In this incredible adventure, things are not as they seem. It's a world turned upside down that you must help the warrior make right. And the only way to succeed is to solve the Secret of Mana.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Secret of Mana-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seiken Densetsu 3.zip</path>
		<name>Seiken Densetsu 3</name>
		<desc>The Legend of the Holy Sword Continues...

Formerly, when the world was enshrouded in darkness, the Mana Goddess ussed the Mana sword to destroy the 8 Mana beasts that intended to destroy the world, and sealed them into 8 Mana stones. Thus the darkness dissipated, and the world was reborn. The Mana Goddess turned herself into a tree, and went to sleep.

Many years passed. But then, the 8 seals started to dissolve, and the Mana beasts were free. They now aim to gain power enough to rival the gods. Meanwhile, due to greedy people who want to make the world their own, wars have started to break out...

The era of peace has come to an end... Mana itself is starting to fade from the world. Even the Mana tree is beginning to die.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Seiken Densetsu 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skyblazer.zip</path>
		<name>Skyblazer</name>
		<desc>Skyblazer is an Action game, developed by Ukiyotei and published by Sony Imagesoft,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Skyblazer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Blazer.zip</path>
		<name>Soul Blazer</name>
		<desc>Money... The root of all evil.King Magridd sold out.Obsessed with the desire for wealth, he cut a dastardly deal with the ruler of evil. Now the Freil Empire is in shambles and you are chosen to save it. Free the kingdom's captive souls. Teach the King a thing or two about integrity. Rescue a beautiful maiden. Liberate an imprisoned inventory.You'll boldly traverse the six complex stages in this action-RPG. An array of weapons, armor and magic are at your disposal. After you revive the kingdom, you will confront Deathtoll. Then, make him pay...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Soul Blazer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Megaforce.zip</path>
		<name>Space Megaforce</name>
		<desc>'Space Megaforce&amp;trade;'. The game's thrilling speed is its most attractive feature. The enemy movements are fast. Your shots and the enemies' shots are fast. Finally, the scrolling is fast. The screen filled with battle action just overflows with high speed shooting excitement. On top of that there is the Shot Control System operated wiith the 'R' button. You can attack the enemy in a multitude of ways with a weapon using this system. Naturally, the features of the Super NES&amp;trade; such as rotation, enlarging, and shrinking functions are used to their fullest and huge enemies never before possible are packed into this exciting MEGA game!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Space Megaforce-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sparkster.zip</path>
		<name>Sparkster</name>
		<desc>He's back, and he's one oppumped-up opposum! SPARKSTER is jet-packin' into action as the toughest Rocket Knight to ever swing a sword. Grab the controls and blast through 8 wild stages in your quest to rid the world of the evil King Gedol and his allies - a pack of lizards that are tougher than a suitcase! Oh yeah, and before you get too comfortable - Axel Gear is here. This Rocket-Knight-gone-bad has a score to settle with Sparkster. Our hero will need his revved-up new rocket pack and powerful new attack moves to kick Axel's tail back to the dark side of the planet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Sparkster-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man and the X-Men in Arcade's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Spider-Man &amp; X-Men: Arcade's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man and his mutant pals need your help to escape from Arcade's diabolical amusement park - battling killer clowns, hungry piranhas, lethal doom balls and deadly robot replicas of super-villains like Carnage and Juggernaut! Will Spidey's webs, Wolverine's claws, Gambit's energy cards, Storm's lightning bolts and Cyclops' optic blasts mean GAME OVER for Arcade? That depends on YOU!!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Spider-Man and the X-Men in Arcade's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spriggan Powered.zip</path>
		<name>Spriggan Powered</name>
		<desc>Spriggan Powered is an Action game, developed by Micronics and published by Naxat Soft,which was released in Japan in 1996.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Spriggan Powered-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micronics</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Ocean.zip</path>
		<name>Star Ocean</name>
		<desc>A young boy named Ratix lives in the town Clatos on a planet with medieval culture, together with his best friends Dorn and Milly. They belong to respectable families of warriors and healers, and excel in battles kills. One day, a letter from a neighbor town arrives. A strange disease has plagued the town and its inhabitants plead the healers of Clatos to help them. Milly's father decides to go, but he himself catches the disease. The young adventurers must save Milly's father and other people at all costs. But in the beginning of their journey, they discover a crashed space ship with people who belong to a much more advanced civilization. People from two different worlds must work together to solve the grand mystery...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Star Ocean-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sunset Riders.zip</path>
		<name>Sunset Riders</name>
		<desc>You're the fastest gun in the West and a bounty hunter voted most popular by the Dodge City Undertaker's Union. But look what's waiting to knock you off your high horse:Shotgun blast for shotgun blast, this game features the same 7 levels you had a showdown with at the arcade. Doesn't that make your trigger finger itch like crazy?!Lead will fly non-stop from authentic old west towns, to desert ambush zones, to Indian villages.Catching up to train robbers and stagecoach bandits will not only exhaust your horse, it'll make you feel like you've just run a marathon with a cactus in your shorts.Search for the hideouts of Hawkeye Hank Hatfield, the Smith Brothers and other notorious outlaws. Along the way be sure to round up special weapons that'll quicken your draw and double your firepower.As a real ladies' man, you'll also be rewarded handsomely for your efforts off the trail. Talk about riding into the sunset!If you think beans and a campfire don't mix, wait'll you see what hits the fan when you mix it up with desperadoes in the bonus bounty stage.Not enough? Oh, buffalo chips - you know it is!Heck, even Clint in his prime (many moons ago) would find this game a fistful.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Sunset Riders-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Adventure Island.zip</path>
		<name>Super Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>Master Higgins is back in his wildest and greatest adventure of all! His girlfriend, Jeannie Jungle, has been turned to stone by the evil Dark Cloak. Now he must leap into action to defeat the scores of guardian animals and monsters that protect the wicked wizard.Join Master Higgins as he reaches new heights of adventure on his high flying skateboard. Speed through underground caves in a crazy mine car ride! Go from tropical shores to the belly of a whale - all in search of his final battle with the mad magician, Dark Cloak!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Adventure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Produce</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Adventure Island II.zip</path>
		<name>Super Adventure Island II</name>
		<desc>After a disastrous previous relationship, our chubby hero, Master Higgins, finally found true happiness with his new love, Tina. Things couldn&amp;acirc;€™t have been going any better for Master Higgins as he sailed across the beautiful tropical water with his beautiful tropical wife. But little did he know that trouble loomed just over the horizon. A vicious hurricane tore apart the raft that Higgins and Tina were on, and they soon found themselves tossed into the sea. They became separated and beached on different islands, and both had amnesia. Tina was taken in by the king of Waku-Waku Island, and soon she was betrothed to him. Then Master Higgins made his way to the island&amp;acirc;€&amp;brvbar;and the adventure continues.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Adventure Island II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Make</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Back to the Future Part II.zip</path>
		<name>Super Back to the Future Part II</name>
		<desc>Marty has returned from his bizarre trip to 1955 all thanks to Doc's prized invention, the DeLorean time machine. He decides to do some skateboarding around the neighborhood and visits his girlfriend Jennifer. However, this is cut short as Doc arrives from his trip to the future. He tells them that their children's future is at stake and proceeds to take them both to the year 2015. Here, Marty assumes the identity of his son Marty Jr. and faces off with Biff's grandson Griff and then his gang members one-by-one.

With Griff and his gang arrested, future history changes to ensure that the lives of Marty's children stay on track. But when Marty and Doc are not looking, old Biff takes an old sports almanac, hijacks the DeLorean, travels back to 1955 and gives the book to his teenage self. Then he returns to 2015 with Marty, Doc, and Jennifer none the wiser. When the three return to 1985, they discover that everything around them has drastically changed. Hill Valley now plagued with crime and pollution, Biff Tannen is now a multi-millionaire and Marty's stepfather, and the Doc has been certified insane. Now Marty must go throughout Hill Valley and figure out what has happened and try put time back to the way it was.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Back to the Future Part II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daft</developer>
		<publisher>Toshiba EMI</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bonk.zip</path>
		<name>Super Bonk</name>
		<desc>Super Bonk is an Action game, developed by RED Entertainment and published by Hudson,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Bonk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RED Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Castlevania IV.zip</path>
		<name>Super Castlevania IV</name>
		<desc>A century of Transylvanian tranquility is about to come to a shocking end. Once again the mortifying screams of helpless villagers shake the ground as they huddle against new nightmarish horrors unleashed by the Duke of Darkness, Count Dracula. And this time he has a tombstone with your name on it, Simon Belmont.You must descend into Castle of the Undead and its gruesome ground, accompanied by the most chilling sound effects to ever tingle your spine. Inside, a freshly dug 11 levels maze features the treacherous Terrace of Terror, the dangerous Rotating Dungeon, the Sunken Ruins of Lost Spirits, torture chambers and creature filled caves. Use your whip like a grappling hook and swing past hundreds of traps and a host of ghost freaks, living corpses and hidden goblins. All while dodging or destroying the unpredictable spitting lizards, carnivorous coffins, and more.Find the concealed weapons needed to defeat everything from eerie phantoms to haunted furniture. Then prepare to find yourself face-to-thing with hideous torments like the Tongue Lasher, the Darkest Knight, the Bone-Afide Horseman and the Granite Crusher. When your nerves get shot, use your password and take a breather. But forge on, Simon Belmont, because if you though Dracula was down for the count, he's only just begun to fright!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Castlevania IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Genjin 2.zip</path>
		<name>Super Genjin 2</name>
		<desc>﻿In this sidescrolling action-platformer, Bonk is once again trying to save his world from the evil clutches of the reptilian king, who once more is threatening the prehistoric era.  Boy, you'd think that after being defeated four times prior that he would take a hint.  This time, you also get to face his five best soldiers, who will try to stop you in your tracks.  Bonk controls rather smoothly, and he is really fun to control.  To those of you that are not familiar with the series, Bonk is a caveman who attacks his enemies with his noggin; after jumping down, from below, while swimming, and while in the air.  He can even bounce off walls with his head, skip on the water like a stone if his head is facing down, climb certain walls with his teeth, scale up waterfalls, flip in the air (so long as the attack button is repeatedly being tapped), and so forth.  As is the case with the series, you start with a regular amount of health, but if you find a translucent heart icon, you'll increase your capacity.  What's neat is how collecting the food not only scores you some points but how it also replenishes a little bit of your health, too.  This time Bonk can also run if you hold down the A button, and the X button is used if you have a special ability on you.  If you find a power-up, whether it be piece of meat, or a different icon, then you will be given a power-up ability that will be taken out the moment you're hit once (damn).  Among the power-ups are the one where the fire will be spreading if Bonk hits his head on the ground (you know, the one where he looks freaky), one where Bonk turns into a bird and gains the ability to fly, one where Bonk becomes tiny and can make platforms made out of Japanese characters, and there is one where Bonk has the ability to double-jump as a girl.  Yes, Bonk becomes a girl if he eats the pink-colored meat.  I'm dead serious.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Genjin 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950728T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ghouls'n Ghosts.zip</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>You are Arthur, the boldest bladesman alive. You are caught in a dangerous quest! Fiendish foes and grim demons are about to hurl disaster your way!You must save the wondrous Princess Guinevere. But beware! The reeking ruler of the forbidden land can call forth evil and destruction. Who knows what creeping, leaping terrors haunt this dripping realm!You may lose your armor and your strength. You may be hexed. You may become a baby, a duck, or a skeleton! But you are never without a weapon. And magic awaits to help you.Destroy the witches, ogres and ghosts. Escape the snapping skulls and ghastly ghouls. And save Guinevere from the mysterious depths of the Phantom Zone in Super Ghouls 'N Ghosts!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Ghouls'n Ghosts-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario All-Stars.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario All-Stars</name>
		<desc>Revisit the magic and fun of the classic Super Mario Bros. series on your Super NES! All the great Super Mario Bros. games for the NES have been powered up with 16-bit graphics and sound and collected on one super game pak. As an added bonus, the previously unreleased 'Lost Levels' are included. These super challenging courses have never been available in this country until now!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario All-Stars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Kart.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Kart</name>
		<desc>The Super Mario GoKart Park is open for tons of racing fun! Hit the track with Mario, Luigi, Yoshi and the Princess. Get tough and lock fenders with Donkey Kong, Jr. and Bowser. Even Toad and Koopa Troopa will mix it up in an all-out quest for the Gold Cup! Race head-to-head with a friend or challenge the computer in great, split-screen, Mode 7 graphics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario Kart-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Driving</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T235444</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars</name>
		<desc>Mario returns in this incredible new role-playing adventure! His latest rival is Smithy, a menacing creature who causes fear and treachery in the Mushroom Kingdom. Mario must recover seven stars and repair the Star Road before he can make his way to Bowser's castle for a final confrontation with Smithy. Powerful weapons, sinister spells and other useful items help Mario to complete his harrowing journey. New friends and old allies support him along the way. Even Bowser lends a hand!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid.zip</path>
		<name>Super Metroid</name>
		<desc>Take on a legion of Space Pirates and a new Metroid force as you forge into the covert underworld of Planet Zebes! It's up to you and Samus to recapture the long-surviving Metroid hatchling before evil hands unleash its energy. An army of ominous creatures are poised for battle at every turn of Zebes' twisted, threatening passageways...including the menacing Ridley and the great lizard Kraid. Knock down enemies with a killer somersault and swing on an electric beam through narrow passageways! They're no match for you and Samus...but wait! It seems the Mother Brain has returned...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Metroid-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T235431</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Punch-Out!!.zip</path>
		<name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Slug your way through the grueling and sweat-pounding matches of the Minor, Major and World Circuits. Dodge bone-bruising punches and dance to the top of the supreme Special Circuit. Face off against old favorites including Bear Hugger, Piston Hurricane, Bald Bull, Mr. Sandman and Super Macho Man plus a cast of new and weird challengers. With a right hook! Body blow! And precise quick jabs! The referee announces 'Knock Out!' Your opponent lies face down as you win the title of Nintendo Video Boxing Association Champion!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Punch-Out!!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars</name>
		<desc>Join Luke, Han and Chewbacca in their fierce war against the evil Empire. Battle treacherous aliens. Pilot two vehicles in high-speed, first-person, 3-D sequences. Fight your way through the wastelands of Tatooine to the hostile streets of Mos Eisley and beyond. So grab your blaster, strap on your lightsaber, and take on the fight for galactic freedom.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Star Wars-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi.zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars: Return of the Jedi</name>
		<desc>Join the Rebellion and crush the Death Star in a giant 16-meg universe filled with all the action and adventure of the Star Wars&amp;reg; finale. The command of five different characters-- from Wicket the Ewok to Princess Leia--and go up against the Empire's worst, from Jabba the Hutt to the Emperor himself! This is it! You're going to need every ounce of Force you're got in you.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back.zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>Pursued across the galaxy, and your Rebel Forces now marshall new strength on the remote ice world of Hoth. Although tracked by probe droids, attacked by ice monster, and confronted by an army of gigantic Imperial Walkers, you must not give in. You are the Alliance's only hope. Learn the ways of the Force, then test your skills in this fast-paced, action-packed sequel to the high game, Super Star Wars&amp;reg;.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican.zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican</name>
		<desc>You are Bren McGuire, on a United Planets Freedom Forces mission to save the peaceful planet Katakis from the Machine, source of all that is cruel and evil in the universe. The only weapon on your side is the state-of-the-art Turrican Assault Suit. Equipped with multiple weapons, including the incredible Freeze-Beam that temporarily immobilizes almost any enemy, the Turrican Assault Suit gives one man the power of an entire army.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Turrican-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican 2.zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican 2</name>
		<desc>Super Turrican 2 is an Action game, developed by Factor 5 and published by Ocean,which was released in Europe in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Turrican 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Valis IV.zip</path>
		<name>Super Valis IV</name>
		<desc>Super Valis IV is an Action game, developed and published by Laser Soft,which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Valis IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terranigma.zip</path>
		<name>Terranigma</name>
		<desc>A boy's curiosity triggers events that leads to the resurrection of life to this planet.In the Distant past, a calamitous struggle between light and dark took place on this planet. The clash of the two opposing powers scoured the planet's surface entirely of life, and those two forces fell into a deep sleep...In the world on the inside of the planet, there exists just one small village of Crysta. Ark, a mischievous teenage boy, somehow causes a crisis in the village that makes him necessary to leave. His trip to save his fellow villagers eventually becomes a journey across time to resurrect the planet. On his epic journey, Ark must resurrect continents, revive all forms of life, and re-establish civilization. What fate awaits Ark at the end of his journey?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Terranigma-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Attack.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris Attack</name>
		<desc>The Tetris sensation has landed at Yoshi's Island. Kamek and Bowser await to test your dexterity with a demanding race of strategic moves in this exciting new contest. As the stack of perplexing panels rises from the bottom, think fast to counteract the merciless enemy attack dropping in from above. Rapid switches and quick response are the key to clearing the way to the next challenging level. An incredible selection of competitive modes and options provide escalating action and endless fun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tetris Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin</name>
		<desc>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin is an Action game, developed and published by Konami,which was released in Europe in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Kid Kleets, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Kid Kleets</name>
		<desc>The Adventures of Kid Kleets is an Action game, developed by Krisalis Software and published by Yanoman,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Adventures of Kid Kleets, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Amazing Spider-Man, The - Lethal Foes.zip</path>
		<name>The Amazing Spider-Man: Lethal Foes</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man's greatest villains take the spotlight, struggling to make their way against heroes and rival villains alike! Featuring the Beetle and Speed Demon, later of the Thunderbolts! Dr. Octopus! The Vulture! Stegron! Swarm! Hydro-Man! The Rhino! The Kingpin! The Answer! And more! And guest-starring Spidey, natch!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Amazing Spider-Man, The - Lethal Foes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Agenda, Epoch</developer>
		<publisher>Epoch</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Firemen, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Firemen</name>
		<desc>The Firemen is an Action Adventure game, developed and published by Human Entertainment,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Firemen, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - The Treasure of Sierra Madrock.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones: The Treasure of Sierra Madrock</name>
		<desc>When things go wrong in Bedrock, it's up to Fred Flintstone to set them right. Fly the skies on a Pterodactyl, do some tough driving in your trusty Flintmobile and hop aboard the Dino Express! Use your club to fend off zany monsters in this excellent cartoon adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Flintstones, The - The Treasure of Sierra Madrock-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sol</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie</name>
		<desc>Mickey and Minnie plan to spend a fun-filled day at the circus but to their dismay all the performers have disappeared. Some unknown force has replaced them with crazy characters who are out to make Mickey and Minnie's day an unpleasant one. And on top of that, Donald Duck and Pluto are nowhere to be seen.As Mickey and Minnie search for clue, the trail leads them beyond the circus. Travel along with our hero and heroine as they explore 6 hostile levels like the Haunted House, Frozen Plains and the Jungle. Use special Safari or Western outfits to fend off the enemy and climb through treacherous terrain looking for Donald and Pluto. Hopefully along the way the happenings at the circus will beging to make sense.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of the Mystical Ninja</name>
		<desc>A curse has stricken the village of Horo-Horo. Their beloved princess has vanished. And without her powers, a plague of giant locusts will ravage the helpless. Talk about sick!All hope rests on the village's two ninja guardians. Kid Ying and Dr. Yang. Ying is a daring young mystical ninja who often rips apart opponents while riding a psychedelic tiger. Yang is his all-powerful mentor and master of the invincible spirit transformation. Together they must overcome ten Levels of the Dragonbeast, until they find the princess or die trying.With double Warlock Stages in most levels and intense 3D and 2D zones blasting savage stereo sound effects, you'll be challenged to perform dozens of attack moves and solve magical problems before advancing. And talk about enemies! There's the Carp Meister, who stuns victims with poisonous fighting fish; Tanaka-U-Out, a knock out artist who wallops opponents with a bone crushing hammer; and the Sumo Tag Team, kings of the unbeatable belly buster crunch.All-powerful sinjin items like the fire staff must also be captured. And if you fail to collect gold coins from defeated foes you won't receive important clues from the Fortune Palace and Char Cheddar Sushi Joint, or be allowed to go for broke at 'hidden risk' areas such as the Quiz Hose and Horse Races.But that's only the tip of the volcano. Which is why your ultimate strength must come not from your might, but from your mind.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Lion King</name>
		<desc>You think you want to be King? Get real. You're starting life as Simba, the cub. To survive and grow into a powerful adult lion, you must perfect your savage pounce, reckless roar and master fighting with all four paws. If you survive the challenge, you'll grow into a strong, ferocious adult lion.So prepare to scrap with hyenas. Blast through an elephant graveyard. Battle an in-your-face stampede of trampling wildebeests. And you'd better quit hanging with slackers like Timon and Pumbaa, unless you want to be scarfing bugs the rest of your life!Are you sure you want to be King? Then it's time to cut loose in the deadliest one-on-one brawl ever. Defeat your evil Uncle Scar. Recapture the Pridelands. And reclaim your rightful place in the Circle of Life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lion King, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>The Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>Pluto has disappeared and his pal Mickey is hot on his trail! But evil Emperor Pete won't make it easy. He's snatched poor Pluto and hidden him deep within his dungeon. Now, Mickey must summon his courage and begin a treacherous trek through Emperor Pete's magical world to rescure his chum before it's too late!Jump and touch the clouds as you and Mickey leap past buzzing bees and sinister snakes in the Treetops. Journey through the Dark Forest and dazzle Pete's guards with the power of Mickey's magical turban! Sink into the blazing inferno of the Fire Grotto and help Firefighter Mickey extinguish the flames! Scale the rocky heights of Pete's Peak and head straight for Emperor Pete's castle. Sneak inside, and Mickey must face the awesome might of Emperor Pete's sinister magic! Hurry! Pluto needs your help!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mask, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Mask</name>
		<desc>The Mask is based on the movie with the same name. The story follows poor guy Stanley Ipkiss who finds a mysterious mask and is given mysterious powers from it..

As in the movie, Stanley (aka The Mask) has some funny weapons, like the Guns, the Horn, the Hammer and the ability to transform into a big Tornado. He battles through levels inspired by the movie, including his apartment, the city streets, the bank, the park, the jail, and the night club for the final showdown.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mask, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Pearl</developer>
		<publisher>Black Pearl</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates of Dark Water, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Pirates of Dark Water</name>
		<desc>Set sail for a swashbuckling search! The Pirates of Dark Water puts you in the middle of the popular Saturday morning cartoon! Sail from island to island as one of three warrior heroes. Become Ren, the young heir to the throne and leader of the quest. Or choose Tula, the spirited heroine whose skills are as dazzling as her beauty. Or Ioz, the fortune hunting ex-pirate who's ready for action! The action will be fast and furious, so cast off! And let the hunt begin!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pirates of Dark Water, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SunSoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Twisted Tales of Spike McFang</name>
		<desc>Can Spike McFang, junior magician and vampire in training, rescure his island kingdom from the evil hands of Von Hesler? Help Spike use his magical powers to conquer the sinister leaders of 9 island areas and restore his father, Dracuman, to power.Spike's weapons? A magical hat and cape that spin at high speeds. Sure, they're unusual, but you have to get creative when you're facing killer garlic and zombies! Along the way, Spike will need to find plenty of gold and magic cards to keep going, so keep your eyes peeled. It's Spike's first chance to test his skills in real action!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RED Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tin Star.zip</path>
		<name>Tin Star</name>
		<desc>Tin Star is an Action game, developed by Software Creations and published by Nintendo,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tin Star-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose!.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Buster Busts Loose!</name>
		<desc>It's just like a real cartoon, except you're the main character!But be warned. Accept the role of Buster Bunny, and your tail will be on the line against Calamity Coyote, Elmyra, Dizzy Devil, Dr. Gene Splicer, Montana Max and gazillions of other 16 bit bullies craving a pot of Hasenpfeffer stew. Gulp!Only you can stop those pesky pranksters from getting the jump on your pal Buster Bunny. But it won't be cake, Jake! You'll have to use Buster's all new Spin Kick and Mad Dash to bust through ACME Looniversity's toughest classes. If you pass that test, you'll hop aboard a Wild West Train Ride. Then explore a spooky Monster Mansion. Play in a far-out Foot Game. Bounce through an aerial Sky Jinx in search of stratospheric treasures. And blast-off on a Babs Bunny (no relation!) rescure mission that's totally spaced-out.Ready to fork over the bucks, Buster? Well hang on your ears - there's more! Between each level are five subgames, including Furrball's Championship Squash, Hungry Boy Hamton and Plucky Duck's Go-Go Bingo. SO ACTUALLY IT'S LIKE ELEVEN GAMES IN ONE! And we haven't even mentioned the Pinball Wizardry, Acme Anvils and Icky Tricky Sticky Traps that'll make you feel like you're in an actual cartoon.Wow! To make it through all that Buster better have a lucky bunny's foot. Or else you'll be the one getting stewed!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spawn.zip</path>
		<name>Todd McFarlane's Spawn: The Video Game</name>
		<desc>They're vanishing - pawns in an unholy war! And out of the darkest shadows of the fearful city rises...Spawn! Enemies like Violator, Redeemer, Overtkill, and Malebolgia himself, are everywhere - from Bedlam Asylum to the nightmarish Darklands! Can Spawn's special powers help him survive this madness? Experience awesome combat and intense graphics in the incredible style of the comic that started is all: Todd McFarlane's Spawn!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Spawn-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Treasure Hunter G.zip</path>
		<name>Treasure Hunter G</name>
		<desc>Brothers Red and Blue G. decide to leave their idyllic village in search of their long lost father, who left the kids years ago to go treasure hunting. Unfortunately, as soon as they begin their quest, they become entangled with a mysterious girl on the run from evil monsters who holds the key to the resurrection of a great demon. Now its up to the brothers to save the world if they ever want to find their father.

Treasure Hunter G is a top-down RPG in which you control your party of four characters as they explore the fantasy/sci-fi game world in search for quests and grinding their stats while the plot advances. The game is divided in a world-map screen, a top-down "town" mode and a turn-based fight mode in which the characters are taken to generic tiled top-down arenas in which they select each character and move or attack depending on their action points.

Enemies can be seen on the map instead of jumping at you at random intervals, and you can freely decide whether to engage them or simply circle them around. The game uses a combination of hand-drawn sprites and CGI pre-rendered one (mostly for the main characters) with a distinct cute or Super Deformed design (as usual for most console RPGs).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Treasure Hunter G-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Uniracers.zip</path>
		<name>Uniracers</name>
		<desc>Single-wheeled and single-minded. Uniracers are the best at what they do: accelerate to screen-blurring speed! They're also awesome at pulling flips, twists, turns and catching monster air off the many mondo ramps, hills and half pipes of their race track worlds. The more outrageous the stunt, the faster the Uniracer goes! The sky's the limit!Racing is the entire purpose of a Uniracer's existence. You can race against the clock, against friends head-to-head or in a custom tournament. Challenge the mysterious ghost bike to become the uni-versal champion! It's one of the fastest races on the Super NES yet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Uniracers-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario's Woods.zip</path>
		<name>Wario's Woods</name>
		<desc>Wario's Woods is a Miscellaneous game, developed by Intelligent Systems and published by Nintendo,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Wario's Woods-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Miscellaneous</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Guns.zip</path>
		<name>Wild Guns</name>
		<desc>Wild Guns is an Action game, developed and published by Natsume,which was released in Japan in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Wild Guns-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wolfenstein 3D.zip</path>
		<name>Wolfenstein 3-D</name>
		<desc>Achtung! You are OSA super agent B.J. Blazkowicz. Your goal is to escape from Castle Wolfenstein and defeat the twisted Nazi regime in Wolfenstein 3D. Fight all of the memorable enemies from Hans Grosse to Mecha-Hitler in the legendary game that launched the first-person shooter genre. Search classic levels for hidden secrets revealing stolen Nazi treasure, health packs, ammo and weapons, or even short cuts.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Wolfenstein 3D-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X Zone.zip</path>
		<name>X Zone</name>
		<desc>X-Zone is an Action game, developed and published by Kemco,which was released in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/X Zone-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse.zip</path>
		<name>X-Men: Mutant Apocalypse</name>
		<desc>For years, the tiny island nation of Genosha has enslaved its mutant population while the rest of the world has turned a blind eye. Now, as the situation turns bleak, Professor Charles Xavior is stunned to find the true force lurking behind the Genoshan government. With the fate of all mutantkind hanging in the balance, Professor Xavior must unleash the X-Men to face the most powerful mutant of them all- The Mighty Apocalypse!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sandro no Daibouken.zip</path>
		<name>Xandra no Daibouken: Valkyrie to no Deai</name>
		<desc>Whirlo is an Action game, developed by Nova Games Ltd. and published by Namco,which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Sandro no Daibouken-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nova Games Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Safari.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Safari</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Safari is an Action game, developed by TOSE and published by Nintendo,which was released in Japan in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Yoshi's Safari-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys.zip</path>
		<name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<desc>Adventure beckons! Test your skills in a ralm wrought with savage monsters hungry for blood! Dare to answer the call of the unknown in Adol's continuing saga against the forces that threaten to engulf the enchanted land of Ys!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ys III - Wanderers from Ys-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Advance Communication Company</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys IV - Mask of the Sun.zip</path>
		<name>Ys IV: Mask of the Sun</name>
		<desc>After having defeated the ultimate evil in his previous adventure, the great hero Adol stands on a sea shore, thinking about the fate of the once peaceful Utopian land of Ys, while the wind is blowing through his red hair. Suddenly, Adol notices a bottle, thrown onto the shore. It contains a letter, written in a foreign language, in which an unknown person asks Adol to come to his land and save it from a mysterious evil. Adol decides to accept the offer, and thus his adventure begins again...

Ys IV: Mask of the Sun is an action RPG with a combat system like the earlier Ys games. An enemy should be rammed from the sides in order to hurt him. If performed incorrectly, the player will get hurt himself. It's also possible to use magic and position oneself strategically in battle so that the enemy won't be able to inflict any damage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ys IV - Mask of the Sun-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tonkin House</developer>
		<publisher>American Sammy</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys V - Kefin, Lost Kingdom of Sand.zip</path>
		<name>Ys V: Lost Kefin, Kingdom of Sand</name>
		<desc>Ys V: Kefin, The Lost City of Sand is the fifth game of the series. It was released for Snes in 1995. A remake was released for PS2 in 2006.

Adol is travelling through new lands, in search of more adventure, when he hears of the vanished desert city of Kefin. He sets off to investigate this ancient city's disappearance.

The RPG-style statistical elements and the overhead view of most of the previous games are retained in Ys V. As in Ys III, there is no auto-attack; the player must press a button to swing Adol's sword. Adol is also given the ability to jump and defend with his shield. A new magic system is introduced in Ys V as well, which requires the player to charge up spells by holding a button before they can be cast.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ys V - Kefin, Lost Kingdom of Sand-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19951229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel.zip</path>
		<name>Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel</name>
		<desc>Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel is an Action game, developed by Iguana Entertainment and published by SunSoft,which was released in 1994.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Pop'n.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Pop'n</name>
		<desc>The game is a side-scroller which is divided into six stages. The player starts with a three-heart life gauge and one spell attack. The player can increase Princess's lives by collecting golden tokens (which look like the Princess's face), gaining one life for every three coins collected. The player can also increase health by finding heart containers in treasure chests. Spells can be obtained throughout the game and are important for advancing further.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Magical Pop'n-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polestar</developer>
		<publisher>Pack-In-Video</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chavez.zip</path>
		<name>Chavez</name>
		<desc>Julio César Chávez is undefeated. You want a piece of him? You'll get your shot, as this game allows you to create your fighter and rise through the ranks against fighters of all styles. The 65 fighters include a list of 25 ranked opponents each with a unique approach to boxing. In Career mode, your fighter will actually age throughout the course of the game, and complete stats on you efforts are recorded. You'll go through rigorous training between bouts, each session designed to help you against Bowe, himself. You'll get plenty advice from Chávez, but that doesn't mean he'll go easy on you when your time comes to square off against him.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chavez-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>American Softworks Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Malibu Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS Zelda no Densetsu.zip</path>
		<name>BS Zelda no Densetsu</name>
		<desc>BS Zelda no Densetsu was an expanded version of The Legend of Zelda that was released for the Satellaview attachment of the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in Japan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/BS Zelda no Densetsu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>St. GIGA</publisher>
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bushi Seiryuuden - Futari no Yuusha.zip</path>
		<name>Bushi Seiryuuden: Futari no Yuusha</name>
		<desc>Bushi Seiryuuden: Futari no Yuusha is a Role-Playing game, developed by Game Freak and published by T&amp;E Soft, which was released in Japan in 1997.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Bushi Seiryuuden - Futari no Yuusha-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>T&amp;E Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos Seed.zip</path>
		<name>Chaos Seed</name>
		<desc>Delve into the depths of vast underground labyrinths, seeking aid from the spirit world in bringing life back to a dying planet!  Chaos Seed is a role-playing game with elements of action and strategy blended in.  Players will have to make smart use of their resources and use feng shui to their advantage to proceed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chaos Seed-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Macross - Scrambled Valkyrie.zip</path>
		<name>Choujikuu Yousai Macross: Scrambled Valkyrie</name>
		<desc>A.D. 2009: The human race is in the middle of a three-way war with a race of giant humanoid aliens split into the Zentrans and Meltlans. After executing a space fold that sent it and part of South Ataria Island to the edge of the Solar System, the space fortress Macross is on its way back to Earth. During a small skirmish with Zentradi forces, young pilot Hikaru Ichijyo rescues idol singer Lynn Minmay and their relationship develops as they're stranded somewhere within the ship. But shortly after returning to Macross City, Minmay is captured by the Zentradi, and Hikaru and female officer Misa Hayase end up back on Earth—only to view the aftermath of the destruction of their civilization. Only a song discovered eons ago—along with Minmay's voice—can determine the outcome of the war.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Macross - Scrambled Valkyrie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Winky Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Zamuse</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow.zip</path>
		<name>Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow</name>
		<desc>When he morphs into a ninja, you better duck! Play as Maui. Play as the Ninja. Play as Maui. Play as the Ninja. Try not to get dizzy. Find the missing Shabuhm Shabuhm idol before your island paradise goes kaboom kaboom! 40 hours of intense gameplay. So pack plenty of attitude. And your bug gun. Come beak to beak with MudDrakes, Rotting Pirates, Duck Zombies, Amazon Warriors. And a bunch of fowl-tempered hangers-on. Laugh in the face of danger from the top of a volcano, the bottom of the sea, the Realm of the Dead, and Ninja Training Grounds. Then get the heck out! Live every level like it's your last - 'cuz it may be!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat 2.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>Following his failure to defeat to Liu Kang in the first Mortal Kombat game, the evil sorcerer Shang Tsung begs his master, Shao Kahn, to spare his life. He tells Shao Kahn that the invitation for Mortal Kombat cannot be turned down, and if they hold it in Outworld, the Earthrealm warriors must attend. Kahn agrees to this plan, and even restores Tsung's youth. He then extends the invitation to Raiden, who gathers his warriors and takes them into Outworld. The new tournament is much more dangerous, as Shao Kahn has the home field advantage, and an Outworld victory will allow him to subdue Earthrealm.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mortal Kombat 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rockman &amp; Forte.zip</path>
		<name>Rockman &amp; Forte</name>
		<desc>Join Rockman and Forte's fight for humankind as you face off with the newest menace in town--Robot King. King's captured all of the data plans for Dr. Wily's creations. They will equip King with all the knowledge he needs to build his own indestructible army of robots. As either Rockman or Forte, you'll set out separate adventures using a variety of battle moves and weapons to defeat robot masters. Hidden bolts and CDs give you extra items to assist in battles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Rockman &amp; Forte-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW2 - SMW2+2 - Yoshi's Island.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World 2+2: Yoshi's Island</name>
		<desc>The first of several full-length hacks of 'Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island' created by Golden Yoshi.  This hack brings a total of 54 entirely original levels to the classic Yoshi's Island that we all love.  While not as polished as his second (and most popular) hack, this one still features excellent level design with some of the most challenging Yoshi stages you'll see.  Make no mistake, these stages are tough, but not unfair.  Veteran players rejoice, but newbies beware; Conquer the original Yoshi's Island first, then give this one a try.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW2 - SMW2+2 - Yoshi's Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GoldenYoshi</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW2 - NEW! Yoshi's Island.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World 2: New! Yoshi's Island</name>
		<desc>The first of several full-length hacks of 'Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island' created by Golden Yoshi.  This hack brings a total of 54 entirely original levels to the classic Yoshi's Island that we all love.  While not as polished as his second (and most popular) hack, this one still features excellent level design with some of the most challenging Yoshi stages you'll see.  Make no mistake, these stages are tough, but not unfair.  Veteran players rejoice, but newbies beware; Conquer the original Yoshi's Island first, then give this one a try.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW2 - NEW! Yoshi's Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GoldenYoshi</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid (Z-Factor).zip</path>
		<name>Super Metroid Z-Factor</name>
		<desc>"Take on a legion of Space Pirates and a new Metroid force as you forge into the covert underworld of Planet Zebes! It's up to you and Samus to recapture the long-surviving Metroid hatchling before evil hands unleash its energy. An army of ominous creatures are poised for battle at every turn of Zebes' twisted, threatening passageways...including the menacing Ridley and the great lizard Kraid. Knock down enemies with a killer somersault and swing on an electric beam through narrow passageways! They're no match for you and Samus...but wait! It seems the Mother Brain has returned..."

(Japanese Version)</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Metroid (Z-Factor)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tales of Phantasia.zip</path>
		<name>Tales of Phantasia</name>
		<desc>In "Tales of Phantasia", you play a young boy named Cless, who lives together with his parents in a quiet village. It was a day like all the others when Cless decided to go hunting with his best friend Chester. Chasing a wild boar, Cless discovered a strange talking tree in the forest who was pleading him for help. But as soon as it stopped speaking, the two friends heard the sound of an alarm. They returned to the village and found it burnt down, and all its inhabitants murdered. Before Cless' mother died in his arms, she told him this terrible massacre had something to do with the pendant she and her husband gave Cless for his birthday... what connection could there be? Cless decides to visit his uncle who lives in another town, but he doesn't realize his journey will take him to much more remote places than that!

The game's main claim to fame is its intro theme, which incorporates a vocal track. Normally, such a track cannot be done on the SNES, as all assets for a single song must fit into the 64kB audio buffer before the song can be played. This technical limit was overcome by slicing the vocal track into small samples and swapping them in and out of the audio buffer. The rest of the intro theme is standard MIDI.

"Tales of Phantasia" presents a unique combat system. The battles have a lot in common with fighting games: you fight on a platform that slowly scrolls forward and have to attack your enemy in real time. Other party members are controlled by AI. You can pause the game at any time and use magic, items, or choose an overall strategy for your allies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tales of Phantasia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda - A Link to the Past.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past</name>
		<desc>Venture back to Hyrule and an age of magic and heroes.  The predecessors of Link and Zelda face monsters on the march when a menacing magician takes over the kingdom.  Only you can prevent his evil plot from shattering the land of Hyrule.

In your quest, you’ll venture into twisting mazes, dungeons, palaces and shadowy forests.  Test your mettle with mighty swords and magical weapons.  Or heft a boulder and hurl it at your enemies.  If the going gets tough, dive into a river--you can swing to escape!  Learn powerful spells, locate magical artifacts and solve the mysteries of the evil magician and the hidden realm of Hyrule.

This exciting Super NES sequel to the Legend of Zelda and The Adventure of Link uses 16-bit power to create a quest so colorful and detailed you don’t just play it, you live it!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Zelda - A Link to the Past-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda - Goddess of Wisdom.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Goddess of Wisdom</name>
		<desc>Hack of The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Zelda - Goddess of Wisdom-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20101017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Omega, SePH, Dude Man, PuzzleDude, Francais</developer>
		<publisher>RomHacking.net</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda 3 - Parallel Remodelled.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Parallel Worlds Remodel</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: Parallel Worlds is a fan overhaul of The Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past using new graphics, new music, a new overworld and underworld, and a new storyline. This is a conversion which lowers the difficulty and minimize the backtracking.

You moved here from another land with a friend to find treasure. Not long after your arrival, a lot of strange occurrences started.

Seven people "appeared out of nowhere" and beings questioning about the Parallel Tower and the inhabitants of Kakariko Village. The Parallel Tower was situated in the Sky Islands northeast of the village. The legend behind the Parallel Tower was long lost, and only the elders knew the legend.

Word begins to spread out about the Parallel Tower, and people started to learn about the legend again. The legend says it was a by product of a war long ago and a power, known as the Triforce, existed at the top of it. It is said that nobody knows about the clues as to how to get to the top of the Tower. The seven people are said to know about these "clues" to the Tower.

The king was notified of these seven people and he invited them to the castle to find out what they wanted with the tower. Just the night before the seven people are to have an audience with the king, the king's assistant, Draegor, eliminates the king and claims the throne by default.

The seven people walked right into an obvious trap. Draegor, who people believe is a power hungry person, caught all 7 people and forces them to tell him what they know about the Tower.

When the people learned of the king's fate, a rebel force is gathered in secret to plot against Draegor. The rebel force learned that 2 out of 7 people whom Draegor caught are still alive and imprisoned in the guardhouse. They quickly rallied anyone who may be interested in the Tower and the locals to help these last 2 people.

You and your friend heard about this plan and are willing help the rebels against Draegor.

The night of the operation begins the story...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Zelda 3 - Parallel Remodelled-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20120728T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Euclid, PuzzleDude, SePH</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking.net</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombies Ate My Neighbors.zip</path>
		<name>Zombies Ate My Neighbors</name>
		<desc>In the game you are a male or female protagonist (Zeke or Julia), fighting the vampires, mummies, zombies, etc. on over 50 levels (not including secrets) and saving all of the people you find. There are defined number of neighbors you save on every level. When they are free then "Exit" door opens and you jump on next level.The levels differ from mall and grocery store to beaches and football fields. Using different weapons such as bazooka or water gun you have to kill the bosses such as huge babies, dragons or ants at the end of levels. You can play the game with two players cooperatively.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Zombies Ate My Neighbors-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy: Mystic Quest</name>
		<desc>Focus Tower is the center of the world and balances the forces of the world. However 4 monsters have taken the 4 elemental crystals (Earth, Water, Fire, Wind) for their own use, and also taken the 4 keys that for doors inside of Focus Tower. With the balance disrupted, disasters befall the world. A young boy by the name of Benjamin finds his home village destroyed. Meeting a mysterious old man while trying to escape from earthquakes, he soon learns that he is the prophesized hero and the only one who can save the world. Benjamin must recover the 4 crystals, unlock Focus Tower and defeat the ultimate monster before the 5th crystal, the Crystal of Life is corrupted.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X2.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X2</name>
		<desc>Just when Mega Man X thought he had brought down all the X-Hunters, several months later an uprising moves from within an abandoned factory. While 8 all-new X-Hunters occupy Mega Man X, a triple threat plots to resurrect a secret weapon that is all too familiar!

The good Dr. Light supplies Mega man X with incredible new abilities hidden in capsules buried deep below the surface. And with new vehicles like the mobile attack cycle plus powers he gains from the X-Hunters, Mega Man X will be ready to face his destiny as a Maverick Hunter. Now it's all or Zero for Mega Man X!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Megaman X2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Super Zero Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid: Super Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>Created by none other than the brilliant SB in 2011, this Super Metroid hack is perhaps, "the most tightly woven, intricate, satisfying, and worthwhile Metroid experience ever created since the original. Big words, you say? Well, they're justly deserved."

MSZM paints the picture of the original Zero Mission as we only had imagined it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Metroid Super Zero Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20111022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SB</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking.net</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Tuff.zip</path>
		<name>Mr.Tuff</name>
		<desc>Mr. Tuff is a 2D platform game in development by Sales Curve Interactive (SCI) and presumably set to be published by Ocean in 1994-1995. The game was done by the same people as Super SWIV, and as such, the graphics are incredibly polished. The game was apparently too ambitious, and was never fully complete (although the game engine and graphics certainly indicate that it is close).

The game follows a demolition robot known as Mr. Tuff. After the entire population of earth escapes to the planet Utopia, the army robots take over the world. It is up to Mr. Tuff to save the world for the peaceful domestic robots. The levels involve standard platform action, though there are a few shooter-esce hoverboard levels. Each world is set up into standard levels and a boss level.

***Mr. Tuff is a cancelled platform game that was in development by Sales Curve in 1995, for the Super Nintendo. The project was almost finished but for some reasons it was never officially released in the end. A playable prototype was leaked online sometime ago and you should be able to find searching for “Mr Tuff (Prototype).smc” on Google***

NO boxart ever existed for that game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mr. Tuff-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCI</developer>
		<publisher>Laguna</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninjawarriors Again, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Ninja Warriors Again</name>
		<desc>The land is under the grip of a tyrant named Benglar, who is able to brainwash those he captures. Using this ability he has taken over the military forces and now appears unstoppable. However, resistance forces lead by Mulk have been developing a new weapon: Cybernetic Special Forces with the ability to think, dubbed the Ninja Warriors. Untested, these machines are given the orders to assassinate Benglar...

Ninja Warriors plays as a side scrolling beat 'em up, and is a single player adaptation of The Ninja Warriors arcade game. Players can choose from 3 different Ninja Warriors: Ninja, Kunoichi or Kamaitachi. The characters play differently, but share some common controls. Each can attack, jump, grab the enemy, block attacks or unleash a special attack on the entire screen. This special attack charges up gradually and can be reset by being knocked to the ground.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ninjawarriors Again, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<folder>
		<path>./SMW Hacks</path>
		<name>Super Mario World Hacks &gt;</name>
		<desc>A large compilation of Super Mario World Hacks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hacks.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaizou Chounin Shubibin Man Zero.zip</path>
		<name>Kaizou Choujin Shubibinman Zero</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kaizou Chounin Shubibin Man Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Masaya</developer>
		<publisher>NCS</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gulliver Boy.zip</path>
		<name>Kuusou Kagaku Sekai Gulliver Boy</name>
		<desc>Spain is trying to take over Europe, and Judo, prince of Spain or something, killed Gulliver’s father. Now Gulliver’s pissed off and wants revenge. Who wouldn’t? And so you set off to kick ass with nothing but Edison’s bombs, Gulliver’s hadouken thing, and Gulliver’s gigantic hair. Misty eventually joins you, but ends up being dead weight at first :P Oh, and in the second part of the game, you get this badass mech thing for all of two or three boss battles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Gulliver Boy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170303T225520</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest III.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest III: Soshite Densetsu e...</name>
		<desc>Your father, the brave Ortega, is dead. He set off to destroy the Archfiend Baramos but fell in glorious battle. Unless stopped, Baramos will unleash a torrent of evil that will destroy the world. You must stop Baramos and discover the legend of Dragon Quest! Your journey starts in Aliahan. Only you decide where it ends...

Originally not released outside of Japan, this version has earned itself several fan translations over the years.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dragon Quest III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19961206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heart Beat</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby no Kirakira Kids.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby no KiraKira Kids</name>
		<desc>Kirby no KiraKira Kids is a Puzzle game, developed by HAL Labs and published by Nintendo, which was released in Japan in 1998.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kirby no Kirakira Kids-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Labs</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox.zip</path>
		<name>Star Fox</name>
		<desc>Lead the Star Fox Team to Victory!

In the distant Lylat star system, imagine yourself at the controls of a futuristic, heavily armed, space fighter - Arwing.

Lead the counter-attack on an invasion force of hundreds of alien tanks, fighter ships, laser gun emplacements and super battleships.  Maneuver at warp speed through fog-enshrouded canyons, dense asteroid belts and waves of the enemy's best defense.  You must use skill and cunning to bring the fight to the enemy's home planet Venom and smash the Core Brain for victory!

* The Super FX micro chip is on-board for fluid game control and special effects previously unavailable in home video games!  The action explodes from all directions in realistic, real-time, three dimensions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Star Fox-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 2.zip</path>
		<name>Star Fox 2</name>
		<desc>Star Fox 2 continued the battle against Emperor Andross who seeks to conquer the Lylat system, with the Star Fox team assembled once again to defeat him. The game introduces a new semi-real time game play system, featuring new ship types and two new Star Fox team members. It also features a more advanced 3D game engine thanks to a new improved version of the Super FX chip. Cancelled. 

The Japanese version was completely finished except for minor debugging tools that weren't yet removed. It is unknown if there are any complete official English versions, though an unofficial fan translation exists.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Star Fox 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island</name>
		<desc>The Evil Magikoopa, Kamek, is out to kidnap Baby Mario!  In this sequel to Super Mario World, you play as Yoshi.  Your goal is to successfully carry Baby Mario back to his parents in the Mushroom Kingdom while avoiding all of Kamek’s clever traps and evil minions.  Enjoy the various backgrounds of the rich and vibrant locales of Yoshi’s Island as you race to complete your quest.

Is Yoshi up to the momentous task at hand?  Help him toss his eggs, manipulate unique objects and solve puzzling situations!  When in doubt, don’t be afraid to try EVERYTHING!!

* 16 megs of memory provide 6 worlds - each with 8 stages!
* Morphmation delivers powerful special effects - scaling, rotating, and 360 degree scrolling.
* Huge characters and even bigger bosses require quick thinking!
* Battery back-up to save your progress.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T011537</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter II - The New Challengers.zip</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II</name>
		<desc>A New Challenge Awaits

For two years, they have reigned supreme. Twelve of the most gifted fighters from across the world have battled each other in the World Warrior tournament. But the time has come for them to step aside - Now is the time of the New Challengers!

Cammy, Dee Jay, T. Hawk and Fei Long have earned the right to enter the World Warrior Tournament. Each of them possess a lethal combination of martial arts skills that they believe can destroy M. Bison. But can they survive the original Street Fighters and their new abilities? Only the true Street Fighters among you will find out!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Street Fighter II - The New Challengers-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAPCOM</developer>
		<publisher>CAPCOM</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 4 - Turtles in Time.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV: Turtles In Time</name>
		<desc>Sunday evening. You're sitting around the sewer watching your main reported, April O'Neil do a live remote from the Statue of Liberty. Then it happens. A humungoso flying android screams out of the sky and rips Lady Liberty from her foundation, sending hundreds of freaked out tourists into the harbor below. "No way!" cries Raphael. "Way," replies Donatello. And the crazy quantum chase is on!
Journey through ten levels of enormous arcade graphics, the largest and craziest talking Turtles ever with eons of bodacious battlegrounds, from prehistoric to futuristic galaxies. To prepare for the toughest Shred-heads you've ever seen, try the Versus mode, a Turtle-on-Turtle combat arena that finally proves who's the mightiest mutant of all. Also test your slice-em-up speed in the Time Trials mode to find out how fast you can clear three courses.
Get ready for the 3-D jab and toss that sends enemies flying right in your face. Mondo body slams and pizza power bonuses make you more Turtle than ever before. You better believe you're going to need it. Shredder's out for Turtle hide. And he's got all the time in the world to get it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 4 - Turtles in Time-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wile E Coyotes Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Wile E. Coyote's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Wile E. Coyote's Revenge is a sidescrolling platform game that was developed by Software Creations and planned to be released by Sunsoft for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. However, Sunsoft's American offices closed due to bankruptcy before this would come to fruition, and the game went unreleased. The original concept was created by Rene Boutin and Mark Dawson. The game was a sequel to Road Runner's Death Valley Rally. The player controls Wile E. Coyote. His goal is to catch the Road Runner. However, true to the cartoon, the Road Runner will speed away as soon as Wile E. gets remotely near him.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Wile E Coyotes Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM</developer>
		<publisher>Suncorp</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dracula X.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dracula X</name>
		<desc>In Transylvania, people lived in fear of the evil Count Dracula. The ultimate embodiment of evil, Dracula swept his dark hand over the land, making the people mere sheep for his thirst for blood. But when a young woman named Sonia Belmont came forth to confront him, he made a horrible mistake: he underestimated her. Thus, the battle between Dracula and the Belmont family began.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Castlevania - Dracula X-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Front Mission</name>
		<desc>Set in 2090, the story of Front Mission revolves an Oceania Community Union (OCU) officer by the name of Roid Clive. An OCU squadron lead by Roid and Ryuji Sakata entered a special United States of the New Continent (USN) ammunition dump at the Larcus District on Huffman Island (a fictional Pacific island roughly the size of Oahu, "formed in 1995 from volcanic activity, east of the Pacific Ocean, south of Mexico's west coast. The landmass was large enough to classify as an island in 2002 and all authority and proprietary rights was granted to the United Nations."). Roid's fiancee, Karen Meure, is already inside. However, the uneasy quiet is broken when a USN Wanzer squad led by an officer named Driscoll ambushes Meure on the premises. Driscoll himself kills her, setting the stage for the game's first mission, called "The Larcus Incident."

After the player defeats the rest of the USN force, Driscoll escapes, but not before he detonates bombs inside the complex.

The entire incident is pinned on Roid and Sakata, who are summarily dismissed from the OCU Ground Defense Force. The fiasco also broke a peace treaty between the OCU and USN, setting off the Second Huffman War. One year later, OCU Colonel Guri Olson seeks out Roid (who is a Wanzer fighter in the western town of Barinden) to work with the Canyon Crows mercenary unit. Roid joins after Olson dangles the prospect of killing the USN officer responsible for Karen's death.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Front Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>G-Craft</developer>
		<publisher>SquareSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World</name>
		<desc>Mario's off on his biggest adventure ever, and this time he's brought along a friend. Yoshi the dinosaur teams up with Mario to battle Bowser, who has kidnapped Princess Toadstool once again. Guide Mario and Yoshi through nine peril-filled worlds to the final showdown in Bowser's castle. Use Mario's new powers and Yoshi's voracious monster-gobbling appetite as you explore 96 levels filled with dangerous new monsters and traps. Climb mountains and cross rivers, and descend into subterranean depths. Destroy the seven Koopa castles and find keys to gain entrance to hidden levels. Discover more warps and thrilling bonus worlds than ever before!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Mario World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20171205T004223</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Far East of Eden Zero.zip</path>
		<name>Far East of Eden Zero</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Far East of Eden Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Undercover Cops.zip</path>
		<name>Undercover Cops</name>
		<desc>2043. Dr. Clayborn and his army have gained control of New York and Commissioner Gordon made one last plea for help and called three of the finest city sweepers: Matt, an ex-professional football player; Rosa, a former female vigilante and Miss America pageant; and Zan, an ex-karate master and a retired philosophy teacher. They must fight every lackey and vanquish Dr. Clayborn in order to restore law and order to the city.

Go through the game's five stages, defeating enemies along the way and destroying the end-of-level boss before proceeding to the next stage. Along the way, weapons such as fish, rocks, i-beams, cars, and more can be used.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Undercover Cops-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Varie Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20171206T033902</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arcus Odyssey.zip</path>
		<name>Arcus Odyssey</name>
		<desc>This is a Gauntlet-like game: lots of action and magic, with items to collects, and many dungeons to free from monsters. The game is also viewed from an isometric perspective, typical for the genre. Choose one of four characters to battle your way through dungeons and castles, or play with a friend in a 2-player mode</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Arcus Odyssey-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius III.zip</path>
		<name>Gradius III</name>
		<desc>A horizontal shooter where you control Vic Viper, a spaceship that increases its power by collecting capsules left by destroyed enemies. The player chooses the desired power-up by collecting capsules until the required cell is lit on the menu. The game is divided into stages, each containing a boss that must be destroyed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Gradius III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr Nutz.zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Nutz</name>
		<desc>You are the cool squirrel of the title, and you must defeat the evil Yeti before he freezes the entire world. Your quest will make you explore many areas such as a forest, a witch's cottage, a volcano, the clouds, a circus...

Mr. Nutz is a platform game, in which Nutz must jump on enemies to kill them. His tail can also be controlled. You move through levels using ledges, ladders, bridges and platforms. There are some simple puzzles involving object manipulation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mr Nutz-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightmare Busters.zip</path>
		<name>Nightmare Busters</name>
		<desc>Synchronized with the wavelengh of dreams, the miserable Tyrant has discovered a way to enter them and convolute what children see, hear and feel while they sleep - all for the benefit of his twisted amusement. Enter Flynn and his twin brother Floyd, two virtuous leprechauns who refuse to sit idly by while the Tyrant weaves his dreadful delusions. Get going, gents! There's no time to lose!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Nightmare Busters-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20131223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arcade Zone Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Super Fight Team</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid Redesign.zip</path>
		<name>Super Metroid Redesign</name>
		<desc>Take on a legion of Space Pirates and a new Metroid force as you forge into the covert underworld of Planet Zebes!  It’s up to you and Samus to recapture the long-surviving Metroid hatchling before evil hands unleash its energy.

An army of ominous creatures are poised for battle at every turn of Zebes’ twisted, threatening passageways… including the menacing Ridley and the great lizard Kraid.  Knock down enemies with a killer somersault and swing on an electric beam through narrow passageways!  They’re no match for you and Samus… but wait!  It seems the Mother Brain has returned…</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Metroid Redesign-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family Values.zip</path>
		<name>Addams Family Values</name>
		<desc>Baby Pubert, the most recent addition to the Addams Family, has been abducted by Debbie Jellinski, his former nanny. As Uncle Fester it is your job to rescue little Pubert. You must search the surrounding areas (forests, swamps, gardens and the like) of Addams mansion, while avoiding traps, solving puzzles and killing monsters. You'll face such hellish creatures as vultures, gargoyles, bats, ghosts and ghouls.

During your mission, you'll run into Gomez, Morticia, Lurch and other members of the Addams Family, who are on the grounds to lend advice and provide items. These items include a box of seeds for producing enemy-attacking mini bushes, black beetle cookies which give Fester a dose of ill-health (this is a good thing), stone marbles for turning attackers into rock, a bowling ball for hitting enemies and breaking through walls and a battery, which powers up Fester's standard Zzap attack. Within the seven levels of play, there are tons of other creatures to zap and items to find.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Addams Family Values-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<developer>Ocean Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Addams Family</name>
		<desc>Creepy, Kooky, Ooky, Spooky.

THE ADDAMS FAMILY has been evicted! To save their home from Tully Alford, the family attorney, who is after the family fortune - Morticia, Lurch, Granny, Pugsley and Wednesday have gone to the house to reason with him. But when Gomez arrives, his family is missing! As Gomez, you must save your loved ones, your home and your loads of wealth. You'll have to watch out for scary obstacles like falling spikes, frightening monsters and ghosts, and you'll need to look for clues as you search for your family. Get a move on... 'cause you're gonna make a call on THE ADDAMS FAMILY!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Addams Family, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animaniacs.zip</path>
		<name>Animaniacs</name>
		<desc>Animaniacs is a video game that is based on the hit animated series of the same name. Unlike regular platform games, the player usually runs from the enemies rather than fighting them. Characters include Yakko, Wakko, and Dot, Pinky and the Brain, most of the supporting cast, as well as Ralph, the Warner Brothers studio guard. Animaniacs was made into two games which bore no relation to each other in terms of gameplay, despite both being made by Konami. One was for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System and the other was for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis and Game Boy. The SNES and Mega Drive/Genesis version were released in 1994, and the Game Boy version in 1995.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Animaniacs-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arkanoid - Doh It Again.zip</path>
		<name>Arkanoid: Doh It Again</name>
		<desc>Much like the game Breakout, the player controls the "Vaus", a space vessel that acts as the game's "paddle" which prevents a ball from falling from the playing field, attempting to bounce it against a number of bricks. The ball striking a brick causes the brick to disappear. When all the bricks are gone, the player goes to the next level, where another pattern of bricks appear. There are a number of variations (bricks that have to be hit multiple times, flying enemy ships, etc.) and power-up capsules to enhance the Vaus (expand the Vaus, multiply the number of balls, equip a laser cannon, break directly to the next level, etc.), but the gameplay remains the same.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Arkanoid - Doh It Again-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assault Suits Valken.zip</path>
		<name>Assault Suits Valken</name>
		<desc>In a future where fossil fuels are limited, major countries and forces of the world are at war with one another over territory. Alliances are made, forming two major sides: The Axis and The Federation. The elite units in these wars are Assault Suits, man-piloted combat mechs called Assault Suits. Jake is one such pilot, drafted into the Pacific States' Marine Corp under the Federation. During his training, the war has grown substantially and upon being assigned to a platoon, he is immediately thrown into combat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Assault Suits Valken-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bahamut Lagoon.zip</path>
		<name>Bahamut Lagoon</name>
		<desc>Bahamut Lagoon combines RPG mechanics with squad-based combat. Characters have HP, MP (SP for fighter characters), EXP, equipment, stats and class-specific, SP-draining special elemental abilities very much like traditional console RPGs. The player can explore his surroundings, talk to people and visit shops when not in battle, though to a limited degree as there is no world map and no way to leave the current area.

The game's core is its turn-based battles fought on a 2d grid. Characters are assembled into parties of four and the player allowed a maximum of six parties, which are usually well outnumbered. The two opposing sides act in alternating turns so that each party can move once and/or attack once a turn. Attacks are divided into distant and close-up combat. In the former, a party uses a special ability (e.g. casting fireballs, throwing lightning, healing allies) of one of its members at a distance. The range and possible area of effect damage vary per ability. If the attacking party has two or more characters with the same ability, they join in the action to multiply its effectiveness. Distant combat results in less money and generally less damage, but the target cannot retaliate. Distant attacks can also affect the field; fire and ice ignite or extinguish forests and melt or freeze ice, etc. Close-up, each unit in two adjacent opposing parties can act once. Very much like Final Fantasy SNES combat, they can attack an enemy, use an item or a special ability (though these can't be combined and most only affect one target instead of all) or defend.

Dragons are the player's ace in the hole. They have their own stats and gain experience like normal characters do. In battle, each party has a dragon attached to it and draws a large portion of its strength from that of its dragon: if a party's dragon is slain, the party will lose the ability to use special attacks and class-specific abilities for the remainder of the map. The beast acts as a very powerful autonomous unit that moves after its party does and it cannot be controlled beyond very simple commands, e.g. "Come!" Out of battle, dragons will eat anything and raising them by feeding them items is an important part of the game. Feeding can improve their stats as well as affect their behavior on the field, and the dragons develop into new forms as they grow.

The player can change the characters in each of the parties, their formation as well as what dragon represents them at will.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Bahamut Lagoon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Biker Mice from Mars.zip</path>
		<name>Biker Mice from Mars</name>
		<desc>The fish-faced Plutarkians have devastated Mars--the home planet of Throttle, Vinnie and Modo. These three rebel rodents escaped the mayhems and landed in Chicago, only to find that Limburger, the Plutarkian Leader, set Earth as his next target!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Biker Mice from Mars-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2.zip</path>
		<name>BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2</name>
		<desc>BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2 (BS F-ZEROグランプリ２?) is the direct sequel to the original F-Zero game released for the Super Famicom via the Satellaview. Two versions were released - a non-SoundLink game and a SoundLink game. The original non-SoundLink version was released as BSF-Zero 2 Practice (BSF-ZERO2プラクティス?) on June 1, 1997 (although the title screen remained the same). It contained the four courses first seen throughout BS F-Zero Grand Prix (a Satellaview remake of the original), along with a new course called Mute City IV. Little is known about the later SoundLink version outside of surviving videos, but it was distributed in two halves in August 1997 and had a similar announcer and redone soundtrack as the previous Satellaview entry. At least the first week rearranged a few courses, and replaced two with new locations called "Forest I" and "Forest II". Presuming no areas were repeated, this likely means the SoundLink version had twice as many courses total. In addition, it can be seen that the player cannot choose between Grand Prix and Practice modes in the SoundLink version; as it was a live broadcast, the player is forced to play each course in a timed Practice mode, and then the Grand Prix race.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/BS F-Zero Grand Prix 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubsy in Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind.zip</path>
		<name>Bubsy in: Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind</name>
		<desc>A race of fabric-stealing aliens called "Woolies", who have stolen the world's yarn ball supply (especially Bubsy's, who owns the world's largest collection). Naturally, Bubsy does not take too kindly to the theft and sets out to "humble" the Woolies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Bubsy in Claws Encounters of the Furred Kind-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Solid Software</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move.zip</path>
		<name>Bust-a-Move</name>
		<desc>Which will burst first: your concentration or the level you're working on? It takes more than just swinging the bubble-turret and taking aim on the falling ceiling; tactical planning and mental dexterity are the only way to string together three or more bubbles and 100 wins to make it through all the bubble and ego-bursting rounds of Bust-a-Move!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Bust-A-Move-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Commando.zip</path>
		<name>Captain Commando</name>
		<desc>The player chooses one of these four characters, who must fight their way through an army of genetically engineered super-criminal, traveling through a series of locations such as the bank, museum, circus, aquarium, and several others, right through to a planet called "Callisto", where the evil behind "Scumocide" awaits. All four characters have their own special attacks. Captain Commando can use the power of his suit to shoot electricity through his palms. Baby Head rides around in a mech suit which does more damage. Mack can use short knives. Each location ends with the character defeating a boss before proceeding to the next one.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Captain Commando-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chavez II.zip</path>
		<name>Chavez II</name>
		<desc>Let's get ready to rumble!

Nine of the most legendary middleweights: Julio César Chávez, Sugar Ray Leonard, Roberto Duran, Thomas Hearns, James Toney, Marvelous Marvin Hagler, Jake LaMotta, Sugar Ray Robinson and Rocky Graziano collide in gigantic proportions. This decisive boxing simulation features a revolutionary perspective and knockout graphics!

Every fighter uses his authentic style, seven power packed punches and three pulverizing super punches! Throw uppercuts, right or left crosses and devastating body blows! Bob and weave, clinch and block. Analyze end of round stats to enhance your performance.

Choose from the eight fighters or create your own legend. Train to hone your fighting skills; choose from three modes of game play. Select the Exhibition or Career modes and master the art of boxing.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chavez II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Softworks Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sculptured Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chessmaster, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Chessmaster</name>
		<desc>The Chessmaster is a game where the player has the chance to play against the CPU controlled Chessmaster at a standard game of chess.

To play the game the player must pick up the chess pieces with there hand cursor and place it in the desired location, within the rules a standard chess game. There are 16 different difficulty levels that includes 2 beginner levels, 13 standard levels (ranging from an average of 5 seconds to 4.5 minutes per shot depending on level), and a infinite level that will keep thinking of a shot until a perfect shot can be made or it is forced to move. There is also a teaching mode that shows the player all the possible moves with the selected piece. Two players can play each other with two controllers and there is also an option of letting the Chessmaster play itself.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chessmaster, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Toolworks</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Mahou Tairiku Wozz.zip</path>
		<name>Chou Mahou Tairiku Wozz</name>
		<desc>The magic world of Wozz, populated by magicians, alchemists, and other kinds of people - including simple town and village inhabitants - was a seemingly peaceful place, until one day, a poisonous rain started turning its inhabitants into monsters. The chief wizard realizes that the demon Balaam is trying to link the world of Wozz with the world of humans. Only a human hero can stop Balaam, and the wizard's teleporting magic brings... three young humans: the Japanese girl Reona Kitazato, and two boys: the American Shot Phoenix and the Chinese Chun Chingtao. Will those youngsters be able to stop Balaam?

The game is a traditional Japanese-style RPG similar to Breath of Fire: turn-based battles are viewed from an isometric perspective. You control all three characters as a party, but in the beginning of the game you choose one of them as the main character, and therefore will see the game from his/her perspective. In case the characters split up, you'll be able to control only the one you chose.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Chou Mahou Tairiku Wozz-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RED Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daze Before Christmas.zip</path>
		<name>Daze Before Christmas</name>
		<desc>Christmas is a time where people get together and give others presents and spend all day eating food. But there's only one problem this year. You see, while Santa was sleeping in his bed, the cold and evil snowman spooked all the elves away, and the Timekeeper has stolen Santa's plans from his house. There won't be any Christmas if Santa doesn't stop them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Daze Before Christmas-image.jpg</image>
		<developer>Funcom</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death and Return of Superman, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Death and Return of Superman</name>
		<desc>Brace yourself for a hard-hitting fight to the finish that lets you relive the classic DC comic book series! As Superman, fight for your life against mighty Doomsday, the vile distributor of death and destruction! Then, control the destiny of the four Supermen - each claiming to be the one, true Superman! Explode through 10 levels of super-powered battles and fly at furious speeds - until only the real Superman is left standing!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Death and Return of Superman, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon - The Bruce Lee Story.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon: The Bruce Lee Story</name>
		<desc>Martial arts action is defined by only one man: Bruce Lee! Now enter the world of Dragon for the ultimate martial arts showdown... authentic, fierce, brutal. It's a jeet kune do fight to the finish with multiple combat modes, deadly weapons and chain-wielding villains. In the end, you must face The Phantom... in a mystical battle for your very soul!

3-Player Fighting Action With Multi-Player Adapter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dragon - The Bruce Lee Story-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19950705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest V - Tenkuu no Hanayome.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest V - Tenkuu no Hanayome</name>
		<desc>You are the son of the brave warrior, Lord Papas. It appears that your mother died just after giving birth to you, and your father took you on a long journey when you were a little baby, and all you know is that he was searching for something. Now you are six years old, and Lord Papas brings you to your home village. After some time, you learn that His Highness Prince Henry was kidnapped by bandits. Your father attempts to rescue him, and during this action you discover that perhaps your mother is still alive... The game follows the story of Papas' son, and this story is stretched over years, as the hero grows and becomes a man of courage and virtue. During the game, the hero will discover the truth about his mother, and will have to make some crucial decisions, such as which girl to marry (the decisions affect the course of the game and its ending).

"Dragon Quest V" is a party RPG with turn-based combat, and battles viewed from 1st person perspective, just like all its predecessors. Your party roams about the world, fighting random enemies, performing quests, and defeating bosses. The novelty is in the game's unusual story, which spans almost a lifetime of the hero. 

"Dragon Quest V" was not available outside of Japan until 2009, when the DS version was released in the United States.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dragon Quest V - Tenkuu no Hanayome-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon View.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon View</name>
		<desc>Solve puzzles and fight monsters in order to save your love. She's been taken by Giza an evil sorcerror bent on destroying all life in the world. You'll journey through different lands in search of clues and powerful items and magic.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dragon View-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari Europe S.A.S.U.</developer>
		<publisher>KEMCO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero.zip</path>
		<name>F-Zero</name>
		<desc>The future of racing is here! F-ZERO, an intergalaxtic Grand Prix, uses machines that weigh more than a ton, reach dash speeds of over 500km/h and hover a mere twelve inches off the ground! Choose from the heroic Captain Falcon, or the suave, Dr. Stuart. Need more choices? Then try the sly alien, Pico or the not-so-honest Samurai Goroh, and race for intergalactic fame and fabulous fortune in the F-ZERO Grand Prix.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/F-Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy II.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy II</name>
		<desc>The fourth entry in the Final Fantasy series was released as Final Fantasy II in the West, because the second and the third game were not released there at the time. The game is a Japanese-style RPG with top-down world map navigation, automatic leveling up, and random enemy encounters. The player can freely roam an overworld containing several towns and dungeons. A menu-based system allows the player to outfit each character with equipment and up to two—often disposable—items for battle. Magic spells are assigned to the character from the item menu, and certain spells, such as "Cure", can be used outside of battle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fantasy II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight</name>
		<desc>Mayor Mike Haggar vows to snatch the streets of Metro City back from the crooks with his bare knuckles! But the Mad Gear Gang snatches his daughter Jessica. Now there's gonna be some bone-crunching dues to pay!

Jessica's boyfriend Cody hits the streets hard with Haggar, denting heads downtown and slugging it out in the slums. He's a one man army! His weapons are anything he can find -- swords, knives, or pipes.

Now you're Haggar or Cody, each with his own fighting style. Demolish gangland henchmen, samurai swordsmen and musclebound crime bosses in a fist-to-nose frenzy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fight-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight Guy.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight Guy</name>
		<desc>Mayor Mike Haggar vows to snatch the streets of Metro City back from the crooks with his bare knuckles! But the Mad Gear Gang snatches his daughter Jessica. Now there's gonna be some bone-crunching dues to pay!

The urban ninja Guy hits the streets hard with Haggar, denting heads downtown and slugging it out in the slums. He's a one man army! His weapons are anything he can find -- swords, knives, or pipes.

Now you're Haggar or Guy, each with his own fighting style. Demolish gangland henchmen, samurai swordsmen and musclebound crime bosses in a fist-to-nose frenzy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Final Fight Guy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./First Samurai.zip</path>
		<name>First Samurai</name>
		<desc>The First Samurai is a platform action game very much similar to other platform games, but with a medieval oriental touch to it in addition to various unique features.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/First Samurai-image.jpg</image>
		<developer>Vivid Image</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flashback - The Quest for Identity.zip</path>
		<name>Flashback: The Quest for Identity</name>
		<desc>2142 AD. Stranded on a bizarre alien planet with your memory artificially erased, you must battle your way back to Earth to stop the invading mutant forces...

FLASHBACK... the ultimate test in survival.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Flashback - The Quest for Identity-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghoul Patrol.zip</path>
		<name>Ghoul Patrol</name>
		<desc>In the sequel to Zombies Ate My Neighbors you as the kids - Zeke or/and Julie - have to save the world from demon the lord of skeletons, ghouls, ghosts and etc. Shooting them by super-new weapons like Plasma Gun or Lobbing Smash Gun, you need to rescue ten trapped victims on each level and fight the boss at the end. But also you have to remember that ammo is limited.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ghoul Patrol-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper V-Ball.zip</path>
		<name>Hyper V-Ball</name>
		<desc>A volleyball simulation seen from a side-view perspective, meaning it is only possible to move players to the left or right. The player can choose between three different leagues: Men's League, Woman's League and Hyper League, which is a league for robots. Two buttons are used to control the ball, one for normal actions and one for "Hyper Plays", special attacks that can only be learned and used in the Hyper League. How a player will block or attack depends on the ball's speed and the players position. Team members who aren't under the player's direct control will also act on their own by positioning themselves or preparing spikes. They will, however, not block spikes on their own but it is possible to let players not under direct control block spikes by pressing one of the action buttons at the right moment.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Hyper V-Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HyperZone.zip</path>
		<name>HyperZone</name>
		<desc>Hyper Zone plays like a cross between a racing game and shooter. The object of the game is to navigate each level while shooting enemies and earning points, until finally an encounter with a boss ends each level. After enough points are acquired, the player earns an "extend" and his or her ship is upgraded in the next stage. The player's ship can receive up to six upgrades.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/HyperZone-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Superstar Soccer Deluxe.zip</path>
		<name>International Superstar Soccer Deluxe</name>
		<desc>It's a whole new ball game... Reallistic prites with 36 teams featuring recognisable celebrity players. Increased CPU intelligence to challenge beginners and experts alike. Choose from 15 formations, 8 strategies, 20 players and 9 adjustable player skills. Four way play possible with adaptor.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/International Superstar Soccer Deluxe-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jelly Boy 2.zip</path>
		<name>Jelly Boy 2</name>
		<desc>Jelly Boy 2 is an Action game, developed by Game Freak and published by Sony Music Entertainment, which was cancelled before it was released.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jelly Boy 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Music Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetsons, The - Invasion of the Planet Pirates.zip</path>
		<name>The Jetsons: Invasion of the Planet Pirates</name>
		<desc>George Jetson was about to run out to work when his pal Captain Zoom appears out of thin air. Zoom tells him that Zora, the leader of SPREE ("Space Pirates Revelling in Evil Enterprises"), is planning on looting this solar system of all its resource! Unfortunately, in his last encounter with Zora, Zoom has used up all his strength and now he is powerless so he asks George to take over. He gives George his Pneumo Osmatic Precipitator (or P.O.P.) and bids him good luck.  Can George save his family and this galaxy?

Guide George through 9 stages of intergalactic action armed with only his wits and the P.O.P....which is like a super vacuum. The P.O.P. can be used as a traveling tool by sucking onto walls and ceilings, it will enable George to climb up and across platforms.  As a weapon, the P.O.P. can be used to suck up blocks or enemies and spit out at other enemies. George can also use the P.O.P. to breathe under water! Talk about multi-functional!

George's conditions are indicated by the number of hearts he has at the top of the screen.  By collecting more hearts, it will refill George's health. Food items will increase your score and by getting a high enough score in each stage, you may get to play a bonus game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jetsons, The - Invasion of the Planet Pirates-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jimmy Connors Pro Tennis Tour.zip</path>
		<name>Jimmy Connors Pro Tennis Tour</name>
		<desc>Using crosshairs, aim your ball to the other side of the court and hope you hit where you want. If you are lucky, you might even score an Ace. If not, you will need to be ready to return your opponent's return. Run back and forth as you try to keep hitting the ball over the net until your opponent misses, or you do. When you hit the ball, you will want to attempt changing the direction and speed of the ball to throw your opponent off balance. This is the real challenge of any tennis game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jimmy Connors Pro Tennis Tour-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics.zip</path>
		<name>Joe &amp; Mac 2: Lost in the Tropics</name>
		<desc>Improving on the original's platformer/brawler co-op gameplay, this game adds adventure and role-playing game elements that create a more involving experience compared to the first game. You can now collect coins in the levels to purchase items from Tiki Village, such as meat to recover your health, or even remodel your hut back at your home village. The game also uses a password system to track your progress. The game also shifts to an overhead map so you can wander to whichever level you wish, and return to completed levels to earn more money or power-ups.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jungle Book, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Jungle Book</name>
		<desc>Based on the famous animated movie, The Jungle Book is a platform game where you control Mowgli, the boy who was raised by wild animals deep in the jungles. Your goal is to find the human village so you may you join your kin once again. Mowgli is an athletic individual, and can jump, run, swing on vines or climb them without any problems. Most of the animals he comes upon, however, are inexplicably hostile, so he must defend himself with a variety of thrown weapons, such as bananas and boomerangs. To complete each level, Mowgli must collect a number of crystals (how many - it depends on the difficulty levels) within a time limit. A compass in the corner of the screen helps him by showing the direction where the nearest crystal is.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Jungle Book, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Avalanche.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Avalanche</name>
		<desc>King Dedede has challenged Kirby and other members of Dream Land to an Avalanche Competition in the Dream Fountain. Kirby, taking on the challenge, has decided to battle his way through the forest and into the Dream Fountain to win the Avalanche Cup from King Dedede.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kirby's Avalanche-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Course.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Course</name>
		<desc>Scan the course and check out the obstacles ahead. Get ready for the most surprising game play imaginable in Kirby's battle against King Dedede!

This checkboard challenge brings outrageous hazards and bizarre surfaces. Warp panels instantly transport you to new and exciting challenges. Conveyer belts provide higher levels of adventure. Turntables take the action in a whole new direction.

Gordo, Kracko, Whispy Woods and a cast of zany characters await you. Gain special powers including Fireball, Freeze, Spark and Parasol. Transform your enemies into stars revealing eight hidden cups of each wildly different course. Control the force and angle of your shot and sink Kirby for a hole-in-one!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Kirby's Dream Course-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knights of the Round.zip</path>
		<name>Knights of the Round</name>
		<desc>Arthur, who had been training himself to be a great knight, pulled out the sacred sword Excalibur from the rock. After pulling it out, Arthur realized his destiny was to become the first King of the Britons. Merlin then sends Arthur and his two closest companions, Lancelot and Perceval, to overthrow the evil king Garibaldi and to unite England.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Knights of the Round-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Live A Live.zip</path>
		<name>Live A Live</name>
		<desc>Live A Live's story is split across seven seemingly unrelated chapters that can be played in any order, based on popular genres such as Western, science fiction, and mecha. Each chapter has its own plot, setting, and characters. Although the basic gameplay is the same throughout the game, each chapter adds a new factor to the basic formula, such as the stealth elements in the ninja chapter. After the first seven chapters are completed, two final chapters take place to establish the connection between the seven previous and resolve the story.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Live A Live-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes B-Ball.zip</path>
		<name>Looney Tunes B-Ball</name>
		<desc>Looney Tunes B-Ball is a 2-on-2 Basketball game, similar to the more well known NBA Jam. However, Looney Tunes is much more informal and silly, though this level of silliness is set by the player via the Wackiness Meter on the main menu. Players choose their teams from the likes of: Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Elmer Fudd, Wile E. Coyote, Tasmanian Devil, Sylvester, Yosemite Sam and Marvin Martian. Each player has unique statistics for their shooting, 3-pointers, defense, stamina and speed.

Once on the court, the player can pass the ball, shoot the ball, grab a burst of speed or unleash a special defensive ability or a special offensive ability.. These abilities include cream pies, time bombs, sticks of dynamite and other fun toys from the ACME Corporation. Offensive Abilities must be "bought" by collecting gems and other items which occasionally show up on the basketball court.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Looney Tunes B-Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia &amp; The Fortress of Doom.zip</path>
		<name>Lufia &amp; the Fortress of Doom</name>
		<desc>The Sinsitrals, four masters of Doom, arrived in this land on their floating island 100 years ago. You will begin your quest by travelling through time to join in a temendous battle against them--and you will determine the outcome. When you return to present time, you and Lufia, your companion, must join forces with two others to prevent the Sinistrals from regaining control of your world. It will be a long and difficult task--This land is larger than that of most RPG games. And in the end, the balance of fate will be overturned in a contest of love and betrayal that could destroy you all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lufia &amp; The Fortress of Doom-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals.zip</path>
		<name>Lufia II: Rise of the Sinistrals</name>
		<desc>This exciting sequel to the Lufian legend pits monster hunter Maxim and six adventuring companions against the sinister Sinistrals. The story develops into a complex maze, challenging you with big battles, puzzles and loads of surprises. You can even grow your own monsters! You will enjoy countless hours on a fantastic journey in the world of Lufia!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maerchen Adventure Cotton 100%.zip</path>
		<name>Marchen Adventure Cotton 100%</name>
		<desc>Marchen Adventure Cotton 100% is a side scrolling shooter by Success and Datam Polystar, and likely sequel to the arcade game Cotton originally released in 1989. The cute witch and her flying broom are back in this exclusive adventure for the Super Famicom system.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Maerchen Adventure Cotton 100%-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Datam Polystar</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic Sword.zip</path>
		<name>Magic Sword</name>
		<desc>As the hero, you must climb up a monster-ridden tower to defeat Drokkmar, master of the Blackorb. To do this, you must defeat his army that stands in your way with whatever weapon you are carrying. Health is decreased by coming into contact with various monsters, attacks, traps, and the passage of time. It is increased by finding food. Every certain amount of points, a "Food Fairy" appears and drops off food as well.

Throughout your journey, you can smash open chests to find treasure and artifacts. Some of these artifacts can be recovered that alter gameplay, such as providing more damage or increased magical power. Also throughout your journey, you can collect keys, which are used to free imprisoned allies, who not only help you defeat monsters, but also leave you an item that will help you on your quest. Only one person can join you at a time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Magic Sword-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario to Wario.zip</path>
		<name>Mario and Wario</name>
		<desc>This is the Spirit Forest. Within these woods lives a sprite, and those who meet it find happiness, or so the tale goes. One day, Mario came to the woods to confirm the legend. Peach and Yoshi should have been together with Luigi......but alas, the visage of Luigi was missing. Mario's group of three have separated to find lost little Luigi.

At once, the suspicious sound of an engine was in the air. I wonder what it could be? It was Wario riding his personal plane, the Bulldog, and it dropped a bucket from the sky.

"Whew, woosh!"

And suddenly, the bucket was a snug fit on Mario's head.

"Uwagh, I can't see in this thing!"

The sprite of the woods, Wanda, witnessed it. The petite pixie did not have the strength to remove the bucket on her own, but she desired to help somehow. Thus, Wanda sends Mario a signal with her magic wand, determined to reunite him with Luigi......</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mario to Wario-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monstania.zip</path>
		<name>Monstania</name>
		<desc>The hero of the game is Fron, a sixteen-year old boy who lives on the island of Monstania. One day, strolling in the forest, he notices a strange light. The light lead him to a clearing, and then suddenly disappeared. But Fron realized what was the meaning of that light - it was a fairy! Of course, everybody knew that fairies had been long extinct, but Fron never believed in that. All his life he wanted to meet a real fairy, and now, when the opportunity has come, he firmly decides to find her. His girlfriend Tia helps him on the dangerous journey, during which they meet a mysterious little girl named Chitta, and get involved in a grand adventure, that will ultimately lead them to the battle against the dark force that threatens the whole Monstania!

"Monstania" has a somewhat unusual gameplay within the frames of console RPGs. You don't explore the world in the game: it is entirely linear and takes you to the next destination by itself (only at a few points you can choose where to go next by selecting an appropriate answer). Once within the location, you cannot leave it until you complete all your objectives there, which then take you to the next location. The objective is usually a large strategic battle. You navigate your party members on the battle field, attack with melee and long-ranged weapons, and use special technique which require action points. Unlike most other turn-based strategy games, an enemy makes a move immediately after you did the same with one of your characters, without waiting for the "enemy turn". The RPG element is not very significant: your characters level up automatically after each battle. There are also some puzzles to solve in certain locations.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Monstania-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amccus</developer>
		<publisher>Pack-In-Video</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>PREPARE YOURSELF...

The #1 arcade hit is here: from Sub-Zero, Rayden and the rest of the Kombat Warriors to the grueling endurance and intense mirror matches! Execute bone-shattering combos and ferocious finishing moves! Defeat the half human dragon Goro, and destroy the shape-changing Shang Tsung to become the Supreme Mortal Kombat Warrior!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Mortal Kombat-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Jam.zip</path>
		<name>NBA Jam</name>
		<desc>NBA Jam, which featured 2-on-2 basketball, was one of the first real playable basketball arcade games, and was also one of the first sports games to feature NBA-licensed teams and players, and their real digitized likenesses.
A key feature of NBA Jam was the exaggerated nature of the play - players jumped many times above their own height, making slam dunks that defied both human capabilities and the laws of physics. There were no fouls, free throws, or violations except goaltending and 24 second violations. This meant the player was able to freely shove or elbow his opponent out of the way. Additionally, the game had an "on fire" feature, where if one player made three baskets in a row, he would become "on fire" and have unlimited turbo, no goaltending, and increased shooting ability, until the other team scored (or the player had scored four consecutive baskets while "on fire").</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/NBA Jam-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Trilogy.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Here it is! The complete NINJA GAIDEN TRILOGY you asked for. Enjoy the 3 classic Nintendo Ninja Gaiden games on one Super NES Game Pak.
Follow Ryu's adventures as he fights the ancient forces of darkness with his Ninjutsu powers. Use strategy, cunning and deception to acquire the special ninja weapons needed to be successful in this epic quest.

The Ninja Gaiden series tells it's story through Tecmo's unique cinema screen animation. This one is not to be missed!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Ninja Gaiden Trilogy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Out of This World.zip</path>
		<name>Out of This World</name>
		<desc>You'll think you're actually on a movie set when you star in the cinematic action/adventure Out Of This World™.
Out Of This World™ is like no other game on the Super NES™. Using a completely new graphic system of cinematic zooms, pans, close-ups, and cuts, Out Of This World™ gets you involved in a breathtaking story of inter-dimensional travel.
You'll duck as lasers blast, boulders crash, and monsters roar. The complete musical score and realistic, digitized sound effects will make you feel like you're on a movie sound stage.
Being a hero is hard work, and you'll experience it first-hand as you run, jump, dodge, and shoot your way across a hostile world of deadly earthquakes and alien monsters. So, grab your hat and whip, charge up your blasters, and get ready to star in your own movie that'll take you Out Of This World™!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Out of This World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panel de Pon.zip</path>
		<name>Panel de Pon</name>
		<desc>Panel de Pon is a tile-matching puzzle game series developed by Intelligent Systems, where gameplay involves matching three or more tiles of the same color at once to remove them from play. The first game in the series was released on the Super Famicom in Japan in 1995, and starred a series of fairies as its main characters. Its storyline involved the Fairy of Flowers, Lip, setting out to free her friends from the control of the demon king Thanatos and save the world of the fairies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Panel de Pon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parodius - Non-Sense Fantasy.zip</path>
		<name>Parodius: Non-Sense Fantasy</name>
		<desc>This is mostly the parody of Gradius (Nemesis on some systems), with some flavor from other shoot-em-ups, like Twinbee. The series is available on numerous platforms.

The game is a right-to-left scrolling shoot-em-up. You can choose from 4 different flying creatures, with different weapons. You must finish 7 stages, each having a boss at the end. You may start at either one, but must complete every level to advance to the final stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Parodius - Non-Sense Fantasy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pilotwings.zip</path>
		<name>Pilotwings</name>
		<desc>Are you ready to earn your wings at the most exclusive flight school in the world? Then report immediately to the secret Pilotwings Flight Club, where your training begins! You'll see the ground twist beneath you as you jump from your plane and attempt a precision skydive (don't forget to pull your rip cord!). You'll relive the early days of flying as you bring your biplane in for a pin-point landing. After you master the basics, you'll be called on to test an experimental rocket pack, soar in a hang glider, and pilot an advanced attack helicopter in a hazardous rescure mission.

The realism is incredible as the Super NES takes you airborne with multi-dimensional graphics, endless skylines and the freedom to fly wherever you like. Do you have what it takes to earn your wings? Then get going! You're late for your first class!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pilotwings-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Flight Simulator</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pop'n TwinBee.zip</path>
		<name>Pop'n Twinbee</name>
		<desc>Heroes Light and Pastel decide to go out and help a young maiden bring sense back to her scientist father, who apparently has bumped his head and transformed into a evil mastermind that seeks world domination.

As the other games in the series Pop'n Twinbee is a vertically-scrolling arcade shooter in which you and a friend get behind the controls of Twinbee and Winbee, the cutest starfighters ever created, and try to clear stage after stage of enemies with your weapons. Being a console original instead of a port, Pop'n features a number of additions to the gameplay mechanics, including an energy bar, eight difficulty levels and a handicap feature when playing with a friend (which makes most enemies target one fighter instead of the other).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Pop'n TwinBee-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Putty Squad.zip</path>
		<name>Putty Squad</name>
		<desc>Putty Squad is a platform game in which the player controls an amorphous blue blob, tasked with rescuing imprisoned putties. The player's putty can stretch in a variety of ways: sidewards to cover ground faster, squash flat to absorb pick-up items, stretch upwards to climb, morph a fist to attack, or inflate to float upwards.

Putty can collect stars that increase his attack power: at first increasing the potency of his punch, but later allowing him to blow darts, electrocute enemies or throw bombs. This star power is reduced every time Putty is hit by an enemy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Putty Squad-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RoboCop 3.zip</path>
		<name>RoboCop 3</name>
		<desc>RoboCop 3 is a side-scrolling platform shooter. You get missions (such as rescuing your colleagues who are being kept hostages), which are divided into several smaller levels. The levels usually consist of several platforms, and are heavily populated by enemies who shoot at you. You can gather special repair kits, which will be used to restore your health after you've completed a level. "RoboCop 3" is more of a shooter than its predecessors, having more and tougher enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/RoboCop 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rock n' Roll Racing.zip</path>
		<name>Rock n' Roll Racing</name>
		<desc>The game pits four racers against each other, with up to two of them being player-controlled and the rest being AI opponents. Each race consists of four laps around tracks viewed from an isometric perspective, which enables players to discern the presence of frequent sloping sections spread throughout the game's various tracks. In addition to navigating the turns, racers must also maneuver hills and dips without falling or jumping over the guard rail at the track's edge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Rock n' Roll Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Law - The Meaning of Death.zip</path>
		<name>Dark Law: The Meaning of Death</name>
		<desc>Dark Law is a Role-Playing game, developed by SAS Sakata and published by ASCII Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 1997.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dark Law - The Meaning of Death-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SAS Sakata</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario.zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Dr. Mario-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Earth Defense Force.zip</path>
		<name>Earth Defense Force</name>
		<desc>A SUPER SAGA OF 23RD CENTURY SATELLITE WARFARE!

The graphics will dozzle you, the speed will astound you... but if you don't think fast and shoot faster, you won't have a chance against the alien firestorm. Because in EARTH DEFENSE FORCE, the best defense is always a great offense. So get ready to hit first and hit fast in the hardest-hitting adventure to hit the Super NES screen!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Earth Defense Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exhaust Heat.zip</path>
		<name>Exhaust Heat</name>
		<desc>In Exhaust Heat you drive in race car and compete in a series of sixteen races on tracks from around the world. You will earn money for each race depending on how you placed (for instance, first place nets you $7000) which you can use to purchase upgrades for your car. You need to find a good balance between the parts. To test the effectiveness of your parts you can run a test race to see how the car works before you buy. Data can be saved on the cartridge so you will not lose your parts or your race statistics. The goal is simply to complete all sixteen tracks; you will get a bonus at the end depending on how well you do so there is an incentive to play again and do better.
   </desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Exhaust Heat-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Striker.zip</path>
		<name>Firestriker</name>
		<desc>A long time ago the kingdoms of wind, fire, earth and water
   competed for the Trialight, a weapon created by the Arch Mage Wylde that can only be used by a Firestriker. The kingdom of wind won and united the four kingdoms. Wylde however, was not satisfied with peace and conjured four monsters to overthrow the united world. Now, only the kingdom of wind remains and the player takes control over the last Firestriker to free the other kingdoms and defeat the monsters.

   Even though Firestriker looks like a typical SNES RPG, it is in fact an action game that has more in common with a pinball-game than with any other genre. The Trialight is a ball of fire that basically behaves like a pinball. The player controls the Firestriker who can freely walk across the screen and strike at the Trialight to control its movement. Levels are filled with obstacles, destroyable block and monsters. Monsters and blocks can only be destroyed by the Trialight. The goal of each level is to maneuver the Trialight towards the exit of the screen. The exit is usually blocked by destroyable obstacles and sometimes certain conditions (such as killing all monsters or destroying certain objects) have to be fulfilled before a level can be completed. If the Firestriker is killed or the Trialight falls off the screen, the player loses a life. Additionally to the Firestriker, the player can use the shoulder buttons to control a magician who (in single player mode) stays at the bottom of the screen. The levels consist of several screens and are entered from a world map. As the game progresses, the player will also fight several bosses and free other Firestrikers whose special abilities are necessary to complete the game.

   Firestriker also features a two-player cooperative mode as well as a duel-mode for up to four players.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Fire Striker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Axes Art Amuse</developer>
		<publisher>DTMC, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunforce.zip</path>
		<name>Gunforce: Battle Fire Engulfed Terror Island</name>
		<desc>The player takes control of a soldier who is dropped off onto an island and must fight his way through hordes of enemy soldiers until he gets to the final showdown in order to protect Mother Earth from the invaders.

Gameplay consists of moving forward and blasting all the enemies who get in the way. The player starts out with a normal gun, but can find other weapons throughout a level, such as a flamethrower or a laser gun. While the normal gun has an infinite amount of bullets, the other types of weapons will eventually run out of ammo. With these weapons, the player can shoot either straight, up, or on a diagonal. The player will also have the opportunity to commandeer a vehicle, which they can also fire bullets from.

The player starts with 5 lives and 3 continues. Each of the stages must be defeated in a certain amount of time or the player loses one of those lives.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Gunforce-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Pop'n Twinbee - Rainbow Bell Adventures</name>
		<desc>You play as either Twinbee, Gwinbee or Winbee. Cooperative play is also available. In this mode the second player takes control over one of the two characters left. Either way your task is to find and defeat the evil Dr. Warmon who tries to enslave the islands of Dunburi.

To deal with the many villains Dr. Warmon throws at you, you need to collect colored bells. Depending on the color of the bell you can use different attacks like a laser (blue bells) or a lash (orange bells). But even without the bells you're not defenseless. Your standard-attacks include a shock wave and the ability to fly.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowrun.zip</path>
		<name>Shadowrun</name>
		<desc>Disoriented and confused, you are forced into a race against time, technology and termination. Running in the shadows and cracks between the Megaplexes, survival depends on your wits, your weapons and your wayward companions. Plunge into the dark side of the future, where technology and magic become one, where devolution and destruction are a way of life. Plunge into Shadowrun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Shadowrun-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SimCity.zip</path>
		<name>Sim City</name>
		<desc>SimCity sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops. There are 50 types of these, allowing for homes of all standards and different types of businesses. Make sure to consider which sites are effective for which tasks. Some power sources pollute, others don't but are more expensive. Taxes must be raised to ensure an income, and then portions allocated to public services such as policing and roads. Earthquakes, floods and fires are all emergency situations that must be dealt to contain any damage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SimCity-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Construction and Management Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smart Ball.zip</path>
		<name>Smart Ball</name>
		<desc>The game involves going through 8 stages (broken up into two parts each) of side-scrolling action. At the end of each stage is a boss monster that must be disposed of.

Jerry moves by sliding across the ground and can latch on to walls and climb them. Jerry can also jump, stretch out to cling to ceilings, and also move at a faster pace. Jerry can consume balls that he finds during a stage and can then fire them out of his body at enemies blocking his path. Enemies can also be defeated by jumping on them and then flattening Jerry's body on them. Also, there are flowers that contain items for Jerry to collect. Items include life, which refills health, a 1-up that adds an extra life, and a seed, which will grow a climbable beanstalk when planted. If the player collects the scattered letters that appear in every stage that spell out the name Jerry, the player will earn two extra lives.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Smart Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smash Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Smash Tennis</name>
		<desc>The controls of Smash Tennis work similar to other tennis games and especially Namco's previous tennis game World Court Tennis: the player moves the athlete over the court and presses buttons with the correct timing in order to win the match. This time there is no story mode, but a tournament mode instead. Here the goal is to win the Grand Slam by playing various tournament matches. However. a match only has a single set. There are 20 athletes (both male and female) to choose from which have different advantages and drawbacks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Smash Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Blast Man II.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Blast Man II</name>
		<desc>Heavy Blast Man is once again trying to take over the Earth. People are being turned into hideous monsters and being made to serve him. Sonic Blast Man returns along with some new friends, Sonia and Captain Choyear. Together, they battle Heavy Blast Man and his minions to save the Earth from destruction.

You control one of three characters in this side-scroller, as you fight your way through various levels filled with enemies and bosses. Beat them up with the basic punches and kicks or use your super moves to get out of tight spots.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Sonic Blast Man II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speedy Gonzales in Los Gatos Bandidos.zip</path>
		<name>Speedy Gonzales: Los Gatos Bandidos</name>
		<desc>In a small Mexican village, all the mice were enjoying a fiesta until Los Gatos Bandidos, a group of cats, came and kidnapped them all. Only Slowpoke escaped and sent for his cousin, the fastest mouse in Mexico... Speedy Gonzales! Following the trail of the Bandidos, Speedy will enter each level and try to rescue as many mice as possible while chasing after cheese and avoiding natural hazards. Ariba! Ariba!

The gameplay in Speedy Gonzales resembles the Sonic the Hedgehog series of games more than anything else. For the most part Speedy will run, run across fields and up slopes and into tunnels. There are also mousetraps which function similarly to Sonic's trampolines and will propel Speedy into the air. Speedy has a short range kick for attacking and can occasionally pick up items and use them at a later time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Speedy Gonzales in Los Gatos Bandidos-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Mitsui</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man &amp; Venom - Maximum Carnage.zip</path>
		<name>Spider-Man &amp; Venom: Maximum Carnage</name>
		<desc>Only one maniacal madman can force Spider-Man to unite with his sinister, arch-nemesis Venom’: CARNAGE’! His deadly rampage is tearing New York City apart! Only wild web-slinging maneuvers, crushing combat moves and Super Hero’ allies can save the city from total obliteration. It's maximum mayhem! It's Maximum Carnage’! Paint the town red!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Spider-Man &amp; Venom - Maximum Carnage-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stargate.zip</path>
		<name>Stargate</name>
		<desc>Based on the movie of the same name, a mystical circular portal called a "Stargate" has been uncovered. In attempting to unlock its secrets, its power is unlocked creating a passageway to a different world named Abydos. A special forces team is sent to the new world to investigate but is soon ambushed and its supplies taken including a powerful nuclear bomb.

As Colonel O'Neil, a variety of objectives must be met starting with the recovery of supplies and the finding of other teammates, including civilian archaeologist Daniel Jackson. Once regrouped, O'Neil must lead the attack on the god, Ra and escape back to Earth before the power of the nuclear bomb can be unleashed on this new world.

The game is a side-scroller platform adventure. The player controls O'Neil on a variety of objectives and is armed with a rifle weapon and grenades. Embarking through desert, caverns and nomad towns... eventually to the palace of Ra.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Stargate-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Cosmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 2.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 2</name>
		<desc>DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?

The bad boys from the Street Fighter series are back for more fisticuffs of fury! Eighteen different combatants, some old and some new, are here to lay claim to the title "World's Best". Screamin' moves like Ken's Dragon Punch, Adon's Jaguar Tooth and M. Bison's Somersault Skull Driver will blow you away! Play alone or pummel a friend in two-player simultaneous action. This ain't no cakewalk. This ain't no cakewalk. This is Street Fighter Alpha 2 and it's blazing on your Super NES!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Street Fighter Alpha 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II - The World Warrior.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II</name>
		<desc>GET READY TO RUMBLE!

From across the globe comes eight of the wildest fighters the world has ever known. Choose your champion, gather your courage and prepare to battle your opponents in a bare knuckle brawl. Face Ken and his devastating "Dragon Punch"! Watch the temperature rise as Dhalsim incinerates you with his mystical Yoga Flame! Hear your spine crack as Zangief smashes you to the pavement with his spinning pile driver! Cover your ears as Guile breaks the sound barrier with the awesome power of the Sonic Boom!

Annihilate your competition and claim the right to test your skills against the bone-crushing power of the Grand Masters! Can you survive? Can Anyone?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Street Fighter II - The World Warrior-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II Turbo - Hyper Fighting.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Feel the Need for Speed!

They're back and they're badder than ever! Faster, stronger and with all new moves, twelve of the greatest fighters from across the globe are ready to do battle! Choose your champion and get ready for the big brawl as they try to earn the right to battle M. Bison for the title. And just when you think you've mastered it all, crank it up a notch and go TURBO!

Cover your head as Blanka dives at you from above and hear your neck crack as Zangief hits you with the Turbo Spinning Clothesline. Stare in disbelief as Dhalsim disappears before your eyes and Chun Li unleashes her blazing fireball! Watch in awe as Sagat fights Sagat and Ryu does a Hurricane Kick in mid-air! Survive all this and you may live long enough to become the greatest Street Fighter ever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Street Fighter II Turbo - Hyper Fighting-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stunt Race FX.zip</path>
		<name>Stunt Race FX</name>
		<desc>The game features four modes of play: Speed Trax is basically an arcade mode where the player has to qualify for each upcoming race by reaching checkpoints while collecting items to restore his damage- and boost-bar. It is divided into a Novice-, Expert-, and Master class, with each class featuring four unique tracks. In Stunt Trax the player has to complete courses filled with obstacles within a certain time limit while trying to collect as many stars as possible. Battle Trax is a two player mode taking place on special tracks without any CPU-controlled opponents. Finally, Test Run let's the player practice all tracks that have been unlocked.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Stunt Race FX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Alfred Chicken.zip</path>
		<name>Super Alfred Chicken</name>
		<desc>Alfred the chicken must rescue his friends and his bird (pardon the pun) Floella from the Meka Chickens. The result is a platform game across differently-themed levels, which are finished by either climbing to the top of the level or killing a boss. Bonus games and secret rooms have been included, and progression sometimes requires solving positional puzzles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Alfred Chicken-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Twilight</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman.zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Super Bomberman is the first video game in the Bomberman series to appear on the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. It is also the first four-player game to be released on the Super NES.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Bomberman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman 3.zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman 3</name>
		<desc>This game scales back a lot of gameplay additions made in Super Bomberman 2 and returns to the classic formula. As for multiplayer, the game adds a lot over the previous game by adding more characters, each representing a country of Earth (including one of the villains, Pretty Bomber, as France, which marks her first appearance as a non-enemy character). There are also new cutscenes for the Story mode, which centers around the resurrection of the Five Dastardly Bombers who were previously defeated in Super Bomberman 2, as Shirobon and Kurobon adventure across various element themed stars in which the Five are causing havoc, under the rule of their creator, Bagular.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Bomberman 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Double Dragon.zip</path>
		<name>Super Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>The two greatest martial arts heroes of all time are back -- in SUPER DOUBLE DRAGON, an all-new adventure with awesome new moves, impossible new missions, and a hair-raising new cast of enemies!
Marian, a beautiful policewoman, is a student of Kung Fu and part-time assistant instructor at the martial arts training school run by Billy and Jimmy Lee. A narcotics investigator, she has disappeared while attempting to infiltrate the rughtless criminal mob known as the Black Shadow Warriors.
It will take all your incomparable fighting skill and knowledge to find and rescure Marian. Alone, or with the help of your brother, you must face the fearsome onslaught of the Shadow Warriors with the fabled power and ferocity of the DOUBLE DRAGON!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Double Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Nova.zip</path>
		<name>Super Nova</name>
		<desc>The intergalactic menace Belser has been long-defeated. However, he is rising again and is ready to cause trouble. Only a group of well-trained starpilots can defeat him. You take to the stars in this horizontal and sometimes vertical scrolling shooter. There are several power-ups to be obtained in your mission to defeat the evil Belser. 

There are three ships to choose from, each having different weapons for attack. There are eight attack levels for each, increasing with each Red Orb collected. The Blue Orb gives a limited defense shield.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Nova-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super R-Type.zip</path>
		<name>Super R-Type</name>
		<desc>In this SNES sequel to the arcade R-Type shooters, you are the R-9, Earth's most advanced form of defense against the evil BYDO Empire. There are seven stages you must go through, picking up power-up items to defeat the stage bosses which have returned from the arcade versions of R-Type and R-Type II. Your R-9 ship can also be united with FORCE, which are invincible units that surround your ship to protect you and can also power up and attack.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super R-Type-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Super Tennis</name>
		<desc>The world circuit of tennis awaits you. Select from 20 male and female players, each with their own style of game play (strengths and weaknesses) and play singles, doubles either against or with a human opponent or a CPU controlled player(s) on all the major surfaces (clay, grass &amp; hardcourt).

The circuit mode is the meat of the game. Here, using a password save system, you play a selection of tournaments all around the world. The more games you play and win, the more points you receive. These points go towards your rank in the world tour rankings. There are 4 major tournaments (as in real life) and many minor tournaments to play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Tetris 3.zip</path>
		<name>Super Tetris 3</name>
		<desc>Super Tetris 3 is yet another version of the famous soviet puzzle game. However, despite what the title may suggest, contained within are actually four different versions of Tetris: Tetris Classic, Familiss, Sparkliss, and Magicaliss. Tetris Classic, of course, is the basic version of the game, which comes with an endless mode and a 25-line "standard" mode. Familiss, as the name might suggest, is a family mode for up to four players simultaneously. Sparkliss, meanwhile, is very similar to Bombliss from Super Tetris 2, only with a medieval fantasy theme and different explosion patterns. Sparkliss includes both a stage mode and a puzzle mode.

The most unique mode is Magicaliss, which has never shown up on any other version of Tetris. In Magicaliss, pieces come in three basic colors, and by rotating the piece, the player can choose between them. Creating a line entirely out of one color will clear all blocks on the screen of that color. There are also grey pieces, which can only be cleared by creating a line made entirely from one color, which will cause all grey blocks on screen to become that color. There are also rare rainbow pieces which will act as any color. Besides these additions, the game itself is basic Tetris.

Tetris Classic, Sparkliss, and Magicaliss can also be played in a two-player battle mode, besides the four-player Familiss mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Super Tetris 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19941216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Blue Planet Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tactics Ogre - Let Us Cling Together.zip</path>
		<name>Tactics Ogre: Let Us Cling Together</name>
		<desc>Tactics Ogre is a 3D isometric tactical role-playing game. The player starts out with a band of troops, builds a small army and fights many battles with choices to make in between, that will determine which one of the eight possible endings will be reached in a non-linear storyline. The player has the option to recruit characters, control individual equipment of each character, with over six male character classes, six female character classes, three demi-human classes, and more. It is also possible to train at safe locations to prepare the army before the next battle or storyline advancement.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tactics Ogre - Let Us Cling Together-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Taekwon-Do.zip</path>
		<name>Taekwondo</name>
		<desc>Taekwondo is a Super Famicom title that was released exclusively in Japan and South Korea in 1994. The game is based around the Korean martial art of Taekwondo, featuring realistic techniques and tournament rules. It features nineteen fighters with their own special moves, and players are also given the option of creating their own custom fighters. The game can be played in either Japanese or Korean.

The fighting control is very simple, and features the standardized control method of combining attack and directional button inputs to perform a variety of techniques. There are four different game modes: Tournament, Versus, Tag Battle by Turns and Practice.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Taekwon-Do-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Human</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo Super NBA Basketball.zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Super NBA Basketball</name>
		<desc>Tecmo Super NBA features real teams (all 27 contemporary teams) and a roster of real players (over 320).  One or two players can compete in regular, reduced, or short seasons, or play an exhibition game.   Though primarily horizontal scrolling, digitized speech and cinemas, along with a free throw point of view, add drama to the proceedings.  Besides the expected elements of basketball (substitutions, penalties, steals and blocks, time-outs, overtime), Super NBA gives you the chance to call offensive plays and to program win/loss records.  Has a battery to back-up season play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tecmo Super NBA Basketball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tournament Fighters</name>
		<desc>Trash the surf board and heave the 'za. It's a whole new breed of Turtles and they're fixated on fighting. We're dead serious, Tournament Fighters takes dude-on-dude demolition to new heights of intensity with 4 modes of pain-producing battles, deadly warriors, secret arenas, astounding graphics and sound effects that'll make you cringe! Clash with Krang-created clones of the Turtles, Casey Jones, April O'Neil, Ray Filet and Sisyphus, plus bosses Triceraton, Krang's Android and Karai. There's flying body presses, knee drops, head butts, rocket punches, elbow smashes, somersault throws, you'll feel and inflict them all. And the settings include Magma Ocean Planet, Jungle Planet, and every other bizarre corner of Dimension X!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Shadow</name>
		<desc>The Shadow was once a vicious criminal captured by a mystic and taught the powers of the mind. He became the nemesis of evil.

Now, donning his sweeping cape and disguise, The Shadow takes on his most dangerous foe yet; the last descendant of the great Genghis Khan.

Join the fight and with your help, The Shadow will be victorious.

The Shadow was a canceled SNES game published by Ocean. It is based in the film of the same name. It is currently available for download.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Shadow, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Wacky Sports Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Wacky Sports Challenge</name>
		<desc>Humor! Wackiness! Sports!
ls that what you're looking for? if so. this game's got it! Plus cool graphics.

STARRING YOUR FAVORITE TINY TOON ADVENTURES CHARACTERS FROM THE ANIMATED TV SERIES!!
You can play as Buster Bunny. Babs Bunny (no relation). Plucky Duck or Dizzy
Devil! You'll also run into your other favorite cast characters.

HIDDEN BONUSES!!! TWELVE DIFFERENT EVENTS!!! MULTIPLE SKILL LEVELS WITH DIFFERENT HAZARDS!!!
Face it. if you want a laugh riot. sports action. and tons of replay value. then this is the game you're looking for! Just check out those screen shots.

BUY THE GAME. PLAY THE GAME. BE THE GAME.
Besides. where else are you going to find Bungee Jumping, Chicken Race. Ice Cream Toss, Weight Lifting and eight other games in one convenient package?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Tiny Toon Adventures - Wacky Sports Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gear.zip</path>
		<name>Top Gear</name>
		<desc>In the first of three released games for Super NES, players can choose among 4 different cars, each one with different attributes (maximum speed, fuel consumption, boost power and tire grip) to face 32 challenging courses situated in several places around the world as Brazil, USA, France, Japan etc.

In more longer tracks, players will find a Pit Stop section, where they can enter to replenish the fuel meter (total or partially). The game has a split-screen display for 1 or 2 players. In 1-Player mode, you'll dispute the races against the computer, that has a slightly bigger speed than yours, helping to give a lot more of competitiveness. A password system was included, being possible to stop a current game and resume it later.

Through the game, players will find several obstacles scattered by the courses, like rows of iron plates or even lots of stones. In order to qualify for the next circuit, it's required to complete it at least in the 5th position, or else the game is over.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Top Gear-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gear 2.zip</path>
		<name>Top Gear 2</name>
		<desc>This third-person racing game resembles Gremlin's earlier Lotus series, in terms of its general look and feel, right down to the text font used in the game. Your task is to race through 16 countries, each of which features four races, with many real-world circuits recreated in incongruous locations (such as the Monza layout in Ayers Rock, and the old Hockenheim in Vancouver). 

These four-race blocks each represent their own mini-championship, in which you race against 19 cars, needing to finish in the top 10 to continue, and with the top 6 scoring points 10-6-4-3-2-1, and the respective amount of money in thousands. This can be spent on various upgrades, ranging from engine to tires (wet and dry) and from shocks (front, side and rear) to gearboxes. The ideal approach is to buy the more expensive versions ASAP, as you get no saving when upgrading. If you win the four-race championship, you get the next password. 

You get a set amount of nitro boost to use during each race, although bonus nitros, money and instant speed-up token appear on many tracks. Hazards such as puddles, barriers and ramps are also frequent.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Top Gear 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./True Lies.zip</path>
		<name>True Lies</name>
		<desc>True Lies is a 1994 video game based upon the film of the same name with Arnold Schwarzenegger's character Harry as the protagonist. The game followed the movie's path reasonably well, beginning at the Chateau and ending with the death of antagonist Aziz on the roof of the high rise. The game, which is oriented from a top-down perspective, had numerous weapons, from pistols and shotguns to anti-personnel mines.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/True Lies-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./U.N. Squadron.zip</path>
		<name>U.N. Squadron</name>
		<desc>Soar to glory in a high-tech aircraft! The Evil Project 4 has torn freedom from the people of Aslan. Mercenaries control the entire country, except for a tiny airfield. But this field is headquarters for the best fighter pilots in the world -- UN Squadron!
You must destroy all eight of Project 4's bases as you force back an overpowering enemy war machine. Dog-fight a wolfpack of stealth fighters in a battlefield of clouds! Strafe enemy tanks!
A giant missile launcher, laser cannon and desert aircraft carrier hammer at your plane. Counterstrike with missiles, thunder lasers, napalm and bombs. Lead an airstrike for freedom!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/U.N. Squadron-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Whirlo.zip</path>
		<name>Whirlo</name>
		<desc>A platformer title starring Valkyrie's lizard friend Xandra. In the game, which plays as a prequel of the Valkyrie games, you control Xandra as he leaves his enchanted forest in order to get help for his family. This will eventually lead him to meet up with our beloved Valkyrie and mark the beginning of their adventures.

Xandra has all the abilities of a standard platformer character, which allow him to jump around and navigate the many obstacles found in the game. Additionally he's armed with a pitchfork which he can use to impale his enemies and stick to some surfaces. Collecting coins allow him to purchase extra lives, but there are no added weapons or spells as in the Valkyrie games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Whirlo-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Winter Gold.zip</path>
		<name>Winter Gold</name>
		<desc>Winter Gold is a winter sports game with events like bobsled, ski jump and snow boarding, all in a 3D graphics environment.

Both single player and multi player options are available; you can play with up to eight people in compete mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Winter Gold-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Funcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Cookie is a fast-paced puzzle game that can be enjoyed by everyone as it is easy to play, but challenging to complete. To play, you move the randomly placed cookies into rows and columns of cookies with similar patterns. When you successfully assemble a row or column of the same cookies, the line will disappear, and you can begin on a new row or column. The "Yoshi" cookie is very special in both the 1-player and the 2-player game. Since the Yoshi Cookie is the key to both games, you must use it wisely.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Yoshi's Cookie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - 1st Annual Vanilla LDC.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - 1st Annual Vanilla LDC</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - 8th Annual Vanilla LDC.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - 8th Annual Vanilla LDC</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Bowser Cataclism Trap.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Bowser Cataclism Trap</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Bowser Rampages Again.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Bowser Rampages Again</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - CMW3 The Finale.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - CMW3 The Finale</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Colossus.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Colossus</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Evil Conquest.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Evil Conquest</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Hack.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Hack</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Hack 2.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Hack 2</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Hack 3.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Hack 3</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Hunter's Revenge ReVised.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Hunter's Revenge ReVised</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - JUMP.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - JUMP</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Kamek's Island.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Kamek's Island</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Luigi's Adventure 3 OSE.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Luigi's Adventure 3 OSE</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Luigi's Adventure OSE.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Luigi's Adventure OSE</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario &amp; Luigi Kola Kingdom Quest.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario &amp; Luigi Kola Kingdom Quest</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario &amp; Luigi Starlight Island Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario &amp; Luigi Starlight Island Adventure</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario Gives Up 3.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario Gives Up 3</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario Is Missing.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario Is Missing</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario X World BSB.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario X World BSB</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario X World DX.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario X World DX</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario's Amazing Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario's Amazing Adventure</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Mario's Strange Quest.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Mario's Strange Quest</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Master Quest 4 Redrawn.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Master Quest 4 Redrawn</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - NSMW1 The 12 Magic Orbs.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - NSMW1 The 12 Magic Orbs</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Redrawn.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Redrawn</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - SMB The Early Years.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - SMB The Early Years</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - SMB The Hunt For The Magical Key.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - SMB The Hunt For The Magical Key</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - SML3 - Tatanga's Return.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - SML3 - Tatanga's Return</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - SMW2+3 The Essence Star.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - SMW2+3 The Essence Star</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Something Else.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Something Else</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Mario Bros 2 Dream Courses.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Mario Bros 2 Dream Courses</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Mario Bros 3X.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Mario Bros 3X</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Mario Bros 5 Reborn.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Mario Bros 5 Reborn</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Mario Logic.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Mario Logic</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Mario Omega.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Mario Omega</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Super Yoshi Land.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - Super Yoshi Land</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - The 7 Golden Mushrooms.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - The 7 Golden Mushrooms</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - The Ancestors Treasure.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - The Ancestors Treasure</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - The Secret of the 7 Golden Statues.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - The Secret of the 7 Golden Statues</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - The Treasure Hunt.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - The Treasure Hunt</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - This Hack Needs a Name.zip</path>
		<name>SMW - This Hack Needs a Name</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - The Second Reality Project Reloaded.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World The Second Reality Project 2</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - TSRP2 - Zycloboos Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World The Second Reality Project 2-Zycloboo's Challenge</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Return to Dinosaur Land.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World: Return to Dinosaur Land</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMW Hacks/SMW - Yoshi's Strange Quest Beta.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Strange Quest</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SMW Hack-image.jpg</image>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nosferatu.zip</path>
		<name>Nosferatu</name>
		<desc>It's a race of time. Kyle must save his fair maiden Erin before the evil cutches of Nosferatu can sway her fate forever! Dungeons and graveyards are only a few obsticles in his path, littered with traps and beasts of unspeakable nature. Join Kyle's journey into darkness to return his love before her soul is lost for eternity!

-16 megs of dramatic action and adventure at its best!
-With 6 master stages, 14 sub-levels, and countless hidden rooms, Nosferatu will challenge you with fun and adventure!
-Discover treasures and hidden secrets of every level!
-Fluid play control for speed and maneuvering!
-Multiple hit combinations including flying reverse kicks, roundhouse kicks, spinning back fists and many more!
-Awesome movie like graphics, including more than 350 frames of character animations! Realistic arcade style action!
-Battle creatures like Werewolves, Beholder Eyes, Stone Gholems, Gargoyles, and Vlad the Impaler (Nosferatu) himself!
-Superb soundtrack and quality special effects!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/Nosferatu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19941018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seta</developer>
		<publisher>Seta</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOS.zip</path>
		<name>SOS</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/snes/SOS-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
</gameList>
