<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Alisia Dragoon.zip</path>
		<name>Alisia Dragoon</name>
		<desc>The pace is intense. Enemies come at Alisia from everywhere. And nowhere. Battle hordes of crazed barbarians, mow down mobs of poisonous centipedes, and slay squadrons of winged gargoyels. Blast enemies in waves or one by one with multi-directional, auto-targeting laser fire.

Recruit killer companions like the DragonFrye, Ball O'Fire, Thunder Raven and Boomerang Lizard. Use them to hurl blistering boomerangs, fireballs, and electrical attacks. With Alisia's super-tough fighting skills, fry enemies to a crisp. And prove once and for all that you can go hand-to-hand with evil and come out the champion!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Alisia Dragoon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19920423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gainax Network Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>After her defeat by the Galactic Corporation at the battle of Canis Major, the evil Dark Queen and her renegade space troops retreat to the outer reaches of the universe, hiding out in dark spaces between the stars. Meanwhile, on board the spaceship Vulture, Professor T. Bird and the trio of Battletoads - Rash, Zitz and Pimple - are escorting the Princess Angelica back to her home planet, where her father, the Terran Emperor, awaits her safe arrival. Along the way, Pimple, the biggest Battletoad, takes Angelica out for a cruise in the Toadster to a nearby Leisure Station, but the Dark Queen ambushes them before they can get there, and they are kidnapped and carried away to Ragnarok's World, the Dark Queen's planet. Professor Bird sends remaining Battletoads down on Ragnarok to save Pimple and Angelica, but it will be a hard battle against planet's dangerous environments, traps and Dark Queen's troops. They have to go a long way from the planet's rough surface to deep caves and landed Gargantua and ultimately to the Tower of Shadows, where the Dark Queen awaits.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Battletoads-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19910114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beyond Oasis.zip</path>
		<name>Beyond Oasis</name>
		<desc>On the mystical island of Oasis, Prince Ali embarks on a crusade against evil. The warrior prince must unleash the powers of the four Wild Spirits to stop the resurrection of a ruthless sorcerer and save the empire! As Ali, you can call on the powers of the four wild spirits to battle the evil minions of Agito. Fight off enemies with Ali's weapons, punches and kicks... or dig deeper to discover the Hidden Super Moves...a Sega first! Flip switches, trigger plates, and use what's left of your brain to solve mind-boggling puzzles that lead to Huge Bosses... like the Fire-breathing Red Dragon!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Beyond Oasis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ancient</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master 2.zip</path>
		<name>Blaster Master 2</name>
		<desc>It has been four years since Jason's Encounter with the Plutonium Boss and the radioactive mutants under the Earth. His only reminder of the incident is S.O.P.H.I.A., the vehicle he used to stop them, which he has hidden in an abandoned barn. One day, one bolt of lightning struck the house and caused the ceiling to crumble, knocking Jason unconscious. When Jason woke up, S.O.P.H.I.A. was in pieces and the parts he had collected from his first dealings with the Mutant Bosses were missing. Little does Jason know that there are more lightning beings where the first one came from and they are planning to destroy the Earth. The beings started digging towards the Earth's core in order to shift the planet's weight off its axis, leading to total annihilation. The parts from S.O.P.H.I.A. are being used to create a robotic army to assist the being in accomplishing their mission. Now, Jason must stop them, but he won't make it without the help of S.O.P.H.I.A. Since he can't recover the parts, he decided to redesign it to better prepare himself for the ordeal facing him. After 29 days, S.O.P.H.I.A. was completely rebuilt and ready for battle. Remembering where he saw the being's footsteps, Jason jumped in his vehicle and headed towards the mountains where the challenge begins.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Blaster Master 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>The search is on! Mickey is on the trail of a wicked Witch named Mizrabel, who has kidnapped Minnie. Mickey must find seven gems hidden in the fantastic chambers of Mizrabel's Castle of Illusion and use them to save Minnie. Can Mickey find them? It's up to you.

Be on your guard! Behind every door lurks an enchanted land of beauty and danger. You must defeat angry chess knights, overcome the evil haunted trees, and do battle with ghoulish ghosts and a deadly dragon. No place is safe -- even the library is fraught with danger. Playing three levels in the practice mode will prepare you for the challenge you will face. Then, just when you think you've mastered the Illusions, you come face to face with the most dangerous of them all -- Witch Mizrabel!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6599999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19901122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170204T012614</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Bloodlines.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Bloodlines</name>
		<desc>Time refuses to forget the Belmont family's horrifying, bloody destiny. And in 1917 two of its descendants are summoned by fate into epic battle. Their enemy? The most evil incarnation of Castlevania legacy to ever rise from the grave, the vampiress Countess Bartley. This spine-tingling, 6-stage fear-fest overflows with graphic sights and sounds from your worst nightmares. As John Morris, the whip wielding vampire hunter, or Eric Lecarde, master lanceman, you'll pursue the demonic Countess all across Europe before she resurrects Dracula for a final reign of global terror. Alas, her trail of doom is laden with zombies, hideous mutants, grotesque giants, ghouls and ghastly creatures. Taste the sweat dripping into your mouth as you try rescuing yourself from diabolical traps. Feel the torturous strain on every muscle as you wield again and again sacred weapon power-ups such as Holy Water, the Battle Axe, the Crystal Blade Boomerang and the Mirror of Truth. But in the end, make sure you've saved enough strength to scream!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Castlevania - Bloodlines-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra - Hard Corps.zip</path>
		<name>Contra: Hard Corps</name>
		<desc>Kickin' cyborg butt... That's what it's all about, dude. Jack into this game of genetic engineering gone bad. Real bad. It's five years after the mother of all wars ended - and things still aren't right. Your job is to fix it. The ever-popular Contra series makes its Sega Genesis debut with a pulse-pounding new storyline. At 16 megs, HARD CORPS pushes the technology to bring you over ten gut-wrenching levels with huge boss characters, great graphics and dynamic sound. Find high powered weapons such as the homing gun, crush gun, needle laser or mine setter. Do you think you can handle it? Trust me, you can't. You still here? Okay, then get ready for the fight of your life. Pick one of the four heroes and begin your search across many dark levels of doom. The ending changes, depending on the paths you choose - but every pass crosses boss characters that will blow you away. Literally!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Contra - Hard Corps-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crusader of Centy.zip</path>
		<name>Crusader of Centy</name>
		<desc>Millions of years ago, heinous creatures that lurked in the shadows and darkness that blanketed the planet inhabited the Earth. When light finally broke through, only a few beasts were able to survive by burrowing into deep caverns. Over time, they multiplied, evolved, and patiently waited for the right time to emerge and rule the Earth once again. You are Corona, and you've just celebrated your 14th birthday. By law of the king, you must now go seek out these creatures of the dark and destroy them. As you travel in search of your destiny, you'll make animal allies that will prove invaluable on your quest. Each level will offer mind-bending puzzles and challenges that will help you get one step closer to completing your mission.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Crusader of Centy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nextech</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin.zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin</name>
		<desc>Hang on to your carpet for ACTION and FUN! Aladdin slashes his shining scimitar to fight through Agrabah, escape the Sultan's dungeon, survive the fiery Cave of Wonders, snatch the Genie's Lamp and save Princess Jasmine from the evil Jafar! All-new technology creates animation so smooth, it's like watching a real animated film. Aladdin battles thieves and desert warriors, and barely dodges danger on his high-speed carpet. Survive Jafar's troops for a dash through special bonus rounds. Hilarious! Palace Guards drop their drawers and camels spit dirt wads. Aladdin ping-pongs like a pinball INSIDE the Genie's Lamp!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Aladdin-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19931126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynamite Headdy.zip</path>
		<name>Dynamite Headdy</name>
		<desc>Hot-headed Headdy gets into some real head-banging to thwart the Dark Demon's devious deeds. This wacky headcase is up to his neck in surprises! Switch heads to match the job! Over 15 heads to choose from! Bash heavy objects with Slammer Head! Suck up foes with Vacuum Head! Stick it to your enemies with Spike Head! Headdy's spring-loaded head gets him where he's gotta go! Use it to swing over ledges, grab onto objects and shoot hoops in the basketball bonus round. Use your head to whiz through a radical variety of play! Action, shooting and strategy speed you on to a surprise ending!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Dynamite Headdy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940804T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunstar Heroes.zip</path>
		<name>Gunstar Heroes</name>
		<desc>Gunstar Heroes is a side scrolling shooter. The player has four weapons to choose from, and they can be combined in various pairs to create a total of 14 unique weapons. In addition to the weapons, the player can engage enemies in close quarters combat. It is possible to grab and toss enemies, perform sliding and jumping attacks and a long-range skid.

Unlike most games in the genre, the player has a life total calculated in numbers. Death to a player requires multiple hits but just one death will issue the option to continue from the start of the level or to end the game. Players have unlimited continues.

The main highlight of the game are its boss encounters, which often feature large enemies made up of multiple sprites allowing for fluid movement.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Gunstar Heroes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./James Pond II - Codename Robocod.zip</path>
		<name>James Pond 2: Codename RoboCod</name>
		<desc>To: James Pond... For your fish eyes only! 

Pond, the fiendish Dr. Maybe is back. His bombs are ticking in the North Pole toy factories. No human crime fighter has been able to defeat him. So F.I.S.H. (Finned Investigators of Shady Humans) has designed a special Robosuit for your survival on land. Pond, go to it! Remember, Dr. Maybe has a screw loose, so stay on your fins!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/James Pond II - Codename Robocod-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VectorDean</developer>
		<publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Landstalker.zip</path>
		<name>Landstalker</name>
		<desc>Eons ago, evil King Nole tyrannized the mythical island of Melcatle. With an insatiable greed for power and wealth, he crushed the people with heavy taxes while destroying their freedom. At last, in fury, the enslaved citizens stormed the palace. But King Nole was gone! And with him, the vast treasure, stolen from his subjects!

Now Nigel, the Landstalker, journeys to this fantastic realm in search of the legendary fortune and power to reunite a divided kingdom!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Landstalker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19921029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters.zip</path>
		<name>Lethal Enforcers II: Gunfighters</name>
		<desc>You are the sheriff of a town set in the old Wild West. Using the control pad or Konami's own Justifier lightgun, you'll be taking out outlaws who are robbing banks and kidnapping innocents. You have the opportunity to upgrade and keep you gun, as long as you don't shoot the people you are trying to save.

The action is usually shown on a single screen with enemies "popping out" from various sections. If you do not shoot them in time they will either shoot or throw various weapons at you. You will lose energy if they hit you or you hit an innocent civilian.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman - The Wily Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man: The Wily Wars</name>
		<desc>In the last few years, a titanic struggle for control of the planet has raged. Each time it has pitted Mega Man, a cybernetic champion of justice against the villainous Dr. Wily and his renegade robots. And each time, Mega Man has emerged victorious! Now, in a desperate attempt to change the past, Dr. Wily has used a time machine to slip back to the time of his first battles with Mega Man. There he plans to make sure that this time, Mega Man will be history!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Megaman - The Wily Wars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Turrican.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Turrican</name>
		<desc>After many generations of peace, the Dark Forces have assembled again, and as a member of the USS Freedom Forces, it is your job to defeat them once again. This means you will have to complete numerous large levels always searching for secrets to pick up and enemies to shoot. To do this, you can pick up three different, upgradeable shots: a multiple, a laser and a rebound. You can also go into wheel-mode (as long as you have enough special energy) or use a rope. In wheel-mode, you are invincible and can lay mines or explore previously unreachable areas.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Mega Turrican-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster World IV.zip</path>
		<name>Monster World 4</name>
		<desc>Monster World IV is an action-adventure platform game, developed by Westone and released exclusively in Japan by Sega for the Mega Drive in April 1994. It is the sixth and final game in the Wonder Boy/Monster World series.

The story involves a young girl named Asha, who upon hearing spirits whisper on the wind pleading for help, embarks on a journey to find and aid them. Along the way she becomes master of a genie and adopts a small monster known as Pepelogoo.

Monster World IV is a mix of action-adventure, platforming and RPG genres, in which the player traverses a 2D landscape fighting a variety of monsters as well as interacting with non-playable characters.

Expanding upon previous games in the series, Asha has the ability to swing her sword upward, downward, and across while in air, depending on which direction is pressed. She can also use her shield in a standing position by holding down.

Asha can summon her pet Pepelogoo to reach areas that she cannot on her own. By holding onto him, she can slow the descent of her jump (via his flying ability) or even perform a double-jump. Pepelogoo can also protect Asha from falling rocks, be used as a platform over lava geysers, and blow out fires that obstruct Asha's progress.

Equipment upgrades are purchased in the hub town. Armor increases Asha's pink life heart meter. Shields increase her defense and give her stat defenses to certain elements, such as fire or ice. Swords increase Asha's attack stats with critical effects depending upon the sword.

Some items cannot be purchased and must be found in the temples and caverns that Asha must explore. Healing medicine will restore Asha's health or bring her back to life if she has Pepelogoo. Gold bars can be traded with the rich lady in town for in-game currency. And finally, there are 150 life drops hidden throughout the game. Collecting ten will add a blue life heart to the life meter.

Items can be permanently missed. Once an area's boss is defeated, that area is inaccessible for the rest of the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Monster World IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor.zip</path>
		<name>MUSHA: Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor</name>
		<desc>A spin-off from the successful Aleste series by Compile, Musha Aleste takes the same top-down shooter mechanics of it's predecessors but stages the action in a bizarre universe that merges traditional Japanese lore with sci-fi mecha action.

Instead of commanding a ship, you will actually step into the cockpit of a ninja-styled mecha as you fight through the many levels in the game, with several option satellites that can be configured to use different formations.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Seismic Software Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star IV.zip</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star IV: The End of the Millennium</name>
		<desc>Launch into the biggest RPG ever on Genesis! This is the explosive magic-and-monster packed FINALE to the incredible Phantasy Star saga. An ancient, hideous Dark Force stalks the Algol star system. You, a young hunter, are destined to become Motavia's greatest warrior and strike the death-blow that destroys evil FOREVER!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Phantasy Star IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pier Solar and the Great Architects.zip</path>
		<name>Pier Solar and the Great Architects</name>
		<desc>Pier Solar and the Great Architects is an independently developed Sega Mega Drive game, released worldwide in December 2010 by WaterMelon, a group of developers from the Mega Drive homebrew and research scene. It is a turn-based RPG, and, at 8 megabytes (64 megabits) in size means it is currently the second largest Sega Mega Drive game available. It is the first internationally commercially released Mega Drive game since 2002's Mega Games 10 (not counting Super Fighter Team's releases, which have all been translations of games released in the 1990s).

The game ships for $35 USD and has a clamshell case with a choice of three cover arts which resemble those used by Sega in Japan, North America and Europe towards the end of the Mega Drive's lifespan. Also included is a 24-page full colour instruction manual and a "MEGA Soundtrack Booster CD", containing the game's soundtrack, which, if the player has a Sega Mega-CD attached, can be used as an alternate source of the game's music during gameplay (however it is not a standalone Mega CD game). 500 "Posterity Packs" were also sold, with buyers receiving their names in the game's credits and instruction booklet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Pier Solar and the Great Architects-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20101214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WaterMelom</developer>
		<publisher>WaterMelon</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>The Grand Vizier Jaffar has thrown you into a dark dungeon and plans to marry the girl of your dreams in an hour. You're not going to let that happen are you? Try to escape from the dungeon, take out Jaffar's guards, find your way through the Sultan's palace and defeat Jaffar himself. Now go, you've got 60 minutes!

Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer with run and jump gameplay. Your hero must avoid deadly traps, solve some simple puzzles and engage in sword fights with the guards. The player has an infinite amount of lives, but has to restart at the beginning of a level each time he dies, and must complete the game within an hour. An especially noteworthy aspect of the game is the very fluent animation of your character.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brøderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pulseman.zip</path>
		<name>Pulseman</name>
		<desc>Pulseman (originally known as Spark) is a platform game for the Sega Mega Drive. It was only released on cartridge for a Japanese audience, but was available to North American consumers via the Sega Channel. The game was not sold in Europe.

It was developed by Game Freak, the development team that would later go on to produce the Pokémon series of games for Nintendo. Many of Pulseman's staff, including director Ken Sugimori and composer Junichi Masuda worked on both games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Pulseman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./QuackShot Starring Donald Duck.zip</path>
		<name>Quackshot: Starring Donald Duck</name>
		<desc>Donald unearths an ancient scroll that reveals a long-lost treasure. Off he dashes on a dangerous expedition! He leaps over cacti, sidesteps scorpions, and slides down slopes to claim the loot before Big Bad Pete can get it. Donald's temperamental tantrums keep the bad guys runnin'! He thonks 'em with his plunger and bounces on the handle to hop over their heads. Then he blasts 'em with gooey bubblegum! Yuck-a-duck! Donald creeps through the evil Count's castle, and plumbs the depths of Aztec ruins. With Huey, Dewey, and Louie's help, he'll find the key to unlock the secret of the most fabulous treasure on earth!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/QuackShot Starring Donald Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ristar.zip</path>
		<name>Ristar</name>
		<desc>Ristar, the son of a legendary hero who's been captured, is the solar system's last hope against the evil space pirate Greedy. Ristar must travel to the 7 planets of his home system to restore peace to their once happy worlds and ultimately free his father. Ristar stretches his long elastic arms to grab enemies and head-butt them! His long limbs help him climb up walls or swing out of danger. Discover totally different worlds and new creatures on each planet! Battle strange beings who aren't always what they seem! Shoot through a variety of gameplay! Action, puzzle and strategy combine to challenge Ristar at every turn.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Ristar-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76</rating>
		<releasedate>19950217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocket Knight Adventures.zip</path>
		<name>Rocket Knight Adventures</name>
		<desc>He's courageous! He's clever! He's one good lookin' opossum. It's Sparkster the Rocket Knight, the heroic jet pack jockey with warp speed, quick wits and pumped up personality. After all, who else do you know can get a grip with his tail? Rocket through 7 epic stages of animalistic adventure, home of the hugest, strangest enemy pig creatures imaginable. (In fact, your mission is crammed with more ham than a Hollywood premier.) Destroy the Emperor who's on a porcine power trip that will take him to the Key to the Pig Star. In every stage you'll be moving, flying and riding in a new direction to escape opossum punishment. You're the thrust-meister controlling Sparkster's jet pack and his assault sword. Confront mechanized menaces like the Giant Pigbot, the Drill Of A Lifetime, and the snappy Crab Rangoon. Things take a turn for the worst in the room of rotating gravity where Axle Gear, the Black Knights awaits you. And you've never seen anything like the unreal mirrored lava pools where things will reflect badly on you. The tricks, the traps and challenges never end. But the world as you know it will if you don't grind those pigs for sausage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Rocket Knight Adventures-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic &amp; Knuckles.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic &amp; Knuckles</name>
		<desc>Sonic and Knuckles join forces to defeat rotten Dr. Robotnik's Death Egg invasion! Play Sonic &amp; Knuckles by itself or Lock-on with other Sonic games. This game's revolutionary Lock-on technology adds all new features to your other Sonic games for ultimate replays! Play as Sonic and let loose on Robotnik with amazing new powers. Play as Knuckles and tackle Robotnik and Metal Sonic with bare-fisted attacks, high-speed glides and wall-climbing power! Lock-on with Sonic 3 and transform Floating Island into a huge 34 meg Sonic-epic loaded with new secrets! Play as Sonic, Knuckles, and even Tails - with Game Save! Lock-on with Sonic 2 and play as Knuckles with all his signature moves!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic &amp; Knuckles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19941018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic the Hedgehog.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog</name>
		<desc>Super Speed! Bust the video game speed barrier wide open with Sonic the Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the super sonic spin attack. Loop the loop by defying gravity. Plummet down tunnels. Then dash to safety with Sonic's power sneakers. All at a frenzied pace. Super Graphics! Help Sonic escape bubbling molten lava. Swim through turbulent waterfalls. Scale glistening green mountains. And soar past shimmering city lights. There's even a 360 degree rotating maze. You've never seen anything like it. Supper Attitude! Sonic has an attitude that just won't quit. He's flip and funny, yet tough as nails as he fights to free his friends from evil. So just wait. Sonic may be the world's next SUPER hero...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic the Hedgehog-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.72222</rating>
		<releasedate>19910623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic the Hedgehog 3.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 3</name>
		<desc>Swing from vines, launch new attacks, survive deadly traps and summon Tails to airlift Sonic out of danger. Discover hidden rooms and passageways in the mega-sized Zones. Transform into Super Sonic and experience the ultimate in speed and ultra-sonic power. Save your progress using the new Game Save Feature.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic the Hedgehog 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19940202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Streets of Rage 2.zip</path>
		<name>Streets of Rage 2</name>
		<desc>Original rumblers Axel and Blaze slam the asphalt with bigger, better, totally devastating attacks! Skull-crushing ex-wrestler Max Thunder joins up with earth-shattering body slams and spinning fist attacks. New thrasher Skate slices punks with high speed in-line skate attacks and spinning jump kicks. Go maniac with jaw-shattering, bone-busting punches, head-cracking jump kicks and secret weapons. Gangs of dirt bikers dive into you from every side. Smash 'em with a pipe as they speed by. 16 gigantic megs of compound fractures! All new moves, and more of 'em! Bust knuckles with a friend in an all-new 2-player head-to-head mode!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Streets of Rage 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19921220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT - The Hyperstone Heist.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Hyperstone Heist</name>
		<desc>Shredder steals the powerful Hyperstone to shrink New York City and it's up to you to teach that treacherous troublemaker not to mess with the fearless foursome! Pick your favorite Cowabunga commando to slash through 5 lawless levels of lambasting. Four levels each have 3 intense stages and the other is packed with brand new challenges that will make you hurl your pizza lunch. Pulverize shrink-happy Shredder before he pockets our whole planet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/TMNT - The Hyperstone Heist-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin</name>
		<desc>From the award winning animated TV series comes the most action-packed Batman adventure yet! The Dark Knight returns with Robin to battle the forces of evil. But wait... the iceman cometh!!! Mr. Freeze is about to unleash his super-powered ice cannon and has teamed up with the most notorious criminals to help him turn Gotham City into a diabolical winter wonderland!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clockwork Tortoise</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170204T012835</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones</name>
		<desc>It's the weekend and Fred Flintstone returns home from work very excited about the Bedrock Super Bowl final tonight. As he arrives home Wilma reminds him of his promise to paint the living room before her mother arrives on Sunday. Wilma insists that Fred can only go bowling if he paints the living room. Reluctantly, Fred agrees, but he doesn't bargain for baby-sitting Pebbles and painting at the same time. Chaos, fun and the Flintstones humor is everywhere!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Flintstones, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy in Monster World.zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy in Monster World</name>
		<desc>Townsfolk cower in fear as legions of deadly monsters invade the planet. Only Wonder Boy can fight smart enough - and tough enough - to wipe out the terrible beasts. Sleuth out secret clues to thwart the undead. Match wits against an evil force of otherwordly dimensions. And prove the awesome strength and courage of the amazing Wonder Boy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Wonder Boy in Monster World-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T013453</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III.zip</path>
		<name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<desc>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games, allowing Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. Beside changing the battle system, the game's perspective switches to a side-scrolling view, as opposed to the top-down one of the previous games. Adol also has the ability to jump now. New to the series is the use of magical rings, which give Adol different powering-up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Ys III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lethal Enforcers MD.zip</path>
		<name>Lethal Enforcers</name>
		<desc>Lethal Enforcers is out to clean up the streets in the baddest parts of Chicago. Digitized graphics and sound will slam you into cold reality and heated action. Your job is to defend the innocent and protect yourself from a fatal case of lead poisoning.
Your side iron is packed inside and ready to blow you away with a true arcade experience. Just like the arcade game, you've got the quick reload feature. Time it just right so you don't run out of ammo while you're trading bullets with the scum of the earth. Upgrade your firepower along the way to magnum, 12-round automatic, assault rifle, shot gun, machine gun or grenade gun.
Your type of street cleaning takes place where the dirtiest deeds go down. But first, a training level lets you take target practice and take out your frustrations, then on to reality. Be on the lookout for bank job in progress, high speed chase, ninjas downtown, hijacking at the international airport, gunrunners at the shipping dock, helicopter chase, chemical plant sabotage with volatile Heat of the Night Vision. The pressure under fire is so intense you'll be sweating bullets. Start shooting in any stage you select. At the end of each level, you'll get your hit percentage and your performance rank, from petrolman to commander.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Lethal Enforcers MD-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Fantasy Zone.zip</path>
		<name>Super Fantasy Zone</name>
		<desc>The next-gen sequel to Fantasy Zone, Super Fantasy Zone starts as a strange gravitational force appears in the Menon planet, home of the evil Menon empire and thus a new threat looms over the Fantasy Zone.

In a sudden strike by the Menon forces O-Papa, Opa-Opa's father, is fatally wounded. Thus Opa-Opa once again sets forth to destroy the Menon empire and avenge his father.

EU release</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Super Fantasy Zone-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SunSoft</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Soldier.zip</path>
		<name>Alien Soldier</name>
		<desc>Alien Soldier is a side-scrolling action game in which the player takes the role of Epsilon-Eagle, the former leader of the Scarlet mutant group. The mutants are now lead by the evil Xi-Tiger who had turned them to terrorism, and one of their goals is to kill Epsilon-Eagle...

At the start of the game the player chooses four out of six weapons - each with special advantages or disadvantages against certain enemies. As mutant Epsilon-Eagle also has other special powers, e.g. teleporting across the screen or (with full health) morphing into a powerful phoenix destroying everything in his way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Alien Soldier-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure Co</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170304T164008</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia 2</name>
		<desc>Similar to the first Prince of Persia, the character explores various deadly areas by running, jumping, crawling, avoiding traps, solving puzzles and drinking magic potions. Prince of Persia 2 is, however, more combat-heavy than its predecessor. In the first game, enemies appear only occasionally and are always alone, while in the sequel, up to four enemies may appear at once, sometimes flanking the player, and may even be instantly replaced by reinforcements when they are killed. As in Prince of Persia, the trick is to complete the game under a strict time limit that passes in real time. Lives are unlimited, but time cannot be regained except by reverting to a previously saved game. In other areas, more significant improvements have been made. The graphics are far more complex than the simple look of the game's predecessor, the areas explored are larger, and the variety of backdrops is greater.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tougiou King Colossus.zip</path>
		<name>Tougiou King Colossus</name>
		<desc>Tougi-Ou: King Colossus is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Sega, which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Tougiou King Colossus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T013104</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chelnov.zip</path>
		<name>Chelnov</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Chelnov-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20171205T013338</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ESWAT - City Under Siege.zip</path>
		<name>ESWAT: City under Siege</name>
		<desc>ESWAT: City under Siege, released in Japan as Cyber Police ESWAT (サイバーポリス イースワット?),[1][2] is a 1990 side scrolling platform video game for the Sega Mega Drive and Genesis video game consoles.

City under Siege was based on the arcade game Cyber Police ESWAT released a year earlier in 1989. The console game maintains the main characters, plot and some of its enemies from the arcade game, but features some different levels, weapons, and bonuses.

The game is a sidescrolling platformer similar to Shinobi. The game is set in the near future, where the player controls a blonde police officer named Duke Oda (デューク・オダ?) who, over a series of levels, turns into the cyborg E.S.W.A.T. At first, as a rookie member of the Cyber Police force in the city of Liberty, the player has to clean the streets of an overwhelming crime wave and terminate the most wanted criminals. In the first and second levels of the game, the completely human Duke Oda can only utilize a single shot weapon and can only survive one hit. A second hit will kill him.

A mysterious and high-tech organization, named "E.Y.E.", quickly threatens to take over the entire city and, after being promoted at the end of the second level, Duke Oda is given power armor called the "ICE Combat Suit". With this suit the player can use new and more lethal weapons; "Super Shot", a plasma rifle, rockets, and a devastating fire attack if he finds them. The player also has access to a jet pack with limited fuel that replenishes over time. Finally, this armor will allow the player to take more damage before being defeated. Unfortunately, because the suit makes him larger, it is harder for him to dodge enemy attacks. The final boss of the game, the leader of E.Y.E., is revealed to be a robot with artificial intelligence that is attempting to replicate its own ICE Combat Suits to take over Liberty.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/ESWAT - City Under Siege-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20171205T060721</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Mania Daiginjou.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Mania - Dai Gin Jou</name>
		<desc>Battle Mania Dai Gin Jou (バトルマニア大吟醸), sometimes referred to as Battle Mania Daiginjou and Battle Mania 2, is a shoot-'em-up developed and published by VIC Tokai in 1993 for the Sega Mega Drive exclusively in Japan and South Korea. It is the sequel to Battle Mania (which was released in the US as Trouble Shooter). The ROM header's International Title field calls the game Trouble Shooter Vintage; this may have been in the intended name had the game been released overseas, and is another name the game is commonly referred to as. Translation group M.I.J.E.T. translated the game's dialogue text to English and included it with their Tougi Ou King Colossus patch as an extra before releasing it separately later.

A group calling itself the Kikokukyou have resurrected the leader of Blackball, the antagonist group of the original game, and the Trouble Shooters are called to stop Blackball and destroy Kikokukyou.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Battle Mania Daiginjou-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19931224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VIC Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>VIC Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blades of Vengeance.zip</path>
		<name>Blades Of Vengeance</name>
		<desc>Blades of Vengeance is a platform game that was developed by Beam Software and published by Electronic Arts for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis. In this game, one or two players can select one of three fantasy warriors to fight through a large range of platform levels in order to defeat the forces of darkness.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Blades of Vengeance-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Caliber .50.zip</path>
		<name>Caliber.50</name>
		<desc>Caliber.50 is a top-down run and gun video game originally released in arcades (as Cal.50) before being brought to the Sega Mega Drive in 1991. The Mega Drive version was only released in North America.
The Mega Drive version is severely watered down from the arcade original, not just in terms of graphics and sound, but also gameplay, as the controls need to be mapped to three buttons. This means unlike the arcade original B takes the roll of shooting and throwing grenades, A rotates left and C rotates right. The arcade cabinet used special joysticks which could be spun around to rotate the player. To compenstate, there are fewer enemies on screen, and the player is given a life bar.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Caliber .50-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Mentrix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dahna - Goddess Birth.zip</path>
		<name>Dahna Megami Tanjou</name>
		<desc>Dahna: Megami Tanjō (Dahna 女神誕生, Dahna: Goddess' Birth) is a 1991 platform action game developed by and published by IGS for the Mega Drive exclusively in Japan and South Korea. Player controls the title character who struggles against the powers of an evil sorceress raiding her village. The story is told through cut scenes and Dahna was helped along the way by various mythical beasts.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Dahna - Goddess Birth-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>IGS</developer>
		<publisher>IGS</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demolition Man.zip</path>
		<name>Demolition Man</name>
		<desc>Finally! The power of 3DO. The action of a hit movie. The challenge of a video game. But deeper. And better. Because this time, you control the outcome of a real movie. With real stars Sylvester Stallone and Wesley Snipes, real suspense and real challenges that demand real skill. Actually control cinematic-quality live action footage of Stallone as the Demolition Man in a game that merges movie and video footage so smoothly you'll feel plunged into the movie itself. Contains never-before-seen footage of Stallone and Snipes filmed especially for this interactive adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Demolition Man-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Alexandria</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./El Viento.zip</path>
		<name>El Viento</name>
		<desc>El Viento (エル・ヴィエント Eru Viento?, derived from Spanish meaning "The Wind") is a 2D platform video game released by Wolf Team and published by Renovation Products for the Sega Mega Drive/Sega Genesis game console in 1991. It is the second in a trilogy of games, which include Earnest Evans and Anett Futatabi.
The game possesses many references to H. P. Lovecraft's esteemed Cthulhu Mythos.
The game shares the same fictional universe with Earnest Evans, and happens several years later.

New York City, 1928. A mad religious leader known as Henry seeks to awaken the ancient and malevolent god Hastur. A sorceress named Restiana offers herself to Henry as a sacrifice for a cause which will bring the inevitable down fall of mankind.

There are some people that have descended from Hastur's ancient bloodline, one of which is the young Peruvian sorceress, Annet Myer. With some assistance from Earnest Evans, Annet attempts to stop the cult from resurrecting Hastur using the very spells of this bloodline.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/El Viento-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wolf Team</developer>
		<publisher>Wolf Team</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gargoyles.zip</path>
		<name>Gargoyles</name>
		<desc>Gargoyles is a traditional 2-D side-scrolling action game based on the mid-90's cartoon of the same name.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Gargoyles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Buena Vista Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./High Seas Havoc.zip</path>
		<name>Havoc</name>
		<desc>The story is about an anthropomorphic pirate seal named Havoc (Lang in the Japanese version), his young sidekick Tide (Land in the Japanese version), a girl named Bridget, and an evil pirate named Bernardo.  Bernardo is looking for Emeralda, a gem with powers that can cause whole armies to be toppled. A map shows where Emeralda is located, and Bernardo is looking for the map. Havoc and Tide discover Bridget unconscious at a beach. When she wakes up in a dwelling, she instructs Havoc to keep her and the map safe. Havoc hides the map in a cliff. After Bernardo's henchmen kidnaps Bridget and Tide; Havoc, the playable character, sets off to rescue them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/High Seas Havoc-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./It Came from the Desert.zip</path>
		<name>It Came from the Desert</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/It Came from the Desert-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>This game can be played in two modes, either as Dr. Alan Grant or as a Velociraptor. Playing as each provides the user with an alternative story and level design. The climax of the game mirrored the unused climax of the film, in which Grant must defeat a pair of Velociraptors by causing the Tyrannosaurus rex skeleton in the Visitors Center to collapse on top of them. Grant himself is the final boss in the same location for the raptor storyline: your dinosaur character must cause the bone structure to collapse via specifically placed kicks to cause Grant to flee. A sequel was released using a new game engine and new artwork (with some of the original art as well), entitled Jurassic Park: Rampage Edition. In it, Grant's helicopter (that he just escaped on in the first game) crashes. Now he must deal not only with dinosaurs, but InGen as well. A new raptor must also make it off the island.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel Land.zip</path>
		<name>Marvel Land</name>
		<desc>n the land of Coni, its inhabitants lived in harmony. At its center lies a mountain called "Peace", in which an amusement park known as "Marvel Land" resides. This park is well-protected by the Fairies. Later, King Mole became rule of the under dwellers and sent his minions to take over Marvel Land, imprisoning the Fairies inside crystal balls.

A young lad named Talmit is called upon to rescue Wondra the princess, and free the Fairies from King Mole. Marvel Land consists of five worlds with seven stages each, and the game plays in platform style, in which you need to run through the level, killing enemies, and find the exit door. More often than not, you have to go through a bullseye to reach it. If you hit the bullseye at its center, you are awarded more points than you do by hitting it above or below.

You kill enemies by either jumping on their heads or attacking them with clones, which trail your movement unless you use them to attack enemies or collect food. The clones have a limited life and disappear one by one as you use them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Marvel Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Limited</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panorama Cotton.zip</path>
		<name>Panorama Cotton</name>
		<desc>Panorama Cotton (パノラマコットン) is a 1994 shoot-'em-up for the Sega Mega Drive developed by Success and published by Sunsoft exclusively in Japan. It is the third game in the Cotton series of so-called "cute-'em-ups" for their unique visual style, and diverts from the gameplay of other Cotton titles. The release packaging included a promotional tea cup, which is now quite rare. Its method of gameplay would be reprised for the Dreamcast Rainbow Cotton.

Willows are special types of candies in a world of witches and fairies. Fairy Queen Velvet starts saying things that don't make sense, and the fairy Silk realizes it is because of monsters who are burning Willows (a burnt one was found near the castle garden). The witch Cotton, who loves eating Willows, conveniently shows up, learns of this, and vows revenge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Panorama Cotton-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940812T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ranger-X.zip</path>
		<name>Ranger X</name>
		<desc>The player assumes the role of Ranger X, piloting a powered exoskeleton who leads the fight back for his home planet against the invading Rahuna forces. Ranger X is equipped with a jet pack and an assortment of weapons. The jet pack allows for short periods of flight, the duration of which is limited by the jet pack's temperature. Upon overheating, the player must land and wait for cool down. Alongside Ranger X's standard pulse rifle, the player has access to various special weapons including a flamethrower and homing attacks. Unlike the pulse rifle, the special weapons drain a power bar, which can only be recharged when Ranger X is in a bright light source. This special arsenal can be increased by collecting power ups scattered across the levels. On certain levels, the player may also control a supporting vehicle - an Ex-Up, such as Indra - a futuristic motorcycle, a premise described as "RoboCop on a Harley".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Ranger-X-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GAU Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RoboCop Versus The Terminator.zip</path>
		<name>Robocop vs. the Terminator</name>
		<desc>Set a few years after RoboCop's invention, the story involves SAC-NORAD contracting Cyberdyne Systems on building Skynet. Cyberdyne used RoboCop's technology in creating Skynet. When activated, Skynet becomes self-aware and launches a war against mankind. In the future, Skynet sends several Terminators back to the past to cripple the Resistance. After destroying one of the Terminators, RoboCop proceeds to Delta City, where he confronts RoboCain.

After RoboCain was destroyed, RoboCop battles his way to the OCP building, where he defeats all the Terminators. After defeating an ED-209 unit reprogrammed by the Terminators, RoboCop plugs himself into a console. Unknown to him, RoboCop gave Skynet information it can use. This ends up with RoboCop falling into a trap. In the future, RoboCop assembles himself, where he battled in the Terminator-infested future and destroyed Skynet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/RoboCop Versus The Terminator-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940519T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rolling Thunder 3.zip</path>
		<name>Rolling Thunder 3</name>
		<desc>The events in the third game in the series are synchronous with RT2. At the end of the twentieth century, satellites around the globe are being shot down, disrupting communications. Secret agency Rolling Thunder discovers the organization behind the terror: Geldra. While agents Leila and Albatross are fighting the leader Gimdo (RT2), agent Jay is instructed to bring down Dread, the second-in-command.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Rolling Thunder 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Second Samurai.zip</path>
		<name>Second Samurai</name>
		<desc>The Second Samurai is a beat-em-up developed by Vivid Image and Psygnosis and released exclusively in Europe for the Commodore Amiga (1993) and Sega Mega Drive (1994). It is the sequel to The First Samurai, a beat-em-up released for various home computers and the SNES internationally a few years prior.

You play as one of two Samurais (the 1-player mode has the male protagonist from The First Samurai only; the 2-player mode lets the second player control a new female Samurai). A and B both attack depending on what weapon you have equipped right now (only one at a time, some in limited quantities), what enemies/objects are nearby, and which D-pad buttons you are holding at the time. C jumps. A screen at the beginning of the game (also accessible from the Options menu) shows you what each in-game item does for you.

A Sega Mega-CD port was advertised, but never released.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Second Samurai-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<developer>Vivid</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Dancer - The Secret of Shinobi.zip</path>
		<name>Shadow Dancer: The Secret of Shinobi</name>
		<desc>The gameplay remains basically unchanged from the Shadow Dancer coin-op game, the Mega Drive features all new stages and bosses, and a slightly different objective: instead of looking for time bombs, the player must now rescue hostages scattered around each stage before facing the boss. The bonus rounds were also changed from a first-person minigame to one in which the player must shoot down ninjas below them while skydiving from a building.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Shadow Dancer - The Secret of Shinobi-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skeleton Krew.zip</path>
		<name>Skeleton Krew</name>
		<desc>Wanna pack a BIG GUN with enough ammo to level a city? You got it...! Wanna massakre seriously psykotic Psykogenix mutants and get paid? You got it...!
Wanna blast your way through the savage secret zones, deadly Krewtraps, mad n' bad buildings and hideous end-of-level Psykos comprising 6 HUMUNGOUS levels of 3D isometrik karnage - and wear a spectacularly sexy, hyper-hi-tek, Big Ordanance Neutralising Exo-skeleton, to boot?
Well you got it all - but only if you join Spine, Joint and Rib, otherwise known as the SKELETON KREW, in their first outRAGEous blastfest!!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Skeleton Krew-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 2.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog 2</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Sonic the Hedgehog 2 builds upon the basic set-up of the original Sonic the Hedgehog game. The player finishes each level, generally moving from left to right, within a time limit of 10 minutes.  Along the way, rings are collected and Badniks are defeated. Star posts serve as checkpoints, where if the player was to lose a life then he or she would return to one.  When the player has collected at least 50 rings, star posts can be run past for an optional Special Stage.  At the end of the last act of each zone (with the exception of Sky Chase Zone which does not have a boss), Sonic confronts Dr. Robotnik.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sonic The Hedgehog 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Splatterhouse 3.zip</path>
		<name>Splatterhouse 3</name>
		<desc>Splatterhouse 3 is a video game released by Namco for the Mega Drive/Genesis in 1993. It is the sequel to Splatterhouse 2 and was one of the first games to be given a rating by Sega's own Videogame Rating Council.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Splatterhouse 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sub-Terrania.zip</path>
		<name>Sub Terrania</name>
		<desc>Some rather aggressive aliens have invaded the underground depths of the Earth, and you're just the subterranean fighter pilot to get rid of them. Fly through the darkest caverns in search of the terrifying enemies in this detailed trip below the surface. You'll need quick reflexes and nerves of steel to get these critters out of the Earth's hair, and the gravitational pull towards the surface won't exactly help matters. If you can pick up some cleverly placed gear, you might just be able to transform your fighter into a submarine to get out to the ocean. Incredible graphics and a massive gaming experience make SUB TERRANIA the perfect sci-fi addition to your Mega Drive collection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Sub-Terrania-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zyrinx</developer>
		<publisher>Scavenger</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Galahad, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Galahad</name>
		<desc>The titular hero travels through this platform action game, slashing up mutant creatures with a sword and battling the evil Thanatos in hopes to save the life of Princess Lucanna.

The controls are fairly simple and include jumping, walking or attacking. Collect icons that will help in the enhancement of your armor, gain an extra life and coins to spend in the shop for new weapons. Be sure not to collect any skull icons or else it will call Thanatos' Ethereal Presence where you will have to use Rune Bombs to destroy it. After you complete one of the three worlds, you will be given a password so you can resume later after running out of lives.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Legend of Galahad, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park 2 - The Lost World.zip</path>
		<name>The Lost World Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>The player takes control of characters struggling to survive on INGen’s “Site B” populated by over 20 species of dinosaurs in an environment of escalating chaos. There are 5 characters in all to choose from, each with their own special abilities and attributes. While the game is in 3D, the game play resembles early 2D platformers in which you generically either go left or right, limiting the mobility of each character.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Jurassic Park 2 - The Lost World-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreamworks Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twinkle Tale.zip</path>
		<name>Twinkle Tale</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Twinkle Tale-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wonder Amusement Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Toyo Recording Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Undead Line.zip</path>
		<name>Undead Line</name>
		<desc>A forward-scrolling action game featuring medieval fantasy characters and enemies battling in gameplay somewhat like a shoot-em-up.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Undead Line-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>T&amp;E SOFT</developer>
		<publisher>PALSOFT</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis III.zip</path>
		<name>Valis III</name>
		<desc>King Glames leads denizens of the Dark World to destroy both Earth and Vecanti. Against this common foe, Yuko Asou finds help in her new girlfriend, a Vecanti warrior-maiden named Cham, who was born in the Dark World and uses a deadly whip, and her own sister Valna Asou, who grew up within Vecanti and became strong in the ways of magic. Furthermore, the Valis sword is shown to be capable of more than what Yuko has accomplished with it thus far.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Valis III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Telenet Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wardner.zip</path>
		<name>Wardner</name>
		<desc>The player controls a character by the name of Dover through various forest game levels battling creatures in an attempt to rescue his kidnapped girlfriend, Mia, from the evil Wardner. The simple run and jump controls are supplemented with the ability to throw balls of fire. The player collects gold coins throughout the game; at the end of each level, the coins are exchangeable for protective devices, and weapons.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Wardner-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Water Margin - Tales of Clouds &amp; Winds.zip</path>
		<name>Water Margin: A Tale of Clouds and Wind</name>
		<desc>Water Margin: A Tale of Clouds and Wind is a Sega Genesis Beat'em up which was exclusively available only in China, Taiwan and Hong Kong markets mostly, during the late 90's.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Water Margin - Tales of Clouds &amp; Winds-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Piko Interactive</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wings of Wor.zip</path>
		<name>Wings of Wor</name>
		<desc>Wings of Wor/Gynoug is a horror-themed shoot'em up similar to Thunder Force and other horizontal shooters. But other than most of them where you play a spaceship of some sort, here you play as Wor, a member of the so-called 'Flying men' who look quite similar to angels. The home planet of these people, Iccus, has been taken over by a virus that has mutated into a collection of quite horrible creatures, and every previous attempt to battle them has failed. So now it is Wor's turn to save his home planet and destroy these mutants once and for all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Wings of Wor-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse &amp; Donald Duck.zip</path>
		<name>World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck</name>
		<desc>Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck are sucked into a magical world, while preparing for a magic act. Now they must survive over a dozen different side-scrolling levels, in order to return home.

Mickey and Donald can run, jump, or attack by flourishing their capes. Enemies defeated in this way turn into doves, cards, or other harmless objects depending on the enemy. After defeating the boss of each level, a new magic spell is learned, allowing the pair to traverse the next level; i.e. flying on a magic carpet or going underwater in an air bubble. This was one of the few Genesis games to feature voice samples.
The gameplay changes depending on if the player selects Mickey or Donald, in a one player mode, or if two people want to control both characters at once. For instance, Mickey can squeeze through certain gaps, while Donald must find a different route; if both are playing, Mickey can pull Donald through the gap. Either can stand on the others' shoulders to ascend higher, and lower a rope to pull the other up.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse &amp; Donald Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fix It Felix Jr.zip</path>
		<name>Fix It Felix Jr.</name>
		<desc>In the quarter-muncher Fix-It Felix Jr., the thick-headed thug Wreck-It Ralph tries to destroy a building while the daring do-gooder Fix-It Felix repairs the damage with his magic hammer.

This "arcade" game is the basis of the Disney animated movie Wreck-It Ralph. In the film, Ralph is the bad guy, but that doesn't mean he is a "bad" guy, -- it's just his job to be a heartless demolisher so that Felix can save the day. But countless games where Ralph has played the villain has taken its toll, and after becoming the outcast of his mostly-wrecked town, Ralph is ready to look for more out of his pixelated life.

Fix-It Felix Jr. is seen in the movie Wreck-It Ralph, and Disney has produced promotional display cabinets as part of the marketing of the film. Whether this arcade game itself will be released for the public to play is unknown at this time; a web version of the game is playable courtesy of Disney.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/megadrive/Fix It Felix Jr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Airwalk Studios</developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20171223T063444</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
