<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
      <game id="2610" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Alien Soldier.zip</path>
          <name>Alien Soldier</name>
          <desc>Alien Soldier is a side-scrolling action game in which the player takes the role of Epsilon-Eagle, the former leader of the Scarlet mutant group. The mutants are now lead by the evil Xi-Tiger who had turned them to terrorism, and one of their goals is to kill Epsilon-Eagle...&#xA;&#xA;At the start of the game the player chooses four out of six weapons - each with special advantages or disadvantages against certain enemies. As mutant Epsilon-Eagle also has other special powers, e.g. teleporting across the screen or (with full health) morphing into a powerful phoenix destroying everything in his way.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Alien Soldier-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure Co</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="9415" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The.zip</path>
          <name>The Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin</name>
          <desc>From the award winning animated TV series comes the most action-packed Batman adventure yet! The Dark Knight returns with Robin to battle the forces of evil. But wait... the iceman cometh!!! Mr. Freeze is about to unleash his super-powered ice cannon and has teamed up with the most notorious criminals to help him turn Gotham City into a diabolical winter wonderland!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19950210T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Clockwork Tortoise</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="157" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Aladdin.zip</path>
          <name>Disney&#39;s Aladdin</name>
          <desc>Hang on to your carpet for ACTION and FUN! Aladdin slashes his shining scimitar to fight through Agrabah, escape the Sultan&#39;s dungeon, survive the fiery Cave of Wonders, snatch the Genie&#39;s Lamp and save Princess Jasmine from the evil Jafar! All-new technology creates animation so smooth, it&#39;s like watching a real animated film. Aladdin battles thieves and desert warriors, and barely dodges danger on his high-speed carpet. Survive Jafar&#39;s troops for a dash through special bonus rounds. Hilarious! Palace Guards drop their drawers and camels spit dirt wads. Aladdin ping-pongs like a pinball INSIDE the Genie&#39;s Lamp!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Aladdin-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19931126T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Disney Interactive Studios</developer>
          <publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4243" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Alisia Dragoon.zip</path>
          <name>Alisia Dragoon</name>
          <desc>The pace is intense. Enemies come at Alisia from everywhere. And nowhere. Battle hordes of crazed barbarians, mow down mobs of poisonous centipedes, and slay squadrons of winged gargoyels. Blast enemies in waves or one by one with multi-directional, auto-targeting laser fire.&#xA;&#xA;Recruit killer companions like the DragonFrye, Ball O&#39;Fire, Thunder Raven and Boomerang Lizard. Use them to hurl blistering boomerangs, fireballs, and electrical attacks. With Alisia&#39;s super-tough fighting skills, fry enemies to a crisp. And prove once and for all that you can go hand-to-hand with evil and come out the champion!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Alisia Dragoon-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate>19920423T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Gainax Network Systems</developer>
          <publisher>Game Arts</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="736" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Battletoads.zip</path>
          <name>Battletoads</name>
          <desc>After her defeat by the Galactic Corporation at the battle of Canis Major, the evil Dark Queen and her renegade space troops retreat to the outer reaches of the universe, hiding out in dark spaces between the stars. Meanwhile, on board the spaceship Vulture, Professor T. Bird and the trio of Battletoads - Rash, Zitz and Pimple - are escorting the Princess Angelica back to her home planet, where her father, the Terran Emperor, awaits her safe arrival. Along the way, Pimple, the biggest Battletoad, takes Angelica out for a cruise in the Toadster to a nearby Leisure Station, but the Dark Queen ambushes them before they can get there, and they are kidnapped and carried away to Ragnarok&#39;s World, the Dark Queen&#39;s planet. Professor Bird sends remaining Battletoads down on Ragnarok to save Pimple and Angelica, but it will be a hard battle against planet&#39;s dangerous environments, traps and Dark Queen&#39;s troops. They have to go a long way from the planet&#39;s rough surface to deep caves and landed Gargantua and ultimately to the Tower of Shadows, where the Dark Queen awaits.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Battletoads-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>1</rating>
          <releasedate>19910114T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Rare</developer>
          <publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="3872" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Beyond Oasis.zip</path>
          <name>Beyond Oasis</name>
          <desc>On the mystical island of Oasis, Prince Ali embarks on a crusade against evil. The warrior prince must unleash the powers of the four Wild Spirits to stop the resurrection of a ruthless sorcerer and save the empire! As Ali, you can call on the powers of the four wild spirits to battle the evil minions of Agito. Fight off enemies with Ali&#39;s weapons, punches and kicks... or dig deeper to discover the Hidden Super Moves...a Sega first! Flip switches, trigger plates, and use what&#39;s left of your brain to solve mind-boggling puzzles that lead to Huge Bosses... like the Fire-breathing Red Dragon!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Beyond Oasis-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19941208T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Ancient</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="115" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
          <name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
          <desc>The search is on! Mickey is on the trail of a wicked Witch named Mizrabel, who has kidnapped Minnie. Mickey must find seven gems hidden in the fantastic chambers of Mizrabel&#39;s Castle of Illusion and use them to save Minnie. Can Mickey find them? It&#39;s up to you.&#xA;&#xA;Be on your guard! Behind every door lurks an enchanted land of beauty and danger. You must defeat angry chess knights, overcome the evil haunted trees, and do battle with ghoulish ghosts and a deadly dragon. No place is safe -- even the library is fraught with danger. Playing three levels in the practice mode will prepare you for the challenge you will face. Then, just when you think you&#39;ve mastered the Illusions, you come face to face with the most dangerous of them all -- Witch Mizrabel!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6599999999999999</rating>
          <releasedate>19901122T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sega</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2619" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Castlevania - Bloodlines.zip</path>
          <name>Castlevania: Bloodlines</name>
          <desc>Time refuses to forget the Belmont family&#39;s horrifying, bloody destiny. And in 1917 two of its descendants are summoned by fate into epic battle. Their enemy? The most evil incarnation of Castlevania legacy to ever rise from the grave, the vampiress Countess Bartley. This spine-tingling, 6-stage fear-fest overflows with graphic sights and sounds from your worst nightmares. As John Morris, the whip wielding vampire hunter, or Eric Lecarde, master lanceman, you&#39;ll pursue the demonic Countess all across Europe before she resurrects Dracula for a final reign of global terror. Alas, her trail of doom is laden with zombies, hideous mutants, grotesque giants, ghouls and ghastly creatures. Taste the sweat dripping into your mouth as you try rescuing yourself from diabolical traps. Feel the torturous strain on every muscle as you wield again and again sacred weapon power-ups such as Holy Water, the Battle Axe, the Crystal Blade Boomerang and the Mirror of Truth. But in the end, make sure you&#39;ve saved enough strength to scream!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Castlevania - Bloodlines-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.75</rating>
          <releasedate>19940317T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="3897" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Crusader of Centy.zip</path>
          <name>Crusader of Centy</name>
          <desc>Millions of years ago, heinous creatures that lurked in the shadows and darkness that blanketed the planet inhabited the Earth. When light finally broke through, only a few beasts were able to survive by burrowing into deep caverns. Over time, they multiplied, evolved, and patiently waited for the right time to emerge and rule the Earth once again. You are Corona, and you&#39;ve just celebrated your 14th birthday. By law of the king, you must now go seek out these creatures of the dark and destroy them. As you travel in search of your destiny, you&#39;ll make animal allies that will prove invaluable on your quest. Each level will offer mind-bending puzzles and challenges that will help you get one step closer to completing your mission.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Crusader of Centy-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19940616T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nextech</developer>
          <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="3876" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Blaster Master 2.zip</path>
          <name>Blaster Master 2</name>
          <desc>It has been four years since Jason&#39;s Encounter with the Plutonium Boss and the radioactive mutants under the Earth. His only reminder of the incident is S.O.P.H.I.A., the vehicle he used to stop them, which he has hidden in an abandoned barn. One day, one bolt of lightning struck the house and caused the ceiling to crumble, knocking Jason unconscious. When Jason woke up, S.O.P.H.I.A. was in pieces and the parts he had collected from his first dealings with the Mutant Bosses were missing. Little does Jason know that there are more lightning beings where the first one came from and they are planning to destroy the Earth. The beings started digging towards the Earth&#39;s core in order to shift the planet&#39;s weight off its axis, leading to total annihilation. The parts from S.O.P.H.I.A. are being used to create a robotic army to assist the being in accomplishing their mission. Now, Jason must stop them, but he won&#39;t make it without the help of S.O.P.H.I.A. Since he can&#39;t recover the parts, he decided to redesign it to better prepare himself for the ordeal facing him. After 29 days, S.O.P.H.I.A. was completely rebuilt and ready for battle. Remembering where he saw the being&#39;s footsteps, Jason jumped in his vehicle and headed towards the mountains where the challenge begins.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Blaster Master 2-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19930616T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Software Creations</developer>
          <publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4351" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Dynamite Headdy.zip</path>
          <name>Dynamite Headdy</name>
          <desc>Hot-headed Headdy gets into some real head-banging to thwart the Dark Demon&#39;s devious deeds. This wacky headcase is up to his neck in surprises! Switch heads to match the job! Over 15 heads to choose from! Bash heavy objects with Slammer Head! Suck up foes with Vacuum Head! Stick it to your enemies with Spike Head! Headdy&#39;s spring-loaded head gets him where he&#39;s gotta go! Use it to swing over ledges, grab onto objects and shoot hoops in the basketball bonus round. Use your head to whiz through a radical variety of play! Action, shooting and strategy speed you on to a surprise ending!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Dynamite Headdy-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19940804T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4666" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Flintstones, The.zip</path>
          <name>The Flintstones</name>
          <desc>It&#39;s the weekend and Fred Flintstone returns home from work very excited about the Bedrock Super Bowl final tonight. As he arrives home Wilma reminds him of his promise to paint the living room before her mother arrives on Sunday. Wilma insists that Fred can only go bowling if he paints the living room. Reluctantly, Fred agrees, but he doesn&#39;t bargain for baby-sitting Pebbles and painting at the same time. Chaos, fun and the Flintstones humor is everywhere!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Flintstones, The-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19931022T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Taito Corporation</developer>
          <publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="1936" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Contra - Hard Corps.zip</path>
          <name>Contra: Hard Corps</name>
          <desc>Kickin&#39; cyborg butt... That&#39;s what it&#39;s all about, dude. Jack into this game of genetic engineering gone bad. Real bad. It&#39;s five years after the mother of all wars ended - and things still aren&#39;t right. Your job is to fix it. The ever-popular Contra series makes its Sega Genesis debut with a pulse-pounding new storyline. At 16 megs, HARD CORPS pushes the technology to bring you over ten gut-wrenching levels with huge boss characters, great graphics and dynamic sound. Find high powered weapons such as the homing gun, crush gun, needle laser or mine setter. Do you think you can handle it? Trust me, you can&#39;t. You still here? Okay, then get ready for the fight of your life. Pick one of the four heroes and begin your search across many dark levels of doom. The ending changes, depending on the paths you choose - but every pass crosses boss characters that will blow you away. Literally!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Contra - Hard Corps-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19940914T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="540" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Landstalker.zip</path>
          <name>Landstalker</name>
          <desc>Eons ago, evil King Nole tyrannized the mythical island of Melcatle. With an insatiable greed for power and wealth, he crushed the people with heavy taxes while destroying their freedom. At last, in fury, the enslaved citizens stormed the palace. But King Nole was gone! And with him, the vast treasure, stolen from his subjects!&#xA;&#xA;Now Nigel, the Landstalker, journeys to this fantastic realm in search of the legendary fortune and power to reunite a divided kingdom!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Landstalker-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.56667</rating>
          <releasedate>19921029T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Climax Entertainment</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="542" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters.zip</path>
          <name>Lethal Enforcers II: Gunfighters</name>
          <desc>You are the sheriff of a town set in the old Wild West. Using the control pad or Konami&#39;s own Justifier lightgun, you&#39;ll be taking out outlaws who are robbing banks and kidnapping innocents. You have the opportunity to upgrade and keep you gun, as long as you don&#39;t shoot the people you are trying to save.&#xA;&#xA;The action is usually shown on a single screen with enemies &#34;popping out&#34; from various sections. If you do not shoot them in time they will either shoot or throw various weapons at you. You will lose energy if they hit you or you hit an innocent civilian.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Lethal Enforcers II - Gun Fighters-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="4462" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./James Pond II - Codename Robocod.zip</path>
          <name>James Pond 2: Codename RoboCod</name>
          <desc>To: James Pond... For your fish eyes only! &#xA;&#xA;Pond, the fiendish Dr. Maybe is back. His bombs are ticking in the North Pole toy factories. No human crime fighter has been able to defeat him. So F.I.S.H. (Finned Investigators of Shady Humans) has designed a special Robosuit for your survival on land. Pond, go to it! Remember, Dr. Maybe has a screw loose, so stay on your fins!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/James Pond II - Codename Robocod-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>VectorDean</developer>
          <publisher>Millennium Interactive Ltd.</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="138" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Gunstar Heroes.zip</path>
          <name>Gunstar Heroes</name>
          <desc>Gunstar Heroes is a side scrolling shooter. The player has four weapons to choose from, and they can be combined in various pairs to create a total of 14 unique weapons. In addition to the weapons, the player can engage enemies in close quarters combat. It is possible to grab and toss enemies, perform sliding and jumping attacks and a long-range skid.&#xA;&#xA;Unlike most games in the genre, the player has a life total calculated in numbers. Death to a player requires multiple hits but just one death will issue the option to continue from the start of the level or to end the game. Players have unlimited continues.&#xA;&#xA;The main highlight of the game are its boss encounters, which often feature large enemies made up of multiple sprites allowing for fluid movement.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Gunstar Heroes-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.45</rating>
          <releasedate>19930909T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Treasure</developer>
          <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4485" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Lethal Enforcers MD.zip</path>
          <name>Lethal Enforcers</name>
          <desc>Pick up your pistol and be the cop you need to be in order to rid the streets of the criminals out to make your day hell. Aim wisely and quickly, otherwise your lives will be lost quickly in this 1st person arcade shooter, cleaning up the streets. The higher the difficulty level, the more crimes there will be to eliminate, but watch out for the other weapons that can help you along the way.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Lethal Enforcers MD-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19930725T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Shooter</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="4489" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor.zip</path>
          <name>MUSHA: Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor</name>
          <desc>A spin-off from the successful Aleste series by Compile, Musha Aleste takes the same top-down shooter mechanics of it&#39;s predecessors but stages the action in a bizarre universe that merges traditional Japanese lore with sci-fi mecha action.&#xA;&#xA;Instead of commanding a ship, you will actually step into the cockpit of a ninja-styled mecha as you fight through the many levels in the game, with several option satellites that can be configured to use different formations.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/MUSHA - Metallic Uniframe Super Hybrid Armor-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Compile</developer>
          <publisher>Seismic Software Inc.</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="2281" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Megaman - The Wily Wars.zip</path>
          <name>Mega Man: The Wily Wars</name>
          <desc>In the last few years, a titanic struggle for control of the planet has raged. Each time it has pitted Mega Man, a cybernetic champion of justice against the villainous Dr. Wily and his renegade robots. And each time, Mega Man has emerged victorious! Now, in a desperate attempt to change the past, Dr. Wily has used a time machine to slip back to the time of his first battles with Mega Man. There he plans to make sure that this time, Mega Man will be history!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Megaman - The Wily Wars-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19941021T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Capcom</developer>
          <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2217" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Mega Turrican.zip</path>
          <name>Mega Turrican</name>
          <desc>After many generations of peace, the Dark Forces have assembled again, and as a member of the USS Freedom Forces, it is your job to defeat them once again. This means you will have to complete numerous large levels always searching for secrets to pick up and enemies to shoot. To do this, you can pick up three different, upgradeable shots: a multiple, a laser and a rebound. You can also go into wheel-mode (as long as you have enough special energy) or use a rope. In wheel-mode, you are invincible and can lay mines or explore previously unreachable areas.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Mega Turrican-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19941005T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Data East</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="127" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Phantasy Star IV.zip</path>
          <name>Phantasy Star IV: The End of the Millennium</name>
          <desc>Launch into the biggest RPG ever on Genesis! This is the explosive magic-and-monster packed FINALE to the incredible Phantasy Star saga. An ancient, hideous Dark Force stalks the Algol star system. You, a young hunter, are destined to become Motavia&#39;s greatest warrior and strike the death-blow that destroys evil FOREVER!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Phantasy Star IV-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6</rating>
          <releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sega</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4105" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
          <name>Prince of Persia</name>
          <desc>The Grand Vizier Jaffar has thrown you into a dark dungeon and plans to marry the girl of your dreams in an hour. You&#39;re not going to let that happen are you? Try to escape from the dungeon, take out Jaffar&#39;s guards, find your way through the Sultan&#39;s palace and defeat Jaffar himself. Now go, you&#39;ve got 60 minutes!&#xA;&#xA;Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer with run and jump gameplay. Your hero must avoid deadly traps, solve some simple puzzles and engage in sword fights with the guards. The player has an infinite amount of lives, but has to restart at the beginning of a level each time he dies, and must complete the game within an hour. An especially noteworthy aspect of the game is the very fluent animation of your character.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Brøderbund Software</developer>
          <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="24135" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame.zip</path>
          <name>Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame</name>
          <desc>Prince of Persia 2: The Shadow and the Flame is the sequel to the 1989 hit Prince of Persia. Released for DOS computers in 1993, ports were made to the Apple Macintosh in 1994 and the Super Nintendo in 1995. It was followed by Prince of Persia 3D, which saw a release on the Sega Dreamcast and Windows PCs in 1999. Prince of Persia 2 is more action packed than its predecessor, focusing less on dungeon mazes and more on fighting and puzzle solving.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Prince of Persia 2 - The Shadow and the Flame-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.5</rating>
          <releasedate></releasedate>
          <developer>Brøderbund Software, Microïds</developer>
          <publisher>Brøderbund Software, Psygnosis</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="20347" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Pier Solar and the Great Architects.zip</path>
          <name>Pier Solar and the Great Architects</name>
          <desc>Pier Solar and the Great Architects is an independently developed Sega Mega Drive game, released worldwide in December 2010 by WaterMelon, a group of developers from the Mega Drive homebrew and research scene. It is a turn-based RPG, and, at 8 megabytes (64 megabits) in size means it is currently the second largest Sega Mega Drive game available. It is the first internationally commercially released Mega Drive game since 2002&#39;s Mega Games 10 (not counting Super Fighter Team&#39;s releases, which have all been translations of games released in the 1990s).&#xA;&#xA;The game ships for $35 USD and has a clamshell case with a choice of three cover arts which resemble those used by Sega in Japan, North America and Europe towards the end of the Mega Drive&#39;s lifespan. Also included is a 24-page full colour instruction manual and a &#34;MEGA Soundtrack Booster CD&#34;, containing the game&#39;s soundtrack, which, if the player has a Sega Mega-CD attached, can be used as an alternate source of the game&#39;s music during gameplay (however it is not a standalone Mega CD game). 500 &#34;Posterity Packs&#34; were also sold, with buyers receiving their names in the game&#39;s credits and instruction booklet.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Pier Solar and the Great Architects-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>1</rating>
          <releasedate>20101214T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>WaterMelom</developer>
          <publisher>WaterMelon</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4581" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./QuackShot Starring Donald Duck.zip</path>
          <name>Quackshot: Starring Donald Duck</name>
          <desc>Donald unearths an ancient scroll that reveals a long-lost treasure. Off he dashes on a dangerous expedition! He leaps over cacti, sidesteps scorpions, and slides down slopes to claim the loot before Big Bad Pete can get it. Donald&#39;s temperamental tantrums keep the bad guys runnin&#39;! He thonks &#39;em with his plunger and bounces on the handle to hop over their heads. Then he blasts &#39;em with gooey bubblegum! Yuck-a-duck! Donald creeps through the evil Count&#39;s castle, and plumbs the depths of Aztec ruins. With Huey, Dewey, and Louie&#39;s help, he&#39;ll find the key to unlock the secret of the most fabulous treasure on earth!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/QuackShot Starring Donald Duck-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19911219T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sega</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="24025" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Pulseman.zip</path>
          <name>Pulseman</name>
          <desc>Pulseman (パルスマン) (originally known as Spark) is a platform game for the Sega Mega Drive. It was only released on cartridge for a Japanese audience, but was available to North American consumers via the Sega Channel. The game was not sold in Europe.&#xA;&#xA;It was developed by Game Freak, the development team that would later go on to produce the Pokémon series of games for Nintendo. Many of Pulseman&#39;s staff, including director Ken Sugimori and composer Junichi Masuda worked on both games.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Pulseman-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Game Freak</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="2269" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ristar.zip</path>
          <name>Ristar</name>
          <desc>Ristar, the son of a legendary hero who&#39;s been captured, is the solar system&#39;s last hope against the evil space pirate Greedy. Ristar must travel to the 7 planets of his home system to restore peace to their once happy worlds and ultimately free his father. Ristar stretches his long elastic arms to grab enemies and head-butt them! His long limbs help him climb up walls or swing out of danger. Discover totally different worlds and new creatures on each planet! Battle strange beings who aren&#39;t always what they seem! Shoot through a variety of gameplay! Action, puzzle and strategy combine to challenge Ristar at every turn.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Ristar-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.76</rating>
          <releasedate>19950217T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="685" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Rocket Knight Adventures.zip</path>
          <name>Rocket Knight Adventures</name>
          <desc>He&#39;s courageous! He&#39;s clever! He&#39;s one good lookin&#39; opossum. It&#39;s Sparkster the Rocket Knight, the heroic jet pack jockey with warp speed, quick wits and pumped up personality. After all, who else do you know can get a grip with his tail? Rocket through 7 epic stages of animalistic adventure, home of the hugest, strangest enemy pig creatures imaginable. (In fact, your mission is crammed with more ham than a Hollywood premier.) Destroy the Emperor who&#39;s on a porcine power trip that will take him to the Key to the Pig Star. In every stage you&#39;ll be moving, flying and riding in a new direction to escape opossum punishment. You&#39;re the thrust-meister controlling Sparkster&#39;s jet pack and his assault sword. Confront mechanized menaces like the Giant Pigbot, the Drill Of A Lifetime, and the snappy Crab Rangoon. Things take a turn for the worst in the room of rotating gravity where Axle Gear, the Black Knights awaits you. And you&#39;ve never seen anything like the unreal mirrored lava pools where things will reflect badly on you. The tricks, the traps and challenges never end. But the world as you know it will if you don&#39;t grind those pigs for sausage.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Rocket Knight Adventures-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.45</rating>
          <releasedate>19930616T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="733" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Sonic &amp; Knuckles.zip</path>
          <name>Sonic &amp; Knuckles</name>
          <desc>Sonic and Knuckles join forces to defeat rotten Dr. Robotnik&#39;s Death Egg invasion! Play Sonic &amp; Knuckles by itself or Lock-on with other Sonic games. This game&#39;s revolutionary Lock-on technology adds all new features to your other Sonic games for ultimate replays! Play as Sonic and let loose on Robotnik with amazing new powers. Play as Knuckles and tackle Robotnik and Metal Sonic with bare-fisted attacks, high-speed glides and wall-climbing power! Lock-on with Sonic 3 and transform Floating Island into a huge 34 meg Sonic-epic loaded with new secrets! Play as Sonic, Knuckles, and even Tails - with Game Save! Lock-on with Sonic 2 and play as Knuckles with all his signature moves!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Sonic &amp; Knuckles-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.65</rating>
          <releasedate>19941018T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sega</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="691" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Sonic the Hedgehog 3.zip</path>
          <name>Sonic the Hedgehog 3</name>
          <desc>Swing from vines, launch new attacks, survive deadly traps and summon Tails to airlift Sonic out of danger. Discover hidden rooms and passageways in the mega-sized Zones. Transform into Super Sonic and experience the ultimate in speed and ultra-sonic power. Save your progress using the new Game Save Feature.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Sonic the Hedgehog 3-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
          <releasedate>19940202T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Adventure</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="8100" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Super Fantasy Zone.zip</path>
          <name>Super Fantasy Zone</name>
          <desc>The next-gen sequel to Fantasy Zone, Super Fantasy Zone starts as a strange gravitational force appears in the Menon planet, home of the evil Menon empire and thus a new threat looms over the Fantasy Zone.&#xA;&#xA;In a sudden strike by the Menon forces O-Papa, Opa-Opa&#39;s father, is fatally wounded. Thus Opa-Opa once again sets forth to destroy the Menon empire and avenge his father.&#xA;&#xA;EU release</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Super Fantasy Zone-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>SunSoft</developer>
          <publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="694" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Streets of Rage 2.zip</path>
          <name>Streets of Rage 2</name>
          <desc>Original rumblers Axel and Blaze slam the asphalt with bigger, better, totally devastating attacks! Skull-crushing ex-wrestler Max Thunder joins up with earth-shattering body slams and spinning fist attacks. New thrasher Skate slices punks with high speed in-line skate attacks and spinning jump kicks. Go maniac with jaw-shattering, bone-busting punches, head-cracking jump kicks and secret weapons. Gangs of dirt bikers dive into you from every side. Smash &#39;em with a pipe as they speed by. 16 gigantic megs of compound fractures! All new moves, and more of &#39;em! Bust knuckles with a friend in an all-new 2-player head-to-head mode!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Streets of Rage 2-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.45</rating>
          <releasedate>19921220T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sega</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
      <game id="114" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Sonic the Hedgehog.zip</path>
          <name>Sonic the Hedgehog</name>
          <desc>Super Speed! Bust the video game speed barrier wide open with Sonic the Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the super sonic spin attack. Loop the loop by defying gravity. Plummet down tunnels. Then dash to safety with Sonic&#39;s power sneakers. All at a frenzied pace. Super Graphics! Help Sonic escape bubbling molten lava. Swim through turbulent waterfalls. Scale glistening green mountains. And soar past shimmering city lights. There&#39;s even a 360 degree rotating maze. You&#39;ve never seen anything like it. Supper Attitude! Sonic has an attitude that just won&#39;t quit. He&#39;s flip and funny, yet tough as nails as he fights to free his friends from evil. So just wait. Sonic may be the world&#39;s next SUPER hero...</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Sonic the Hedgehog-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.72222</rating>
          <releasedate>19910623T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="729" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Wonder Boy in Monster World.zip</path>
          <name>Wonder Boy in Monster World</name>
          <desc>Townsfolk cower in fear as legions of deadly monsters invade the planet. Only Wonder Boy can fight smart enough - and tough enough - to wipe out the terrible beasts. Sleuth out secret clues to thwart the undead. Match wits against an evil force of otherwordly dimensions. And prove the awesome strength and courage of the amazing Wonder Boy!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Wonder Boy in Monster World-image.jpg</image>
          <rating>0.7</rating>
          <releasedate>19921204T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Westone</developer>
          <publisher>Sega</publisher>
          <genre>Platform</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
      <game id="4746" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./Ys III.zip</path>
          <name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
          <desc>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys breaks away from the &#34;bumping into enemies&#34; battle system of the first two games, allowing Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. Beside changing the battle system, the game&#39;s perspective switches to a side-scrolling view, as opposed to the top-down one of the previous games. Adol also has the ability to jump now. New to the series is the use of magical rings, which give Adol different powering-up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/Ys III-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
          <publisher>Renovation Products</publisher>
          <genre>Role-Playing</genre>
      </game>
      <game id="1971" source="theGamesDB.net">
          <path>./TMNT - The Hyperstone Heist.zip</path>
          <name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Hyperstone Heist</name>
          <desc>Shredder steals the powerful Hyperstone to shrink New York City and it&#39;s up to you to teach that treacherous troublemaker not to mess with the fearless foursome! Pick your favorite Cowabunga commando to slash through 5 lawless levels of lambasting. Four levels each have 3 intense stages and the other is packed with brand new challenges that will make you hurl your pizza lunch. Pulverize shrink-happy Shredder before he pockets our whole planet!</desc>
          <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/genesis/TMNT - The Hyperstone Heist-image.jpg</image>
          <releasedate>19921221T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Konami</developer>
          <publisher>Konami</publisher>
          <genre>Action</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
  </gameList>