<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game id="6704" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Castlevania Portrait of Ruin.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin</name>
		<desc>Celebrating 20 years of vampire hunting action, the legendary Castlevania series is back with an all-new action packed adventure. Take control of two heroes, Jonathan Morris, a vampire killer and his close friend Charlotte Orlean, a girl with tremendous magical ability. Amidst the chaos of World War II, two mysterious sisters emerge, working to resurrect Dracula and David and Charlotte are all that stand in their way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania Portrait of Ruin-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.625</rating>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6706" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Children of Mana.zip</path>
		<name>Children of Mana</name>
		<desc>This installment of the series takes place in the world of Fa'diel on the island of Illusia where, at the center of the island, stands the famous Tree of Mana. Several years ago, on the island of Illusia, an event known the "great disaster" took place at the base of the Mana Tree and many lives were lost. During this event, a brave young boy and girl used the Sword of Mana to save the world from disaster. Now, years later, a group of orphans sets out to investigate the details of the event that took so many loved ones away from them. The player must journey through the rest of Fa'diel's five continents of Jadd, Topple, Wendell, Ishe, and Lorimar to complete the game, traveling to the other continents by riding Flammie from place to place using the "Flammie Drum."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Children of Mana-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6702" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The team that developed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow returns to bring the sequel, CastleVania: Dawn of Sorrow, to the Nintendo DS. This time, you must infiltrate a castle belonging to a cult that is planning to resurrect Lord Dracula. Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow lets you defeat evil spirits using the "Magic Seal" system which utilizes the Nintendo DS touch screen. You can trade captured souls with other players using the wireless system as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.625</rating>
		<releasedate>20051004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="11217" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Contra 4.zip</path>
		<name>Contra 4</name>
		<desc>The action franchise that started it all is celebrating its 20th anniversary with an all-new adventure on Nintendo DS! Set after the events of Contra III: Alien Wars, the game follows mercenaries Bill Rizer and Lance Bean as they battle to save the world from a new extraterrestrial threat. Contra 4 takes advantage of the dual screens of the Nintendo DS to deliver larger than life action, with massive enemies, detailed platforming and mind-blowing set pieces.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Contra 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.625</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6794" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IV: Chapters of the Chosen</name>
		<desc>The Legends of Zenithia starts here!

A prestigious army captain, an adventurous princess, a humble merchant, two sisters, and you, the hero. Dive into this unique adventure, and discover the grand tale told through the experiences and emotions of characters from all walks of life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6789" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Dementium - The Ward.zip</path>
		<name>Dementium: The Ward</name>
		<desc>Dementium - The Ward is a mature-themed first-person shooter/survival horror game for the Nintendo DS that tells the tale of a man who awakens to find himself alone in a mysterious, derelict hospital that is frozen in time. Confronted by the deadly, grotesque surgical experiments that wander the halls, a series of challenging puzzles and a cast of peculiar characters, he must face his deepest fears, unlock the mysteries of the hospital, and escape with his life. The Ward offers a completely new experience on the Nintendo DS and pushes the platform to its limits with full 3D visuals and bone-chilling audio that brings the world screaming to life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dementium - The Ward-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Kid</developer>
		<publisher>Gamecock</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="11043" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies</name>
		<desc>In Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies, players begin their adventure as a city guardian who is sent to retrieve a sacred trees fruits, which have the power to grant wishes. Players travel the world, conquer fearsome monsters and unravel an epic storyline. During their journey, players will encounter mighty opponents in fast-paced battles, and also interact with a colorful cast of characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6799999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>20100711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6909" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>Four elemental Crystals, each possessing awesome power, lie scattered throughout the realm. However, men are quick to covet things which offer strength, and easily corrupted by the might which they possess. Seduced by the promised power of the Crystals, the kingdom of Baron begins employing unprovoked force to seize them from peaceful nations. The dark knight Cecil - Lord Captain of Baron's elite force, the Red Wings - is ordered by his king to obtain the Crystals, but soon begins to question the monarch's motives. Stricken with grief at his own actions, yet burdened by his loyalty to his country and his personal sense of honor, Cecil at last decides to turn from the path of darkness and destruction. Enraged, the king accuses him of disloyalty, strips Cecil of his command, and sends him off to slay a mysterious beast that lurks in the nearby Valley of Mist. Cecil embarks on a fateful journey that will bring trials, betrayals, friendship, loss and self-discovery. Can Cecil open his eyes and become the man of honor that he must be? Dive into the first RPG to incorporate the innovative Active Time Battle system, now further enhanced and refined for the Nintendo DS. Train and customize Whytkin by playing a variety of mini-games and challenge another player to head-to-head battle via local wireless connection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20080905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="11049" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Rings of Fates.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Ring of Fates</name>
		<desc>Yuri and Chelinka are fraternal twins who live happily with their father in a small village, but their happiness comes to an abrupt end when an ancient evil force arrives. Now, with his family shattered, Yuri begins to train so that he can be strong enough to fight when the evil returns. Yuri and Chelinka set out on their quest to find their friends, avenge their family, and heal their world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles Rings of Fates-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="11263" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Kirby - Mass Attack.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby: Mass Attack</name>
		<desc>One day, an evildoer with a magic cane appears and splits Kirby into 10 pieces. Kirby sets off on a journey to return to his original form. Players use the touch screen to control a mass of Kirby characters in a new and novel way. Swipe the touch screen to launch them in a mass attack against enemies, then tap the enemies into submission.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby - Mass Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="2245" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Phantom Hourglass.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass</name>
		<desc>The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass is the fourteenth game in Nintendo's The Legend of Zelda series. It was released after The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess for the Wii and before The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks for the Nintendo DS. An action-adventure game developed by Nintendo Entertainment Analysis and Development and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS, Phantom Hourglass was released in Japan in June 2007, and in North America, Australia, and Europe in October 2007. The game features 3D cel-shaded graphics with an overhead camera perspective, uses Nintendo DS features for game controls including the touchscreen and microphone, and takes advantage of the Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection for online play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Legend of Zelda - Phantom Hourglass-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.72</rating>
		<releasedate>20070623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6815" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Kirby - Squeak Squad.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby: Squeak Squad</name>
		<desc>Kirby: Squeak Squad, known in Europe as Kirby: Mouse Attack and in Japan as Kirby of the Stars: Calling on the Dorotche Gang (Japanese: 星のカービィ 参上! ドロッチェ団 Hepburn: Hoshi no Kābī Sanjō! Dorocche Dan?), is a 2006-07 platforming video game developed by HAL Laboratory, Flagship and Natsume (the latter as seen in the end credits) and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld video game console. Unlike the previous Nintendo DS title, Kirby: Canvas Curse, Squeak Squad is a traditional platformer which uses the face buttons instead of the touch screen to control Kirby.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby - Squeak Squad-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20061204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Labs</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6835" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time.zip</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Partners in Time</name>
		<desc>The famous Mario Brothers return in this sequel to the humorous Superstar Saga. In this adventure, Princess Peach takes a trip in a time machine, but when it returns, there's only a monster inside! The heroic brothers travel back in time only to discover that evil alien life forms known as the Shroobs have taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and no-one is safe! They soon meet up with their younger selves, and set out to stop the alien menace, not to mention rescue the Princess!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6837" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Mario Kart DS.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Kart DS</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart DS is the continuation of the long running racing game series that began on the Super Nintendo. It features 16 new tracks as well as 16 tracks from the previous 4 games, with each set split up into the Nitro and Retro Grand Prix respectively. Eight racers are initially available, each with two go-karts to choose from. A number of characters and additional karts are also available to unlock. New items have been added to the arsenal, including a Blooper squid that squirts ink onto the screens of other players and a Bullet Bill power up that transforms the player into a giant, fast-travelling bullet on autopilot.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario Kart DS-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6838" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Mario Vs Donkey Kong 2 March of the Minis.zip</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2: March of the Minis</name>
		<desc>Mario vs. Donkey Kong 2: March of the Minis is an action/puzzle game where the object is to bring as many Mini-Marios to the exit door as possible by solving the puzzle. All the puzzles are fairly small and take up anywhere from one screen to four screens (2x2) in size. All the Mini-Marios that are collected in each room are then used in the Donkey Kong boss battle at the end of the world. All of the control is done with the stylus; no buttons are used at all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario Vs Donkey Kong 2 March of the Minis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6844" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Megaman ZX.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man ZX</name>
		<desc>This game contains elements from the Mega Man X series and the Mega Man Zero series. The players are on a 2-dimensional overlay map with sprites where they engage enemies to finish their mission. When a player receives a Biometal, he is able to change form, gaining various abilities, such as the charge moves, or charging the player's weapon with an element of that Biometal; for example, Biometal H will charge the weapon with electricity. While in a special form, using the form-specific abilities use up weapon energy. When the player receives the other half of the Biometal, he is able to perform a different special ability.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Megaman ZX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6845" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./MegaMan ZX Advent.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man ZX Advent</name>
		<desc>In Mega Man ZX Advent, the main characters discover the power of the mysterious "Biometal model A," which on its own has several attacks, but also has a special Megamerge ability which allows the character to transform into one of eight "Pseudoroid" bosses that each have a unique set of abilities. Once a boss is defeated, players can emulate their powers to find hidden routes, discover rare items and aid their battles against more powerful enemies. The title takes full advantage of the Nintendo DS features to enhance the action-packed gameplay and story line of the popular series.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/MegaMan ZX Advent-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6848" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Metroid Prime Hunters.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime Hunters</name>
		<desc>The famous Metroid series lands on the Nintendo DS with Metroid Prime: Hunters. A once-strong race has gone extinct, leaving powerful artifacts to be found by bounty hunters from across the galaxy. The game features a variety of bounty hunters, both old and new, to the series. It also features multiple competitive game modes--such as deathmatch and king of the hill--for battling wirelessly with up to three other players.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Metroid Prime Hunters-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NST</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6853" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Nanostray.zip</path>
		<name>Nanostray</name>
		<desc>Nanostray is a vertical scrolling shooter video game for the Nintendo DS. Similar to many games in the genre, the user takes control of a futuristic spacecraft against a seemingly endless horde of enemies. A sequel to the game was released in 2008, entitled Nanostray 2.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nanostray-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin'en Multimedia</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game id="6854" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Nanostray 2.zip</path>
		<name>Nanostray 2</name>
		<desc>Nanostray 2 is a scrolling shooter video game for the Nintendo DS, and is the sequel to the original Nanostray. It was released in North America on March 11, 2008, October 9, 2008 in Europe.
		Taking place in the future, the supply ship E.S.S. Ariga is returning from its latest voyage when the awakening crew is alerted by a three-year-old distress call. The colonized area the Ariga is returning to has been contaminated by a techno-virus known as Nanostray. According to the distress call, the Nanostray virus had infected the colonist technology from computers to war-machines and made each one hostile. A flight commander has been assigned to win back the infested areas and, with the help of Officer Diane Stewart aboard the Ariga, discover and destroy the source of the Nanostray virus.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Nanostray 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin'en</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="9607" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./SEGA Superstars Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Sega Superstars Tennis</name>
		<desc>Sega Superstars Tennis is a tennis video game developed by Sumo Digital, crossing over numerous Sega franchises, including Sonic the Hedgehog, Alex Kidd, Space Channel 5 and 12 more.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/SEGA Superstars Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20080318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="11421" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sonic Rush Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<desc>Sonic returns to the DS with all the classic 2D dual screen action of "Sonic Rush," as well as a new high-seas adventure where he clashes with ruthless pirates. As Sonic, set off from Windmill Village to explore seven islands for action-packed adventures spread across a large map. As you venture, you'll uncover valuable items and materials that will help Tails build new ships so that Sonic can track down the villainous pirates in a variety of ways.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sonic Rush Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6879" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Sonic Rush.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush</name>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog has a new partner, Blaze the Cat, in this fast-paced platformer, Sonic Rush. You can play as either Sonic or Blaze as you try to track down powerful Sol emeralds. Sonic Rush displays the level over both screens, allowing for screen-spanning jumps and dives. Some gameplay modes include stylus support as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Sonic Rush-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6885" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith.zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith</name>
		<desc>The singleplayer mode is a side-scroller with a depth of field, which give a new dimension to explore while not in 3D. As you progress in the levels, the player can pick Mission Points that will help him to customize his character. It is actually the GBA version of the game but you can make the specials moves of the characters by pressing them on the touch screen. There is also 3 3D levels in each path that has been added to enhance the singleplayer experience.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Montreal</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game id="11424" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./StarFox Command.zip</path>
		<name>Star Fox Command</name>
		<desc>Star Fox Command lets you hop into your fight through a unique branching storyline of missions, all rendered in gorgeous 3-D. This game brings a whole new strategic element to the series, with a commander's view of the mission. Using the touch screen, players can draw the routes they and their teammates will take. Battle the enemies they encounter as they take over bases and strategically advance across the map. Players can also blow their friends out of the sky, as they dogfight 8 players over a local wireless connection -- or take on 4 players from around the world on Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/StarFox Command-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6886" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<desc>Super Mario 64, the classic 3D platformer for the Nintendo 64, arrives on the Nintendo DS with all-new features that take advantage of the portable system's dual screens, touch screen, and wireless multiplayer capability. Like the original game, Super Mario 64 DS challenges you to find all the power stars hidden throughout the royal castle in the effort to free Peach imprisoned inside the castle. This time, you can play as Mario, Luigi, Wario, and Yoshi, each of whom has unique abilities. Overcome the challenges on your own or battle up to three of your friends in the multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Super Mario 64 DS-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5875</rating>
		<releasedate>20041121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6887" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Super Princess Peach.zip</path>
		<name>Super Princess Peach</name>
		<desc>Princess Power!
Bowser's up to no good again...but this time, it's Princess Peach to the rescue! When Mario, Luigi, and the Mushroom Castle Toads get kidnapped it's up to Peach and her magical umbrella to save them.
* Feel the vibes! Use the Touch Screen on the DS to channel Peach's emotional vibes into special abilities. Float when she's happy, burn through walls when she's mad, or make vegetation grow with her tears!
* Save Mario! Join the princess as she runs, jumps, floats, and fights her way through eight worlds, from Fury Volcano to Spooky Shriek Mansion.
* Keep your eyes peeled! Every area hides secrets, including Touch-Screen Minigames, cool puzzles, and and plenty of power ups for both Peach and her umbrella!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Super Princess Peach-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="19234" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Wario Master Of Disguise.zip</path>
		<name>Wario: Master of Disguise</name>
		<desc>The world's most low-down and ornery garlic-lover never lets a get-rich quick scheme pass him by. Wario: Master of Disguise opens with our money-mad hero taking a break from being a shady software impresario to watch a TV show about a master thief. Working himself up into a lather of jealousy, Wario leaps through the screen and embarks on his own glamorous globe-trotting career as a thief.
With the helpful advice of a mustachioed magic wand named Goodstyle, you'll soon learn how to use your DS stylus to draw specific designs on Wario to give him new costumes. Break into exotic locations, from a luxury liner &amp; watery ruins to an Egyptian pyramid, all in the hopes of grabbing as much treasure and loot as Wario can carry.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Wario Master Of Disguise-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20070305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Suzak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6906" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Yoshi Touch &amp; Go.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi Touch &amp; Go</name>
		<desc>Yoshi and Baby Mario are back together at long last, and it'll take a steady hand to guide them through their latest adventure. As Yoshi charges across the island, you use the stylus to throw eggs at enemies, lead him to egg-replenishing fruit, and make him jump over danger. On vertical-scrolling levels, you use the stylus to draw clouds to encircle enemies, throw coins, and guide Baby Mario through the dangerous skies. Take on the single-player challenges or compete against a friend using the wireless link of the Nintendo DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Yoshi Touch &amp; Go-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game id="6907" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Zoo Keeper.zip</path>
		<name>Zoo Keeper</name>
		<desc>In Zoo Keeper for the DS, you can see if you have what it takes to take care of all the animals in a zoo. Maintain an orderly zoo by using the stylus to match up animals on the screen. Once you've lined up three or more animals of the same type, the animals are captured, and more animals fall in their place. Zoo Keeper features a variety of gameplay modes as well as wireless multiplayer capabilities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Zoo Keeper-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Buddiez</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game id="6905" source="theGamesDB.net">
		<path>./Yoshi's Island DS.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Island DS</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Island DS is a sequel to the SNES game, Yoshi's Island. In it, players control Yoshi as he travels to Kamek's castle to rescue Luigi. Yoshi can carry Baby Mario, Peach, DK, Wario or Bowser on his back - depending on the baby carried, Yoshi will gain a special ability; for example, Mario lets Yoshi dash, Peach allows Yoshi to float for a longer period of time, and Wario whips out a gigantic magnet to attract coins and other metallic objects. If Yoshi is hit by an enemy, a counter appears, and begins to slowly count down to zero. If it reaches zero, the baby is kidnapped, and Yoshi loses a life. Yoshi can increase his counter by collecting stars that are rewards for some puzzles and defeating certain enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Yoshi's Island DS-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20061113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artoon</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens - Infestation.zip</path>
		<name>Aliens Infestation</name>
		<desc>GAME OVER, MAN!  The Xenomorph, the ultimate killing machine, returns.  Only the Universe's toughest, the Colonial Marines, can exterminate the galaxy's most feared species.  Can you fight off the terror of the alien infestation?

-Choose you squad and watch the dynamic story system adapt
-Pick up where the Aliens crew left off and fight through the U.S.S. Sulaco, planet LV-426, and more!
-Load up with iconic weapons from the film, including pulse rifles, smart guns, and flamethrowers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Aliens - Infestation-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20111011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Barnyard Blast - Swine of the Night.zip</path>
		<name>Barnyard Blast: Swine of the Night</name>
		<desc>One Halloween evening, young piglet Cliffy Belmart and his rebellious friends decide to test their bravery by tee-peeing Barnyard Town's Ancient Castle ruled by Darkness. But as soon as the fun begins, horrendouse evil trees sweep them all into the castle. Instantly aware of his son's peril, Robert Belmart equips himself with a slew of weapons and a plan to get Cliffy back. But first, Robert must tackle six different spooky worlds - each with their own tough monsters and dangerous bosses. Is Robert a bad enough dude to rescue his son? In Barnyard Blast, you control Robert Belmart, the Swine of the Night. Through 6 levels you kill zombies, exterminate monsters, slash ghouls, and more!

Vintage shooting and platform gameplay with simple, intuitive controls
Hilarious characters and scenes combined with intense, state-of-the-art fighting
Six long and unique levels: A Night Walk in the Graveyard, The Ancient Castle Ruled by Darkness, The Volcano BBQ, The Old Creepy Wooden Jail, The Forest in the Way, and The Castle of Intolerable Pain
Challenging enemies and bosses including Pumpkin Zombies, Assassin Rats, Evil Trees, and Sinister Monkeys
A collection of weapons (whip, shotgun, gun, dynamite), items and upgrades</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Barnyard Blast - Swine of the Night-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20080115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Destination Software</developer>
		<publisher>Destination Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty - World at War.zip</path>
		<name>Call of Duty - World at War</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: World at War from Activision for the Nintendo DS brings WWII gameplay to the palm of your hand. Achieve victory in seven unique mini-games as you confront enemies on European and Pacific battlefields. Gameplay employs the Nintendo DS stylus and dual-screen interface for unique control. Transmit secret messages with Morse Code, disarm mines, parachute to safety, heal fellow soldiers, provide artillery support, and more. Connect online in four-player multiplayer action with more than 10 maps available for Deathmatch, Team Deathmatch, Capture the Flag, and Hunter/Prey.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Call of Duty - World at War-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20081110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>N-Space</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T192056</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<desc>Following the success of Dawn of Sorrow and Portrait of Ruin, the legendary Castlevania series is back on the Nintendo DS. This time you play as a member of the Ecclesia, an organization that has sworn to defeat the evil forces of Dracula. Use the brand new Glyph attack system which has more than 100 different combinations to battle Dracula and his minions throughout 20 explorable areas. Take part in side quests and collect items to power up your character in the next great Castlevania game produced by Koji Igarashi.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dementium II.zip</path>
		<name>Dementium 2</name>
		<desc>Dementium II continues to push the horror experience by melding FPS action and puzzles with a story and ambience that will have players on the edge of their seats. New wrinkles to gameplay, all new weapons, dual wielding items, improved interface and save system, and mind-boggling environments promise to engage gamers and spawn fear the likes of which some never thought possible.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dementium II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20100504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Kid</developer>
		<publisher>SouthPeak Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DK Jungle Climber.zip</path>
		<name>DK Jungle Climber</name>
		<desc>King K. Rool is up to no good again, and it-s up to Donkey Kong to swing into action. Using the same simple control scheme that made the DK: King of Swing Game Boy Advance SP game so accessible and fun to play, players of all skill levels can swing and climb to new heights made possible by the dual screens of Nintendo DS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/DK Jungle Climber-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20070910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paon Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Echoes of Time.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Echoes of Time</name>
		<desc>An innovative new concept in multiplayer gaming, Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles: Echoes of Time enables Wii and DS users to play side by side for the first time. This breakthrough in gaming connectivity allows players on both Nintendo platforms to journey together in the fantastical world of the beloved Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles series. Echoes of Time offers a gameplay system that allows for a seamless, hassle-free in-game switch from single to multiplayer mode. Play anytime, anywhere, with anyone and experience a new level of connectivity with this latest adventure in the FFCC series. A triumphant return from a monster-infested forest marks the completion of the 16-year-old hero's coming-of-age ceremony. However, the hero's joy is short-lived as a young village girl is found to be afflicted by a mysterious illness known as "crystal sickness." Determined to obtain the cure, the hero steps out of the secluded village for the first time, only to discover a world in which crystals are merely artifacts of the past and no longer exist. Players can switch between single and multiplayer modes at any time while playing, enjoying two great gaming options in one integrated experience. A personalized hero can be generated from a choice of the four familiar races of the series; Clavats, Lilties, Selkies or Yukes. Players can continue to enjoy the game even after completing the main adventure, as the New Game+ feature provides increased difficulty and better items with every new round.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Final Fantasy Crystal Chronicles - Echoes of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20090324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - Dark Dawn.zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: Dark Dawn</name>
		<desc>After going dark six years ago, 2010 will see a new dawn. Golden Sun DS updates the popular portable Golden Sun role-playing series with an impressive graphical style. This installment follows the story of the previous heroes' descendants and immerses players into the magic of its adventure by pushing the boundaries of intuitive touch-screen controls.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Golden Sun - Dark Dawn-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20101129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story.zip</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story</name>
		<desc>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story is the third game in the Mario &amp; Luigi series of games. Players control Mario and Luigi simultaneously in the side-scrolling platform environment of Bowser's body, while also controlling the Koopa King himself in the top-down world of the Mushroom Kingdom. Similar to games like Earthbound, enemy encounters are seen as actual enemies that players can avoid or attempt to strike early. The actual battles are a combination of turn-based menu attacks, and timed reactions to enemies during battle. By watching the way an enemy reacts, you can anticipate their attack and avoid it or counterattack.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20090914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem!.zip</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong: Mini-Land Mayhem</name>
		<desc>At the grand opening of Mario's third theme park, the first 100 guests receive a new Mini Pauline toy. Donkey Kong arrives as the 101st guest and finds himself out of luck. He grabs Pauline and heads into the park with Mario and his Mini Marios in hot pursuit. The fourth game in the series adds new challenges and new opportunities for users to share what they have created.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20101114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug 7.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 7</name>
		<desc>The Peregrine Falcon Strike Force, the Ikari Warriors, and the SPARROWS are once again on a search for General Morden and his army. Their mission is to catch General Morden and prevent his attempts at another coup d'état on the government. However, as soon as Morden was defeated, a strange army from the future came to his aid. Now, they must face Morden once again and this time, put a stop to his plans once and for all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Metal Slug 7-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzzle League DS.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle League DS</name>
		<desc>Use the DS stylus to grab panels and slide them left and right. If you match three or more panels of the same color, they will vanish. Form chains and combos to create cascading waterfalls of panels to rack up high scores. The basic game play is similar to the classics Tetris Attack and Pokémon Puzzle League, but the touch screen gameplay adds a new dimension of fun, giving Planet Puzzle League a bright new feel.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Puzzle League DS-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co.,</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radiant Historia.zip</path>
		<name>Radiant Historia</name>
		<desc>In the midst of an unending war for dominance between two super-powers, Special Intelligence Agent Stocke is assigned to a routine escort mission that goes horribly awry...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Radiant Historia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soma Bringer.zip</path>
		<name>Soma Bringer</name>
		<desc>Under the warmth of the enormous ring that embraces the planet, enveloped within the atmosphere charged with Soma, people slumber, awaken, and live

This is a world where an energy called Soma dominates.

Lately, the balance of Soma tipped, and a mysterious life form, called visitors appeared and people started to live in fear. To defeat these visitors, the people established a military group called the Falsif. During an investigation in the Junel Forest, a member of the seventh troop met a girl who has lost all her memories, and thus...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Soma Bringer-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20080228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Spirit Tracks.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks</name>
		<desc>For the first time in the 23-year history of The Legend of Zelda series, Princess Zelda is leaving the villainous clutches of the underworld behind and joining the adventure with Link. In The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks, the spirit of Zelda accompanies Link on his quest to save Hyrule. Directly impacting game play like never before, Zelda's spirit can take control of hulking suits of armor known as Phantoms, allowing the player to direct both Link and these new allies as they battle enemies, solve puzzles and uncover secrets. Zelda also rides alongside Link on his customizable train, offering wisdom that will help players find new areas, storylines and items. The team of Link and Zelda presents countless new storyline details for fans to enjoy, including a closer look at Princess Zelda herself, one of the most iconic video game characters of all-time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Legend of Zelda - Spirit Tracks-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T190527</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legendary Starfy.zip</path>
		<name>The Legendary Starfy</name>
		<desc>Starfy has been a hero in Japan for years, and The Legendary Starfy marks his North American debut.
Players must guide Starfy through a variety of lush environments to the end of each stage by swimming, jumping and bouncing - all while defeating comical enemies and big bosses. No two stages are alike. Each one has its own mazes, puzzles and challenges to keep Starfy on his toes.
]Starfy's main ability is the Star Spin, an attack that propels him into his enemies with great force. It also lets him burst through walls and barriers, or power through strong currents. As the adventure continues, Starfy learns new skills, such as the Shooting Star attack, which lets him shoot into the ground like a meteor, and Air Jump, which gives him increased jumping abilities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Legendary Starfy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20090607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Heroes: Rocket Slime</name>
		<desc>Dragon Quest Heroes: Rocket Slime is based in the fictional world of Slimenia, specifically in the capital city of Boingburg. It begins with four Slimes, Rocket, Hooly, Bo, and Swotsy, who are playing in front of the castle. Hooly has gotten his hands on a valuable flute, and in response to the flute being blown by Rocket, his father comes running over, forcing Hooly to stick the flute in Rocket's mouth. Afterward, an organization known as the Plob invades Boingburg, capturing 100 of its 101 inhabitants. Because he was distorted and long, the Plob mistakenly believed Rocket was not a Slime but a worm, and discarded him into Forewood Forest. There, Rocket begins his journey to rescue his fellow slimes, who have been locked up in large treasure chests.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T192748</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest V: Hand of the Heavenly Bride</name>
		<desc>The legend of Zenithia continues!

What begins as an innocent voyage of a boy traveling alongside his father develops into an eye-opening adventure that transcends generations. You - a hero in the making - determine your own path, choose your own wife and befriend a wagonload of quirky monsters along the way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T194256</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation</name>
		<desc>Coming to North America for the first time, Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation for Nintendo DS brings the classic console title into the handheld scene. Explore two parallel worlds while distinguishing reality from illusion and seeking to discover the true meaning of your very existence.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ArtePiazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T194744</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Geometry Wars - Galaxies.zip</path>
		<name>Geometry Wars: Galaxies</name>
		<desc>The Geometry Wars: Galaxies videogame allows players to blast-off on action-paced quests across the galaxy, defending solar systems one by one, defeating waves of alien enemies on new and classic Battle Grids.

For the first time ever, the Geometry Wars videogame will let players battle via hot seat, co-op, simultaneous and versus in multiplayer mode. Those that own both the Nintendo DS and Wii can link the game together using Wi-Fi to unlock bonus content. Elite players will be able to challenge the universe by posting high scores on the Wii’s online leader board.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Geometry Wars - Galaxies-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20071127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T193029</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros.zip</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>In an all new 2D side-scrolling adventure, Mario and Luigi return after nearly fifteen years. The first traditional Mario Bros. game since Super Mario World.

The character models are rendered in real time 3D, allowing for a far greater number of moves ever before seen in a Mario Bros. title. Also as the game is on DS, the touch screen allows players to store an additional power-up and view the distance still to go in a level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/New Super Mario Bros-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7571399999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>20060517T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T195034</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Dragon Sword.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Dragon Sword</name>
		<desc>This action-adventure title is presented in a third person, pseudo-3D manner, meaning all the game-models are rendered in full 3D, but the world the player travels around in is pre-rendered. When played, the Nintendo DS is held sideways, as in Hotel Dusk: Room 215 and Brain Age: Train Your Brain in Minutes a Day!. The left screen shows the area map, while the right displays the main gameplay, when set for right-handed play, and reverse when set for left-handed play.
Set six months after Ninja Gaiden, Ryu Hayabusa has rebuilt the Hayabusa Village. When fellow villager and kunoichi, Momiji, is kidnapped by the Black Spider Ninja Clan, he is forced to find her, while uncovering the secrets behind the mysterious Dark Dragonstones and their relation to the Dragon Lineage</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Ninja Gaiden Dragon Sword-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20080325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ninja</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170325T194044</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Ball - Origins.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball: Origins</name>
		<desc>Dragon Ball: Origins follows Goku and his clever sidekick Bulma as they travel the world overcoming enemies and obstacles to collect the 7 Dragon Balls. In the shoes of Goku, the player must protect Bulma from incoming enemy attacks using special skills, such as fighting with his power pole, or unleashing a kamehameha. Combined with Bulma’s ability to invent machines and weapons, the intrepid pair make a formidable team able to defeat even the strongest enemies or trickiest of obstacles.

The innovative controls mean the player uses only the touch pad to control Goku. Players must draw lines or shapes to direct the character and control the action by tapping on the screen, for example a double tap on Goku followed by tapping on the Ka-me-ha-me-ha letters unleashes his devastating signature move.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Dragon Ball - Origins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20081104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Republic (JP)</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goldeneye 007.zip</path>
		<name>Goldeneye 007</name>
		<desc>A NEW GOLDENEYE FOR A NEW BOND The GoldenEye story comes to life once again with an updated single player storyline featuring Daniel Craig as Bond and written by Bruce Feirstein, the screenwriter for the original movie. Surprise enemies covertly or engage in a full on firefight and use Bonds latest gadget to uncover intel in augmented reality as you relive all the classic GoldenEye movie moments. Infiltrate the dam and destroy the facility; chase Ourumov in the tank through the streets of St. Petersburgh; and investigate the secret jungle base.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Goldeneye 007-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20101102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure</name>
		<desc>In Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure players embark on single player fun like no other. Here Henry Hatsworth, a quirky, lighthearted character serves as your guide on a journey through a new style of gaming on your Nintendo DS that combines the action of an adventure game with the challenge of a puzzle game.

In this two-in-one extravaganza players explore five exotic worlds, fight a variety of opponents, and venture through more than 30 levels, including nearly a dozen hidden levels while taking on outrageous world-ending bosses.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tiburon</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Canvas Curse.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby: Canvas Curse</name>
		<desc>Your DS stylus has been infused with the power to paint! When Kirby gets turned into a ball by an evil witch, your hand-drawn rainbow paths become the only way he can find power-ups and reach the gates of each world. Draw loops to make him speed up, make ramps to jump danger, and draw walls to block laser beams and cannon blasts as you explore seven worlds packed with adventure! Get in touch: Stun enemies, break blocks, and much more - all with a touch of the stylus! Be a copycat: Tap Kirby to dash into enemies and copy their abilities. Eleven abilities in all! So many modes: Try timed challenges, take on bosses, or play simple but fun mini-games!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby - Canvas Curse-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20050613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia - The Fallen King.zip</path>
		<name>Prince Of Persia: The Fallen King</name>
		<desc>Prince of Persia: The Fallen King is a third-person action-adventure video game developed by Ubisoft Casablanca.[1] The game was released for the Nintendo DS in December 2008, as a spin-off of Prince of Persia. The plot, taking place in ancient Persia, concerns the player character's role in a celestial battle between two gods; Ahriman and Ormazd. The player assumes the role of the Prince, and Zal, fighting Ahriman's forces with a variety of different physical and magical attacks. Prince of Persia: The Fallen King has received mixed reviews, with the most agreed-upon problem being the control scheme.[1][2][3]</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Prince of Persia - The Fallen King-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Bubbles.zip</path>
		<name>Soul Bubbles</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Soul Bubbles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mekensleep</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star Ultra.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby: Super Star Ultra</name>
		<desc>Kirby Super Star Ultra for the Nintendo DS re-imagines one of the most beloved Kirby games of all time. The game features new graphics and fully rendered animated cut scenes. With so many adventures waiting to be unlocked, there will never be a dull moment as Kirby runs, floats, copies enemies and uses Helpers to fight King Dedede and Meta Knight. New modes like Revenge of the King and Meta Knight Ultra await, along with classics like The Great Cave Offensive and Milky Way Wishes. On top of the main modes, there are also three new touch-screen-controlled mini-games that can be played with up to three friends via DS Download Play. Not only that, but players can go on Kirby adventures with a friend via local wireless as well.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nds/Kirby Super Star Ultra-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20180120T194447</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
