<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Dracula X - Rondo Of Blood.cue</path>
		<name>Dracula X - Rondo Of Blood</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170206T052307</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Air Zonk.zip</path>
		<name>Air Zonk</name>
		<desc>The powered-up Zonk gathers his friends to form Team Cool, and they set out to stop King Drool’s plan to conquer the world. Choose from 3 levels of difficulty and 3 types of Friend Modes. Shoot King Drool's cyber robots and avoid their attacks while collecting the Air Bones to unleash a variety of attacks. Enjoy unique moves such as combining with a friend to create an invincible hybrid form or blasting enemies with a charged attack. Air “Zonk” is filled with humor, like its wacky theme song that plays when you post a huge score or when your game is over.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Air Zonk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Red Company</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blazing Lazers.zip</path>
		<name>Blazing Lazers</name>
		<desc>Blazing Lazers is a top-down shooter featuring 9 levels of varied and fast-paced action. The story here is the usual save-the-world variety. You must pilot your ship against 8 super-weapons and ultimately destroy the menace once and for all.

The power-up system in Blazing Lazers deserves special mention. There are four main types of weapons, and each type of weapon can be upgraded several times to produce an incredible amount of firepower. In addition, there are secondary weapons systems that provide you with shields, homing missiles, multi-fire units, or super weapon power.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Blazing Lazers-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk 3: Bonk's Big Adventure</name>
		<desc>Bonk is back! And he's bigger and better than ever! Use your head (literally) to traverse 6 wild locations- including a forest grove, an antartic ice prison and more! Chomp on blue miracle candy to grow to gigantic proportions and break right through large obstacles. Chomp red candy to shrink to microscopic size and slip right under narrow cracks to discover secret items! Catch the magic flower in each stage to be transported to a bonus round- where you can score more points and earn bonus men! On your way, you will defeat menacing bosses that include acrobatic dinosaur, a sneaky squid and other! Are you ready to save the world, little cave dude!?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Adventure</name>
		<desc>Bonk yourself out in this head-buttin', head-splittin' adventure. As Bonk the Caveman, use your head against Kongo Zilla, Tractorhead and wackiest array of prehistoric foes ever seen. Be sure to eat your meat-and-vegetables as you power-up to battle Evil King Drool himself. It's a real head-banger!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Bonk's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Bonk is back! Last year's video smash is bashing his way through a totally awesome new adventure! Help that radical cave dude save the Dinosaur Kingdom from the heinous King Drool III. Bigger, badder bosses. More powerful power-ups. More excellent hidden secrets. And more worlds of pre-hysterical action that'll have you cracking up while you're out cracking heads. Blast back to the Bonk Age, mankind's coolest era, and Bonk yourself out!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Bonk's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mutech</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cross Wiber - Cyber Combat Police.zip</path>
		<name>Cross Wiber: Cyber-Combat-Police</name>
		<desc>Cross Wiber is an special inspector of the cyber combat police. Several years after the happenings in Cyber Cross, a new threat threatens Earth: Duma and his alien forces. Wiber now starts his counter-attack on Duma.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Cross Wiber - Cyber Combat Police-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FACE</developer>
		<publisher>Sankindo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Genji Tsuushin Agedama.zip</path>
		<name>Genji Tsuushin Agedama</name>
		<desc>Agedama Genji is a 4th grader boy in elementary school, and a hero on the training from 'Hero Planet.' Though the cheerful kid is no one special in appearance, he can transforms into a superhero called "Agedaman" by combining himself with his computer friend called Wapuro. He believes in Kiai power and he tries to handle all the problems that he encounters with that, so his father decided to let him go training on the earth accompanied by only Wapuro on summer vacation. After his arrival to Morisoba city, where an enormously wealthy clan rules arbitrarily, he joined East-Morisoba elementary school, then met a diva girl of the clan named Rei Kuki who has an ambition to conquer the world and, as a first step, attacks the city with a variety of chimera monsters that she and her grandfather create with the Monster-Cooker, which the rich old man invented. When they plot to attack the city she transforms into a super-villainess called "Onyomiko". The battles of Agedaman and Onyomiko began!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Genji Tsuushin Agedama-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interchannel</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu.zip</path>
		<name>Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu</name>
		<desc>Jackie and his sister, Josephine, are tough on tyrants. As China's supreme kung fu champs, they guard their country against the Prince of Sorcerers, who lurks just beyond the Great Wall. It comes as no surprise when this fiend and his ghouls try yet again to seize China for themselves. But this time they're clever, casting a spell over Josephine which causes her to vanish into thin air! Jackie is in shock! How can he save his country without his sister? The two have been an unbeatable team! Meanwhile, a demon horde led by the Sorcerer storms the Great Wall and prepares to establish a fierce empire. At the urging of his revered Master, Jackie must now battle the dreaded Sorcerer and rescue Josephine. Maybe he can learn a little magic on his own, because he's going to need all the help he can get!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neutopia.zip</path>
		<name>Neutopia</name>
		<desc>You are Jazeta, a berserker warrior, fearless in combat. Now you face your greatest quest: to rescue Princess Aurora from the evil Boss Dirth. Conquer a dangerous land of dungeons and demons, magic and monks. Choose which armor, what spell, which weapon you will use to capture each of the 8 medallions that bring you closer and closer to your final battle with demonic Dirth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Neutopia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neutopia II.zip</path>
		<name>Neutopia II</name>
		<desc>Jazeta brought peace back to the land. But as long as evil and fear live in the human heart, the dreaded Dirth, Emperor of Darkness, will be plotting his return. The Emperor is stirring under the peaceful surface of Neutopia, bringing suffering to its people. Who will save them? Jazeta, the hero, is lost in a labyrinth in a foreign land. Can his son withstand the powers of the Emperor of Darkness to rescue the good people of Neutopia from fear and despair?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/Neutopia II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1943 Kai.zip</path>
		<name>1943: Kai</name>
		<desc>Developed and released alongside the Family Computer version, 1943 Kai: Midway Kaisen is an arcade game, an "alternate" version of the original 1943, released in 1987[3] only in Japan. Most of the graphics and sounds have been reworked, and the game has been made more "extreme" (laser-firing WWII planes and ships that run on ground). Further, the trademark P-38 has been replaced with a Boeing Stearman E75 N68828.

In 1991, this version was converted to the PC Engine as simply 1943 Kai, again Japan-only; this version itself contains many additional levels and original music.

The game is set in the Pacific theater of World War II, off the coast of the Midway Atoll. The goal is to attack the Japanese air fleet that bombed the American aircraft carrier, pursue all Japanese air and sea forces, fly through the 16 stages of play, and make their way to the Japanese battleship Yamato and destroy her. 11 of these stages consist of an air-to-sea battle (with a huge battleship or an aircraft carrier as the stage boss), while 5 stages consist of an all-aerial battle against a squadron of Japanese bombers with a mother bomber at the end.

As in 1942, players pilot a P-38 Lightning. Controls are also similar: button 1 fires main weapons, and button two performs two special actions: a loop maneuver like in 1942, or one of three special attacks in exchange for some of the player's fuel. Indeed, players now have only one life, in the form of a large "fuel" meter; constantly depleting, but refillable by collecting various powerups (chiefly "Pow" icons). In 2-player mode, when both players overlap their planes on screen, the energy bar can be transferred from the player with more fuel to the player with less. Destroying a complete formation of red enemy planes will result in a power-up, such as a health boost or a new main weapon.

There are cheat codes, different for every stage, ranging from holding down a fire button or pointing the joystick in certain direction, player(s) are rewarded with fully upgraded weapons.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pcengine/1943 Kai-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170306T060314</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
