<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./sonicwi2.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 2 / Sonic Wings 2</name>
		<desc>The game is played with two buttons, with the A button firing bullets from the plane and the B button launching a special bomb attack which uses a bomb from a limited stock of bombs. Power bullets can be obtained by destroying buildings and armored enemy planes. There are 2 types of Power bullets: "P" Power bullets, that increases the plane's firepower by one level, and "F" Power bullets, that increases the plane's firepower to the maximum level instantly. The maximum level only lasts for a limited amount of shots.
When certain ground enemies and buildings are destroyed, money bonuses appear which give a random amount of points each. When the player reaches the end of the stage, the player has to face a boss ship.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/sonicwi2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170210T021444</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sonicwi3.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 3 / Sonic Wings 3</name>
		<desc>The world seems to be free from the menace of the evil alien forces. However, they are not willing to give up and launch a surprise attack against the Aero Fighters' base, effectively destroying their aircraft. Unable to counter the attack, they must use old WWII-era warplanes with strange modifications, in a desperate scramble for victory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/sonicwi3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aof.zip</path>
		<name>Art Of Fighting</name>
		<desc>Yuri Sakazaki has been kidnapped! Her big brother Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia, his best friend, go search for her on the streets of South Town. As they go deeper and deeper they will find clues as to who ordered the kidnapping, the Sakazaki family's relation to the mob, and a person from their past.

This fighting game is a coin-op conversion of the Neo-Geo hit of the same name, and has all characters, stages, and moves featured in the arcade unit. Unlike the original arcade version, players can now play as Mr. Big and the elusive Mr. Karate.

The gameplay differs from most fighting games. In this game, you have a Spirit meter. A Spirit meter is in the game and will decrease as you perform special moves. It can be recharged, but doing so leaves you open to attack. When your health is almost gone, you can perform a secret combination that will unleash a deadly attack on your opponent - provided you have a full Spirit meter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/aof-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19920924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SNK of America</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170210T012647</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ganryu.zip</path>
		<name>Ganryu</name>
		<desc>On April 14, 1612, Musashi Miyamoto and Sasaki Kojirō dueled. Musashi had an opportunity to see Kojiro's sword sometime before the duel and knew of its long length, so Musashi made his sword even longer. When Musashi arrived on the beach for the duel, he jumped over a low strike of Kojiro's, reaching about a meter off the ground and came down on Kojiro's head with his heavy wooden sword. Kojiro lay dying on the sand and Musashi left without killing him. Some of Musashi's critics called Musashi a coward for not killing Kojiro, but Musashi was satisfied that Kojiro had been defeated, but Kojiro comes back from the dead to try to kill Musashi.

The game's selectable characters are swordsman Ganryu and his female counterpart Suzume. The mission of the game is to rescue Ganryu's girlfriend from an evil ninja. Players are armed with a sword and a grappling claw.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ganryu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170206T064048</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./garou.zip</path>
		<name>Garou: Mark of the Wolves</name>
		<desc>It's been several years since Geese Howard was defeated in a battle with Terry Bogard, a young man looking to avenge his father. Rather than looking to be saved from death after falling off his office balcony, Geese instead decided to die, and left behind his young son, Rock. Terry took Rock in and became like a big brother to him, raising the boy throughout his life.

Now Rock is a teenager, and Terry is a man in his 30s, and both are about to come together in a new clash...new faces and old come together for the greatest battle yet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/garou-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170206T175110</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./lastblad.zip</path>
		<name>Last Blade</name>
		<desc>1863. History's hidden secret is revealed. During the age known as "Bakumatsu", 135 years ago, chaos rules! It's all yours: A new type of weapon fighting game in which Power and Speed weapons, in addition to various Repel moves can be used to experience a new sensation in video game thrills!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/lastblad-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T020655</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./lastbld2.zip</path>
		<name>Last Blade 2</name>
		<desc>The Last Blade 2 picks up where the previous title left off and takes the story of battling at the gates of hell to its climax. This time around, there are 16 unique swordsmen from which to choose. Choose from 2 sword types (Strength and Attack). Deflect your enemy's attacks with "Repel". You can also cancel game-changing special moves like "Super Secret Slice" or "Hidden Secret Slice" with a "Sublime Slash", which connects to Super Secret Slice - just like in the previous title. And there are even some new features like aerial repels, aerial guards and knockdown recovery. Take your battles to a whole 'nother level!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/lastbld2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19981125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170207T232748</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./maglord.zip</path>
		<name>Magician Lord</name>
		<desc>Magician Lord puts you in charge of Elta, a wizard who has the task of collecting eight books of wisdom from the clutches of Az Atorse, the god of destruction. By collecting the right power-ups along the way, you can transform into different characters, including the Rajin, Samurai, Waterman, Shinobi, Poseidon, and Dragon Warrior. Each character has different abilities. There are eight areas in the game, and each stage ends with you trying to defeat both a guardian and the end-of-area boss (which are basically Atorse's incarnations). One of the first games that demonstrated the graphical abilities of the Neo-Geo.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/maglord-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslug.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug</name>
		<desc>Players control Marco and Tarma, both members of the special-ops force Team Peregrine Falcon (commonly known as Team PF), and battle their way through stage after stage of intense action. The goal is to try to overthrow General Morden and win back the stolen weapon, the Metal Slug. Players must blast through waves of enemies and machines (while also jumping over any obstacles in the way) to advance through the stages. It's not as hopeless as it might sound, though - weapons such as heavy machine guns, shotguns, rocket launchers and flamethrowers, as well as the Metal Slug itself (which appears frequently in the game), will make the battle easier.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslug-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19960418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170210T055928</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslug2.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 2</name>
		<desc>As Marco, Eri, Tarma, or Fio, you must defeat the evil General Morden and his henchman. To do this, you must defeat various enemies that get in your way. Throughout the game, you can collect new weapons including the Heavy Machine Gun, Shot Gun, Rocket Launcher, Flame Shot, Laser Shot, Flame Bottles, and Armor Piercer. Also scattered throughout the game, you can ride in four different vehicles (aka: Slugs) such as the Metal Slug, Slug Flyer, Camel Slug, and SlugNoid. By using these vehicles, you can cause awesome destruction against Morden's evil army. Other items such as energy, extra ammunition, and food (eat too much and your player will gain weight) are also found throughout the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslug2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslug3.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 3</name>
		<desc>The rebellion orchestrated by General Morden to bring about a new global regime is now ancient history, and order and peace has begun to return to the world. Morden, brought back into power, was attempting another coup d'état, but government forces got wind of the plot beforehand and pre-empted the impending assault.
Instrumental in squashing Morden's rebel forces, Marco and Tarma of the Peregrine Falcon Strike Force are ordered to lead the team after their earlier requests for resignation were denied. Although General Morden has been written off as "missing" by his followers, they have hidden themselves throughout the world, and Marco and Tarma's abilities and experience are seen as a necessity to destroy remaining rebel strongholds, one by one. Throughout the furious fighting against the holdouts, Marco and Tarma cannot help but suspect Morden's involvement in this new evil plan for world domination.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslug3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslug4.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 4</name>
		<desc>One year after the events of Metal Slug 3, the world is trembling under the new threat of a mysterious but deadly cyber virus that threatens to attack and destroy any nation's military computer system. With Tarma and Eri unable to help due to their own assignments in the matter, Marco and Fio are called in to investigate the situation and are joined by two newcomers, Nadia and Trevor. In their investigation, the group discovers that a terrorist organization known as Amadeus is behind the nefarious plot and that they head into battle against Amadeus' forces, hoping to destroy the cyber virus before it gets the chance to wipe out the entire world's military computer system</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslug4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mega Enterprise</developer>
		<publisher>Mega Enterprise</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslug5.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 5</name>
		<desc>A special disc that contains deep and intricate secrets about the Metal Slug project is stolen by a mysterious group called the Ptolemaic Army, whose specialty lies from within archaeological excavation and espionage. Marco and Tarma of the Peregrine Falcon Strike Force follow in hot pursuit against the group and in the process are joined by Eri and Fio of SPARROWS. Together once more, the quartet investigate the shrouded objective of the Ptolemaic Army.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslug5-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mslugx.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug X</name>
		<desc>Metal Slug X is a modified version of Metal Slug 2 released in 1999 for the Neo-Geo console/arcade platform by SNK. It introduces some new features like new weapons, rearranged enemy replacement and greater difficulty.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/mslugx-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nazca</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170302T011413</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./samsho.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the late 18th century and all the characters wield weapons. The game uses comparatively authentic music from the time period, rife with sounds of traditional Japanese instruments, such as the shakuhachi and shamisen, and a refined version of the camera zoom first found in Art of Fighting. True to its use of bladed weapons, the game also included copious amounts of blood.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/samsho-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./samsho2.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown II</name>
		<desc>One of SNK's legendary fighting game series has made a return! In Samurai Shodown II, you can take on one of the roles of 15 warriors as you fight your way through the land to defeat the evil Mizuki! Slash, kick, and slice your opponents in half...do whatever it takes...live by the sword, and die by its blade.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/samsho2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./samsho4.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown IV</name>
		<desc>Samurai Shodown IV: Amakusa's Revenge, also known as Samurai Spirits: Amakusa's Descent in Japan, is the fourth in SNK's flagship Samurai Shodown series of fighting games. Chronologically, it is the second and final chapter of a story between Samurai Shodown and Samurai Shodown II, with Samurai Shodown III being the first chapter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/samsho4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20031010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./shocktro.zip</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers</name>
		<desc>Shock Troopers is an arcade game developed by Saurus. Gameplay involves taking command of one or three commandos in an 8-way shooter through 6 stages of opposing forces, weaponry, and power-ups.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/shocktro-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./shocktr2.zip</path>
		<name>Shock Troopers - 2nd Squad</name>
		<desc>DIO, a terrorist organization led by a man called Nakatomi, has threatened the world's leaders to submit to their will. After DIO completely eradicates a city, a squad of Shock Troopers are sent to deal with the threat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/shocktr2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Snk</developer>
		<publisher>Snk</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./spinmast.zip</path>
		<name>Spin Master</name>
		<desc>Many years ago, a large treasure was hidden by a mysterious guy on an uncharted island. The guy of mystery drew the location of the treasure on a map and hid it deep in the forest of the island. Days turned to weeks, weeks turned to years, and years turned to decades. The guy who hid the map disappeared, never to be seen again. During this time, the map became dirty and weathered, eventually tearing into five pieces which were scattered about the corners of the world. One of these pieces wafted its way into the possession of the young treasure seeker name Johnny. Living with his girlfriend Mary and his rugged sidekick name Tom, Johnny dreamed of the day when he would some day find the ancient treasure on the hidden island of the mysterious guy.

Then one day, the greedy, treasure-seeking mad scientist, Dr. De Playne appeared in Johnny's little town. Seizing Johnny's piece of the treasure map and kidnapping Mary, Dr. De Playne set out to find the treasure and buy up all the toys and candy of the world, plunging the children of earth into a bitter darkness of continuous study and well-balanced meals. Johnny and Tom pursued the mad Dr. De Playne with their yo-yos to save Mary and the world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/spinmast-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof98.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '98</name>
		<desc>The All-Star dream battle is here at last: It's King of Fighters '98! Here come 38 of your favorite characters from the King of Fighters series. Your favorite characters and teams are back! Filled with new surprises like the Roulette Team Edit and Advantage System, King '98 will pop your cork with unrelenting excitement!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof98-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Snk</developer>
		<publisher>Snk</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T023652</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof2000.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2000</name>
		<desc>After the incident at the previous tournament, the commander of the Ikari Team, Heidern, is determined to figure out the objective of the NESTS cartel so that he can stop them from achieving their ruthless ambition. A fellow commander and long-time friend of Heidern, named Ling, tells the veteran fighter that K′ and Maxima were once operatives of NESTS and that they may hold the key to locating the whereabouts of the mysterious organization. Using this information, Heidern decides to focus his efforts in using the next KOF tournament as a way to lure both K′ and Maxima out so that they can be captured and interrogated into telling the authorities about the NESTS cartel. Unknown to Heidern, however, Ling has his own agenda.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof2000-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Snk</developer>
		<publisher>Snk</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170215T003414</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof2002.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2002</name>
		<desc>The game brings back the team play composed by three characters each that was a tradition in previous games. The game has also several important changes in the gameplay, like the "Free Cancel System" or "Max Mode System", the "Quick Emergency Evasion" and "Quick MAX Mode Activation", aside from the countless changes in each character's special moves and their properties.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof2002-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eolith</developer>
		<publisher>Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170216T012341</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tophuntr.zip</path>
		<name>Top Hunter</name>
		<desc>Top Hunter: Roddy &amp; Cathy es un videojuego de plataformas de desplazamiento lateral desarrollado por SNK para su sistema Arcade Neo Geo, que fue lanzado en el año 1994. posteriormente salió para Neo Geo CD, y mucho después para la consola virtual de Wii. El juego ha sido re-editado más tarde en la compilación SNK Arcade Classics Vol. 1, que salió a la venta el 1 de mayo de 2008.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/tophuntr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170206T065439</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof96.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '96</name>
		<desc>A new King of Fighters tournament was announced, though the letters of invitation sent out to the fighters were no longer sent by Rugal Bernstein. The letters also announced many changes, the first of which being a massive overhaul of the tournament's approach. During the time that had passed between the tournaments since the previous year, the King of Fighters tournament's fame had grown immensely, to the point that it turned into a major international event, which had not happened before. Huge corporations transformed the King of Fighters tournament into something widely televised, commercialized, and celebrated, drawing in many crowds from around the world. The tournament is now held by Chizuru Kagura: a descendant of the ancient Yata Clan responsible for sealing the Orochi demon along with the Kusanagi and Yasanaki clan (the clans from Kyo Kusanagi and Iori Yagami, respectively). Chizuru uses the tournament in hopes of finding and recruiting Kyo and Iori in order to stop the upcoming Orochi threat, but Kyo and Iori aren't exactly willing to work together on friendly terms.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof96-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19960730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aof2.zip</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 2</name>
		<desc>In this sequel to the original Art of Fighting, and prequel to the original Fatal Fury, we learn that Mr. Karate, the final boss of the original game, behind the mask, is really Takuma Sakazaki, Ryo and Yuri's father, that Takuma was being used by Geese Howard for his own evil intentions, and that Mr. Big was the one who had originally kidnapped Yuri.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/aof2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aof3.zip</path>
		<name>Art of Fighting 3: The Path of the Warrior</name>
		<desc>In this third and final entry in the Art of Fighting series, the story shifts from Ryo Sakazaki to his best friend and rival, Robert Garcia, as he ventures into Mexico to try and locate Freia Lawrence, a childhood friend, who asked for his help. However, he leaves without the consent of The Garcia Foundation, which sends an agent named Karman Cole to get him back. But not everything is as simple as it looks... because Robert is not the only one looking for Freia.

Art of Fighting 3: The Path of The Warrior features ten playable characters with different fighting styles, a completely new fighting system based on joystick and button combinations, and incredibly detailed graphics and animation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/aof3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19960426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./blazstar.zip</path>
		<name>Blazing Star</name>
		<desc>Sometime in their past, the planets Remuria and Mutras started an interplanetary war that showed no sign of ending. The endless fight between the human-like inhabitants of the two planets had gone so long that weapon development moved into dangerous territory: Organic Weapon Production combined with alien technology. Soon, a sentient weapon - Brawshella - was born. Brawshella gathered all animal life on both planets and forced them to do its bidding and attack the humans. In a week, the humans were assimilated by Brawshella.
Yet, once they were assimilated, they found no other purpose in life but to continue fighting each other. After a while, four of the assimilated fighter pilots regained their consciousness and remembered their pasts. Upon discovering their humanity, the pilots were conflicted with following Brawshella's orders or fighting it to fully regain their independence. The pilots finally turn against the machine in a battle to rediscover themselves and reclaim their planets.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/blazstar-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19980219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bjourney.zip</path>
		<name>Blue's Journey</name>
		<desc>The planet Raguy was once a beautiful place, until the evil Daruma tribe invaded, bringing pollution that corrupted the land. You, as Blue, are a specialist of the Leaf Dump, and you love Princess Fa of the Raguy family. Unfortunately, Princess Fa has fallen sick from the pollution. It's your job to save your princess in Blue's Journey, a 2D side-scrolling platformer with RPG elements. Go through stages jumping on platforms and avoiding traps, while dealing with a multitude of bad guys, with a special bad guy boss at the end of every level to defeat with special means. To help with this, Blue can use a leaf attack and shrink. The leaf attack, only used when Blue is full sized, lets Blue slam a leaf that stuns any enemies he hits. Blue can also pick up power-ups for a more devastating leaf attack, or change his attack entirely. When the enemies are stunned, Blue can pick them up and throw them across the screen to dispose of more baddies. Shrunken down Blue can't use his attacking power, but he can fit into small crevasses and crannies not normally accessible. Of course, Blue can also dispatch enemies by jumping on them. Since Raguy's economy is flower based, Blue can collect flowers to buy things at special huts. But Blue must take care not to fall into traps or bottomless pits, which cause instant death. Being hit by bad guys or their shots is just as bad. Blue starts the game with two hearts, losing one when he gets whacked by a bad guy. When his heart count goes to zero, Blue dies. Play the game alone (as Blue), or with your friend (as a green Blue) for two-player simultaneous fun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/bjourney-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./crsword.zip</path>
		<name>Crossed Swords</name>
		<desc>In the enchanted land of Belkana all was well until plagues of creatures started rampaging through. But it didn't stop there, from deep within the mountains of Graisia, the Demon Warlord Nausizz arose and led the attacks wiping out settlement after settlement. However a brave warrior called "The Knight of the Journey" came a long way on a quest to stop these monstrosities. After aiding the Poor Village of Dio from the Caterdragon, the knight heads to the Castle Pulista, but as he is briefed by the king of the problems they face, an elite dark knight appears and kidnaps the princess. The knight fights his way through the enemy lands in the Matius Tower, the Gauda Fortress, the Land Battleship and finally passes the Entrance to the Devil World. Along his way, he is helped by loyalties of the kingdom. The knight battles through the Castle Graisia and comes face to face with Nausizz. As a demon with honour, Nausizz is so impressed with the knight's progress, that he has sent the princess back to Pulista. As the knight defeats Nausizz, he transforms into a fiendish demon dragon. The knight slays him and escapes the collapsing castle. Back in Castle Pulista the knight is offered to come and live with the king. Peace can proceed once more in Belkana.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/crsword-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cyberlip.zip</path>
		<name>Cyber-Lip</name>
		<desc>Cyber-Lip is a horizontally scrolling, side-view platformer shoot 'em up (this combination is sometimes referred to as "run and gun") arcade game released by SNK in 1990 for the SNK Neo-Geo MVS. The player(s) control(s) Rick and/or Brook, two human veteran soldiers, who are sent by an unspecified "federal government" into combat on a last-ditch attempt to save Earth from a malfunctioning military supercomputer in charge of all military androids. Gameplay consists of battling through large amounts of enemies, collecting power-ups and defeating several end-of-stage bosses. This makes it comparable to the likes of Metal Slug or Contra in terms of gameplay.

It is noted that a handful of members from Irem developed this title and later went on to create Metal Slug.

The game was later ported over for the Neo Geo CD system, in 1995. The CD featured improved voice acting and added a short introduction to the game explaining the plot.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/cyberlip-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./nam1975.zip</path>
		<name>NAM-1975</name>
		<desc>As a soldier, you and/or a friend must travel through Vietnam to stop the scientist and his world destroying laser machine. In the game, you must shoot enemy soldiers, tanks, helicopters, jeeps, and more by aiming the machine gun cursor and shooting at them. Within each location, you can pick up more powerful weapons such as machine guns and flame throwers, but these have a limited supply of ammunition. Pressing down on the joystick while running at the same time will cause your character to perform a somersault and be invincible for a second. At the end of every location, you will need to defeat a series of bosses, which are not the same every play. Cut-scenes are viewed in between locations, and contain dramatic digitized dialogue.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/nam1975-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ncommand.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Commando</name>
		<desc>Ninja Commando (ニンジャコマンドー?) is a top-down, vertically-scrolling run and gun video game developed by Alpha Denshi and published by SNK. It was first released in May 1992 in cartridge format, and in 1994 for the Neo Geo CD.

An elite group of three young Ninja Commandos (Joe Tiger, an American descendant of the Kōga-ryū ninja whose weapons are shuriken, Ryu Eagle, the 23rd descendant of the famous ninja Fūma Kotarō (from World Heroes), who is using ninja magic fireballs in combat, and Rayar Dragon, the female ninja of the group, a British girl who has learned the ways of the Iga-ryū ninjutsu and whose weapon is a bow with flaming spirit arrows) from around the world must team-up to stop the villain Spider and his Mars Corporation from using a time machine to destroy the past and control the future. The three heroes chase after their enemy in seven time periods, including the Sengoku period in Japan (where Ryu avenges his ancestor by killing Oda Nobunaga), Ancient Egypt, the Stone Age, China in the era of Three Kingdoms, and World War II.[</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ncommand-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./preisle2.zip</path>
		<name>Prehistoric Isle 2</name>
		<desc>The sequel to "Prehistoric Isle in 1930", release more that 10 years after the first one.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/preisle2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pulstar.zip</path>
		<name>Pulstar</name>
		<desc>Pulstar (パルスター?) is a shoot 'em up developed by now defunct Aicom Co. Ltd and published by SNK for the Neo Geo, Neo Geo CD and arcade; it is the prequel of Blazing Star. Pulstar, as well as its sequel, are often regarded as among the best-looking shoot 'em up games for the Neo Geo.
2256 A.D. Alien forces swept into the solar system, and fighting spread throughout the system in two years. An elite group force, codenamed: PULSTAR, remains as Earth's final hope. Take items to snap on powerful options! Break your enemies with the various arsenals!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/pulstar-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pbobblen.zip</path>
		<name>Puzzle Bobble / Bust-A-Move</name>
		<desc>Puzzle Bobble is the ultimate in cute and fun action puzzle games.  The rules are easy; aim left and right and shoot your bubbles.  When three or more of the same color bubbles are joined together, they burst.  The greater the number of bubbles you burst at the same time, the more points you get.  One player versus the computer or against a friend;  It's easy and fun to play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/pbobblen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SunSoft</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sengoku3.zip</path>
		<name>Sengoku 3</name>
		<desc>The third game in the Sengoku series of beat 'em ups, Sengoku 3 once again pits you and a friend against the undead forces of Nobunaga, however this time you can freely select from a group of different characters each with their own weapons and abilities, as well as choose which location in the world (or level) to tackle whenever you want.

The game incorporates a more complex fighting system similar to a one-on-one fighting game, by giving players different attack buttons, special moves based on directional inputs, combos and even a super bar used to unleash devastating super moves. You cannot change weapons or transform into other characters as in the previous games, but you can acquire different ranged weapons for additional attacks as well as unlock certain bosses to increase your available characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/sengoku3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./svc.zip</path>
		<name>SNK vs. Capcom: SVC Chaos</name>
		<desc>The gameplay is based on the KOF series (particularly The King of Fighters 2002), with the same four button configuration and many of the same techniques. However, the game does not use the Team Battle format, but follows the traditional round-based one-on-one format. Each match begins with a dialogue exchange between the player's character and the opponent. One new technique introduced in the game is the Front Grand Step, which allows the player to leap towards the opponent and cancel into a basic attack. The player can perform this technique while guarding from an opponent's attack, which will consume one Power Gauge level.
The game uses a different type of Power Gauge known as the Groove Power Gauge System, which has three levels. The Groove gauge fills as the player lands attacks against the opponents or guard attacks. When the gauge fills to Lv. 1 or Lv. 2, the player can perform Super Special Moves, a Guard Cancel Attack or a Guard Cancel Front Step maneuver. When the gauge is full, its reaches MAXIMUM level and a MAX Activation occurs. During MAX Activation, the gauge will change into a timer and the player gains the ability to cancel any of their moves anytime (in addition to Super Special Moves and Guard Cancels). Once the timer runs out, the gauge returns to Lv. 2.
In addition to the regular Super Special Move, each character also has an Exceed move which can only be performed once when the player's life is less than half.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/svc-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ssideki.zip</path>
		<name>Super Sidekicks</name>
		<desc>SNK's first soccer video game. It features 12 teams divided into two groups which compete for the "SNK Cup" (the main differences between teams is their formations on the field).The players' team plays against all the others in their group, then it goes into an elimination tournament's semifinals and then the final to win the cup.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ssideki-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./superspy.zip</path>
		<name>The Super Spy</name>
		<desc>You are a secret agent sent to infiltrate and enemy base and take out their leader. Armed with your fists, a knife and a pistol, you will have to defeat all enemy soldiers you encounter and rescue any trapped scientists.

The Super Spy is played from a first-person perspective. The actual graphics are done using two-dimensional backgrounds and sprites, but are arranged in such a way so that you view the world from your character's eyes. You can scroll left and right through hallways and enter any doors you come across by pressing forward. You can also walk forward into any vertical hallways you encounter to get to horizontal hallways further in the background. The game consists of a series of levels, all laid out as mazes with horizontal and vertical hallways to traverse.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/superspy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ssideki4.zip</path>
		<name>The Ultimate 11: SNK Football Championship</name>
		<desc>The Ultimate 11 is the fourth game in the Super Sidekicks series. Regional tournaments are replaced with the SNK Football Championship, which is an elimination tournament in which the player's team can select any team from any region to play against. The final team played against in this tournament is the SNK Superstars, which consists of characters from SNK's fighting games. A new addition is the charge bar. It's charged depending on how long a team has the ball, and when full, it can be used when near a goal to make a near-unblockable shot. The game features 80 national teams split into 8 regions:
Europe A: Italy, Spain, Portugal, Wales, France, England, Ireland, Scotland, North Ireland, Iceland
Europe B: Germany, Sweden, Belgium, Denmark, Austria, Holland, Switzerland, Norway, Finland, Croatia
Europe C: Bulgaria, Russia, Turkey, Czech Republic, Romania, Greece, Hungary, Poland, Slovakia, Israel
Africa: Nigeria, Cameroon, Zambia, Côte d'Ivoire, South Africa, Egypt, Morocco, Zimbabwe, Tunisia, Algeria
Americas/Caribbean Sea: United States, Canada, El Salvador, Panama, Guatemala, Mexico, Puerto Rico, Costa Rica, Jamaica, Honduras
South America: Brazil, Colombia, Bolivia, Paraguay, Chile, Argentina, Uruguay, Ecuador, Peru, Venezuela
Asia/Oceania A: Saudi Arabia, India, Iraq, U. A. E., Iran, Qatar, Oman, Bahrain, Kuwait, Uzbekistan
Asia/Oceania B: Australia, China, Taiwan, Thailand, New Zealand, South Korea, Japan, Malaysia, Hong Kong, Singapore</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ssideki4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./neogeo.zip</path>
		<name>NeoGeo BIOS</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ninjamas.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Master's</name>
		<desc>Another one-on-one fighting game straight from the arcades for the Neo Geo. Ninja Master's (sic.) is set on feudal Japan, and tells the story of 10 unique ninjas who fight each other for their own personal reasons and the chance to defeat the evil Nobunaga and bring peace back to Japan.

As expected for the genre, the game pits your selected character against a series of opponents in best-of-3 round matches, with your objective being to deplete your opponents health bar with your basic attacks, special moves (triggered by specific control motions) and super moves (which rely on a power gauge). All the characters in Ninja Master's fight with their weapon of choice, but you can freely choose to put your weapon away and go mano a mano. This does not have a major impact on speed or attack power, but changes the movesets significantly changing the way even basic attacks work.

Uses 2D sprite-based graphics and features 1P or 2P Vs gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ninjamas-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rotd.zip</path>
		<name>Rage of the Dragons</name>
		<desc>Rage of the Dragons is a fighting game based on a story of dragon worshipping and the threatening rise of the evil Black Dragon cult. To stop the rich, powerful, and young man possessed by the Black Dragon, the old master of the Sho Setzu Ken form leaves his dojo for a confrontation. Unfortunately, he's old and weak, and he dies before getting there. His daughter Lynn (White Dragon), pupils Jimmy (Red Dragon) and Billy (Blue Dragon), and many others are swept up into the inevitable conflict. Similar to games like Mortal Combat and Killer Instinct, Rage of the Dragons allows control of 14 different characters each with different moves and powers. The NEO GEO Advanced Entertainment System gets a rare new game with this 2002 release.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/rotd-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20020920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Evoga Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rbff2.zip</path>
		<name>Real Bout Fatal Fury 2: The Newcomers</name>
		<desc>Real Bout 2 revamps the two-line battle system from Real Bout Special. Instead of fighting in either two lines, the player is now forced to fight in a main line, while the second line is a "sway line" used to avoid attacks (similar to the original Real Bout). The one-line trap stages last seen in Fatal Fury Special also return.

The character roster from Real Bout Special returns, including Geese Howard, who is now a normally selectable character, and serves as one of the standard final bosses, alternating with Wolfgang Krauser. However, the extra versions of Tung, Mary, Andy, and Billy are gone. Two new characters are introduced: Li Xiangfei, a Chinese American waitress; and Rick Strowd, a Native American boxer. The game also features biplane pilot Alfred (the protagonist from Dominated Mind, the PlayStation version of Real Bout Special), as a secret final boss.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/rbff2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19980429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./samsh5sp.zip</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown V Special</name>
		<desc>Samurai Shodown V Special is a re-release of the base game, which was the first game in the main series not developed by SNK, but designed by Yuki Enterprise instead. A few problems were corrected in this release, along with the addition of some new features.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/samsh5sp-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20040615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Yuki Enterprise</developer>
		<publisher>Snk Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof99.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters '99: Millennium Battle</name>
		<desc>Two years have passed since the last King of Fighters tournament and no-one has seen Kyo Kusanagi or Iori Yagami since they defeated Orochi at the climax of the 1997 tournament, but out of the blue, new invitations are sent out to many characters, inviting them to a brand new tournament, though this competition is more of a secretive affair than the ones in '96 and '97. Unlike in previous games of the series, there are four characters per team instead of three. In total, there are seven teams, each containing four characters, four Team Edit characters and a boss.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof99-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kof2003.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters 2003</name>
		<desc>The tenth installment in SNK's long running King of Fighters series, and the last KOF to appear on the Neo Geo system. This game's storyline focuses on the unexpected return of the Orochi power, who was thought to have been permenantly sealed away back in 1997 by Kyo Kusanagi, Iori Yagami and Chizuru Kagura. It appears that someone has been tampering with the seal, however...

This year there are 30 characters, 2 edit characters (Kyo Kusanagi and Iori Yagami) and 2 hidden characters (Kusanagi from KOF '02 and Chizuru Kagura) to choose from. There are several returning characters (Jhun Hoon, King, Shingo Yabuki, Hinako Shijou, Billy Kane and Ryuji Yamazaki) and few new fighters as well (Ash Crimson, Shen Woo, Duo Lon, Malin, Adelheid Bernstein and Mukai).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/kof2003-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./alpham2.zip</path>
		<name>Alpha Mission II</name>
		<desc>The lunar nightmare of a bloody 200-year space war was thought to be over in the "original" ALPHA MISSION. But now with the advent of more technically sophisticated weapons, the evil "Fulvar" and his "Seven Star Alliance" have returned to destroy all planets that stand in their way of the ultimate target... Earth! Now in the year of 2525! Your mission as pilot of the new SYD-FX fighter is to use every weapon at your disposal to rid the galaxy once and for all of the evil that now dominates and threatens Earth. So suit up, hold your breath, and stand ready for unbelievable graphics and stereo sound that'll suck you into the far reaches of deep, dark inner space. Be prepared... you may never come back!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/alpham2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ironclad.zip</path>
		<name>Iron Clad Brikin'ger</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/ironclad-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Neo Geo</developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./viewpoin.zip</path>
		<name>Viewpoint</name>
		<desc>One or two players (in hot-seat or cooperative mode) control a spaceship equipped with a laser cannon which can be charged (by holding the shooting button down) for a stronger blast. Besides the main weapon, three special weapons are available: a wall of fire which wipes the screen up in a wave, a nova-like blast and a circle of spherical-green homing missiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/neogeo/viewpoin-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sammy</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20181110T171651</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
