<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Alex Kidd in Miracle World.zip</path>
		<name>Alex Kidd in Miracle World</name>
		<desc>Journey through the planet Aries to the beautiful City of Radactian - and save it from the evil Janken the Great.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Alex Kidd in Miracle World-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alex Kidd in Shinobi World.zip</path>
		<name>Alex Kidd in Shinobi World</name>
		<desc>After ten thousand years, the once banished Dark Ninja returns to make another attempt to take over the Miracle World. Someone's definitely got to stop him! Guess who dares to meet the challenge? You! You're Alex Kidd, the prince who knows no fear.

A lovely girl has been kidnapped and her life is at risk! And she's your girlfriend from the planet Shinobi! By holding her hostage, the Dark Ninja plans to realize his fiendish scheme. She must be saved before it's too late!

You need more than courage to be successful. Transform into a fireball and burn up enemies that come at you. Jump up and across towering walls with your amazing wall-climbing skills. Turn into a tornado and twist your way out. And when you encounter the Dark Ninja, think only of winning. Otherwise you'll lose your girl and, worse yet, the Miracle World will be doomed forever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Alex Kidd in Shinobi World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T023320</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien 3.zip</path>
		<name>Alien 3</name>
		<desc>Alien³ is a video game based on the movie of the same name. The plot of the movie picks up directly after the end of Aliens. Ellen Ripley, the main character of the Alien series, is in cryo-sleep aboard the space ship Sulaco. Unfortunately, an alien or two has stowed away on the Sulaco, and wreaked havoc within the ship. Thus, it crash lands on the prison colony planet Fiorina 161. Ripley and the unarmed prisoners have to figure out a way to survive the aliens terrorizing the colony until help arrives.

The gameplay of the various Alien³ conversions varies from platform to platform. This version is a side-scrolling action game with large maze-like levels. In each level, you have to rescue all the trapped prisoners and then make your way to the exit, all while surviving multiple alien attacks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Alien 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe</developer>
		<publisher>Arena</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044128</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>The search is on! Mickey is on the trail of a wicked Witch named Mizrabel, who has kidnapped Minnie. Mickey must find seven gems hidden in the fantastic chambers of Mizrabel's Castle of Illusion and use them to save Minnie. Can Mickey find them? It's up to you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T001747</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck.zip</path>
		<name>Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck</name>
		<desc>Uncle Scrooge found a magical necklace on a mysterious island, but the necklace put a curse on him. Now Uncle Scrooge is doomed to float around in the air forever! (Of course Donald always said Scrooge was full of hot air anyway!) To take the curse off Uncle Scrooge, Donald has to take the necklace back to the island. But there's plenty of danger awaiting Donald there. How about lending him a hand?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930511T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin.zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin</name>
		<desc>As Aladdin, baffle the guards in the streets of Agrabah. Elude the tempting traps in the Cave of Wonders, and the dangers of the Sultan's Palace. Ride the magic carpet through breathtaking skies. Then challenge the evil Jafar to a duel of swords and magic!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Aladdin-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sims</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170204T013315</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Axe Warrior.zip</path>
		<name>Golden Axe Warrior</name>
		<desc>World peace is at stake! Death Adder, a wicked giant, has stolen the nine crystals from the kingdom of Firewood and has hidden them in nine labyrinths that he has created. These nine magic crystals protected the people from evil – especially from Death Adder's grasp. But now that the crystals are lost, the world is defenseless!

Someone must put an end to the fiend's realm of darkness, death and destruction! Do you have what it takes to bring back peace and happiness? Trek through deep, dark forests and sail across vast, stormy seas. Chop down trees with your Battle Axe and move rocks with your magic spells to find secret caves. When you take on Death Adder's gruesome monsters, think only of winning – or else you won't find the nine crystals. And when you do, you'll find the Golden Axe – the only weapon that can crush Death Adder!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Golden Axe Warrior-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golvellius.zip</path>
		<name>Golvellius: Valley of Doom</name>
		<desc>Enter the world of Golvellius. Where demons rule the valley of water...and control the creatures of land, sea and air. Where almost everyone stands against you. There is only one way in...and no way out except victory or death!

It's an adventure that will take you across deserts and mountains, oceans and forests...through eerie graveyards and caves filled with danger and surprise.

Golvellius has a PASSWORD SAVE feature that lets you keep all your possessions. So you never have to start an adventure empty handed!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Golvellius-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19880814T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>Journey with Mickey Mouse through spooky castle ruins, dark caverns, an enchanted forest and a toy shop gone crazy! Use your wits and Mickey's magic to evade challenging traps, explore secret passages, and restore peace and happiness to the Land of Illusion!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>Legend of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>Legend of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse, known in Japan as Mickey Mouse Densetsu no Oukoku, is a Sega Master System and Sega Game Gear platform game featuring Disney's Mickey Mouse. It is the sequel to Land of Illusion. The Master System version was released exclusively in Brazil by Tectoy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Legend of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect</developer>
		<publisher>Tec Toy</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044139</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Master of Darkness.zip</path>
		<name>Master of Darkness</name>
		<desc>The shadow of Dracula has spread over Victorian England. Make your way through strange and forbidding streets and cavernous warehouses while fighting his army of monsters. Find Dracula, the Master of Darkness, and rescue England from his terrifying grasp.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Master of Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sims</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170209T003205</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
		<desc>The Dragon Ninja village has been massacred! The powerful scroll of the Bushido has been stolen! You are Ryu Hayabusa, last of the Dragon Ninjas, and you must find the Bushido before it can be used to unleash evil across the Earth!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Ninja Gaiden-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SIMS</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170207T231959</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Penguin Land.zip</path>
		<name>Penguin Land</name>
		<desc>The game begins where three penguin eggs are lost on a distant planet. The player controls the Penguin Mission Commander Overbite, who must guide these eggs down to the bottom of a frigid cavern filled with traps, enemies, and secret passages. The Spaceship Crew eagerly awaits at the bottom of this cavern to welcome the hero Overbite and carry the egg to safety.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Penguin Land-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Pony Canyon</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star.zip</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star</name>
		<desc>The time: Space Century 3240. The place: The Algol Star System. It began when King Lassic turned evil and let hordes of hideous, magical creatures run amok on the three planets. When her brother was killed, Alis vowed to avenge his death and put an end to Lassic forever.

Join her in a journey across time and space to worlds where creatures speak...where magic and science combine to take you on the ultimate video quest.

Phantasy Star is total adventure role playing with towns full of people and shops...16 level dungeons full of traps and treasure...three companions who will help you if you find them and some of the most awesome graphics ever put in a video game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Phantasy Star-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7571399999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19871220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rambo - First Blood Part II.zip</path>
		<name>Rambo: First Blood Part II</name>
		<desc>Rambo must tranverse six zones from bottom to top while defending against waves of enemies, ending with a boss at the end of the stage. 

Rambo is armed with a machinegun that can only shoot upwards, left and right, as well as in diagonal between the mentioned directions. He also counts with explosive arrows that are limited in quantity but can be shot in eight directions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Rambo - First Blood Part II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rescue Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Rescue Mission</name>
		<desc>It's war... and your buddies are trapped behind enemy lines! Before they can escape, they urgently need medical attention... and desperately need your help! You're an Army sharpshooter. You have the Sega Light Phaser and lightning-fast reflexes. Now, you are going on a hero's mission to save your friends. With only a railroad handcart for transportation, you're taking three combat medics deep into enemy territory. They'll take care of your friends. Your job: shoot down everything the enemy throws at them... and you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Rescue Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog.zip</path>
		<name>Sonic the Hedgehog</name>
		<desc>Bust the video game speed barrier wide open with Sonic The Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the Super Sonic Spin Attack. Plummet down tunnels and spin through space. Bounce around 'til you're dizzy in a pinball machine. You've never seen anything like it!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Sonic The Hedgehog-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck.zip</path>
		<name>The Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck</name>
		<desc>Evil Magica De Spell has stolen the Lucky Dimes and has captured Huey, Dewey and Louie! Trek through six treacherous lands with Donald to save his nephews and retrieve the Lucky Dimes!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy III - The Dragon's Trap.zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy III: The Dragon's Trap</name>
		<desc>Get ready for the third Wonder Boy adventure! To save Monster Land from the evil Meka Dragon, you've entered his castle and are about to go into battle. If you defeat the dragon, a terrible surprise awaits you...a curse! You'll turn into a lizard-man, and more. The only way you can return to human form is to find the Salamander Cross, a magical item with the power to remove curses.

But where is it hidden? Finding it is an adventure that will take you across strange lands, against strange creatures, into battles where you never know what strange shape you'll turn into! Hawk-man, Lion-man and more! You'll be able to buy armor, weapons and use magic items! Hidden rooms hold even greater surprises!

Can you beat the dragon's bosses and recover the Salamander Cross? When you look at the shape you're in, it's your only hope!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Wonder Boy III - The Dragon's Trap-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy in Monster Land.zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy in Monster Land</name>
		<desc>Wonder Boy is back! But this time he's playing for keeps. No more cute dolls, fruit or milk.

Now it's swords, armor, shields, labyrinths and fire breathing dragons.
Help Wonder Boy through 12 perilous, monster filled levels of challenging adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Wonder Boy in Monster Land-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ancient Ys Vanished Omen.zip</path>
		<name>Ys: The Vanished Omens</name>
		<desc>The hero of Ys is an adventurous young swordsman named Adol Christin. As the story begins, he has just arrived at the Town of Minea, in the land of Esteria. He is called upon by Sara, a fortuneteller, who tells him of a great evil that is sweeping the land.

Adol is informed that he must seek out the six Books of Ys. These books contain the history of the ancient land of Ys, and will give him the knowledge he needs to defeat the evil forces. Sara gives Adol a crystal for identification and instructs him to find her aunt in Zepik Village, who holds the key to retrieving one of the Books. With that, his quest begins.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Ancient Ys Vanished Omen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19881014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zillion II - The Tri Formation.zip</path>
		<name>Zillion II: The Tri Formation</name>
		<desc>They're at it again. The dreaded Norsa Empire is back... and stronger than ever before. This time they won't make any mistakes. Others have tried to stop them and all have failed. The evil Baron Ricks knows you are coming. And it's a trap! But you're the galaxy's last hope. Can you do what's never been done before?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mastersystem/Zillion II - The Tri Formation-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
