<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Dracula X - Rondo Of Blood.cue</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula X: Chi no Rondo</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has returned and captured the young woman close to the famous vampire hunter, Richter Belmont. Will Richter be able to defeat Dracula and rescue his girlfriend in this new CD powered adventure?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Dracula X - Rondo Of Blood-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T022207</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Action.cue</path>
		<name>Kaze Kiri: Ninja Action</name>
		<desc>Kaze Kiri takes place in Feudal Japan where the kingdom princess Shizuhime is abducted by a group of mysterious ninjas. A feared swordsman called Kaze Kiri, hero of the game, is given the task to rescue the poor girl and restore order. Our ninja can can use a broad variety of fightings skills - he can run, jump, dash and slash without mercy anyone who gets in his way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Ninja Action-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical_Fantasy_Adventure_-_Popful_Mail_(NTSC-J)_[HECD4011].cue</path>
		<name>Popful Mail: Magical Fantasy Adventure</name>
		<desc>Kazyr, Necros, Ulgar. Ghosts from the past that nearly once destroyed Popful Mail's world. Now, the Black Seal is about to be broken so they can return to wreak havoc on the world once again. Three ragtag adventurers become the only hope of stopping the second coming of Evil. Play as Mail, tomboy bounty-hunter wannabe who's handy with a blade, Tatt, the ultra-polite apprentice magician with a deadly staff, or Gaw, a winged blue blob with breath of fire, as you search for the manicial Muttonhead, who holds all the answers. During your quest, change characters at any time! You'll need to, because Nuts Cracker and the minions of Evil will stop at nothing to end your party before it starts! And, thanks to the storage power of CD, Popful Mail comes alive with over 2.5 hours of spoken dialogue and 20 minutes of heart-pounding animation. Face it, your butt's gonna be glued to the couch till the credits roll!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Magical_Fantasy_Adventure_-_Popful_Mail_(NTSC-J)_[HECD4011]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940812T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HuneX</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Interchannel</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis III.cue</path>
		<name>Valis III</name>
		<desc>King Glames leads denizens of the Dark World to destroy both Earth and Vecanti. Against this common foe, Yuko Asou finds help in her new girlfriend, a Vecanti warrior-maiden named Cham, who was born in the Dark World and uses a deadly whip, and her own sister Valna Asou, who grew up within Vecanti and became strong in the ways of magic. Furthermore, the Valis sword is shown to be capable of more than what Yuko has accomplished with it thus far.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Valis III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telnet Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170206T060512</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis IV - The Fantasm Soldier.cue</path>
		<name>Valis IV</name>
		<desc>Yuko has become the goddess of the world of Vecanti and has watched over the world in peace since the defeat of Glames. Trouble brews when the Dark World prince named Galgear begins to search for a magical ring. This ring increases his powers, but to the loss of control he could have maintained under its effects, and the gods of Vecanti recognize this and imprison Galgear inside a crystal sunk into the ocean.

Fifteen years pass, and Galgear manages to break out of his prison, kidnapping the former heroine Valna and being pursued by troops led by Cham as a result. A member of her band, named Lena Brande, requests permission to infiltrate Galgear's stronghold and free Valna.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Valis IV - The Fantasm Soldier-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telnet Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170207T231819</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys Book I &amp; II.cue</path>
		<name>Ys Book I &amp; II</name>
		<desc>Journey through the Ancient Land of Ys, a once peaceful and prosperous country suddenly thrust deep into an empty abyss of isolation. The secret to restoring peace rests in the six books of the wise priests. 700 years have passed, and now you have a chance to unlock the mystery. Stunning graphics, intense stereo sound and profound gameplay make this a CD adventure you'll never forget ... and may never return from.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Ys Book I &amp; II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys.cue</path>
		<name>Ys IV: The Dawn of Ys</name>
		<desc>Two years after defeating Darm and bringing peace to Esteria, Adol returns to the town of Minea with his companion in adventure, Dogi. Everything seems fine as friends are reunited and the people hail their hero, but there’s an unseen evil looming in the air. As Adol goes to the seer Sara, she tells him of an even greater darkness in the land of Celceta and asks the red-haired swordsman to go there and seek the truth behind this mystery. Thus, Adol steals away unnoticed in the middle of the night to embark on his next adventure.

In Celceta, Adol will learn of the Romun Empire’s ambitions, fight the mysterious Clan of Darkness that seeks to ressurect their long dead leader, and discover the ancient history of Celceta itself as well as its connection to the land of Ys. The last survivor of a forgotten race of winged beings holds the power that may bring back darkness to the land, and only Adol will be able to stop it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faussete Amour.cue</path>
		<name>FausettÉ amour</name>
		<desc>This is the adventures of Koruku Ransu, a young blue-haired warrior. The evil lord Goat Bone has kidnaped her beloved sister and also controls the minds of most of her best friends. Koruku wears a strong pink armor  Through seven long stages, one of Kokuru's friend awaits at the end of each one of them - however, she will have to defeat their dark side first and free their controlled minds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Faussete Amour-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AIM</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170210T021422</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius II - Gofer no Yabou (J).cue</path>
		<name>Gradius II: Gofer no Yabou</name>
		<desc>Two years after its last epic battle, the GRADIUS army recommissions the VIC VIPER superdimensional warplane to combat the invasion of a new nemesis known as GOFER. Piloting the latest model of the VIC VIPER, players can select between multiple WEAPON MODULES and SHIELDS to tackle the varying stages and enemy attack patterns they come up against. With a total of nine stages, this perfect port of the original boasts one of the longest adventures in the series and features more of its trademark fast-paced background music to accompany the intense action!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/tgcd/Gradius II - Gofer no Yabou (J)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
 Go