<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajo Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku.pbp</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula X: Gekka no Yasoukyoku</name>
		<desc>Known in Japan as Akumajou Dracula X: Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Demon Castle Dracula X: Nocturne in the Moonlight), this game takes place after the first Dracula X game (specifically, “Dracula X: Rondo of Blood”). You play as Alucard, a returning hero from the third installment of the series on the NES. Alucard is Dracula’s son, who had gone into a deep sleep for many years until he was awakened by the return of Dracula’s castle.

As Alucard, you have a large number of equipment to choose from (daggers, one-handed swords, two-handed swords, fist-type weapons, rods, as well as armor, shields, capes, helmets, accessories, and usable items). Many people will play through this game many times and still not see all of the items within. That’s how many items there are!

Alucard has many techniques at his disposal. First, he has a large set of spells (about 10 or so) that he can perform by using his MP (one of the three main statistics, in addition to HP and Hearts). He can transform into a Wolf, Bat, and Mist (each of which has a few abilities of their own). He also gets familiars of varying types (demons, faeries, and even a sentient sword) to help fight his enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Akumajo Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19970320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T010744</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare.pbp</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark: The New Nightmare</name>
		<desc>Set on October 31, 2001. Edward Carnby's best friend and partner, Charles Fiske, has been found dead off the coast of Shadow Island, a mysterious island near the coast of Massachusetts. Carnby's investigation quickly leads him to Frederick Johnson, who informs him of Fiske's search for three ancient tablets with the ability to unlock an incredible and dangerous power. Johnson pleads with Carnby to take the place of Fiske and reopen the investigation in order to recover the tablets. Carnby accepts and makes it his mission to find Fiske's killer. Johnson introduces Edward to Aline Cedrac, an intelligent, young university professor. She joins Edward to recover the missing tablets and assist Professor Obed Morton, who she believes to be her father. While flying over the coast of Shadow Island, Edward and Aline's plane comes under attack by an unknown creature. Edward and Aline both jump out of the plane and parachute to the ground, but are separated immediately. Edward lands in the dense forest just outside a manor, while Aline lands on the roof of said manor.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Darkworks</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assault Retribution.pbp</path>
		<name>Assault: Retribution</name>
		<desc>Assault: Retribution supplies you with some of the best firepower modern technology can provide, as well as various customization options to ensure "better living through quick death disbursement." Washington utilizes a barrage of destructive weaponry such as the P-420 Multi-Phase Pulse Rifle and the aptly named Cutter; Doyle uses a variety of Homing Missiles, Beam Lasers, and the D-16 Magnetic Bolt Accelerator. There's also a plethora of pickups including weapon upgrades, health, ammunition recharges, smart bombs, extra lives, and shields. Save points within each level let you resume the killing when it is most convenient for you. And (rare as of 1999), there is a two-player cooperative mode in case you feel that one ultimate killing machine just isn't enough.

Assault: Retribution is a 3D platform shooting game that takes place across seven futuristic levels, includes two playable characters with alternate routes, analog control, and memory card support. You can't spell action, adrenaline or assault with out an "A," so go out and kick a few!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Assault Retribution-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Candle Light Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T233602</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brave Fencer Musashi.pbp</path>
		<name>Brave Fencer Musashi</name>
		<desc>150 years ago, the legendary warrior known as the Brave Fencer Musashi saved the kingdom of Allucaneet from the evil Wizard of Darkness. Now, his spirit is reincarnated in a young, rather short-tempered boy. Fillet, the princess of Allucaneet, summons the reluctant hero to the palace and gives him the powerful sword Fusion, which he needs to defeat the evil Thirstquencher Empire. It soon turns out that the Empire is after another legendary sword, Lumina, so Musashi's first task is to get it before the bad guys do!..

Brave Fencer Musashi is an action game with strong RPG elements. Controlling Musashi, the player explores the pre-rendered backgrounds from third person view (similarly to Final Fantasy VII), visiting towns, talking to NPCs, etc. There is a day/night cycle in the game, which is manifested in the schedules of NPCs and/or monsters, as well as Musashi's fatigue level, which increases if he doesn't sleep enough. Musashi uses the two swords, Fusion and Lumina, to fight his enemies. The two swords have different properties: while Fusion behaves more or less like a traditional melee weapon, Lumina needs to be imbued with various elemental items in order to unleash powerful attacks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Brave Fencer Musashi-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Cross.pbp</path>
		<name>Chrono Cross</name>
		<desc>Chrono Cross features standard RPG gameplay with some differences. Players advance the game by controlling the protagonist Serge through the game's world, primarily by foot and boat. Navigation between areas is conducted via an overworld map, much like Chrono Trigger's, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Around the island world are villages, outdoor areas, and dungeons, through which the player moves in three dimensions. Locations such as cities and forests are represented by more realistically scaled field maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Like Chrono Trigger, the game features no random encounters; enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Chrono Cross-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Einhander.pbp</path>
		<name>Einhander</name>
		<desc>In 2192, a new city, Selene, is built on the moon. Over the years, Selene grows larger, more powerful, and more independent of the Earth - to the point that the moon and Earth battle in a war that winds down without a definite victory for either side. In 2242, war breaks out again - the Earth slowly begins to win... except for the efforts of an experimental Selene technology known as Einhänders: flying machines with a "hand" that allows them to change weaponry mid-battle.

On December 12, 2245, Selene sends down 3 Einhänders in a last attempt to turn the tide of the war. You get to choose the craft to pilot, and it's up to you to battle your way through the Earth's monstrous defenses and win the battle.

The game is a traditional side-scrolling shooter, with rendered 3D backgrounds and enemies. The atmosphere of the game is very "industrial", down to the German industrial music playing in the background (think Einsturzende Neubauten mixed with Lords of Acid). The weapon-switching and claiming is an integral part of the game, as weapons have limited shots. This forces a bit more strategy than the usual button-mashing shooters inspire.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Einhander-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IX.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IX</name>
		<desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy IX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VIII.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VIII</name>
		<desc>A member of an elite military team, Squall is forced into a conflict beyond imagination.  To survive, he must contend with a desperate rival, a powerful sorceress, and his own mysterious dreams.

* Realistic, detailed characters and background graphics enhanced by a breathtaking musical score
* An epic story based on the theme of love, set in a massive new world
* New Junction System allows characters to be customized with powerful magic spells drawn from enemies
* Nearly an hour of stunning motion-captured CG cinemas seamlessly integrated into gameplay</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy VIII-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunners Heaven.pbp</path>
		<name>Gunner's Heaven</name>
		<desc>Load up: High-velocity, Self-Targeting, Incinerator or Riot Control - it's the last word in close-combat shoot'em ups.
Also known as Rapid Reload.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gunners Heaven-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media.Vision Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve.pbp</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve</name>
		<desc>THE CINEMATIC RPG

One of them is a police officer. The other is possessed by an ancient evil threatening all life on Earth. The horrifying bond between them will continue until something dies.
A chilling adventure that could only come from the creators of Final Fantasy VII
An epic sci-fi tale told through stunning 3D rendered sequences
Battle mutant monsters in real-time polygon combat
Customize weapons, armor, and character abilities</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Parasite Eve-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill.pbp</path>
		<name>Silent Hill</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill is a 1999 survival horror video game for the PlayStation. The first in a series about a mysterious town of the same name, Silent Hill generated a direct sequel, three indirect sequels, a prequel and a film adaptation. The game was included in Sony's Greatest Hits and Platinum Range of budget titles as a result of strong sales. A reinterpretation of the game was developed for the Wii, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable.
The plot focuses on Harry Mason as he searches for his daughter, Cheryl, who has disappeared following a car accident which left Harry unconscious. He finds Silent Hill to be largely abandoned, shrouded in a thick fog, snowing out of season, filled with monsters and being over taken by a hellish otherworld. As Harry scours the town, he begins learning about the history of Silent Hill and stumbles upon a cult ritual undertaken to bring a god to Earth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Silent Hill-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Silent, Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Blade.pbp</path>
		<name>Soul Blade</name>
		<desc>In the 16th century, a sword surfaces that is so powerful, so evil that warriors from all over the globe seek it out. It is Soul Edge, a demon blade. From America to Europe to Japan, these warriors fight each other for the chance to obtain it. Soul Blade is a 3D weapons fighting game that chronicles their story.

A complete 3D fighting game that allows for side steps, Soul Blade has twelve colorful fighters (ten standard, two hidden, plus additional costumes for a few fighters), each with various weapons and styles. The first ten can be used in all the combat modes, while the hidden two can only be used in versus and arcade mode.

Namco enhanced the arcade version (called Soul Edge) by adding a well done CGI intro, plus a story mode to the addition of the traditional team, survival, and time attack modes. The story mode goes into greater detail about each character, and is presented in an ancient book format. The story mode also allows you to unlock more of each characters' extra weapons. These weapons, which vary in lengths, stats, and durability, add to the options available players in the versus mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Soul Blade-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Threads of Fate.pbp</path>
		<name>Threads of Fate</name>
		<desc>Two Amazing Adventures!

Rue is on a quest to revive a lost friend. Mint is seeking power and revenge. Both of them are looking for a powerful relic, but which will be brave and clever enough to reach their goal?
Explore a beautifully rendered 3D world filled with challenging puzzles, unusual enemies, and unknown dangers
Play as both characters to encounter two entirely different storylines
Rue has the ability to shape-shift into the forms of defeated enemies
Mint can learn and use a wide variety of powerful magic spells</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Threads of Fate-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - Racing.pbp</path>
		<name>007: Racing</name>
		<desc>Be Bond, Behind The Wheel
Pay attention, 007. This is for your eyes only. Q-Branch has re-engineered some of your favorite automobiles with additional gadgets and firepower. You'll need everything they've got, plus your own uncanny ability to beat the odds. The free world is depending on you. Oh, one other thing before you go 007--try to bring them back in one piece.

MISSION BRIEFING
• Q-branch Vehicles - BMW, Aston Martin, and Lotus
• Exciting Missions &amp; Beautiful Women
• Ingenious Gadgets - Smoke Screens, Stinger Missiles, and More
• Dangerous Assailants Interfere From Air, Sea and Ground
• 2-player Action</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/007 - Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20101121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - The World Is Not Enough.pbp</path>
		<name>007: The World Is Not Enough</name>
		<desc>Experience the intensity of being the world's top secret agent. Equipped with a full arsenal of Q-Lab gadgets and weaponry, you must be suave and resourceful as you carry out action-packed missions based on the blockbuster movie. Are you cool under pressure? Cunning when necessary? Of course you are--you're Bond... James Bond.

• Bond's Best Missions! Battle through 10 exciting levels with a variety of objectives.
• Over 20 Q-Lab Gadgets and Weapons! Bond's P2K, Infrared Glasses, Cell Phone Stunner, and many more.
• All new 3D Engine! High-resolution textures, fast framerate and amazing view distances make this the best-looking POV game on the PlayStation game console.
• Improved AI! Enemies will react to you, communicate with each other, and even retreat!
• Authentic Dialogue! Interact with other characters and experience movie-like cinematics with full speech.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/007 - The World Is Not Enough-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20001108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Ops Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - Tomorrow Never Dies.pbp</path>
		<name>007: Tomorrow Never Dies</name>
		<desc>As suave secret agent 007, employ your cunning wit and high-tech gadgets to survive multiple levels of espionage based on exciting situations from the blockbuster film. Including challenging shooting, driving, and skiing game modes. Your mission will be dangerous, but you can handle it. After all, you're Bond... James Bond.
The Most Complete Bond Experience!

• Multiple game modes! 3rd-person shooting, driving and skiing
• Classic Bond weapons and gadgets - Cufflink Lasers, Infrared Cameras, and more!
• Use a variety of combat techniques - Tuck-and-roll, dive-and-fire, and stealth attacks
• Follow the storyline with in-game cinematics and movie footage</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/007 - Tomorrow Never Dies-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19991116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Ops Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure of Little Ralph.pbp</path>
		<name>Adventure Of Little Ralph</name>
		<desc>The Adventure of Little Ralph is a 2D platformer. In this game the player controls Ralph, who has been turned back into a child by the evil demons who have invaded his homeland. In order to stop them and return to his former self, he must get through each area filled with enemies, traps, and many hidden routes. Ralph is armed with swords and various magic powers and also has the assistance of a small furry companion. The game's levels are interconnected, unlike the "stages" of most other platform games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Adventure of Little Ralph-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>New Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Agent Armstrong.pbp</path>
		<name>Agent Armstrong</name>
		<desc>Your headed for a showdown in crime dens all over the world. Agent Armstrong's a serious challenge for law abiding citizens everywhere. Features over 30 missions created in glorious 3D polygon graphics. A huge array of weapons, locations, bad guys and a stirring musical score.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Agent Armstrong-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King of the Jungle</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akuji The Heartless.pbp</path>
		<name>Akuji the Heartless</name>
		<desc>In Akuji: The Heartless the player takes the role of Akuji, a voodoo-priest. The title of the game is meant to be taken literally as Akuji's wedding day brought a problem with it: his brother kills him and rips out his heart. Now Akuji has to travel through the underworld to get back to the living and take his revenge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Akuji The Heartless-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Resurrection.pbp</path>
		<name>Alien Resurrection</name>
		<desc>Two hundred years after the events of Alien³, Lieutenant Ellen Ripley is cloned by military scientists interested in the Alien Queen she had become a host for. Like the "Company" from the earlier films, the military intends to use the Queen to breed a force of bio-weapons. But then something goes wrong; the Aliens they are studying manage to escape, and swarm throughout the science ship. It's up to four stranded heroes - Ripley, Call, DiStephano and Christie - to wipe out the Aliens, and return the ship safely to Earth.

Gameplay is standard FPS action, with limited ammo and plenty of hazards to detour around or find the switch to deactivate. The player switches between the four main characters at each level change, each with a slightly different set of abilities (Call has a motion tracker, Christie has his twin pistols from the film). Levels are based around keeping the Auriga running, and making their way through the ship to escape.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Alien Resurrection-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Trilogy.pbp</path>
		<name>Alien Trilogy</name>
		<desc>Alien Trilogy features all the gut-churning fear of the complete Alien saga in one black-death, white-knuckle nightmare. Welcome to the first-person, 3-D blitzkrieg of overwhelming horror that no one can resist! This is the hottest game around!

You're Ripley...and you're facing over 30 levels of hell!
They've lost contact with the colonists on LV426. The Company sent you there to find out what happened. You hope that there is just some communications problem...but deep down, you know... they're back!
But you haven't come unprepared. You're packing the state-of-the-art alien-killer tool kit!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Alien Trilogy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ape Escape.pbp</path>
		<name>Ape Escape</name>
		<desc>Ape Escape is arguably one of PlayStation's most original platform titles. The game exclusively used Sony's Dual Shock controller and required the player to use both analog sticks to control the game's hero. Ape Escape is the story of a band of rogue monkeys that escape from the amusement park and mistakenly break into a genius professor's laboratory. They find the inventions called the Peak Point Helmets and instantly become intelligent, with a particularly ingenious simian named Specter running the others. In a theme reminiscent of Planet of the Apes, these little creeps plan on changing history so that apes rule the world and humankind becomes the special attraction at amusement parks. The premise was damn cool...and more importantly, it had monkeys!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ape Escape-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Apocalypse.pbp</path>
		<name>Apocalypse</name>
		<desc>APOCALYPSE starring BRUCE WILLIS
The end of the world is near. You're Bruce, starring as Trey Kincaid, nano-physicist and sole defender of the world. It's up to you to defeat the Four Horsemen before it's happy trails to us all...

IT'S RAW ACTION
Take control of Bruce Willis, one of the greatest action stars of all time, motion-captured and cyberscanned for the most intense hard-core action ever. Killer cinematics unveil a doomsday plot.

DESTROY IT ALL
Explore multi-level war factories, prisons, sewers and more. Level everything to the ground in 360 degree battle-anywhere environments that echo with explosive sound effects.

LOCK AND LOAD
Brave the dismal future against up to 20 on-screen enemies. Good thing you can don multiple weapons at once like rip lasers, flame-throwers, semi-automatics, and homing missiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Apocalypse-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19981027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Area 51.pbp</path>
		<name>Area 51</name>
		<desc>This is the home port of the popular arcade light gun game. This home version has special bonuses and additional secret levels not found in the arcade. Using a light gun (or a mouse, if available) you blast your way through the secret base, Area 51, which has been taken over by mutant aliens.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Area 51-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mesa Logic</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Army Men Air Attack.pbp</path>
		<name>Army Men: Air Attack</name>
		<desc>The green and tan armies once again battle, this time in the air via the huey(agile helicopter), chinook(Double rotor heavyweight lifting helicopter), Super Stallion and Apache. The tan army are not the only enemies. Insects also get in the way. You must protect tanks, trucks, other helicopters, a train and even a UFO.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Army Men Air Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Army Men Air Attack 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Army Men: Air Attack 2</name>
		<desc>Army Men: Air Attack 2, the sequel to the PlayStation's Army Men: Air Attack, has Captain Blade and his Alpha Wolf Squadron returning to action to continue the now infamous battles between the Green and Tan armies. The sequel features over twenty-five new missions with highly improved graphics, fully interactive environments, and gameplay reminiscent of Electronic Arts' Strike series.

Air Attack 2 has the same gameplay found in the first Air Attack game. You can move in all directions in this plastic 3D world using the left analog stick, strafe using the L1 and R1 buttons, and deploy various artillery, as well as use your chopper's winch, using the controller's face buttons. The different military hardware at your disposal depends on the helicopter and copilot you select between missions. These choices also have an impact on other aspects of the gameplay, such as weapons accuracy, winch speed, chopper speed, and the amount of abuse your craft can handle. These features offer nothing new in the way of gameplay, but their tight and responsive control more than make up for that.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Army Men Air Attack 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master.pbp</path>
		<name>Blaster Master: Blasting Again</name>
		<desc>Years ago, the Earth was threatened by an evil being known as the Plutonium Boss. The Plutonium Boss and his minions were devouring the Earth from within, and if they had succeeded, Earth would've been destroyed.

He didn't count on a young man named Jason, a beautiful alien woman named Eve, and their battle tank, the Sofia MA-01...because of his underestimation, the Plutonium Boss was defeated.

Since then, Jason had been defending the Earth from any threat that arises, with Eve by his side. She even bore him two children, Roddy and Elfie. Jason trained Elfie in engineering, and Roddy in battling in Sofia. But now Jason and Eve have died, and Roddy must take his father's place as defender of the Earth.

And an old threat seems to be arising to challenge this new generation of heroes...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Blaster Master-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SunSoft</developer>
		<publisher>SunSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloody Roar.pbp</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar</name>
		<desc>BLOODY ROAR pits eight fighters with unique "Spirit Animals" against each other. Don't just beat your opponents; pummel them into the ground by using combo after combo, or transforming into the character's "Spirit Animal," which might be a killer rabbit, gorilla, fox, or something else, entirely. See the moment of victory with instant replays that show the blow that put the loser down for good. Every fighter is involved in the tournament for his or her own reasons, and you can play as each of the characters to learn those reasons. With all of the action in BLOODY ROAR, the beast in you just might come out.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Bloody Roar-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bloody Roar 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Bloody Roar 2</name>
		<desc>Transform and do battle as a human-animal hybrid in this classic 3D fighting game! Put your strength to the test and fight your way to the top!

The hook of the Bloody Roar series is that your combatants can transform into animalistic versions of themselves -- human-animal hybrids with a thirst for violence. During each round you can fight as a person or transform into a beast when your meter fills up. As an animal you'll have more moves at your disposal with which to destroy your opponent.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Bloody Roar 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting/Raizing</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BRAHMA Force - The Assault on Beltlogger 9.pbp</path>
		<name>BRAHMA Force: The Assault on Beltlogger 9</name>
		<desc>A mech-based FPS; pilot your Bipedal Robotic Assault Heavy Mechanized Armor (built by Bronx Industries, of course) through the Beltlogger 9 excavation colony...

...discover what happened to the Beltlogger 9 colony- it may be related to the events on Probe Ship Mina 3, wherein a lone person apparently under the control of an outside intelligence slaughtered his shipmates.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/BRAHMA Force - The Assault on Beltlogger 9-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Genki Co.</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire III.pbp</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire III</name>
		<desc>A MYSTERIOUS POWER...AN UNLIKELY HERO...A CLASSIC ADVENTURE...

The lone survivor of a legendary dragon clan, a rebellious youth embarks on a great journey. One of discovery... and danger. The classic role-playing game now returns to continue the epic tales of Ryu and the dragon people. An inner power of uncertain origin matures Ryu into a warrior who ponders his purpose as he embarks on a mystical journey. What lies ahead is shrouded in mystery... yet strangely familiar.

DRAGON GENE SPLICING
LEGENDARY ROLEPLAYING
AN EPIC 3-D ENVIRONMENT
LEARN OR STEAL ADVANCE SKILLS AND TECHNIQUES
POWERFUL MAGIC

NOW YOU POSSESS THE POWER TO CONTROL RYU'S DESTINY.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Breath of Fire III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire IV.pbp</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire IV</name>
		<desc>Stunning New and Improved Graphics - High Resolution, Animated Characters in Vast 3-D Worlds

More Than 200 Spells to Learn and Master - Unlock New Magic From Opponents

2 Epic Intertwining Storylines - Follow the Fates of Ryu and Fou-Lu - A Classic RPG Adventure!
One Princess. Two War-Torn Lands.
An Epic Quest for Peace

After centuries of war, the two lands bordering an impenetrable swampland have finally reached an armistice. Mysteriously, the noble Princess Elena disappears somewhere near the war-ravaged front lines. Distraught, her sister Nina goes in search of the Princess alone and on her journey, meets a mysterious, young warrior named Ryu. Their destinies soon entwine. The next chapter in the epic tale of magic and mystery now unfolds. The fate of what lies ahead rests in your control.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Breath of Fire IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs and Taz.pbp</path>
		<name>Bugs Bunny &amp; Taz: Time Busters</name>
		<desc>Daffy Duck has somehow managing to break Granny's time regulator, causing himself and the Time Gem that acts as the heart of the regulator to be pitched back into the shrouded annals of history. Well, if there are two people you know to call when it comes to times of crisis they would be Bugs Bunny and ... Taz? Well, regardless of the intelligence of the decision, Bugs and Taz will have to work together on this mission, traveling through four different eras in a quest to find Daffy, recover the Time Gem and set things back to the way they ought to be.

Take control of the two famous Warner Bros. characters in Bugs Bunny &amp; Taz: Time Busters for the PlayStation. You will alternate between the wise-cracking rabbit and the Tasmanian eating machine in an attempt to rescue the Time Crystal and Daffy. To do so, they'll have to use the Time Regulator themselves, blasting back through four different eras to complete their quest. These time periods are The Aztec Era, The Viking Era, The Arabian Era and Transylvanian Era.

Each character has his own set of moves, from Bugs' quickness to Taz's spinning fury. You can play each of the characters at any point, calling your friend to your location and switching between them, occasionally using them at nearly the same time to get past a given obstacle. If you don't want to play the game alone, you can even bring in a second friend to play the other character.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Bugs and Taz-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind and Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./C-12 Final Resistance.pbp</path>
		<name>C-12: Final Resistance</name>
		<desc>C-12: Final Resistance is set in the aftermath of a hostile ground invasion of Earth by ravaging alien forces. At first, the purpose of the invasion is unknown, but to the horror of all surviving humans, the objective soon becomes clear: the aliens plan to harvest all non-radioactive carbon from planet Earth (thus the title C-12).

Most of the human race has been decimated, and those captured alive are used for "droning," the process by which the aliens reprogram humans into cyborg warriors.

It is up to you, playing as resistance fighter Riley Vaughan, to save the Earth from impending doom. Armed with an imaging unit that has been implanted to replace his left eye, as well as a powerful arsenal of weapons, Vaughan must complete tasks, collect items, and destroy the enemy in order to carry out his missions and uncover the secrets behind the alien invasion.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/C-12 Final Resistance-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./C - The Contra Adventure.pbp</path>
		<name>C: The Contra Adventure</name>
		<desc>Mission Critical!

You control Ray, the only surviving member of the elite Contra Force. Blast your way through 10 levels to stop the alien hordes from infesting the jungles of South America.

Although equipped with a huge arsenal of weapons of destruction, including a shatter gun, grenades, rockets, super bombs, and an ever-present machine gun, Ray will have his hands full combating hoards of enemies such as snipers, alien soldiers, tanks, UFOs, and spiked slugs in 9 levels of running, jumping, climbing, and shooting 2D and 3D action.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/C - The Contra Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capcom vs. SNK Pro.pbp</path>
		<name>Capcom vs SNK: Millennium Fight 2000 Pro</name>
		<desc>Capcom vs. SNK Pro is the challenge of the millennium, with two monster corporations at war only one solution. A massive martial arts event organized to settle the score and eliminate all conflict between the two parties. Many of the world's most famous warriors have joined and the public is going mad with anticipation. Join over 30 brawlers from Capcom's legendary Street Fighter and SNK's world-renowned King of Fighters series as they fight for universal domination. Capcom vs. SNK Pro is the ultimate collision of strength and power.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Capcom vs. SNK Pro-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20020814T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Chronicles.pbp</path>
		<name>Castlevania Chronicles</name>
		<desc>The Legacy Comes Alive...
The 2D whip-wielding action game Castlevania returns to PlayStation® game console with a classic version never before seen in America. Count Dracula has been resurrected to begin a new reign of terror across the land. As Simon Belmont, descendant of legendary vampire hunters, you enter Dracula's estate to face the Count and his minions - alone. Be prepared for one of the first adventures in the Castlevania series ever!

* Use your powerful whip, holy water, throwing axes and other deadly weapons to slay the minions of Dracula
* Traverse 24 stages in 8 levels, including the Monastery, the Floating Corridor, and Count Dracula's Tower
* Includes Original and Arrange modes with graphic enhancements
* Filmed interview with the producer of the Castlevania series</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Castlevania Chronicles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20011008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos Break.pbp</path>
		<name>Chaos Break</name>
		<desc>Chaos Break is essentially a third-person shooting game, with echoes of survival horror such as Resident Evil. Set in an abandoned biochemical laboratory on an isolated island, the two player characters, Mitsuki and Rick, are part of an investigatory and cleansing force sent to find out the cause of an 'anomalous thermal reaction'. This game is a spin-off, set in the same universe as the arcade game Chaos Heat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Chaos Break-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eon Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chessmaster II.pbp</path>
		<name>Chessmaster II</name>
		<desc>Chess is one of the oldest board games on Earth; even the Egyptians played an early form of it. Now, chess comes to the PlayStation with THE CHESSMASTER II. Choose from 24 animated chess sets, including Mycenae, Egyptian, Isle of Lewis, and Stanton. Try to checkmate your friends, or challenge one of the 64 computer opponents (each with a different style of play and varying degrees of skill), or try to beat one of the 30 Grandmaster profiles. You’ll never miss an opening in the 3D mode, since you can rotate the camera to any angle you want. Or, if you prefer, play on a flat 2D board. THE CHESSMASTER II brings the thrills and challenges of chess to life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Chessmaster II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Starsphere Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chocobo Racing.pbp</path>
		<name>Chocobo Racing</name>
		<desc>The Chocobo has appeared in every Final Fantasy game since Final Fantasy IV as a large yellow bird that you can ride to other destinations or use during fights. With Chocobo Racing, you can race a Chocobo along with a range of different characters both from the Final Fantasy world including Cloud and Cid from Final Fantasy VII and created just for the game through many different fantasy worlds at high speed, using a selection of weapons to aid you. The game supports 1 and 2 player racing</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Chocobo Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Codename - Tenka.pbp</path>
		<name>Codename: Tenka</name>
		<desc>Wars and pollution have driven the Earth to chaos. The year is 2096. The remaining colonists' only dream is to leave the planet and establish on Extrevius 328, a corporate conglomerate manufacturing plant for deadly warriors, known as Bionoids. You are Joseph B. Tenka, future Bionoid, very unpleased with the situation, and determined to stop the corporate evil plans.

Over 20 missions with detailed briefings can be found in this Doom clone with creepy atmosphere which has been compared to Aliens.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Codename - Tenka-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis Limited</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colin McRae Rally 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Colin McRae Rally 2.0</name>
		<desc>Colin McRae Rally 2 is the long awaited follow up to the original racing hit - Colin McRae Rally. Just as the original CMR raised the bar for rally racing games so to does CMR2. CMR2 offers several modes of play including arcade and simulation. Play in arcade mode dueling it out against the others around a course or stick to the more traditional championship mode with three different skill levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Colin McRae Rally 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colony Wars 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Colony Wars: Red Sun</name>
		<desc>Red Sun is the third in Psygnosis' Star Wars inspired "Colony Wars" saga. This time around you follow the personal quest of Valdmar a miner who gets caught up in the wars between the League and the Navy after meeting the enigmatic "General" in a series of mysterious dreams.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Colony Wars 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra - Legacy of War.pbp</path>
		<name>Contra: Legacy of War</name>
		<desc>Aliens have infested the earth once more, and all is lost unless you step into the fray and take action against these otherworldly inhabitants. Contra: Legacy of War is a continuation of the long-running saga that started back on the Nintendo Entertainment System where a lone solider, with the choice of a partner (two-player mode) is faced with the pending threat of a total world domination by galactic creatures. You must battle your way level through hellish level in order to reach the final confrontation with the supreme entity. You wont be unprepared, however. There are numerous weapons and power-ups at your disposal, so, choose wisely soldier, the world is counting on you.

Blast through six levels of running, jumping, and shooting action. Along the way, use classic CONTRA weapons like the spread gun, and few new ones, like the powerful flame-thrower and homing rounds.

CONTRA gets a new look with 3D environments and character models. To make the action pop out of the screen, put on the special glasses included in the package and play in the 3D mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Contra - Legacy of War-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19961129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Covert Ops - Nuclear Dawn.pbp</path>
		<name>Covert Ops: Nuclear Dawn</name>
		<desc>The terrorist organization known as The Knights of the Apocalypse has captured a heavily armored military train called Blue Harvest. But they aren't after any weapons they want the French Ambassador and his family, who happen to be on board the train. You take the role of Jack Morton, the only surviving member of the train's crew, as you attempt to protect the Ambassador from the terrorists. You'll have to travel through more than a dozen train cars, each with multiple levels as you hunt down the evil thugs. Along the way you will also have to solve a variety of puzzles and master three unique mini-games to succeed. When you encounter a terrorist, you can take them out with one of 10 military weapons. For double the terrorist-stopping power, you can also equip a gun in each hand and target two separate enemies at once. Only you can help Morton save Europe and the French Ambassador in COVERT OPS: Nuclear Dawn.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Covert Ops - Nuclear Dawn-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sugar &amp; Rockets</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot.pbp</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot</name>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot, a heroic, agile and mutated marsupial who must save his girlfriend Tawna. The main antagonist is Doctor Neo Cortex, a mad scientist who was often ridiculed by the scientific community for his outlandish (but nearly workable) theories and is now motivated to prove his tormentors wrong by creating a mutated army of beasts to conquer the world. Cortex's henchman is Doctor Nitrus Brio, the insecure creator of the Evolvo-Ray. Crash's love interest is Tawna, a female bandicoot about to undergo experimentation by the Doctors. Helping Crash in his journey is an ancient witch doctor spirit named Aku Aku, who has scattered masks of himself throughout the islands to grant Crash special powers. The boss characters of the game include Papu Papu, the obese and short-tempered chief of the native village; Ripper Roo, a demented kangaroo with razor-sharp toenails; Koala Kong, a muscular but unintelligent koala; and Pinstripe Potoroo, the tommy gun-wielding bodyguard of Doctor Cortex.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crash Bandicoot-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2: Cortex Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>The evil Dr. Neo Cortex is back with a vengeance .. this time ... to save the world? And he's asking for helo from his arch-nemesis, Crash Bandicoot? Or is it just some conniving plan to lure Crash into a deadly trap for his own evil bidding? Find out as Crash takes on a whole new adventure that's out of this world!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crash Bandicoot 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 3: Warped</name>
		<desc>After defeating Dr. Neo Cortex, Crash and his sister, Coco, take a well-deserved vacation. However, their friend, Aku Aku, has a bad feeling, and as usual, he is right. Aku's evil twin, Uka Uka, was the person behind all of Dr. Cortex's schemes. Now Uka and Cortex have hatched a plot to gain control of the powerful crystals they desire. The have hired Dr. N. Tropy to create a time machine, which will allow Uka and Cortex to go back and take the crystals without interference. Take control of Crash and Coco as they travel through 30 levels across five time periods in an effort to stop Uka and Cortex. Use a motorcycle, plane, bazooka, and a baby T-rex to help Crash survive, or destroy the bad guys by using new moves like the super belly flop or the double jump. Will Crash and Coco be able to save the world? Play CRASH BANDICOOT: Warped and find out.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crash Bandicoot 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Team Racing.pbp</path>
		<name>Crash Team Racing</name>
		<desc>The main antagonist of the story, Nitros Oxide, is the self-proclaimed fastest racer in the galaxy who threatens to turn Earth into a concrete parking lot. Preceding Oxide are four boss characters: Ripper Roo, a deranged straitjacket-wearing kangaroo; Papu Papu, the morbidly obese leader of the island's native tribe; Komodo Joe, a Komodo dragon with a speech sound disorder; and Pinstripe Potoroo, a greedy pinstripe-clad potoroo. The four boss characters, along with an imperfect and morally ambiguous clone of Crash Bandicoot named Fake Crash, become accessible as playable characters if the Adventure Mode is fully completed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crash Team Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crime Killer.pbp</path>
		<name>Crime Killer</name>
		<desc>In the 21st century, you are a Crime Killer with three heavily armed police vehicles and a license to kill. Patrol the streets at breakneck speed, and crime will become a distant blur. Because on your shift, noting outruns the long arm of the law.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crime Killer-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pixelogic</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crisis Beat.pbp</path>
		<name>Crisis Beat</name>
		<desc>If you are an action game connoisseur then Crisis Beat is the game for you.
Set on board a futuristic ocean liner, you have to take on the fanatical members of the most ferocious sea-jacking gang of terrorists in the history of piracy.

Choose from four different characters to regain control of the ship.

Confront some of the most devastating end of level bosses ever seen in an action game.

Unique 'Lock On' mode allows you to delivery awesome moves on your opponents.

As the pace of the action increases, you can make use of many objects scattered around the ship to defeat opponents.

Balanced computer AI provides addictive solo gameplay.

Play solo or two player mode

...this is the action game that everyone has been looking for!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Crisis Beat-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Soft Machine</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deception III - Dark Delusion.pbp</path>
		<name>Deception III: Dark Delusion</name>
		<desc>Taken against her will to Alendar Kingdom, Layna who becomes your challenge is now under the control of the evil King Frederick. As her life wears thin, it becomes your sole mission to ensure Layna saves herself as King Frederick's mysterious organization attempts to bring Layna to her final doom. Through preparation of strategic trap setting you begin to plot and devise various techniques to destroy those who hold you captive. With over 2,000 trap variations it is up to you to choose the best combinations to assist you in conquering your enemy. Because there are multiple endings. Layna's final fate may be your worst nightmare or ultimate fantasy. The choice is yours. The options are endless.

* Over 2,000 trap variations
* New and improved trap element system allows more freedom for players to develop traps.
* Advanced 3D Polygon Graphics with Third Person Perspective.
* Four modes of play are offered including the "Scenario Mode", "Trap License Mode", "Free Training Mode", and the "Expert Mode".
* Multiple endings!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Deception III - Dark Delusion-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deep Freeze.pbp</path>
		<name>Deep Freeze</name>
		<desc>In the year 2001, the world has changed, and terrorism has changed along with it. The terrorist organization Hephaestus has become extremely powerful, and in response, the INTER-ANTS (International Anti-Terrorist Service) has come into existence. As Jack Wired, commander of an ANTS squad, you and your teammates will go into battle to resolve hostage situations and remove the terrorist threats.

Deep Freeze is a 3D action-shooting game with pre-rendered backgrounds, similar to such games as Resident Evil and Parasite Eve only with a stronger action focus. Choose a partner from your squad for each mission, then make your way through each situation to eliminate the threat. You can give your partner orders, as well as change formation.

The game features full voice acting completely in English, a rarity for a Japanese exclusive title.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Deep Freeze-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Talon, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Delta Force - Urban Warfare.pbp</path>
		<name>Delta Force: Urban Warfare</name>
		<desc>Delta Force: Urban Warfare is the first Delta Force game developed by UK based Rebellion. Urban Warfare features a new AI system unique to the PlayStation. It will offer players a squad of characters with special military abilities, a variety of fast-paced new missions, and hi-tech weapons. The franchise is modeled after the British Special Air Service (SAS), which served as an overseas counter-terrorist unit and specialized in rescuing hostages.

You are a lone Delta Force operative. You must eliminate terrorists who may be hidden behind any door, and halt a global threat. This is an all-new Delta Force experience, based on the successful franchise developed exclusively for the PlayStation by Rebellion.

Gameplay ranges from wild shootouts to stealth tactics, and includes close-quarters combat, strategic infiltration, time-sensitive ops, sniping, and demolition. You will engage enemies who react to gunfire, dive for cover, employ tactical maneuvers, and pursue using a player's blood trail. Weapons include assault and sniper rifles, grenade and rocket launchers, plus remote explosives. Other gear includes night vision and thermal goggles, combat radar, and a security camera scrambler.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Delta Force - Urban Warfare-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>Novalogic</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Die Hard Trilogy.pbp</path>
		<name>Die Hard Trilogy</name>
		<desc>You're at the center of three totally different, thrill-packed adventures. Every adventure you choose delivers amazing depth, palm-sweating realism and fully-rendered detail over thirty incredible levels.

* Die Hard - Full screen 3-D action as you fight to rescue innocent hostages in a skyscraper wired to explode!

* Die Hard 2: Die Harder - Arcade shooting at its fastest and finest as you eliminate terrorists at Dulles Airport.

* Die Hard With A Vengeance - Heart-accelerating, simulated driving adventure as you race through New York City to find hidden bombs!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Die Hard Trilogy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960820T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Die Hard Trilogy 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Die Hard Trilogy 2: Viva Las Vegas</name>
		<desc>Ready to kick some more terrorist butt? In Die Hard Trilogy 2: Viva Las Vegas for the PlayStation, you'll reprise the role of John McClane as you lay waste to the threats and save innocent people along the way -- this time in the Sin City capital of the world: Las Vegas, Nevada. The game comes packaged as a three-in-one deal, just like the original Die Hard Trilogy, for a total of 25 non-stop action-packed levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Die Hard Trilogy 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis.pbp</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis</name>
		<desc>Dino Crisis is a survival horror game that is very similar in both control and gameplay to its sister series, Resident Evil. As in that series, protagonist Regina will have limited supplies and ammo with which to fight deadly enemies while searching rooms for keys (some figurative, some literal) to open locked areas. Unlike Resident Evil games, Regina will find very few actual supplies laying around, and will instead find "plugs" that are used to open caches of emergency supplies located around the complex. There are only enough plugs to open some of these caches, however, so care must be taken to decide what items are really needed. In another change from Resident Evil, the game is rendered in 3D, allowing the camera to rotate or pan, although camera angles are still out of the control of the player. Even the dumbest dinosaur is smarter than the undead, and enemies can chase and disarm Regina, and even occasionally follow her through doors.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Dino Crisis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis 2</name>
		<desc>One year has passed since Regina’s fight for survival against prehistoric dinosaurs, and the capture of the rogue Dr. Kirk. Third Energy research continued recklessly.

Another "accident" was imminent. Suddenly, Edward City, an entire town devoted to Third Energy research completely vanished, mysteriously replaced by prehistoric jungle. Now, a search and rescue to recover survivors and locate the missing research data begins. Armed with heavy artillery, only Regina has any idea of what to expect when the team arrives…pure terror.

    Features: Sequel to the popular horror-survival game
    Fight off vicious man-eating dinosaurs
    Use 2 weapons simultaneously
    Spin-and-shoot feature allows you to cover more area
    Several weapons to choose from, including automatic rifles and tasers</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Dino Crisis 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Aladdin 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Take control of Aladdin and stop Nasira, the evil sister of Jafar (the bad guy from the Disney movie) and rescue the Sultan and Princess Jasmine. Based on the hit Disney movie and the animated TV series of the same name</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Aladdin 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20010315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Games PLC</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Atlantis.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Atlantis: The Lost Empire</name>
		<desc>The Lost Empire is a 3D action game with puzzle-solving elements, based on Disney's film of the same name. The player can take control of six different characters, trying to reach the lost city of Atlantis and save it from destruction. Each character possesses his or her own unique abilities. The gameplay is reminiscent of Tomb Raider games, involving combat and predominantly physical and environmental puzzles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Atlantis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Donald Duck Goin Quackers.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Donald Duck: Goin' Quackers</name>
		<desc>Donald is goin' quackers!
Donald runs amuck, goes berserk, and gets hyper across 20 levels in 4 cartoon-like worlds in this hilarious quest to rescue Daisy.

- Features favorite characters: Daisy, Huey, Dewey, Louie, the Beagle Boys and more.
- Control Donald's explosive temper, confront wacky characters and obstacles.
- It's non-stop action as Donald runs, jumps, dodges and quacks his way to save Daisy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Donald Duck Goin Quackers-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft Shanghai</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Tarzan.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Tarzan</name>
		<desc>Disney's animated film TARZAN gets the videogame treatment and makes his way to the PlayStation. The game follows the plot of the movie: you must help Tarzan grow from a boy to an adult in the span of 14 levels of action. While many of the levels offer platform-jumping, vine-swinging fun, some of them recreate some of the action sequences from the movie. No matter where he is, Tarzan must collect the tokens and fruit that are scattered about. Collecting 100 tokens earns an extra life, and the fruit can be used to dispose of enemies. If you can collect the four pieces of Jane's baboon drawing, you can earn the chance to play a bonus level. You've got to help the young ape-man discover his place in the world with TARZAN.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Tarzan-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - The Emperors New Groove.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's The Emperor's New Groove</name>
		<desc>Take the role of the jaded Incan Emperor, Kuzco, in The Emperor's New Groove. Unfortunately, Kuzco has been turned into a llama. He eventually encounters a llama herder named Pacha, and now the emperor and Pacha must travel through villages, jungles, and rivers to reclaim the crown. On each level, Kuzco much search for items that open other areas of the stage for exploration. However, some areas are no-llama zones, and Kuzco will not be able to pass. Luckily, there are potions that will change him into a turtle, rabbit, or some other creature. For those who enjoyed the film, actual movie clips and voice work from David Spade help the game look and sound like the movie. All of the action and excitement of the Disney film comes home in The Emperor's New Groove.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - The Emperors New Groove-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment, Disney Interactive Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Treasure Planet.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Treasure Planet</name>
		<desc>Get ready for an epic adventure of bloodthirsty pirates and buried treasure. Treasure Planet brings Robert Louis Stevenson's Treasure Island not just right up-to-date but into the future--one in which the spaceship Legacy is overrun by mutinous pirates, led by the cyborg John Silver. You'll take on the role of Jim as he solar-surfs and performs action moves with the help of Morph, who can transform into various items. Embark on a voyage through 10 levels, minigames, and boss challenges as you view original artwork, behind-the-scenes game footage, and stored movie clips.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Treasure Planet-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20021111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Magenta Software</developer>
		<publisher>SCEA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Valor.pbp</path>
		<name>Dragon Valor</name>
		<desc>The game begins as the first hero, Clovis, sets out to avenge the death of his young sister by slaying the dragon that killed her. Clovis travels to the Lexis Empire and meets many other characters along the way. With luck and skill, Clovis defeats his enemy and the tale moves forward. The next quest in Dragon Valor is assumed by the next hero, who is one of Clovis' children. In an innovative feature, players will actually determine which heroes they will play and which quests they will attempt by choosing a mate for Clovis.

After Clovis completes his quest he chooses a bride from the available women he encountered on his journey. The wife that Clovis chooses determines the nature of his progeny and the challenges that they will face. Different, generation-spanning storylines develop according to the offspring that Clovis and his wife produce and then in turn, by the choices that those heirs make.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Dragon Valor-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001016T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver.pbp</path>
		<name>Driver</name>
		<desc>As Tanner, you're going undercover to be the wheelman for a crime syndicate in order to break open a big case. On the way, you'll eliminate competition, drive getaway cars, scare some people silly, evade plenty of police, dodge bad guys, smash through a few windows, save your love interest, and much more through four cities (Miami, San Francisco, Los Angeles, and New York).

Perform authentic manuevers like donuts, 180 spin, 360 spin, reverse 180 spin, and more as you cut through alley ways, across sidewalks and parks, smash park benches and and drive over traffic cones. Many different cars to try (most you'll recognize). Will you save the day?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Driver-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990708T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Land of the Babes.pbp</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem: Land of the Babes</name>
		<desc>In the distant future, vicious aliens rule the Earth. Only bodacious babes survive, enslaved by the hostile alien overlords. The women and the world need a hero. And there's only one man big enough for the job! Duke Nukem is back, and he's ready to settle the score!

-21 action filled mission to hunt and destroy alien life
-New weapons arsenal including: sniper riffle, flame thrower, grenade launcher and many more.
-High tech gadgets including jetpack and infrared goggles
-Numerous 3D cut-scenes to die for
-In Your Face music by Static-Xtches.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Duke Nukem - Land of the Babes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Time to Kill.pbp</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem: Time to Kill</name>
		<desc>LET THEM EAT LEAD!

Travel through time in an all-new Duke Nukem frag-fest that gives you more of what you crave! More Duke attitude! More hardcore action! More exploration! More shooter mayhem!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Duke Nukem - Time to Kill-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>n-Space</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ehrgeiz.pbp</path>
		<name>Ehrgeiz</name>
		<desc>BEYOND FIGHTING

The world's most brutal tournament has its trophy the legendary weapon 'EHRGEIZ'.

Now, fighters from around the world assemble to claim this prize and its mysterious power.

3 INTENSE PLAYING MODES:
Arcade Fighting Action

* Over ten playable characters, a cast of hidden characters, and favorites from Final Fantasy VII.
* Complete 360 degree range of motion: battle hand-to-hand, with weapons, or with devastating combos and special moves.
* Multiple-level, fully interactive arenas.

Challenging Mini-Games
* Compete in tests of speed, skill, and dexterity in any of four unique mini-games.

Full-featured RPG Adventure
* Descend into ever-changing random dungeon layouts in search of treasure, ever-stronger weapons, and answers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ehrgeiz-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dream Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elemental Gearbolt.pbp</path>
		<name>Elemental Gearbolt</name>
		<desc>Elemental Gearbolt is your typical "save the world from the evil lunatic who wishes to destroy all of mankind for his own tyrannical reasons" story. In this case, a power hungry prince is plotting this scenario by using the Neural Network Computer, which happens to keep the world in balance. He wishes to destroy this machine, which feeds on volunteers, or Elementals. Once you die, your soul is fed to this machine which makes you an Elemental. Such is the case with the two sisters' Nell and Seana. But what the prince did not know is that he caused their death and now the two Elementals are out for his blood and to save all of mankind.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Elemental Gearbolt-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fear Effect.pbp</path>
		<name>Fear Effect</name>
		<desc>It can recognize your fear...can you?
Days before her eighteenth birthday, the quiet, enigmatic Wee Ming Lam, disappears under mysterious circumstances. Hana, Glas, and Deke, three self-motivated and ruthless mercenaries conspire to track her down and ransom her off to her father, Mr. Lam, the most powerful Triad leader in Hong Kong, for a large sum of cold, hard cash.

What begins as a simple extortion mission to retrieve the young runaway becomes a lesson in survival against the most unimaginable of enemies.

Immerse yourself in this intense thriller featuring revolutionary Motion FX technology where you direct your cast of 3D characters within dynamic, full-motion-video worlds. Who lives? Who dies? Only you decide, if you can...

Control Your Fear!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Fear Effect-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kronos Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fear Effect 2 - Retro Elix.pbp</path>
		<name>Fear Effect 2: Retro Helix</name>
		<desc>Delve into the colorful histories of the original cast of mercenaries and the extraordinary circumstances that brought them together in Fear Effect. Discover what drives Hana Tsu-Vachel, the beautiful assassin whose specialty lies in the dealings of love as well as death, Royce Glas, the master counter intelligence operative who is haunted by his past, Jakob "Deke" Decourt, the cold-blooded killer driven by money and murder. And meet Rain Qin, a stunning new character and close companion of Hana with unparalleled beauty wrapped around a dark secret core.

FEATURES:

* New Motion FX 3D technology allows for the most breathtaking anime ever on a gaming console.
* Unparalleled interaction with 8 new environments for mindbending puzzles and intense action.
* Enemies react with cunning AI as you try to obliterate them with an expanded arsenal of weaponry such as tasers and flame throwers.
* Gameplay and cinematics stream seamlessly, eliminating load times even after death sequences.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Fear Effect 2 - Retro Elix-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kronos Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FIFA 2001.pbp</path>
		<name>Fifa 2001</name>
		<desc>FIFA 2001 aims to immerse its fans with the most realistic football experience possible. Over 50 international teams, including England, France, Germany, Holland, Spain, and the United States have made the cut, while 17 of the planet's top leagues have been incorporated as well. New motion captured moves from Matthaus, Mendieta, Scholes, and other soccer legends support the game's realism, with animated linesman and authentic light sourcing add that much more to the presentation. Perhaps the most important features, though, are the advanced sets of artificial intelligence, in-game cinematic cutscenes, and a ton of game modes that have been specially built for tournaments from around the world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/FIFA 2001-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20141127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FIFA 99.pbp</path>
		<name>FIFA 99</name>
		<desc>This was the third FIFA title in a little over a year. It incorporates 42 national sides, as well as 250 club teams from 12 different leagues, to play a complete true-to-life season, the preset Super League, or a league or cup of your own design. Formations and tactics can be set, and players can be moved between teams. 

Gameplay can be viewed from multiple angles. Players have more animation than ever before, with new moves including sliding challenges and close-control trapping. Goalkeepers now have a level of human control.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/FIFA 99-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Force.pbp</path>
		<name>Fighting Force</name>
		<desc>Fighting Force players control one of four characters. They move through urban and science fiction environments, battling waves of oncoming enemies with weapons ranging from fists and bottles to knives, chairs and guns. The player can make some choices as to which territory to travel through.

The four characters have various reasons for taking on Dr. Zeng, a criminal mastermind with an army at his command. The action starts with a police cordon around Zeng's office skyscraper, moving to such locales as a shopping mall, subway and Coast Guard base before finally ending at the top of Zeng's island headquarters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Fighting Force-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CORE Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Origins.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Origins</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Origins delivers the first two games in the Final Fantasy series. Originally released in 1998 in Japan, Final Fantasy II never came to North America, but now RPG fans will be able to experience the emotion-packed sequel and its predecessor with all-new event scenes, enhanced graphics, and improved sound. Whether you're on a quest to recover a magical Crystal or on a journey to stop a merciless ruler, both games provide grand stories complemented with deep characterization and touching music.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Origins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20030408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics</name>
		<desc>Lead epic battles in a new Final Fantasy world.

Betrayal and darker dealings await in Square Soft's game of war.

Fight hundreds of battles across dangerous 3D terrain as an ancient blood feud awakens a deadlier foe.

* Command knights, mages, ninjas and more
* Based on Final Fantasy characters and magic
* 19 character classes, 400 abilities
* Deep customization options
* In-game interactive manual
* Only on PlayStation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Tactics-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19980128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VII.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VII</name>
		<desc>Set in a dystopian world, Final Fantasy VII's story centers on mercenary Cloud Strife who joins with several others to stop the megacorporation Shinra, which is draining the life of the planet to use as an energy source. As the story progresses, the situation escalates and Cloud and his allies face Sephiroth, the game's main antagonist.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy VII-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forsaken.pbp</path>
		<name>Forsaken</name>
		<desc>Forsaken is a first-person shoot 'em up in which you have complete movement freedom in 3 dimensions, as you accelerate, swerve and strafe your craft, making for gameplay resembling Descent. Each level has a defined exit which must be reached within a tight time limit. The surrounding areas are collapsing around you, with spikes and turbine fans among your hazards. Be very aware of other craft out to take all you have, as they alter their approach based on your weaponry and past encounters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Forsaken-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Front Mission 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Front Mission 3</name>
		<desc>Yokosuka, Japan, 2112 AD. The young student Kazuki Takemura works as a test pilot with Kirishima Industries, a production company of military battle wanzers (walking panzers), mechanized walking robots with movement similar to that of a human being. Kazuki has just finished testing the combat capabilities of the new Zeinslev prototype in the lab. Finishing his day's tasks he is asked by his best friend Ryogo to help with a company delivery to the Japanese Defense Force (JDF) military based. This simple choice determines where Kazuki is when strange things begin happening in Japan. A large explosion, a wanzer theft, his sister Alysia being hunted, rumors of a powerful weapon, and accusations of involvement by agents of both the OCU and the USN all make the situation more complicated. Kazuki is swept up in a plot of conflicting loyalties and attacked by various factions. He will need to recruit additional characters and wanzers in order to be victorious in battle and investigate leads to uncover what is going on.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Front Mission 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Future Cop LDAP.pbp</path>
		<name>Future Cop L.A.P.D</name>
		<desc>The city of Los Angeles has a few more problems than usual in 2100 A.D. You see, the future hasn't been exactly kind to urban life and now gangs have overrun the already bleak neighborhoods. Is there any hope? There is as long as you enforce the law!

Command a powerful Tactical Assault &amp; Combat X-1 mech walker (that can also transform into a sleek hovercraft) and battle through 12 levels, each culminating in a showdown with a large boss character. Fortunately for you, fourteen different weapons are available to help you teach "crime doesn't pay." Feeling a little lonely? If so, a friend can join the action in cooperative play!

An additional game mode, Precinct Assault, has also been included. Precinct Assault is a strategy game that involves two teams (red versus blue) in an all-out battle for supremacy. This mode can be played against the computer or another human. Future Cop: L.A.P.D. supports the Dual Shock Analog Controller to make you feel the gunfire, and progress can be saved using either one block of memory card space or a password.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Future Cop LDAP-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Redwood Shores</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./G-Darius.pbp</path>
		<name>G Darius</name>
		<desc>G-Darius revolves around a conflict between the humanoids of Amnelia and cyborg/chimera biovessels known as the "Thiima" (meant to mean simply "bringers of death"). The Thiima had been aroused by the Amnelian army's use of the weapon A.N. (All-Nothing) to annihilate the world Blazar, whom Amnelia had been at war with over jurisdiction over the moon Mahsah. Determined to protect their existence, and long ago programmed to protect the universe from just such threats as A.N., the Thiima swarmed on Amnelia. Although the armed forces were badly ravaged, Amnelian scientists and engineers were able to make use of both A.N. and reverse engineered Thiiman technology/life systems to create the Silver Hawk fighters. Ultimately, two pilots—Sameluck Raida and Lutia Feen—are chosen to perform a decisive attack on the main Thiima base: Kazumn, a satellite of the planet Darius.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/G-Darius-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19980331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aisystem Tokyo</developer>
		<publisher>Taito Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga - Destination Earth.pbp</path>
		<name>Galaga: Destination Earth</name>
		<desc>Galaga, the "slide-and-shoot" arcade classic from 1981, has been updated with nine new worlds, 3D graphics, futuristic backgrounds and more in GALAGA -- Destination: Earth.

It is late in the 22nd century, and the insect-like Galaga are back. Humans have terraformed and colonized most habitable places in our solar system, but the Galaga have only one thing in mind: destruction. The Galaga are mutated nanites that were inadvertently created during the terraforming process. They are deadly, autonomous and great in number, and you must blast them into oblivion. In addition to shooting Galaga, you must perform various mission objectives, such as collecting life pods and activating water turbines.

Like in the original game, you begin this enhanced version of Galaga controlling a ship that moves horizontally along the bottom of the playfield and fires upward at wave after wave of diving, swirling aliens that eventually fly into formation. However, unlike the original, this game, depending on what mission you are playing, features a number of other viewpoints, including over the shoulder, top down and side on. You can fire just two shots at a time, but you can gain the ability to have three shots onscreen at once.

Also like the original game, GALAGA -- Destination: Earth features challenge waves in which you blast streams of enemies for points while not having to worry about your own safety. And, of course, you can let a Galaga capture your ship, then shoot your ship's captor, letting the captured ship fall to you, enabling you to double your firepower. Similar to Gaplus, the sequel to classic Galaga, this game also lets you collect beam power-ups that enable you to capture enemies, place them by your side and use their weapons.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Galaga - Destination Earth-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King of the Jungle</developer>
		<publisher>Hasbro</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galerians.pbp</path>
		<name>Galerians</name>
		<desc>A fleeting memory. A haunting vision. A childhood mystery that can prevent the destruction of mankind. Crave Entertainment, Inc. introduces Galerians, a survival-horror title for the PlayStation that thrusts players into a twisted future.

Rion is a young boy who awakens in a laboratory, unable to remember anything except his name. He soon discovers that he possesses psychic powers, although they come with severe consequences. With only a girl named Lilia, whose voice guides him, Rion must escape his captors and begin putting together the broken shards of his memories.

Players assume the role of Rion and must guide him through four locations in his search for Lilia and the secret of his past. Armed with powerful psychic abilities, Rion must combat human enemies and a variety of frightening genetic experiments. Unfortunately, nothing can prepare him for the confrontation with his own history.

The game spans three discs, combining action and puzzle solving in a horrific setting. Galerians utilizes a third-person perspective and features polygonal characters on pre-rendered backgrounds. The shocking truth is gradually revealed through fragmented visions and confessions, building to an epic struggle between man and machine.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Galerians-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polygon Magic</developer>
		<publisher>Crave</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gamera 2000.pbp</path>
		<name>Gamera 2000</name>
		<desc>Alien monsters and other gigantic nightmares threaten earth. Fortunately for us a special force has been assigned to deal with them which includes the mighty Gamera as an ally.

The game puts you in the shoes of Jack, the star pilot behind the jet fighter designed to take out these nasties. Together with Dr. Mikanuki you take to the skies as swarms of monsters attack you mercilessly through several stages.

Gameplay-wise Gamera 2000 plays like Panzer Dragoon, as you don't have direct control of your jet, but instead try to aim at the incoming monsters from all directions and shoot them down while the jet follows a pre-set path. Facing bosses requires you to target specific weak points while your fighter circles around and at all times you can call Gamera to aid you by instructing it to shoot its homing attacks, as well as a charged attack that clears all enemies on screen.

Some stages switch the action to ground level, as you pilot a futuristic bike, but the gameplay remains the same. Features polygonal graphics and live action FMV sequences that advance the plot between each stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gamera 2000-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19970425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Surveyor Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Datie Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gekido.pbp</path>
		<name>Gekido: Urban Fighters</name>
		<desc>Finally, a fighting game with a strong single player game as well as an intense multiplayer mode, where FOUR players face off in a no-holds-barred brawl.

It's time for Gekido... Raging Fury.

* Get 3 friends to join you, and beat them to a pulp in the no-holds-barred arena mode.
* Solo mission single-player mode pushes 4 characters to the breaking point and unlocks hidden characters.
* Battle through 17 progressive 3-D environments.
* Explode into an adrenaline-activated destroyer as you discover each character's "rage" move.
* Environments are weapon-packed, loaded with both traditional painmakers like guns and flamethrowers and a few exploding"surprises."
* Fighters are trained to use whatever's available-automobiles, soda machines and even other fighters.
* Crack skulls to the mind-blowing soundtrack featuring Fatboy Slim and Apartment 26.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gekido-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>N.A.P.S</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko.pbp</path>
		<name>Gex 3: Deep Cover Gecko</name>
		<desc>When Gex is watching TV one day, he discovers that Rez has kidnapped Agent Xtra (the agent from Gex: Enter the Gecko's backstory), head of the TV Terrorist Defense Unit, to get to him. He teleports to the batcave-like lair he has in the Media Dimension, and begins another adventure. Each level parodies a certain aspect of television culture (here the levels exist as stand-alone channels). Gex enters each level through a television set. He must collect remote controls to advance to the next level in order to complete his mission and rescue Xtra.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost In The Shell.pbp</path>
		<name>Ghost in the Shell</name>
		<desc>3rd person action game based on the Ghost in the Shell original comic by Masamune Shirow rather than Mamoru Oshi's film. You take the role of a new member in Kusanagi's anti-terrorist squad and get to accomplish missions on your Fuchikoma, (a spider-like AI equipped tank) thanks to which you can jump, stick to walls and ceilings and shoot the hell out of terrorists, all from a 1st or 3rd person point of view. As the missions proceed a plot starts to surface concerning a giant skyscrapper, the Aereopolis II, which will eventually be solved after 12 single player missions. Other features include a training sequence, 3D stereo sound and wide anamorphic screen mode for 16x9 TVs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ghost In The Shell-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exact</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghoul Panic.pbp</path>
		<name>Ghoul Panic</name>
		<desc>Ghoul Panic is a comedy adventure game, set in a haunted mansion. Using a PlayStation light-gun, take on the might of vampires, monsters, mummies, skeletons and spooks to open the locked doors and uncover hidden bonuses. A conversion of the arcade game, with 3 difficulties and hidden game modes. There are also PlayStation exclusive game modes, including Survival, Adventure and Remix.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ghoul Panic-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eighting/Raizing</developer>
		<publisher>SCEE</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius Gaiden.pbp</path>
		<name>Gradius Gaiden</name>
		<desc>The setting is between Gradius III and Gradius IV.

During the " Third Bacterian War ", the planet Gradius defeated the Bacterians, and peace returned to Gradius. After two hundred years passed, Gradius prospered, but when the disappearance of a science vessel which went to a nebula known as "The Evil Range", the colony planets of Gradius were attacked by some unknown force that destroyed 99% of the Gradius Army. The Gradius Army Headquarters decided to launch a desperation attack on the "Dark Nebula", which was the source of the invaders. Four Hyper Space Fighters launched from the mothership with orders to stop them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gradius Gaiden-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo 2 - Arcade.pbp</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo 2</name>
		<desc>Gran Turismo 2 is fundamentally based on the racing game genre. The player must maneuver an automobile to compete against artificially intelligent drivers on various race tracks. The game uses two different modes: arcade and simulation. In the arcade mode, the player can freely choose the courses and vehicles they wish to use. However, the simulation mode requires the player to earn driver's licenses, pay for vehicles, and earn trophies in order to unlock new courses. Gran Turismo 2 features nearly 650 automobiles and 27 racing tracks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gran Turismo 2 - Arcade-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia.pbp</path>
		<name>Grandia</name>
		<desc>Embark On An Unforgettable Journey.
Travel across vast worlds and unravel the threads of an ancient legend in a quest that challenges your courage. A luminous empire. An ominous secret. An unbelieveable, intriguing adventure.

-Over 200 weapons, enemies and items to collect.
-More than 80 magic spells and battle techniques.
-A unique magic and character development system that puts your strategic skills to the test.

Warm and enchanting worlds each with their own architectural style.

Over 80 hours of gameplay. Can you solve the mysteries of Grandia?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Grandia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunfighter - The Legend of Jesse James.pbp</path>
		<name>Gunfighter: The Legend of Jesse James</name>
		<desc>Step into the boots of a legend of the Old West for a sharp-shooting adventure of true romance and frontier justice. Jesse James' partner has been shot dead and his best girl Zee has been kidnapped by a band of no-good outlaw varmints. Guide the rogue hero as he blasts away at the bad guys to avenge his lost companion and save the girl. The game is compatible with PlayStation light guns for a true first-person experience. Gunfighter: The Legend of Jesse James also features an assortment of mini-games for variety and replay value.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gunfighter - The Legend of Jesse James-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>Ubi Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gungage.pbp</path>
		<name>Gungage</name>
		<desc>Gungage is a futuristic Third Person Shooter for the PlayStation. In the game, the world is threatened by strange creatures from an alternative world called Dark Moon, who want to take over the Earth.

You start the game with only one character available to play with, but three more can be unlocked. Each character has its own characteristics when it comes to the size of their gun, their speed, and their size. Each character also has their own special psychic powers. The story evolves differently with the various characters, but the same levels are used. During the game, special powers have to be collected.

Settings of the various levels in the game vary from deserts to laboratories. Enemies in the game vary from prehistoric looking beast to futuristic robots and tanks. Enemies can run around, pop out of the ground, fly in the air, and come out of the water. Levels are completed by confronting and defeating a giant level boss. The game can be played in easy, medium, and hard mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gungage-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCE Tokyo</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter - The Chamber of Secrets.pbp</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</name>
		<desc>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets continues the PlayStation adventures of the bespectacled boy wizard as he returns to Hogwarts to begin a second year of studies. Things do not go smoothly, however, as the game closely follows the events found in J.K. Rowling's second book in the international best-selling fantasy series. Harry Potter and friends Hermione and Ron must investigate a terrible danger: students are mysteriously turning to stone.

Developed by Argonaut Software, this PlayStation version offers a completely different experience than the games on other platforms. Play begins at Ron's home at the Burrow, where Harry can practice his magic skills in a number of tasks designed to help the Weasley homestead.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Harry Potter - The Chamber of Secrets-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter - The Philosopher Stone.pbp</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</name>
		<desc>J. K. Rowling's immensely popular boy wizard makes his highly anticipated entrance to the realm of video gaming with this third-person 3D action-adventure based on Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, the first novel in the series. In the role of the prodigious young magician the player begins his first year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, joined by familiar characters such as Ron Weasley, Hermione Granger, and even Draco Malfoy.

Harry Potter can explore the grounds at Hogwarts, spend time with Hagrid, and even hop on a broomstick for a quick game of quidditch. However, as in the novel, Harry's special gifts are noticed not only by his instructors but by darker forces, as well, and the player may even come face-to-face with "You-Know-Who" himself before this adventure is over.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Harry Potter - The Philosopher Stone-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hell Night.pbp</path>
		<name>Hellnight</name>
		<desc>Tokyo at the end of the millennium is a megapolis with a huge system of subway tunnels and sewers. The game opens with the protagonist fleeing from a group of notorious cult members through the city streets and escaping on a late-night subway train. As he contemplates why they specifically want to kidnap him, the scene changes to secluded research station. There, a symbiotic lifeform breaks free of its confines and attacks a research scientist. He soon mutates into a zombie-like creature and makes a bloody exit towards the subway system.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Hell Night-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991230T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Invasion from Beyond.pbp</path>
		<name>Invasion from Beyond</name>
		<desc>The story for Invasion From Beyond is based on the golden age of B-Movie science fiction thrillers, and goes like this: farm workers have been abducted and crop circles were discovered in farmlands outside Washington, D.C.. The locals' insults towards superstitious fears ("Slap an Alien") were a welcome party for the Martians ready to strike. You are a fully qualified Earthlink and must pilot your ship to stop the alien invasion by manipulating the ground-based firepower of Earthlink Command and prevent the aliens from taking over our beloved planet Earth.

The game features more than 30 missions of futuristic action with many secret levels, ships and weapons. Your prime directive is to kill all invading alien forces. However, whenever Earthlink Command wants you to complete a specific objective, you will be notified via a flashing communications icon.

Your ship features a radar, cargo hold, weapon mounts, aiming reticule and the Suck-O-Matic. The Suck-O-Matic is an experimental device used to teleport and blow items in and out of your ship's cargo hold. It is an essential part for much of the game's objectives.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Invasion from Beyond-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19981130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>King of the Jungle</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jinx.pbp</path>
		<name>Jinx</name>
		<desc>Jinx is a 3D platformer for the PlayStation in the vein of other 3D platformers like Spyro the Dragon. The main character Jinx, a court jester, is tasked with finding and rescuing the royal family he works for since it has been kidnapped by Gripply the Pirate King, leaving the realm into a state of chaos. The player has to traverse various different worlds and locations in pursuit of Gripply, while facing a number of enemies, solving puzzles and collecting items. The graphics are notable for being very colourful.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Jinx-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HammerHead, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kagero Deception 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Kagero: Deception II</name>
		<desc>Through the brutal use of brainwashing, the blue-skinned timenoids had for centuries ruthlessly dominated their inferior human counterparts. Immortal in their lifespans and ingenius in their plans, the timenoids had crated armies of unknowing human drones to wage war against the only race that possessed the power to end their reign of terror, and their lives - the human. their plan backfired, though, when Millenia, brainwashed but not braindead, arrived on the scene.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Kagero Deception 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingsleys Adventure.pbp</path>
		<name>Kingsley's Adventure</name>
		<desc>Would you rather watch an adventure or be in one? This is the story of Kingsley, fox club and unlikely hero on a quest to save the Fruit Kingdom from the evil Wizard, Bad Custard. This is a job worthy only of a True Knight. Are you ready for the adventure of a lifetime?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Kingsleys Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis Limited</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa Beach Volleyball.pbp</path>
		<name>Klonoa Beach Volleyball</name>
		<desc>Invite your friends to join in the fun and play at THE volleyball party!

Go head-to-head with Klonoa or one of his friends in this exciting seaside sport! Everyone is sure to hae a very good time. But watch out for those super attacks!

-Play as Klonoa, Popka, Heart Moo, Lolo and even Joka too!
-Lots of fun to pick up and play, on your own or with your friends.
-Perfect your serve, toss and blocking skills</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Klonoa Beach Volleyball-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa - Door To Phantomile.pbp</path>
		<name>Klonoa: Door to Phantomile</name>
		<desc>Explore a magical world of mystery and adventure. Join Klonoa on a fantastic journey in the land of Phantomile, where the mysterious crash of a flying ship starts an epic quest through colorful worlds of thrills and danger.

You're never lost in this 3-D world. Klonoa's "Guided 3-D" construction gives players a vast 3-D world without the aimless and wandering feel of many other 3-D action games.

Beautiful graphics and entertaining puzzles add a whole new level of fun &amp; challenge.

Multiple, forked paths add extra replay value - just remember that shortcuts aren't always what they seem!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Klonoa - Door To Phantomile-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19970310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knockout Kings 2000.pbp</path>
		<name>Knockout Kings 2000</name>
		<desc>Enjoy all of the thrilling challenges of professional boxing with KNOCKOUT KINGS 2000. You can choose from large number of past and present boxing greats like Marvelous Marvin Hagler, Rocky Marciano, Evander Holyfield, Roberto Duran, and Muhammad Ali. Enter a slugfest, and try to knock out your opponent opposition in an arcade-style boxing match. If you are looking for something more realistic, put the boxers into an Exhibition match. For the most hardcore boxing fanatics, you can recreate great boxing matches, including the Thrilla in Manilla. For the ultimate challenge, create your own boxer and fight your way through the ranks to the world championship. Unlike last year's game, players now control the training that takes place between matches. If you are a fan of the sweet science, you will love KNOCKOUT KINGS 2000.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Knockout Kings 2000-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knockout Kings 2001.pbp</path>
		<name>Knockout Kings 2001</name>
		<desc>All the egomaniacal, violent splendor of heavyweight boxing comes to the PlayStation 2 in Knockout Kings 2001 by EA Sports. This title employs EA's new CyberScan technology, which allows the boxers faces to be accurately reproduced in full polygonal glory. In addition to the graphical overhaul, the game features new modes of play and simplified control. Choose your champion from a stable of boxing's greatest, including Muhammad Ali, Joe Louis, Rocky Marciano, and Lennox Lewis. A new career mode allows you to play through several weight classes and to box at famous arenas all around the world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Knockout Kings 2001-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Koudelka.pbp</path>
		<name>Koudelka</name>
		<desc>A Gothic Horror RPG set in the late 19th century. An Epic Tale of Murder, Mystery and Mayhem. A Beautiful Yet Troubled Woman Named Koudelka Who is Summoned To Unravel It All...

Breathtaking Cinematic Scenes and Musical Score
Three Fully Customizable Characters: Allocate Bonus Points to Determine Your Character Growth
Beautifully Rendered 3D Backgrounds
Combat Evil Using The Lifedrinker, Sacnoth Blade, Magic Spells and Many More Weapons...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Koudelka-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy Of Kain - Soul Reaver.pbp</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain: Soul Reaver</name>
		<desc>Soul Reaver is a third-person perspective action game with puzzle-solving and some platforming elements. The game follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans. The player views the environments from behind Raziel's shoulder, moving him in any direction, climbing, attacking, jumping and using specific abilities. Raziel's can grip onto the edge of ledges and his torn wings allow him to glide gently downwards. He can also shift through the "material" world into the "spectral" realm at will, but must find specific locations in order to shift back. The two realms mirror one another, with distortions which give access to new areas and platforms. Existing in the material world drains Raziel's life energy at a constant rate.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Legacy Of Kain - Soul Reaver-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Mana.pbp</path>
		<name>Legend of Mana</name>
		<desc>Create Your World
In ancient times, the world was saved from destruction by sealing locations and events within magical artifacts. Now, you have the chance to recreate this world as you desire by discovering artifacts, placing them, and exploring the mysteries inside.

-Construct a unique world map and story by carefully placing artifacts.
-Explore areas in any order, encountering nearly 70 different gameplay scenarios.
-Battle enemies in real-time with special attacks and customizable controls.
-Control every aspect of your new world: raise faithful net monsters, create powerful golems, forge mighty weapons, and refine magical instruments.
-Adventure with a friend by having them import their Legend of Mana character from a MEMORY CARD, or take control of an NPC .</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Legend of Mana-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lucifer Ring.pbp</path>
		<name>Lucifer Ring</name>
		<desc>You play as a young hero named Nash who is tasked with stopping a dark wizard from using the Lucifer Rings that will open the gates of Hell. Naturally, Nash will have to hack and slash his way through Centaurs, Goblins, Dragons and creatures named Bob to put a stop to the evil forces. There will be mini-bosses and multi-state level bosses to round out this adventure to put our hero to the test.

Dark wizards never let heroes get any rest, do they?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Lucifer Ring-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Soft Machine</developer>
		<publisher>Toshiba EMI</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maximum Force.pbp</path>
		<name>Maximum Force</name>
		<desc>Time to lock and load, pal. Straight from arcades everywhere, here come Macimum Force, where it's you against elusive terrorists and you control the body count. You'll board helicopters, ATV's, underwater vehicles and shoot literally everything in sight. Gun down slimeballs on three completely different missions. Blast your way into over 35 secret rooms and blow away everything with extreme prejudice. With Maximum Force, there's no such thing as too much firepower.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Maximum Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tantalus Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MDK.pbp</path>
		<name>MDK</name>
		<desc>MDK is a 3rd person action/shooter game in which the objective is to basically shoot everything that moves in six massive cities, each with their own sublevels. Because the world is being invaded by aliens, it is up to you and your sidekick Bones to stop the invasion and single handedly save Earth. In order to do so, you must make good use of your special suit, which allows you to do all kinds of things.

The super-suit comes equipped with many features you'll need to utilize in your journey, such as the sniper helmet. This allows you to zoom in on unsuspecting enemies and fire off shots with pinpoint accuracy. There is also a built in parachute (a ribbon-like device) that enables you to glide between different platforms as well as drop down on intruders.

Your suit comes equipped with a chain gun that has an infinite supply of ammunition. You can also pick up special items, like a miniature nuclear bomb and powerful upgrades for your chaingun. In addition to running around and shooting, there are also special means of transportation including a surfboard-like jet and a bomber plane that is used to call in air strikes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/MDK-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny</developer>
		<publisher>Playmates Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor.pbp</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor</name>
		<desc>Medal of Honor is the first in the long-running series of World War II shooters, originally created by Steven Spielberg. The play assumes the role of Lt. Patterson who has to complete different tasks in the OSS. The missions vary from securing a small French village from any Nazi forces, to taking out a Heavy armored German rail gun. The player has access to a wide selection of antique weapons such as P38 pistols, M1 Garand carabines, MP40's and more. The goals also include undercover missions. Split-screen multiplayer is supported for two players.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Medal of Honor-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dreamworks</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor Underground.pbp</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor: Underground</name>
		<desc>The game is a prequel to Medal of Honor and it is set in the early stages of WWII. You play as Manon Batiste, who briefed the missions for you in the original Medal of Honor. She is a new member of a small band of French rebels who fight against the tyranny of the Germans.

There are 7 missions in total, featuring 12 different historical weapons. There are NPCs helping you out by cracking safes and driving. Not all enemies are on foot; expect to face tanks and bikes amongst other things. Enemy AI is responsive and sometimes surprising.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Medal of Honor Underground-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20001125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamWorks Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medievil.pbp</path>
		<name>MediEvil</name>
		<desc>The game starts with a flashback in the 13th century in the fictional English Kingdom of Gallowmere. The game puts the player in control of Sir Daniel Fortesque: the reanimated skeletal remains of a deceased champion knight whom history holds in high esteem, due to his supposed heroics in battle against the evil sorcerer Zarok who, in 1286, had raised an army of demons and set out to take over the kingdom. The legend has it that Fortesque lead the King's army into battle against Zarok's demonic hordes and that Sir Daniel himself killed the sorcerer during the battle - despite having actually been mortally wounded at the outset - cementing his posthumous status as the "Hero of Gallowmere".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Medievil-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Cambridge Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medievil 2.pbp</path>
		<name>MediEvil II</name>
		<desc>After Sir Daniel Fortesque slew the evil sorcerer Zarok, he went to the Hall of Heroes and his body went to rest for all eternity in peace as a true hero. Now, 500 years later, Dan has been awakened in a Victorian museum in Kensington, 1886, and is found by a helpful ghost named Winston. He learns that Zarok's spell book has unfortunately been found by another sorcerer named Lord Palethorn. Upon opening the book, Palethorn managed to scatter all of the pages across London, turn himself into an elf with red skin (a side effect from the book losing all of its content) and unleashed the living dead amongst the city. So, it's up to Sir Dan and his new allies, a professor with metal hands and a mummy princess named Kiya to stop Palethorn from collecting all the lost pages of the spell book to take over all of London.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Medievil 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000509T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCE Cambridge Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman 8.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man 8</name>
		<desc>A gigantic space explosion sends two strange meteors crashing to Earth. The call goes out and Mega Man speeds to the site. There he sees his arch-rival, Dr. Wiley, fleeing the scene, clutching one of the mysterious metallic meteors. Now Mega Man must uncover the secret of the second meteor in a race to stay one step ahead of Dr. Wiley and his new deadly breed of super-powered robots.

• Battle across 14 huge stages to face eight devious new enemies.
• Multiple upgrades for Mega Man - customize to your specifications every game.
• Intense Japanese anime intros, cut scenes and cinema screens.
• Incredibly fluid animation and highly detailed backgrounds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman 8-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Battle &amp; Chase.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man Battle &amp; Chase</name>
		<desc>It's robot mayhem at the Battle &amp; Chase tournament! Dr. Wily is trying to take over the tournament with his army of Robot Masters, and now Mega Man has to enter to try and save the races! Choose your racer and head out on the tracks, and if you win, you'll get to steal parts off your opponent's cars, and eventually, you'll race against the mad Dr. Wily himself!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman Battle &amp; Chase-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Legends.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man Legends</name>
		<desc>THE BLUE BOMBER BLASTS INTO A WHOLE NEW DIMENSION

Mega Man blasts his way into the third dimension in an amazing new adventure. Mega Man Legends combines the best of classic Mega Man action with enormous bosses, a riveting storyline and all the depth of the hottest RPG.

Explore vast 3-D worlds in your quest to find the treasure of all treasures, the Mother Lode. You'll love the new 3-D graphics, deadly weapons and non-stop action... unless of course, you're a boss.

* Awesome Weapons!
* Diabolical Bosses!
* Legendary Gameplay!
* Non-Stop 3-D Action!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman Legends-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Legends 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man Legends 2</name>
		<desc>Mega Man, Roll, and all your favorites are back in this all new 3-D adventure!  Far away, in an isolated wasteland, a mysterious girl and an infamous treasure have been discovered.  It's the legendary "Sealed Key," rumored to unlock an even greater mystery known as the Great Legacy.  What power does the Great Legacy hold?  Now, a raced unfolds as Mega Man and his friends embark on a journey which will alter their destinies forever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman Legends 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X4.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man X4</name>
		<desc>X-PLOSIVE GAMEPLAY.
X-TREME GRAPHICS.
MEGA MAN X4!

Vibrant Animation • Relentless Enemies
Unsurpassed Graphics • Hidden Secrets
Mega Man X4 bombards the PlayStation game console and never lets up!

Battle armies of Maverick Reploid Robots while mastering all-new strategic moves like the Air Hover and Zero's Saber Tactic system. Discover a myriad of power-ups, secret rooms, extra weapons and invincible vehicles to take on 8 all new X-Hunter Bosses. And for the first time, play as Mega Man X or battle with his mighty partner Zero in 2 separate adventures. Mega Man X4 - now you can be a hero, or a Zero!

* Now, play as Mega Man X or Zero!
* New X-Hunter levels with vivid color, brilliant detail, intricate passages, secret rooms and hard-to-reach items
* Invincible vehicles like the Land Chaser superbike and other robot ride armors</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman X4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19970810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X5.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man X5</name>
		<desc>The year is 21XX and the chaos of the Reploid Wars has passed. Lunar colonization is at its peak. The largest colony, Eurasia, is unexpectedly taken over by an unknown band of galactic terrorists. Its artificial gravity device has been hacked and Eurasia is now on a collision course with Earth. The only way to stop it is to deploy an ancient beam cannon, Codename: Enigma. Join Mega Man X and his pal, Zero as they race against time to collect the necessary parts to restart Enigma, prevent total annihilation and save life on Earth!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman X5-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman X6.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man X6</name>
		<desc>Mission Critical... Zero is Missing... Search and Rescue!

It's been three weeks since Earth's near collision with the space colony Eurasia. The disaster was averted by Zero's heroics. Now, on a bruised and battered planet, tales of rampaging reploids are surfacing. It's up to Mega Man X to investigate these mysteries but it's not going to be easy. Mega Man X must battle through a maze of levels and rescue reploids along the way. Return to battle again and again with the new Nightmare System, which randomizes level maps, enemies, and endings based on how you play the game. Mega Man X is back and now it's personal!

* The next action packed-adventure in the Mega Man X legacy – help find Zero!
* Collect stronger powerups by rescuing as many reploids as you can
* Mega Man X now access Zero's sword as a new weapon
* New Nightmare System – randomizes level maps, enemies and endings based on how you play the game</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Megaman X6-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid.pbp</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid</name>
		<desc>Metal Gear Solid follows Solid Snake, a soldier who infiltrates a nuclear weapons facility to neutralize the terrorist threat from FOXHOUND, a renegade special forces unit. Snake must liberate two hostages, the head of DARPA and the president of a major arms manufacturer, confront the terrorists, and stop them from launching a nuclear strike.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Metal Gear Solid-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid - VR Missions.pbp</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid: VR Missions</name>
		<desc>A semi-sequel/prequel to the highly acclaimed Metal Gear Solid (MGS), Metal Gear Solid: VR Missions puts you once again in control of the top-level FoxHound field specialist, Solid Snake. This time around, instead of fighting genetically engineered soldiers and saving the world from Metal Gear, you're in a combat simulator. Aboard the Discovery (the submarine that Solid Snake traveled upon before reaching Angel Island), you will prepare for the dangers ahead.

For those that have yet to experience MGS, the gameplay is based around strategy, tactics and action. Metal Gear Solid: VR Missions's interface and concept is similar to its predecessor, but is based on the simulator game mode that was included in MGS. This time, instead of just a few missions, you have nearly 150 different stages to play (300 including the Time Attack modes). Fans of MGS should be able to quickly pick up on the gameplay style. In fact, not only is the gameplay recognizable by fans of the original Metal Gear Solid, each of the missions (although similarities are sometimes minute) are based on events that occurred in MGS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Metal Gear Solid - VR Missions-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEJ</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Maniacs Racing.pbp</path>
		<name>Micro Maniacs Racing</name>
		<desc>Micro Maniacs is an unofficial sequel to the Micro Machines racing games and features a similar 3D perspective to the previous game, Micro Machines V3.

As with previous games, the racing environments are based in real-world locations such as kitchens, laboratories and gardens, played "zoomed in" due to the miniature nature of the racers

The 12 character choices (some of which are unlockable) are differentiated by various unique attack moves.

Instead of racing with vehicles, the Micro Maniacs race on foot.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Micro Maniacs Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Kids</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mille Miglia.pbp</path>
		<name>Mille Miglia</name>
		<desc>A racing game set in the golden era of BMWs and Mercedes, Alfa Romeos and Bugattis, Enzo Ferrari and Sterling Moss, but with all the 3D rendering effects you would expect from a standard Playstation racer.

Putting you in the seat of some of the most well-known racing cars of the time, Mille Miglia lets you try out well well-honed Playstation 'driving' skills on some new, but old, tracks. Letting you take part in full championship mode, the game sets you about some idyllic countryside scenery in the hopes of obtaining that elusive victory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Mille Miglia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kung Fu Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCI</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mission Impossible.pbp</path>
		<name>Mission: Impossible</name>
		<desc>Tie-in of the popular movie Mission: Impossible, this is a third-person action stealth game with 24 levels. Playing the secret agent Ethan Hunt, the player has to fight international terrorists. Assisted by his IMF team, he sneaks into enemy bases, blows up ammunition depots, retrieves stolen information and takes out the terrorists.

The plot is loosely based on the movie; Ethan Hunt is framed and has to prove his innocence which he is only able to do with the help of his good friends from the IMF team.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Mission Impossible-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Monster Inc.pbp</path>
		<name>Monsters, Inc. Scream Team</name>
		<desc>What would you say if you found out that the scary monsters hiding in children's closet were all part of a corporate conspiracy? Well, that's the premise of the 2001 Disney or Pixar film, Monsters, Inc., and it's the basis of this videogame for the PlayStation. Play as either Sully or Mike two of the monsters hired to scare little kids as you move from house to house, just trying to do your job. The company you work for is in the business of drumming up "scream energy," so you'll have to be extra frightening if you hope to succeed. Each of the game's 3D environments is detailed and expansive, representing the movie well, and there are dozens of hidden bonuses and power-ups that you can use toy your advantage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Monster Inc-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCEA, Disney Interactive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat 4.pbp</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 4</name>
		<desc>Similar to the other Mortal Kombat games. Using 3D characters in a 2D playfield, you have about 20 different fighters to choose from, and each has magical secrets and weapons.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Mortal Kombat 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./N2O - Nitrous Oxide.pbp</path>
		<name>N2O: Nitrous Oxide</name>
		<desc>Somewhere deep in the future our Galaxy is at war. On the nearby planet of Neptune, forces of evil have initiated their new plans to invade the Earth. By accelerating sub-atomic particles around a tubular shaped circuit known as The Torus, they are developing a race of Super Warriors. Together with advanced genetic engineering, this central birthing canal is capable of producing an army of lethal genetically mutated insects.
Nitrous Oxide, a pollutant by-product emitted inside The Torus, provides a high octane fuel for your Tunnel Runner, but unfortunately it also provides the perfect breeding environment for the secretly incubating species.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/N2O - Nitrous Oxide-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Live 2001.pbp</path>
		<name>NBA Live 2001</name>
		<desc>With yet another edition of the annual NBA Live Basketball series surfacing, the question is whether the change is worht the price tag. NBA Live 2001 embraces all of the action of the NBA, while featuring all of your favorite NBA stars and rookies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/NBA Live 2001-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Canada</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Live 99.pbp</path>
		<name>NBA Live 99</name>
		<desc>NBA Live 99 is the 1999 installment of the NBA Live video games series. The cover features Antoine Walker of the Boston Celtics. The game was developed by EA Sports and released on October 31, 1998 for the Windows and PlayStation, then in November 4, 1998 for the Nintendo 64. Don Poier is the play-by-play announcer. It was the first NBA Live game released for Nintendo 64. NBA Live 99 is followed by NBA Live 2000.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/NBA Live 99-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC.pbp</path>
		<name>NBA Showtime: NBA on NBC</name>
		<desc>The NBA like you've never seen it before! NBA Showtime: NBA on NBC brings you the top players from each team in a heart-pounding, pulse-racing above-the-rim match-up! You'll see the intensity on their faces and hear it in their voices, you'll feel the power of every pass and every shot! This is what the NBA is all about! Go for rebounds and 3-pointers in all 28 arenas around the league. Choose from over 130 real NBA players plus hidden characters!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need For Speed Porche Unleashed.pbp</path>
		<name>Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed tests your driving skills while you test-drive some of Porsche's most popular cars. In the game, you'll compete in levels that feature twists, turns, and various driving conditions. You can participate in different types of races, including circuit, streetcar, open road, and more. Survive all the crashes, police, and track challenges to earn prizes and respect. With enough money, you can purchase different custom parts for your vehicle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Need For Speed Porche Unleashed-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightmare Creatures.pbp</path>
		<name>Nightmare Creatures</name>
		<desc>A bloody good time in jolly old London.

In 1834 on London's blackest eve, a secret cult known as The Brotherhood of Hecate, rediscovered the key to man's unholiest fears. It was through this arcane act of terror that the evil leader of the Brotherhood, Adam Crowley, swore to overtake the world... Ever since this fateful night, not a London street, alley or town square has escaped the whispered screams of "Nightmare Creatures!"

Select Your Merciless Alter Ego
Battle as the bloodthirsty monk, lgnatius, or Nadia, the lethal female fatale, seeking to avenge her father's brutal murder.

Confront 21 Hideous Creatures
Butcher brigades of beast and zombies that continue their relentless assaults after losing limbs...

Choose Your Mutilation Technique
Dismember legions of diabolical demons with over 28 mutilating mover until the ultimate confrontation with the evil Adam Crowley.

Explore the Horrors of London
Solve puzzles and search for clues in the dark, damp streets, sewers and alleyways of 16 increasingly ominous levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Nightmare Creatures-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kalisto Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightmare Creatures 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Nightmare Creatures II</name>
		<desc>Assume the role of Herbet Wallace, an escaped test subject, on the trail of the demonic scientist, Dr. Adam Crowley. After enduring years of horrific lab experiments, Wallace is out to settle the score in a chilling and bloody chase through London and Paris.
Little does he know that exacting revenge on Crowley is also the last hope to save the world from a nightmarish demise.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Nightmare Creatures 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja - Shadow of Darkness.pbp</path>
		<name>Ninja: Shadow of Darkness</name>
		<desc>The creators of Tomb Raider and Fighting Force bring you NINJA: Shadow of Darkness.

Enter the mystical world of Kurosawa, the young ninja, as he fights his way through 11 levels of puzzles, baddies and bosses with dozens of fighting moves, weapons and magic spells in this third person action arcade game from Eidos Interactive.

Dozens of fighting moves plus special magic attacks each more powerful than the next!

More baddies and bosses than ever, including numerous Dragons, Demons, Goblins and a host of other monsters.

Ten unique environments including forests, beaches, mountains and demon lairs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ninja - Shadow of Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oddworld - Abes Exoddus.pbp</path>
		<name>Oddworld: Abe's Exoddus</name>
		<desc>Oddworld: Abe's Exoddus is a 2D platform game very similar to its predecessor both visually and gameplay-wise. Like in the previous game, Abe has to outsmart his foes and avoid obstacles rather than confront them directly. The game is larger than its predecessor and is more oriented towards puzzle-solving, featuring more complex interaction with the Mudokons, who can now be angry, wired, depressed, sick, or blind. The first three problematic conditions can be removed with the appropriate "Gamespeak" command; sick Mudokons must be cured with a special item, while blind ones will follow Abe's voice and may fall to their deaths if Abe doesn't stop them in time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Oddworld - Abes Exoddus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oddworld - Abes Odysee.pbp</path>
		<name>Oddworld: Abe's Oddysee</name>
		<desc>In a lush of diabolical danger where everyone wants to eat you, you're the skinny guy with no weapons. Run, jump, hide, scramble and talk your way past the ugliest bunch of carnivorous crustaceans ever created. Unlock Abe's special powers then figure out your foes, and you might save your race. Don't, and you're dinner! Enter Oddworld's surreal, sensory overload of pure gaming and claim your destiny.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Oddworld - Abes Odysee-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Oddworld Inhabitants</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Omega Boost.pbp</path>
		<name>Omega Boost</name>
		<desc>Co-Existence between man and machine is no longer an option. The fate of humankind is hanging by a fiber... time is running out.

-Pilot Omega Boost in a high-intensity action shooter across 19 diverse zones.
-Multiple mission objectives, lethal ground and air assaults and deadly cyber-drogues.
-Free-float in dizzying 360o combat.
-Scan for targets, fire Vulcan guns and bag those bogeys with laser lock-on in the ultimate space dogfights!
-Customize and upgrade equipment and weaponry with every win.
-Review intense battles with the Replay Mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Omega Boost-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./One.pbp</path>
		<name>One</name>
		<desc>ONE is a 1997 third-person action game for the PlayStation. It follows the story of John Cain, who wakes in an apartment to discover that one of his arms has been replaced with a gun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/One-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19971130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>ASC Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-man World.pbp</path>
		<name>Pac-Man World</name>
		<desc>The nonstop action of Pac-Man enters the 3D realm. Pac-Man World offers you three gameplay modes: Quest, Maze, and Classic. During the Quest mode, you'll enter Ghost Island and help Pac-Man save his friends through six unique worlds. In the Maze mode, there are mazes galore to fulfill your cravings to chase Pinky, Inky, Blinky, and Clyde in a variety of 3D maze environments. The Classic mode is for the nostalgic-at-heart to play the original arcade game that made Pac-Man a legend.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Pac-man World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Bandit.pbp</path>
		<name>Panzer Bandit</name>
		<desc>An evil robotic army invades city after city and nothing seems to stop them, that is until fighting hero Kou and his band of heroes decide to put the hurt on the invading forces and set off in a quest to liberate each city and finally destroy their flying robotic whale HQ.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Panzer Bandit-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill In Cafe</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve 2</name>
		<desc>Aya Brea is back. The Neo Mitochondrion Creature infestation has resurfaced and taken on a sinister twist. The outcome of this battle will determine earth's dominant species. Horrifying CG cinemas and sharper graphics bring the shocking new storyline to life as Aya hunts for the source of the outbreak. Fully-upgradable weapons, customizable armor, and a new, real-time battle system will aid in the conflict, along with powerful new Parasite Energy abilities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Parasite Eve 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun Shooting - Simple 1500.pbp</path>
		<name>The Gun Shooting</name>
		<desc>Set in the vast African continent, fight against corruption and destruction in a new 3D shooting game. Adopt simple rules and pursue all enemies similar to the action found in game centers. Additionally, team up for 2P gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gun Shooting - Simple 1500-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nekogumi</developer>
		<publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Dragoon.pbp</path>
		<name>The Legend of Dragoon</name>
		<desc>A peaceful beginning. The legend was born 10,000 years ago. A violent uprising. A civilization of flying creatures enslave the human race. A bloody war. In a bid for freedom, the humans harness the spiritual forces of Dragons and triumph. Tranquility and harmony exist between all. But the past and the future are about to collide...

Unveil a fantasy of Magnificence, Deception, Magical Combat and Retribution.

• 3 years in the making with a development team of over 100 members.
• Transform into Dragoons and unleash extraordinary powers.
• Incredibly diverse characters wield unique weapons and Dragoon attacks powered by the forces of Earth, Light, Fire, Wind, Lightning, Water and Darkness.
• Totally unique and innovative tactical combat "Additionals" System.
• An unforgettable adventure.

The journey that seeks the past ends. And the journey to discover today begins. Unleash the spirit of the Dragoons. And discover your destiny.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Legend of Dragoon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astro Trooper Vanark.pbp</path>
		<name>Vanark</name>
		<desc>Vanark is, at its core, a shooter. Sure, it's a 3D shooter "on rails" in the grand tradition of Star Fox or the Saturn's Panzer Dragoon series, but the difference here, is that it's the PlayStation's first great example of one. It's a tried-and-true method of laying on the action, and while there were plenty of opportunities for Asmik to screw up the formula, but luckily, they never really dropped the ball, at least not when it came to the shooter parts.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Astro Trooper Vanark-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Magical Racing Tour.pbp</path>
		<name>Walt Disney World Quest Magical Racing Tour</name>
		<desc>Walt Disney World Quest Magical Racing Tour boasts more playable characters than any kart racer before it (a total of 13 are offered), and each of the game's tracks allows you to maneuver a different vehicle. Instead of being confined to just a go-kart, you'll get a bobsled, or a rocket ship, and several others. Collect a myriad of power-ups to your vehicle such as Mickey coins which allow you to race a little faster with each additional coin you collect. Or use the guided bottle rocket to get a speed boost and home in on your opponent. You can also collect items that can be used against your opponents like the frog spell, which will leave them hopping in your dust. Or launch an acorn at them and send them flying out of control.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Magical Racing Tour-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alfred Chicken.pbp</path>
		<name>Alfred Chicken</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Alfred Chicken-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney - Toy Story 2 Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue.pbp</path>
		<name>Disney's Toy Story 2: Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue!</name>
		<desc>Woody has been stolen from the bedroom, ready to be sold to the highest bidder by an evil toy collector.  It's up to good friend Buzz Lightyear to fight his way through from the bedroom to the outside world in order to save Woody from the toy market and bring him home.  All of the character from the 3D animated movie appear through-out the side scroller to help Buzz get to where he is needed.  Along with the use of his cannon, Buzz can jump to hard to reach places, also useful in collecting the hidden coins that open bonus levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Disney - Toy Story 2 Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy V.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy V</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Anthology combines two titles from the Final Fantasy series and offers PlayStation owners a glimpse into the past. Huge worlds, in-depth storylines, and innovative battle and magic systems, and an incredible cast of characters all make for a deep gaming experience. The inclusion of Final Fantasy V marks the first time this title has appeared on a console in North America. Final Fantasy VI, originally released as Final Fantasy III on the SNES system in the U.S., makes its first appearance on the PlayStation. Both games in this compilation feature never-before-seen CG movies, adding to the appeal of these classics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy V-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy VI.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy VI</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Anthology combines two titles from the Final Fantasy series and offers PlayStation owners a glimpse into the past. Huge worlds, in-depth storylines, and innovative battle and magic systems, and an incredible cast of characters all make for a deep gaming experience. The inclusion of Final Fantasy V marks the first time this title has appeared on a console in North America. Final Fantasy VI, originally released as Final Fantasy III on the SNES system in the U.S., makes its first appearance on the PlayStation. Both games in this compilation feature never-before-seen CG movies, adding to the appeal of these classics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Anthology - Final Fantasy VI-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Chronicles - Chrono Trigger.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Chronicles - Chrono Trigger</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Chronicles features two previously-released ports by TOSE; Final Fantasy IV and Chrono Trigger were released separately, and Final Fantasy IV was re-released as a part of Final Fantasy Collection, all published in Japan.[15] Chronicles was designed and directed by Kazuhiko Aoki, supervised by Fumiaki Fukaya, and produced by Akihiro Imai.[16] It was created as a follow-up to Final Fantasy Anthology, a compilation of Final Fantasy V and Final Fantasy VI.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Chronicles - Chrono Trigger-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Chronicles - Final Fantasy IV.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Chronicles - Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<desc>Final Fantasy Chronicles features two previously-released ports by TOSE; Final Fantasy IV and Chrono Trigger were released separately, and Final Fantasy IV was re-released as a part of Final Fantasy Collection, all published in Japan.[15] Chronicles was designed and directed by Kazuhiko Aoki, supervised by Fumiaki Fukaya, and produced by Akihiro Imai.[16] It was created as a follow-up to Final Fantasy Anthology, a compilation of Final Fantasy V and Final Fantasy VI.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy Chronicles - Final Fantasy IV-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Horned Owl.pbp</path>
		<name>Project: Horned Owl</name>
		<desc>An invasion of mechanized terrorists turns your city into an urban battleground!

Time: the future- Metro City is under attack from legions of robots directed by a twisted dictator. Your squad of mech-suited cops hits the ground, transformed into deadly defense unit. Your city is buckling, street by street - can you stop a total mech takeover?

-A non-stop action shooter exclusively for the PlayStation game console.
-Two player co-op mode and KONAMI ENFORCER Gun support double the destruction!
-Interactive backgrounds allow you to blast cars, obliterate walls and annihilate mech suits on factory conveyors. Watch out-innocent civilians are everywhere!
-Incredible Japanese anime sequences connect battle scenes into an all out urban war!
-Rapid fire combat packed with futuristic war machines including cybercops, armored mechs with automatic weapons, tanks, missiles, bombs, energy scans and high-tech Heads-Up-displays.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Project Horned Owl-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MOVIC</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake II.pbp</path>
		<name>Quake II</name>
		<desc>A sequel in name only, this follow up to id’s 1996 Quake, is a first-person shooter revolving around the Earth-Strogg war. The Strogg alien race threatens the Earth, but Earth has launched a counter-offensive, Operation Alien Overlord. Overlord takes the battle to the Strogg homeworld with the ultimate objective of securing their capital city and killing their ruler.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Quake II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-type Delta.pbp</path>
		<name>R-Type Delta</name>
		<desc>R-Type Delta is a horizontally scrolling shooter video game. Released only on the PlayStation, this is the fourth game in the R-Type series (hence Delta, the fourth letter of the Greek alphabet), and also the first game offering different fighters, with different Force and Wave Cannon combinations for the player to choose from. Set in 2164, Delta is also the first game in the R-Type series rendered in full 3D graphics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/R-type Delta-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19990731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R4 - Ridge Racer Type 4.pbp</path>
		<name>R4: Ridge Racer Type 4</name>
		<desc>"R4 has to be the best-looking PlayStation racer ever (yes, edging out even Gran Turismo)." – Official PlayStation Magazine, December 1998

* 8 tracks, 45 unique car models, and over 300 different car variations.
* Sensational graphics and lighting effects give every race a cinematic feel.
* Battle head-to-head in the 2-player, split screen VS mode.
* Experience all the ups and downs of a full racing season with your team in the Grand Prix Mode.
* New cars awarded based on your performance in every race.
* Design original logos to customize your car.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/R4 - Ridge Racer Type 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rally de Africa.pbp</path>
		<name>Rally de Africa</name>
		<desc>Rally de Africa is a Racing game, published by Prism Arts, which was released in Japan in 1998.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rally de Africa-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rally de Europe.pbp</path>
		<name>Rally De Europe</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rally de Europe-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Idol Minds</developer>
		<publisher>Prism Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RayCrisis - Series Termination.pbp</path>
		<name>RayCrisis: Series Termination</name>
		<desc>An ambitious and unethical scientist, a secret experiment gone horribly awry, and an artificially intelligent supercomputer gone mad; all the necessary ingredients for the imminent extinction of mankind. You are humanity's last hope, a hotshot pilot given the unenviable task of flying an experimental fighter into the dark heart of the Con-Human Network. Seize the controls of three Wave Rider spacecraft, each equippped with the WR-01 primary weapon array, WR-02 secondary lock-on laser system, and WR-03 single-use weapon for emergency situations. RayCrisis: Series Termination is the final entry in Taito's acclaimed trilogy of shooters, and it bombards your CRT with an abundance of fourth-generation optical stimulation: multilevel scrolling, transparency and lighting effects, and enough polygons to overload your cerebral cortex. Dodge, weave, and blast through two play modes, disintegrating wave after wave of relentless bogeys, to achieve high scores and unlock hidden bonuses. Prepare your senses, reinforce your nerves, and limber your trigger finger - the final assault has begun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/RayCrisis - Series Termination-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Rayman</name>
		<desc>Captivating, mind-bending and addictive one trip and you're hooked!

Enter the challenging world of Rayman and suddenly reality seems far too tame. Free your mind as Rayman takes you on an arduous adventure through a complex realm of psychedelic landscapes, absurd characters, formidable opponents, and uncharted levels of dementia. This mind-altering platform game features...

* Menacing opponents that learn your playing style to defeat you.
* Incredibly intense visuals with 65,000 colors and four independently scrolling backdrops.
* 70 surrealistic levels.
* Over 50 demented characters.
* Exhilarating CD-quality sound effects and music.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rayman 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RayStorm.pbp</path>
		<name>RayStorm</name>
		<desc>The year is 2219 and the Secilia Federation has initiated a plan to destroy Earth. So far, the evil federation has been highly successful in destroying much of the planet's defensive forces and resources. With world destruction at hand, the fate of mankind is looking for a savior.

Unbeknownst to the federation, the Star Federation, an Earth-based organization, has been developing two highly sophisticated aircraft known as the R-Gray prototypes. These destructive machines are packed with homing missiles, laser cannons and other crippling weapons. As the planet's hero, you'll control either R-Gray ship, taking to the skies in a desperate mission to stop the Secilia Federation from carrying out their plans.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/RayStorm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Spaz (Working Designs)</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./RC de GO!.pbp</path>
		<name>RC De Go!</name>
		<desc>Sure, you could race circles around your mother's feet with your old RC car, but can you handle professional racing in RC de GO? This game is all about those Radio Controlled cars that fascinate children and even adults across the country.

Grit your teeth and prepare yourself for racing; RC style! RC de GO is composed of 4 modes of play: Practice, Quick Race, Championship, and Time Attack. The practice mode is a tutorial that takes you through the controls of your RC car in a step-to-step course. After you've gone through the basics, you'll attempt a practice race.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/RC de GO!-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000802T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ready 2 Rumble Boxing - Round 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing: Round 2</name>
		<desc>Ready 2 Rumble: Round 2 is a cartoon style boxing beat 'em up with plenty of strange looking characters to choose from and beat the hell out of. You can train your character up to the best of his/her ability and then fight the best in the world for the championship belt.

Round 2 adds some new play modes and characters into the mix of previous fighters. In this round, there are now 3 levels to the RUMBLE combo gauge (much like a Street Fighter game). Once you reach the third level, you can hit your enemy for six, out of the ring and into the crowd.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing - Round 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Point of View</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 - Claire.pbp</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 - Claire</name>
		<desc>If the Suspense Doesn't Kill You, Something Else Will

Face your fears in the ultimate test for survival. Something is desperately wrong in Raccoon City. A muta-genic virus has broken loose and the entire town is infested. Blood-thirsty zombies, hideous mutations now overwhelm the community. When Leon and Claire arrive in town, their nightmare is just beginning...Now, you control their destiny.
2 Separate Adventures. Play as Leon Kennedy or Claire Redfield in an all out struggle for survival
Loaded with hidden items that contain vital information relating to the entire Resident Evil series
Hidden game modes -- play the panic struck '4th Survivor' mode or as the hidden character, Tofu
Special settings to adjust the intensity of the game according to players skill and experience</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Resident Evil 2 - Claire-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 - Leon.pbp</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 - Leon</name>
		<desc>If the Suspense Doesn't Kill You, Something Else Will

Face your fears in the ultimate test for survival. Something is desperately wrong in Raccoon City. A muta-genic virus has broken loose and the entire town is infested. Blood-thirsty zombies, hideous mutations now overwhelm the community. When Leon and Claire arrive in town, their nightmare is just beginning...Now, you control their destiny.
2 Separate Adventures. Play as Leon Kennedy or Claire Redfield in an all out struggle for survival
Loaded with hidden items that contain vital information relating to the entire Resident Evil series
Hidden game modes -- play the panic struck '4th Survivor' mode or as the hidden character, Tofu
Special settings to adjust the intensity of the game according to players skill and experience</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Resident Evil 2 - Leon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3: Nemesis</name>
		<desc>Join Jill Valentine, the heroine and amazing survivor of the notorious disaster at the mansion, as her nightmare continues. After resigning from S.T.A.R.S. Jill now prepares to head out of Raccoon City...but it's not going to be easy. Caught in a town crawling with flesh eating zombies, more than ever she must rely on brute force and cunning to find a way to escape alive. This unique adventure intricately reveals more of Umbrella Corporation's nightmarish plot and picks up just hours before the events from Resident Evil 2.

More zombies, more terror, and even more evil.
More challenging enemies that come back to life at any time.
Face off against the most terrifying mutations stalking the streets of Raccoon City.
More detailed character actions: Try the dodge move to avoid an enemy's attack.
Interact with the environment like never before: Use background objects defensively.
A unique new drama which reveals more details of Umbrella Corporation's devious activities from the Resident Evil series.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Resident Evil 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Survivor.pbp</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Survivor</name>
		<desc>First there was Raccoon City…but unknown to the rest of the world, another town is also mutating into a chaotic nightmare from the deadly T-Virus. Attempting to flee the carnage, a solitary helicopter loses control and crash lands in the heart of the chaos. As one lone survivor comes to, the sound of screaming and other monstrous sounds surround him. Dazed and unsure where he is or why he is there, he embarks on a nightmarish adventure where cunning and quick reflexes are the key to survival.

Experience Resident Evil in first-person perspective
The only game of its kind! Full, free movement – no predestined track
Surprise elements and hidden secrets entwine with the Resident Evil storyline</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Resident Evil - Survivor-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Directors Cut.pbp</path>
		<name>Resident Evil: Director's Cut</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil: Director's Cut is a reissue of the original Resident Evil. Unlike Resident Evil for the GameCube, it is not a remake of the original game, instead, it is more of a slight remix.

There are three gameplay modes available. "Original" contains the original game with no changes or additions. "Beginner" features double the amount of ammunition and save ribbons, plus increased health for the player, increased damage for their weapons, and an auto-target feature.

"Arrange" mode is the "Director's Cut" version of the original. The default outfits for Jill, Chris, and Rebecca are changed, new camera angles are introduced, and the placement of key items is changed. Most of these changes are designed to play against the expectations of veteran players of the first Resident Evil - so zombie dogs may smash through new windows, or keys will not be where they were, forcing players to hunt for them anew. The default Beretta pistol is also changed to a chromed version with a randomized chance to kill standard zombies in one shot.

The original release of the Director's Cut advertised an uncut version of the opening cinema, in full color, and never-before seen. Notable aspects of this video include shots of a corpse with bites taken out of the face, close-ups of zombie dogs bleeding when shot, and graphic quick-cuts of Joseph being bitten by these dogs. Chris is also shown smoking in his introduction, which was cut from Western releases. However, only the French and German releases contained this footage. U.S. and UK versions retained the censored black-and-white video shipped with the original release. This has never been corrected, either in the Greatest Hits reissue, or with the PSOne Classics downloads on the Playstation Network.

The original issue of the Director's Cut contained a demo of Resident Evil 2 on a second disc. The "Greatest Hits" re-release added Dual Shock support for the controller (left "movement" stick only).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Resident Evil - Directors Cut-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19970925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rising Zan - The Samurai Gunman.pbp</path>
		<name>Rising Zan: The Samurai Gunman</name>
		<desc>Rising Zan is a 3rd person action game with plenty of oddball humor and interesting situations. Zan, the main character wields the weapons of both of his trades... the Sword of a Samurai master, and the six-shooter pistol of an American cowboy. He'll need a variety of techniques to defeat the Jackal Clan and avenge his own lost battle. Zan proceeds through enemies and challenges in each level to eventually reach the boss who he then battles in some form of specialized combat or pattern. Once the boss is defeated, Zan gets the chance to unleash as much punishment on his foe in 30 seconds as he can; higher damage values will change the finishing move he uses to slay his foe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rising Zan - The Samurai Gunman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>UEP Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Agetec</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rival Schools - United by Fate.pbp</path>
		<name>Rival Schools</name>
		<desc>RIVAL SCHOOLS...OUT OF CONTROL!

Capcom unleashes explosive tag-team fighting action in Rival Schools – the most innovative 3-D fighter that teams up 14 brand new warriors united by fate. Vibrant graphics, an intense storyline, outrageous new combos and Capcom's signature gameplay make Rival Schools the 3-D tag-team battle that's completely out of control!
In the ultimate fight for justice, there is no rival!

* Explosive 3-D tag-team fighting
* 14 brand new, outrageous characters
* Features 8 modes of gameplay, including League Battle, Tournament, Edit Mode and more!
* 2 Discs! The arcade perfect translation plus the enhanced "Evolutions" Disc.
* For 1 or 2 players</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rival Schools - United by Fate-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rollcage Stage 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Rollcage Stage II</name>
		<desc>Rollcage Stage II is an arcade-style racing game for PlayStation developed by Attention To Detail, and published by Psygnosis. It is the sequel to Rollcage and was released in 2000. On top of the basic racing concept, the cars can be equipped with weapons, that are picked up on the track as bonuses, which can be used against competing cars. The automobiles themselves, once again, have wheels that are larger than the body of the car thus creating a car that has no 'right way up' and can be flipped and continue to drive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Rollcage Stage 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Attention To Detail</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./S.C.A.R.S.pbp</path>
		<name>S.C.A.R.S.</name>
		<desc>S.C.A.R.S stands for "Super Computer Animal Racing Simulation" giving you the wheels behind animal-based vehicles as you race for the finish line. Featuring 4-player split screen action as you compete and try to destroy your feral opponents in a contest of life and death from within a super computer. Features include a variety of race modes including Grand Prix, Challenge and Time Attack. Choose from 9 different hybrid animal vehicles and a host of wepons in this uniquely entertaining release from Ubi Soft.

The story behind the game is yet another one of post-apocalyptic chaos. In the S.C.A.R.S. universe mankind has lost control of the earth and has been superseded by nine supercomputers. After developing all human emotions, the supercomputers became bored with their existence and decided to pass the time with “the most honorable of human customs”: racing (so much for space exploration). Turning to nature for inspiration, the computers based their new land vehicles on some of earth’s most fearsome creatures. They called their new racing league the Super Computer Animal Racing Simulation.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/S.C.A.R.S-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivid Image</developer>
		<publisher>Ubi Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samurai Shodown - Warriors Rage.pbp</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown: Warriors Rage</name>
		<desc>A story about legendary swords.
"Riten-Kyo", located on a lone island near the coastline of Edo, is now a lawless zone where underground conspiracies are forming. Seishirou Kuki, a young government warrior, quietly entered the island to conduct an investigation. There, he finds the unforgettable enemy that killed his father. Here, he will also find the surprise of his life.

Features:
Start with 11 different warriors
Arcade fighting/adventure action
Hidden fighting techniques
Collect all the character cards</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Samurai Shodown - Warriors Rage-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Japan Vistec</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Master.pbp</path>
		<name>Shadow Master</name>
		<desc>Trading ships have not been reaching your planet recently. It is feared that ships passing through a an outer area get caught in a war between two distant alien races. In an attempt to communicate with the crew of these ships your world has found that communictions throughout the solar system have become silent.

Recent stories have told of a death-black shadow engulfing systems. Now that shadow, the Shadow Master, is coming to claim your world. For Shadow Master to have power he destroys anything organic. It is your mission to take control of a space vehicle and clear 16 levels set over seven different worlds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Shadow Master-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HammerHead</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Bomber.pbp</path>
		<name>Silent Bomber</name>
		<desc>Silent Bomber is an old school style game which takes place in the future. You play as a character named Jutah Fate, a genetically engineered man created by the government. You're an expert at using bombs. You start out being able to set only a few bombs at a time, but eventually you can increase the number by collecting E-Chips. It's a fast paced game of blowing things up before they blow you up.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Silent Bomber-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CyberConnect</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai America</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SkullMonkeys.pbp</path>
		<name>Skullmonkeys</name>
		<desc>Something has gone seriously wrong in Klayman's homeland -- Kogg, an evil megalomaniac, wants to destroy the land and basically rule over anything and everyone. Because the task can get difficult at times, he has enlisted the service of fearsome ape-like creatures, Skullmonkeys, to aid in the destruction of planet Idznak. Needless to say, it is up to the player to stop Kogg and his devious plans.

Much like The Neverhood, Skullmonkeys is a 2D platformer built entirely of Claymation characters, enemies, and environments. Throughout the game's seven worlds spanning ninety levels, the basic objective of each is to destroy as many Skullmonkeys as possible. Destroying the simians can be done one of two ways: firing projectile weapons or butt-bouncing off their heads.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/SkullMonkeys-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Neverhood</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sled Storm.pbp</path>
		<name>Sled Storm</name>
		<desc>Sled Storm is a racing game featuring snowmobiles (referred to as sleds), stunts and fourteen snow-covered courses consisting of slippery slopes, inclement weather and treacherous cliffs. Up to four players can also participate at once, making this title one of the few racing games on the PlayStation (as of 1999) to feature split-screen action with more than two players. Sled Storm also offers two forms of racing for both multi-player and solo competition: Championship and Quick Race.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Sled Storm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul of the Samurai.pbp</path>
		<name>Soul of the Samurai</name>
		<desc>Claim your destiny as a proud warrior and honor your ancestors in Soul of the Samurai for Sony's PlayStation.

It's the end of the Edo Period in Old Japan and forces are plotting against the Shogunate. The most powerful of the Shogun's lieutenant's, Kizumi Danmasa, has made a pact with a demon to destroy him and seize control. But the forces of light are already moving against Kizumi. On the side of good, but unknowing of his role, is the samurai, Kotaro Hiba, who has returned to the village of his youth to visit his parents' grave.

Things have changed, people are wary of him and his parents' grave has been ransacked. All roads seem to lead to Kizumi's castle. The story really begins when you find a young woman being attacked by unruly guards and intervene on her behalf.
Enter Lin of Sekirei, Bakafu spy. After a quick scuffle with the crazed town guards, you exchange remarks and head your separate ways. This will not be the final meeting between you two...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Soul of the Samurai-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Debris.pbp</path>
		<name>Space Debris</name>
		<desc>Space Debris is an Action game, developed by Rage Software and published by SCEE, which was released in Europe in 2000.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Space Debris-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>SCEE</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speed Punks.pbp</path>
		<name>Speed Punks</name>
		<desc>Released as Speed Freaks in Europe, Speed Punks is a kart-style racer starring six miniature miscreants who compete on 12 themed courses, ranging from a moonlit cove to a neon city. Each vehicle is individually rated in top speed, weight, collision recovery, and acceleration. After selecting a character, you can choose from the following five play modes: Tournament, Single Race, Time Attack, Versus, and Multiplayer.

Tournament is a four-event race on one of three difficulty settings, where you'll need to finish in the top three to advance. Collect power-ups and weapons found along each course to improve your chances. The 11 items include missiles, bombs, speed boosts, a machine gun, stealth mode, slime, and more. Up to four players can race against each other via split-screen display. Complete various milestones to unlock bonus features and hidden play modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Speed Punks-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Funcom</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man.pbp</path>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
		<desc>YOU DON'T JUST PLAY IT... YOU LIVE IT He spins a web, swings across the sky and lands with a somersault onto the Daily Bugle building. Who is this masked hero? It's you!

Fight, jump and web-sling as Spider-Man as you take on a legion of sinister villains. The city is depending on you. Start swinging...

-Wall-crawl and web-sling in a totally free-roaming, 3-D New York.
-Fight notorious bosses and an assortment of freak-specimens, criminals and tunnel dwellers.
-Web shooters and Spider-Sense let you thwart your enemies' sinister plans.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spider-Man-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2: Enter Electro</name>
		<desc>The Battle for New York Has Begun.

The city is at risk, and only you can save it from the evil of an old enemy: The powerful Electro. He has a mysterious new device that will make his million volts of destruction even more deadly. But, with Spider-Man on the job, Electro is in for the shock of his life.

You don't just play it . . you live it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spider-Man 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010816T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider - The Video Game.pbp</path>
		<name>Spider: The Video Game</name>
		<desc>In Spider: The Video Game you control a spider that has been implanted with a neural transmitter port, cybernetic legs, and weapon accessories. You begin at a sector map which functions as a blueprint of the research laboratory which you must explore. In order to clear a level, you must collect a required number of microchips. You must also find exits in each area in order to advance to the next level.

The spider is always equipped with a Slasher leg and webbing, and he is capable of enhancing his fighting ability with weapons by collecting power-ups. The weapons include homing missiles, flame throwers, boomerangs, and electro-beams. You'll need these munitions to defend yourself against other spiders, cyber-rats, toxic green frogs, and other laboratory pests in this 3-D side-scrolling platform contest.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spider - The Video Game-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Boss Game Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro 2 - Riptos Rage!.pbp</path>
		<name>Spyro 2: Ripto's Rage!</name>
		<desc>Ripto's Rage is the second game in the Spyro the Dragon series, which started with Spyro the Dragon in 1998. The protagonist of the series, Spyro, is placed in the land of Avalar, rather than the Dragon Worlds, where the previous installment was set. A dinosaur-riding sorcerer, known as Ripto, has invaded the world of Avalar, and is wreaking havoc on its citizens with his magic. The player, as Spyro, must travel through the world of Avalar and undo the damage done by Ripto.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spyro 2 - Riptos Rage!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro The Dragon.pbp</path>
		<name>Spyro the Dragon</name>
		<desc>Spyro the Dragon is a platform game developed by Insomniac Games for the PlayStation. It stars the title character, a young purple dragon named Spyro and his dragonfly friend, Sparx, and is the first game in the Spyro the Dragon series. The first game was massively popular at its initial release and Spyro would later become one of the most recognizable, popular and respected gaming icons for the PlayStation gaming console. Spyro's best friend, Sparx the dragonfly, acts like the player's health meter and assists in gathering gems. The various dragons Spyro unfreezes along the way are also key characters in Spyro's progression through the game. Gnasty Gnorc is the main antagonist, who froze all the dragons of the land in crystal.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spyro The Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro 3 - Year of the Dragon.pbp</path>
		<name>Spyro: Year of the Dragon</name>
		<desc>Spyro: Year of the Dragon is the third installment in the Spyro series and the last Spyro game to be released for the PlayStation. The game was the last Spyro game Insomniac developed; their next title would be Ratchet &amp; Clank for the PlayStation 2. This is the only Spyro game in the PlayStation library to not get released in Japan.

Named after the animal of the Chinese zodiac, which was the symbol at the time of the game's release, Year of the Dragon follows the titular purple character Spyro as he travels to the "Forgotten Worlds" after 150 magical dragon eggs are stolen from the land of the dragons by an evil sorceress. Players travel across thirty different worlds gathering gems and eggs. Year of the Dragon introduced new characters and minigames to the series, as well as offering improved graphics and music.

Upon release, the game sold more than two million units in the United States,and received positive critical response. Reviewers noted the game built on the successful formula of its predecessors by adding more games and expansive environments. At Game Rankings, Year of the Dragon is one of the top twenty highest-rated PlayStation games of all time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spyro 3 - Year of the Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stahlfeder.pbp</path>
		<name>Stahlfeder: Tetsukou Hikuudan</name>
		<desc>Stahlfeder, a german word/expression that means "steel feather". 

Stahlfeder - Tetsukou Hikuudan is a vertical scroller shooter game in the tradition of classic shooter games likes 1942, Flying Shark or Dodonpachi. The game features 4 different aircrafts to choose from, 3 difficulty levels, the classics endings level bosses and is divided into 6 different stages.

Polygonal obstacles using real-time boss characters and terrain, a vertical scrolling shooter experience to enjoy the sky world against the backdrop of heavy yet. Adopt a life damage. You can choose from three difficulty levels, even beginners safe shooting. 4 aircraft to select from different types of ship, overtake the 6 stages fight.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Stahlfeder-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Santos</developer>
		<publisher>Santos</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Ocean 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Star Ocean: The Second Story</name>
		<desc>The game gives the player the choice of playing as Rena or Claude, with the journey evolving and ending differently depending on the choices one makes.

Star Ocean: The Second Story is a world of magic, science, space travel and deadly demons! Enter a world where love knows no bounds, the evil is neverending and good can overcome all if the heart is just and true. Featuring three battle modes, the ability to master skills to create items and an emotional level for each of the characters, Enix has pulled out all the stops in their latest (and first) title to be brought to the North American PlayStation.

Star Ocean: The Second Story takes place twenty years after the original game, Star Ocean. Roughly the first half of the plot of the game takes place on the planet Expel, an underdeveloped planet on the verge of its industrial age. On Expel kings still rule over great kingdoms, swords and sorcery dominate the battlefield, and sailing ships are still made from wood. According to a Federation law, named the Undeveloped Planet Protection Treaty, a planet with such a level of civilization may not be directly contacted under any but the most dire circumstances—and even then, contact must be minimal and secretive. This law is reminiscent of Star Trek's Prime Directive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Star Ocean 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-ace</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Jedi Power Battles.pbp</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Jedi Power Battles</name>
		<desc>Take back the Theed palace in fast and furious lightsaber assaults. You will have the power of the Force and your trusty Jedi saber as you ward off legions of battle droids, destroyer droids, assassins and other creatures from the Star Wars: Episode I worlds. Battle side-by-side with a companion in two-player sessions. Fight as Obi-Wan Kenobi, Gui-Gon Jinn or Jedi Council members Mace Windu, Plo Koon or Adi Gallia. Gain power boosts, new moves and enhanced abilities as you progress through the levels. Threats escalate on each level of the game-specialized droids with new weapons, native beasts and more.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Star Wars Episode I - Jedi Power Battles-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - The Phantom Menace.pbp</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Episode I - The Phantom Menace</name>
		<desc>TURMOIL HAS ENGULFED THE GALACTIC REPUBLIC.

The taxation of trade routes to outlying systems is in dispute. The greedy Trade Federation has stopped all shipping to the small planet of Naboo with a blockade of deadly battleships.

LIVE THE SAGA.

Take part in the events from the Star Wars: Episode Istory and beyond - while takin gon the roles of Obi-Wan Kenobi, Qui-Gon Jinn, Queen Amidala and Captain Panaka.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Star Wars Episode I - The Phantom Menace-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Ape</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starblade Alpha.pbp</path>
		<name>StarBlade Alpha</name>
		<desc>Strap yourself in for a rollercoaster shoot'em up set up in a distant galaxy. Let dizzying 3D graphics immerse you in pitched battles over artificial planets and city-sized space cruisers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Starblade Alpha-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter EX2 Plus.pbp</path>
		<name>Street Fighter EX 2 Plus</name>
		<desc>Conquering the World of 3-D Fighters!

Capcom’s all-time, leading fighting flagship series once again goes 3-D with Street Fighter EX 2 Plus, the sequel to the top-selling Street Fighter EX Plus for the PlayStation game console. Loaded with new enhancements, modes of play and an expanded cast of characters, Street Fighter EX 2 Plus delivers amazing 3-D graphics, lightning fast animation and Capcom’s signature gameplay. Play one-on-one with a buddy or create your own unique Street Fighter team using up to five fighters. Once you’ve perfected your moves, edit your replay data to create and star in your own movie.

• The improved sequel to the best-selling, Street Fighter EX Plus
• 3-D fighting action with amazing 3-D graphics, lightning fast animation and Capcom signature game mechanics
• Loaded with new play features like the Excel Move, Meteor Combo Super Attack, Guard Break and the Super Cancel
• 23 selectable characters from the Street Fighter universe
• 7 Modes of gameplay – Arcade Mode, Versus Mode, Practice Mode, Training Mode, Trial Mode, Director Mode and Bonus Mode
• Featured in the Capcom Edge frequent buyers program</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Street Fighter EX2 Plus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991230T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arika</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter EX Plus Alpha.pbp</path>
		<name>Street Fighter EX Plus Alpha</name>
		<desc>THE 3-D FIGHTER WORTH FIGHTING FOR.

Ryu got your number? New Training Mode adds moves, reduces bruises.
New Multi-Hit combos bring'em to their knees.
Slow Mo Replay makes victory even sweeter.

-8 original Street fighter vets-Guile, Zangief, Ryu, Ken, Bison, Chun-Li, Dhalsim and Sakura-in an amazing arcade hit.
-12 all-new fighters in the biggest Street Fighter ever!
-7 different play modes, playable bosses; a total of 23 characters!
-The Street Fighter legacy continues...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Street Fighter EX Plus Alpha-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arika</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Strider 2</name>
		<desc>Strider 2 is a fast-paced, arcade-style action game. Unlike its predecessor, it features 2D animations placed on 3D backgrounds. There is a range of new moves including a double jump, backward somersault and dash, which allows him to perform longer jumps. He also has the ability to boost his weapon, the Cypher sword, enabling it to release homing plasma waves. There is also a Savage Slash attack, with random slashes.

There are numerous bonuses that can be collected in the levels. These either boost Strider's vitality, increase the power of his sword or increase the player's game score. Another addition to the game is a Boss Gauge which lets the player know how much energy the mid- or end of level boss has left before it dies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Strider 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20000729T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter.pbp</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter</name>
		<desc>Directive: Eliminate the Syphon Filter Virus
"Intelligence has confirmed the development of bio-warfare weapons. Gabe, you are our only chance to destroy the Syphon Filter virus. You've been cleared to use lethal force to complete your directives."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Syphon Filter-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidetic</developer>
		<publisher>989</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon Filter 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter 2</name>
		<desc>Gabe and Lian are now renegade agents on the run from U.S. intelligence after discovering that the Agency was behind the manufacture of the lethal Syphon Filter virus. The Agency wants to secretly sell the virus to the highest bidder, one which will then hold the world hostage. Lian Xing is already infected with the virus and Gabe Logan barely escapes alive from a plane crash. But there's no time to waste. They must prevent the virus from getting into enemy hands as well as find the vaccine, expose the double agents, defeat the terrorists . . . . . . the hard part is just staying alive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Syphon Filter 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidetic</developer>
		<publisher>989</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syphon FIlter 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter 3</name>
		<desc>You eliminated the Syphon Filter virus and prevented the massacre of millions of lives. You escaped from the Agency and exposed them for what they really are. Now the time has come to finish the job once and for all, using whatever means necessary. But remember - you must face your past before you can look to the future! Enter the Syphon Filter drama once more. Play as Gabe Logan, Lian Xing and Theresa Lipan, and discover the truth about their pasts. Journey through Tokyo, Panama, Afghanistan and Costa Rica as you evade, retrieve, demolish and assassinate your way through a host of nail-biting missions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Syphon FIlter 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SIE Bend Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tai Fu - Wrath of the Tiger.pbp</path>
		<name>T'ai Fu: Wrath of the Tiger</name>
		<desc>T’ai Fu - Wrath of the Tiger is a PlayStation game released in 1999. The game is set in an oriental landscape populated by clans of animals, such as Leopards and Snakes. The game's protagonist, T'ai Fu, is the last remaining survivor of the Tiger clan and must journey to defeat the Dragon Master and avenge his kind. On the way, he learns about his clouded past and masters several Kung Fu styles, one from each clan master he defeats.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tai Fu - Wrath of the Tiger-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamWorks</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 3.pbp</path>
		<name>Tekken 3</name>
		<desc>The Fight of Your Life

An ancient evil force has reawakened, attacking in secret and feeding on the souls of mighty warriors. To lure it out of hiding will take the greatest fighting contest the world has ever seen... Tekken 3. Some are fighting for revenge, some for honor. Ultimately, all are fighting for their lives and the fate of all mankind.

Hidden Features
Secret characters, secret game modes, and dramatic cinematic sequences for each character.

New Fighting Styles
Including the Brazilian art of the Capoeira fighting and two new styles of Kung Fu.

New Characters
Includes your favorite arcade characters: Eddy, Jin, Xiaoyu, Hwoarang, Julia, Law, Mokujin, Bryan, Ogre, and more, along with new characters created just for the PlayStation version.

Faster Gameplay
Instant bounce-back from falls, more escapes from tackles and stuns, plus all-new throws make gameplay faster then ever before.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tekken 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu 2 - Birth of the Stealth Assassins.pbp</path>
		<name>Tenchu 2: Birth of the Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>Live by Honor. Kill by Stealth.

Before the events of Tenchu, the House of Gohda is rocked by betrayal. As shadow warriors Rikimaru. Ayame and Tatsumaru, you are called on to restore pride to the name of your master. For you have been born to a life of honor...a life of stealth.

Discover even more ways to slay your foes with 21 new stealth kill techniques.
Take on the role of three ninja assassins, each with their own story and fighting techniques.
Create an infinite number of missions with the Mission Editor mode and share your stealth adventures by trading via memory card or over the internet.
Strike from the shadows in 29 new day and night stealth missions.
Utilize a variety of new ninja weapons and items, like flaming arrows and invisibility.
Conceal and search bodies, swim, and hide underwater using a bamboo reed to breather.

Create your own stealth ninja missions with the Mission Editor mode!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tenchu 2 - Birth of the Stealth Assassins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tenchu - Stealth Assassins.pbp</path>
		<name>Tenchu: Stealth Assassins</name>
		<desc>STEALTH ASSASSINS

Prowl and strike with lethal precision as ninja assassins Rikimaru or Ayame in the shadowy world of feudal Japan. Armed with mystical weapons and sheer cunning, you must shed blood with discretion and move without detection. For only the unseen survive.

Stealth Fighting Tactics
Authentic Ninja Weapons
Go-Anywhere 3-D Environment</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tenchu - Stealth Assassins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acquire</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terra Diver.pbp</path>
		<name>Terra Diver</name>
		<desc>Sōkyū Gurentai (蒼穹紅蓮隊 lit. "Blue Sky Crimson Lotus Squad"?) is a vertically scrolling shooter game released by Raizing in 1996. The game is unusual in that, rather than using a 3:4 aspect ratio to better suit the vertically-oriented gameplay, it uses a horizontal monitor (4:3) in the style of Neo Geo vertical shooters as well as the later Radiant Silvergun and Giga Wing. There is an English version of the game titled Terra Diver, but it was never officially released.

Hitoshi Sakimoto confirmed that a re-release of the soundtrack should be released by the end of 2010 under the Basiscape label</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Terra Diver-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terracon.pbp</path>
		<name>Terracon</name>
		<desc>THE EVIL TERRACON is mercilessly wiping out the Galaxy, planet by planet. As Xed, the toughest little alien ever hatched, you have to face the Terracon Terror in the greatest adventure in the galaxy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Terracon-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Italian Job.pbp</path>
		<name>The Italian Job</name>
		<desc>London, 1969. Charlie Croker has just finished a three year stretch, courtesy of Her Majesty's Prisons, and has an idea: to steal $4,000,000 in gold bullion, right from under the noses of the Mafia and the Turin Police. This is where you come in... as one of his drivers, you'll have to master 14 vehicles, including flashy sports cars and the legendary Mini Cooper, as you screech down sewers, roar over rooftops and tear through the Alps, with the Mob and the law hot on your heels.

It'll be the crime of your life!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/The Italian Job-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pixelogic</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Mummy.pbp</path>
		<name>The Mummy</name>
		<desc>Taking the role of the film's hero, Rick O' Connell, you are transported back to the world of the pharaohs where you must solve devious puzzles and survive shocking encounters with the living dead. The action is non-stop and fraught with danger. Trapdoors, secret corridors, mysterious hieroglyphs and even the great plague of Egypt must all be encountered before facing evil incarnate the dreadful priest...Imhotep!!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/The Mummy-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rebellion</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thrill Kill.pbp</path>
		<name>Thrill Kill</name>
		<desc>Hell Hath No Fury Like... THRILL KILL

Eight fighters, eight souls. Each has died and descended into Hell, except it's not the classical Dante's Hell. It's a modern day Hell based on the real world of today's deviants. The characters are the physical manifestations of their mental illnesses or vices on earth. Marukka, the God of Secrets, is bored and decided that it would be fun to pit them all against each other with the prize being rebirth. Each character is battling for nothing more than self-preservation and the hope to be born again.

-Fast and furious 4-player deathmatches!
-Battle to the death in chambers of horror like he Insane Asylum, the Slaughterhouse and the Morgue!
-Face 11 malformed freaks including a Psycho Redneck Cannibal, a Maladjusted midget on stilts, and a Queen Demon straight from the depths of hell!
-Gang-up and cooperative moves never before seen in a 3D fighter: Hold your opponent while others beat the pulp out of him!
-Advanced AI that will force you to constantly come up with new solo and team moves!
-One of a kind Kill Meter that promotes offensive game play!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Thrill Kill-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradox Development</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thunder Force V - Perfect System.pbp</path>
		<name>Thunder Force V: Perfect System</name>
		<desc>In a grim future where a once-benevolent alien technology has turned against humanity, only a ragtag group of ace pilots can save the Earth from total annihilation. Code name: Thunder Force! Witness the first 32-bit installment of the massively popular shooter series! Five spectacular weapons with multiple power-up levels let you blast through waves of metallic predators, and look good doing it. A constant barrage of innovative enemies keeps you intrigued while you struggle to stay alive. A speaker-imploding soundtrack has your foot tapping as your fingers are mashing. Unbelievable rendered cutscenes draw, no-DRAG you kicking and screaming into the action. Put simply, it's the ultimate hardcore gaming blast-o-rama!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Thunder Force V - Perfect System-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19980831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Techno Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Crisis.pbp</path>
		<name>Time Crisis</name>
		<desc>Time Crisis is a rail shooter, originally released for the arcades, similar to Virtua Cop in gameplay style. The player moves automatically, using the light gun to eliminate appearing enemies, after which he can proceed to the next screen. The stages typically culminate in boss battles. The player can also press a button to make Richard dive for cover. However, using this feature too much might result in expiration of the time limit imposed on each screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Time Crisis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Crisis - Project Titan.pbp</path>
		<name>Time Crisis: Project Titan</name>
		<desc>Project Titan features the same gameplay as the other Time Crisis games. It also retains the signature foot pedal. Players by default are in hiding position. They are shielded from taking fire, but they cannot fire back. In order to begin play, players must step on the pedal and begin firing. Stepping off the pad also allows the player to reload the gun.

This game introduces the a new gameplay mechanic that allows the player to move to multiple fixed locations, which are activated by shooting yellow arrows while the player is hiding. This feature was later reused in the arcade version of Time Crisis 4.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Time Crisis - Project Titan-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Tank.pbp</path>
		<name>Tiny Tank</name>
		<desc>In a future world, an army of steel robots are out to destroy the human race. Our only hope is a little yellow tank armed with some mighty big guns. The sentient Tiny Tank was originally created to appease a public that feared the mindless violence waged by larger war-robots, but he was soon destroyed by one of those jealous automatons at the beginning of the robot revolution 100 years ago. Almost destroyed, at least.

Thanks to nano-technology, hundreds of microscopic "Fix-It Crabs" went to work and Tiny Tank was slowly rebuilt. Now he alone stands against the threat of the cruel MuTank and his deadly robot minions, who have all but erased human civilization from the planet's surface. The spunky little tank will need luck, strategy, and all the futuristic firepower he can get his treads on to save the human race.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tiny Tank-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tobal 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Tobal 2</name>
		<desc>The fighting system in Tobal 2 is the same as in the previous game. The player can freely navigate 3D fighting arenas under the condition that he or she faces the opponent. High, medium, and low attacks can be executed using assigned buttons. As in Tobal No. 1, the grappling and blocking system offers the player a variety of offensive and defensive maneuvers. A new unblockable fireball attack has been added for each character. Tobal 2 was released on the same day as Sony's Dual Analog Controller in Japan, noted as the first game compatible with the peripheral. Graphically, the game features Gouraud shaded and higher-resolution character models compared to Tobal No. 1, but still runs at 60 frames per second.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tobal 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19970425T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dream Factory</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tobal No. 1.pbp</path>
		<name>Tobal No. 1</name>
		<desc>Fighting game with a unique quest mode, from Square. The publisher enlisted the help of Seiichi Ishii, who had previously worked on both Tekken and Virtua Fighter. On these strengths, Square helped Ishii start his own development company, Dream Factory, and Tobal No.1 is the first game from the developer. The game offers some 3D movement for more behind-the-back attacks that fighting games released around the same time. Tobal also introduced an interesting grapple move, which allows you to grab your opponent and, depending on your button execution, throw them in a myriad of ways. The game features Gouraud-shaded players displayed in hi-res mode (640x480) and shipped with an included Final Fantasy VII demo.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tobal No. 1-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamFactory</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider.pbp</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider</name>
		<desc>In Tomb Raider, the player controls the female archaeologist Lara Croft, in search for the three mysterious Scion artefacts across the world. The game is presented in third person perspective. Lara is always visible and the camera follows the action from behind or over her shoulder. The world she inhabits is fully drawn in three dimensions and characterized by its cubic nature. Ledges, walls and ceilings mostly sit at 90 degrees to each other, but sometimes feature sloping planes.
The object of Tomb Raider is to guide Lara through a series of tombs and other locations in search of treasures and artefacts. On the way, she must kill dangerous animals and other creatures, while collecting objects and solving puzzles to gain access to an ultimate prize, usually a powerful artefact. Gunplay is restricted to the killing of various animals that appear throughout each stage, although occasionally Lara may be faced with a human opponent. Instead the emphasis lies on solving puzzles and performing trick jumps to complete each level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tomb Raider-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19961114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider 4 - The Last Revelation.pbp</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: The Last Revelation</name>
		<desc>The intrepid archaeologist Lara Croft ventures to India, searching for a legendary stone that once belonged to the tribe of Infada. Shortly after recovering the precious stone, she encounters a Dr. Willard, the head of an organization known as RX Tech. Willard is interested in an ancient Polynesian city build by people of a now defunct civilization, which worshipped a mysterious meteorite that hit the Earth millions of years ago. Willard tells Lara that the Infada Stone is in fact one of the four artifacts the ancient Polynesians fashioned from the material contained in the meteorite's core. Willard suggests Lara should look for the other three, scattered and hidden in various regions of the planet. It looks like another dangerous adventure awaits the fearless "tomb raider"!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tomb Raider 4 - The Last Revelation-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomba.pbp</path>
		<name>Tomba!</name>
		<desc>Evil pigs. Man-eating plants. Hidden paths. Wacky weapons. Moving obstacles.
Can you believe what Tomba has to go through to conquer the menacing wine?!
A wild actoin game with sone RPG and adventure mixed in, too.
130 events to clear deliver non-stop action.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tomba-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Whoopee Camp</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomba 2.pbp</path>
		<name>Tomba! 2: The Evil Swine Return</name>
		<desc>TOMBA'S BACK ON THE WILDEST 3D ADVENTURE EVER.

Explore an all new 3D world. Use your trusty fire hammer, ice boomerang or blackjack to turn the evil pigs into bacon. Throw on super-duds like a flying squirrel suit or high speed turbo pants. There's no limit to the stuff you can do.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Tomba 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Whoopee Camp</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trap Gunner.pbp</path>
		<name>Trap Gunner: Countdown to Oblivion</name>
		<desc>The purpose of the game to run around various levels and to set traps, which are invisible to your opponent. Players can shoot at one another while setting traps. Each character has a different melee weapon with unique attributes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Trap Gunner-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Racdym</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vagrant Story.pbp</path>
		<name>Vagrant Story</name>
		<desc>Vagrant Story is a role-playing game with several distinguishing characteristics. The entire game (including the numerous cutscenes that advance the plot) is rendered in 3D. The game focuses on exploration of large, complex dungeon-like areas and combat; there are no "friendly" areas, NPC interaction, or monetary system. Dungeons contain many optional rooms and environmental puzzles that mostly involve pushing, destroying, and re-arranging different types of crates to access higher areas. Ashley can also jump and grab ledges of higher platforms during exploration.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Vagrant Story-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valkyrie Profile.pbp</path>
		<name>Valkyrie Profile</name>
		<desc>Wade into a battle between the Viking Gods in VALKYRIE PROFILE. In this action-stuffed PlayStation game based on fabled Norse mythology, you play as the powerful demigoddess Valkyrie Lenneth. As a female warrior in the service of the gods it's your duty to collect the souls of the fallen from a mystical Northern European battleground and ferry them safely to the heavens of Valhalla. The great Odin needs these souls to fight for him in his war against Ragnarok, and he greatly appreciates your efforts. After taking souls into her possession, they can then fight alongside Lenneth in their quest for redemption. More than 20 characters are available for your party and it's your duty to improve their stats, complete quests, and gain valuable artifacts before you send them to join Odin's army. How well you achieve this important goal determines how the game plays out. VALKYRIE PROFILE's lush graphics, engaging storyline, entertaining battle system, and Viking-styled mayhem will keep adventure fans enthralled.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Valkyrie Profile-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wanted!.pbp</path>
		<name>Wanted!</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Wanted!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warhawk.pbp</path>
		<name>Warhawk</name>
		<desc>Warhawk is an action/simulation game built around a futuristic VTOL craft. The player maneuvers with 360 degrees of flight control through 6 unique levels.

Take to the skies over desert and volcanic planets, through ancient castles and towers, and against massive airships in WarHawk. As a member of the Strikeforce Omicron, your goal is to wipe out the aggressive forces of Kreel. You will have complete 360 degree movement over large 3D worlds as you evade or attack in any direction: reverse, bank left or right, dive, barrel-roll, perform loops or even use the Immelmann turn to blast enemies out of the sky.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Warhawk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19951110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SingleTrac</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warriors of Might and Magic.pbp</path>
		<name>Warriors of Might and Magic</name>
		<desc>Warriors of Might and Magic is an action game with RPG elements set in the Might and Magic universe. The gameplay style is similar to that of Crusaders of Might and Magic. The player navigates Alleron through predominantly dungeon-like environments, fighting enemies in action-based combat, executing various melee moves (including blocking), and casting spells.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Warriors of Might and Magic-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3DO</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild 9.pbp</path>
		<name>Wild 9</name>
		<desc>Wex Major is a teenager from Earth whose parents were kidnapped by aliens. Traveling through space, Wex comes into contact with a powerful weapon system known as The Rig. Apparently the young boy is the only one who can harness the power of The Rig, and he is proclaimed The Great Champion, a legendary leader who can rid the oppressed people of the Andromeda Galaxy from the tyranny of the evil gigantic monster named Karn. Wex recruits other teenage mutants and becomes the leader of Wild 9, an organization that aims to overthrow Karn and liberate the galaxy.

Wild 9 is a 2D platformer with 3D graphics, featuring gameplay similar in vein to the company's Earthworm Jim games. Unique to the game is the The Rig, a weapon the protagonist wields. The Rig functions like an electronic lasso, capable of moving objects as well as carry around and smash enemies, which is often needed to solve puzzles and progress through the game's ten levels. A few stages focus on avoiding obstacles and taking on boss enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Wild 9-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wip3Out.pbp</path>
		<name>Wipeout 3</name>
		<desc>Wipeout 3 is a racing game that retains the same basic elements of its predecessors, and introduces players to the F7200 Anti-Gravity Race League. Players control futuristic anti-gravity ships owned by racing corporations and pilot them on eight circuits. Each craft is equipped with an energy shield that absorbs damage sustained on the track; if the shield is disabled, the player's craft can be knocked out of the race. Shields are regenerated in a pit lane that is set apart from the main course. The less time spent in the pit lane, the less the shield will regenerate.

In addition to shields, each racing craft contains air brakes for navigating tight corners, as well as a "hyper-boost" option. Players can activate the hyper-boost to increase their speed, but the boost drains energy from the shields, making the craft more vulnerable. Using special speed pads on the course allows players to increase their speed without resorting to the boost.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Wip3Out-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psygnosis</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xena - Warrior Princess.pbp</path>
		<name>Xena: Warrior Princess</name>
		<desc>Xena must make her way through many large levels, hacking, kicking, slashing, and cutting everything that gets in her way. Items can be found and upgraded as she proceeds through the levels. Apart from a variety of moves, the game also features little gimmicks such as a "Karma Meter", which gives Xena benefits if she saves hostages or defeats enemies without killing them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Xena - Warrior Princess-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Universal Digital Arts, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xenogears.pbp</path>
		<name>Xenogears</name>
		<desc>Stand tall, and shake the heavens.

A mysterious organization is turning the tides of a century-long war with ancient technology - giant combat robots. A failed attempt to steal one of these powerful mechanized weapons places it in the unwilling hands of Fei and his dubious allies. Now he is pursued by military governments, royal pirates, spies, the Emperor, and his own forgotten past.

* Over 20 minutes of stunning hand-drawn animé tells this complex, futuristic tale.
* Battle in giant robots or hand-to-hand using intuitive combat systems without menus
* Explore detailed, fully-rotatable polygonal environments</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Xenogears-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xevious 3D.pbp</path>
		<name>Xevious 3D/G+</name>
		<desc>Xevious 3D/G+ puts the classic arcade vertical shoot 'm up Xevious game in a third-person 3D perspective. The game brings some new weapon systems to the player-controlled fighter jet and contains many new enemies, some of which are quite large and pose new challenges to the player. During the game the player can collect three types of power-ups: bullets, lasers and plasma beams.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Xevious 3D-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Missadventures of Tron Bonne.pbp</path>
		<name>The Misadventures of Tron Bonne</name>
		<desc>The other side of Mega Man Legends!

Now Mega Man's female rival, Tron from Mega Man Legends is back with her trusty Servbots in an entirely new adventure! Join Tron and the Servbots as they circle the world in their air ship, Gesellshaft, in search of adventure and priceless treasure. Brave Tron's wild exploits in q unique mix of action-adventure, RPG, and puzzles in this irresistible game for all ages.

Unique gameplay and storyline, mixing the best action-adventure, RPG, and puzzles in a vast 3-D world.
Vibrant colorful graphics! -explore huge 3-D environments for puzzles, treasures and other surprises
"Guide Shot System" sends Servbots to retrieve treasure and perform Tron's bidding
Includes Demo of Mega Man Legends 2</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Missadventures of Tron Bonne-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Macross - Do You Remember Love.pbp</path>
		<name>Macross: Do you remember love</name>
		<desc>A.D. 2009: The human race is in the middle of a three-way war with a race of giant humanoid aliens split into the Zentrans and Meltlans. After executing a space fold that sent it and part of South Ataria Island to the edge of the Solar System, the space fortress Macross is on its way back to Earth. During a small skirmish with Zentradi forces, young pilot Hikaru Ichijyo rescues idol singer Lynn Minmay and their relationship develops as they're stranded somewhere within the ship. But shortly after returning to Macross City, Minmay is captured by the Zentradi, and Hikaru and female officer Misa Hayase end up back on Earth—only to view the aftermath of the destruction of their civilization. Only a song discovered eons ago—along with Minmay's voice—can determine the outcome of the war.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Macross - Do You Remember Love-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990527T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Scarab</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
