<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajo Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku.pbp</path>
		<name>Akumajou Dracula X: Gekka no Yasoukyoku</name>
		<desc>Known in Japan as Akumajou Dracula X: Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Demon Castle Dracula X: Nocturne in the Moonlight), this game takes place after the first Dracula X game (specifically, “Dracula X: Rondo of Blood”). You play as Alucard, a returning hero from the third installment of the series on the NES. Alucard is Dracula’s son, who had gone into a deep sleep for many years until he was awakened by the return of Dracula’s castle.

As Alucard, you have a large number of equipment to choose from (daggers, one-handed swords, two-handed swords, fist-type weapons, rods, as well as armor, shields, capes, helmets, accessories, and usable items). Many people will play through this game many times and still not see all of the items within. That’s how many items there are!

Alucard has many techniques at his disposal. First, he has a large set of spells (about 10 or so) that he can perform by using his MP (one of the three main statistics, in addition to HP and Hearts). He can transform into a Wolf, Bat, and Mist (each of which has a few abilities of their own). He also gets familiars of varying types (demons, faeries, and even a sentient sword) to help fight his enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Akumajo Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19970320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T010744</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare.pbp</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark: The New Nightmare</name>
		<desc>Set on October 31, 2001. Edward Carnby's best friend and partner, Charles Fiske, has been found dead off the coast of Shadow Island, a mysterious island near the coast of Massachusetts. Carnby's investigation quickly leads him to Frederick Johnson, who informs him of Fiske's search for three ancient tablets with the ability to unlock an incredible and dangerous power. Johnson pleads with Carnby to take the place of Fiske and reopen the investigation in order to recover the tablets. Carnby accepts and makes it his mission to find Fiske's killer. Johnson introduces Edward to Aline Cedrac, an intelligent, young university professor. She joins Edward to recover the missing tablets and assist Professor Obed Morton, who she believes to be her father. While flying over the coast of Shadow Island, Edward and Aline's plane comes under attack by an unknown creature. Edward and Aline both jump out of the plane and parachute to the ground, but are separated immediately. Edward lands in the dense forest just outside a manor, while Aline lands on the roof of said manor.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Darkworks</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assault Retribution.pbp</path>
		<name>Assault: Retribution</name>
		<desc>Assault: Retribution supplies you with some of the best firepower modern technology can provide, as well as various customization options to ensure "better living through quick death disbursement." Washington utilizes a barrage of destructive weaponry such as the P-420 Multi-Phase Pulse Rifle and the aptly named Cutter; Doyle uses a variety of Homing Missiles, Beam Lasers, and the D-16 Magnetic Bolt Accelerator. There's also a plethora of pickups including weapon upgrades, health, ammunition recharges, smart bombs, extra lives, and shields. Save points within each level let you resume the killing when it is most convenient for you. And (rare as of 1999), there is a two-player cooperative mode in case you feel that one ultimate killing machine just isn't enough.

Assault: Retribution is a 3D platform shooting game that takes place across seven futuristic levels, includes two playable characters with alternate routes, analog control, and memory card support. You can't spell action, adrenaline or assault with out an "A," so go out and kick a few!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Assault Retribution-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Candle Light Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T233602</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brave Fencer Musashi.pbp</path>
		<name>Brave Fencer Musashi</name>
		<desc>150 years ago, the legendary warrior known as the Brave Fencer Musashi saved the kingdom of Allucaneet from the evil Wizard of Darkness. Now, his spirit is reincarnated in a young, rather short-tempered boy. Fillet, the princess of Allucaneet, summons the reluctant hero to the palace and gives him the powerful sword Fusion, which he needs to defeat the evil Thirstquencher Empire. It soon turns out that the Empire is after another legendary sword, Lumina, so Musashi's first task is to get it before the bad guys do!..

Brave Fencer Musashi is an action game with strong RPG elements. Controlling Musashi, the player explores the pre-rendered backgrounds from third person view (similarly to Final Fantasy VII), visiting towns, talking to NPCs, etc. There is a day/night cycle in the game, which is manifested in the schedules of NPCs and/or monsters, as well as Musashi's fatigue level, which increases if he doesn't sleep enough. Musashi uses the two swords, Fusion and Lumina, to fight his enemies. The two swords have different properties: while Fusion behaves more or less like a traditional melee weapon, Lumina needs to be imbued with various elemental items in order to unleash powerful attacks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Brave Fencer Musashi-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Cross.pbp</path>
		<name>Chrono Cross</name>
		<desc>Chrono Cross features standard RPG gameplay with some differences. Players advance the game by controlling the protagonist Serge through the game's world, primarily by foot and boat. Navigation between areas is conducted via an overworld map, much like Chrono Trigger's, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Around the island world are villages, outdoor areas, and dungeons, through which the player moves in three dimensions. Locations such as cities and forests are represented by more realistically scaled field maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Like Chrono Trigger, the game features no random encounters; enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Chrono Cross-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Einhander.pbp</path>
		<name>Einhander</name>
		<desc>In 2192, a new city, Selene, is built on the moon. Over the years, Selene grows larger, more powerful, and more independent of the Earth - to the point that the moon and Earth battle in a war that winds down without a definite victory for either side. In 2242, war breaks out again - the Earth slowly begins to win... except for the efforts of an experimental Selene technology known as Einhänders: flying machines with a "hand" that allows them to change weaponry mid-battle.

On December 12, 2245, Selene sends down 3 Einhänders in a last attempt to turn the tide of the war. You get to choose the craft to pilot, and it's up to you to battle your way through the Earth's monstrous defenses and win the battle.

The game is a traditional side-scrolling shooter, with rendered 3D backgrounds and enemies. The atmosphere of the game is very "industrial", down to the German industrial music playing in the background (think Einsturzende Neubauten mixed with Lords of Acid). The weapon-switching and claiming is an integral part of the game, as weapons have limited shots. This forces a bit more strategy than the usual button-mashing shooters inspire.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Einhander-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IX.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IX</name>
		<desc>A band of thieves are hired to kidnap Princess Garnet of Alexandria. After they succeed, they end up becoming her guardians. And while protecting the fair Princess from a powerful evil...they hold the fate of the world in their hands. Play along on the epic journey filled with danger, mystery, war and love.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy IX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VIII.pbp</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VIII</name>
		<desc>A member of an elite military team, Squall is forced into a conflict beyond imagination.  To survive, he must contend with a desperate rival, a powerful sorceress, and his own mysterious dreams.

* Realistic, detailed characters and background graphics enhanced by a breathtaking musical score
* An epic story based on the theme of love, set in a massive new world
* New Junction System allows characters to be customized with powerful magic spells drawn from enemies
* Nearly an hour of stunning motion-captured CG cinemas seamlessly integrated into gameplay</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Final Fantasy VIII-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunners Heaven.pbp</path>
		<name>Gunner's Heaven</name>
		<desc>Load up: High-velocity, Self-Targeting, Incinerator or Riot Control - it's the last word in close-combat shoot'em ups.
Also known as Rapid Reload.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Gunners Heaven-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Media.Vision Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan X4.pbp</path>
		<name>Mega Man X4</name>
		<desc>X-PLOSIVE GAMEPLAY.
X-TREME GRAPHICS.
MEGA MAN X4!

Vibrant Animation • Relentless Enemies
Unsurpassed Graphics • Hidden Secrets
Mega Man X4 bombards the PlayStation game console and never lets up!

Battle armies of Maverick Reploid Robots while mastering all-new strategic moves like the Air Hover and Zero's Saber Tactic system. Discover a myriad of power-ups, secret rooms, extra weapons and invincible vehicles to take on 8 all new X-Hunter Bosses. And for the first time, play as Mega Man X or battle with his mighty partner Zero in 2 separate adventures. Mega Man X4 - now you can be a hero, or a Zero!

* Now, play as Mega Man X or Zero!
* New X-Hunter levels with vivid color, brilliant detail, intricate passages, secret rooms and hard-to-reach items
* Invincible vehicles like the Land Chaser superbike and other robot ride armors</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/MegaMan X4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19970810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170205T192648</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve.pbp</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve</name>
		<desc>THE CINEMATIC RPG

One of them is a police officer. The other is possessed by an ancient evil threatening all life on Earth. The horrifying bond between them will continue until something dies.
A chilling adventure that could only come from the creators of Final Fantasy VII
An epic sci-fi tale told through stunning 3D rendered sequences
Battle mutant monsters in real-time polygon combat
Customize weapons, armor, and character abilities</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Parasite Eve-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill.pbp</path>
		<name>Silent Hill</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill is a 1999 survival horror video game for the PlayStation. The first in a series about a mysterious town of the same name, Silent Hill generated a direct sequel, three indirect sequels, a prequel and a film adaptation. The game was included in Sony's Greatest Hits and Platinum Range of budget titles as a result of strong sales. A reinterpretation of the game was developed for the Wii, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable.
The plot focuses on Harry Mason as he searches for his daughter, Cheryl, who has disappeared following a car accident which left Harry unconscious. He finds Silent Hill to be largely abandoned, shrouded in a thick fog, snowing out of season, filled with monsters and being over taken by a hellish otherworld. As Harry scours the town, he begins learning about the history of Silent Hill and stumbles upon a cult ritual undertaken to bring a god to Earth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Silent Hill-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Silent, Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami Digital Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Blade.pbp</path>
		<name>Soul Blade</name>
		<desc>In the 16th century, a sword surfaces that is so powerful, so evil that warriors from all over the globe seek it out. It is Soul Edge, a demon blade. From America to Europe to Japan, these warriors fight each other for the chance to obtain it. Soul Blade is a 3D weapons fighting game that chronicles their story.

A complete 3D fighting game that allows for side steps, Soul Blade has twelve colorful fighters (ten standard, two hidden, plus additional costumes for a few fighters), each with various weapons and styles. The first ten can be used in all the combat modes, while the hidden two can only be used in versus and arcade mode.

Namco enhanced the arcade version (called Soul Edge) by adding a well done CGI intro, plus a story mode to the addition of the traditional team, survival, and time attack modes. The story mode goes into greater detail about each character, and is presented in an ancient book format. The story mode also allows you to unlock more of each characters' extra weapons. These weapons, which vary in lengths, stats, and durability, add to the options available players in the versus mode.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Soul Blade-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro the Dragon 2 - Ripto's Rage.pbp</path>
		<name>Spyro 2: Ripto's Rage!</name>
		<desc>Ripto's Rage is the second game in the Spyro the Dragon series, which started with Spyro the Dragon in 1998. The protagonist of the series, Spyro, is placed in the land of Avalar, rather than the Dragon Worlds, where the previous installment was set. A dinosaur-riding sorcerer, known as Ripto, has invaded the world of Avalar, and is wreaking havoc on its citizens with his magic. The player, as Spyro, must travel through the world of Avalar and undo the damage done by Ripto.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Spyro the Dragon 2 - Ripto's Rage-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Threads of Fate.pbp</path>
		<name>Threads of Fate</name>
		<desc>Two Amazing Adventures!

Rue is on a quest to revive a lost friend. Mint is seeking power and revenge. Both of them are looking for a powerful relic, but which will be brave and clever enough to reach their goal?
Explore a beautifully rendered 3D world filled with challenging puzzles, unusual enemies, and unknown dangers
Play as both characters to encounter two entirely different storylines
Rue has the ability to shape-shift into the forms of defeated enemies
Mint can learn and use a wide variety of powerful magic spells</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psx/Threads of Fate-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
