<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./spnchout.zip</path>
		<name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Isn't it time you got in on the action?

Once again, Nintendo has created a smash hit —Punch-Out— a fast action dual-monitor video boxing game. Its been knocking out the competition week-after-week in earnings and player appeal across the nation.

With Punch-Out in your corner, you gain the added muscle of the
Champ!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/spnchout-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T014907</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1942.zip</path>
		<name>1942</name>
		<desc>1942 is set in the Pacific theater of World War II. The goal is to reach Tokyo and destroy the entire Japanese air fleet. The player pilots a plane dubbed the "Super Ace" (but its appearance is clearly that of a Lockheed P-38 Lightning). The player has to shoot down enemy planes; to avoid enemy fire, the player can perform a roll or "loop-the-loop".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/1942-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1943.zip</path>
		<name>1943: The Battle of Midway</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the Pacific theater of World War II, off the coast of the Midway Atoll. The goal is to attack the Japanese Air Fleet that bombed the players' American Aircraft Carrier, pursue all Japanese Air and Sea forces, fly through the 16 levels of play, make their way to the Japanese battleship Yamato and destroy her. 11 Levels consist of an Air-to-Sea battle (with a huge battleship or an aircraft carrier as an End-Level Boss), while 5 levels consist of an all-aerial battle against a squadron of Japanese Bombers and a Mother Bomber that needs to be destroyed.
As in 1942, players pilot a P-38. Two buttons are used: one for regular attacks (with several weapons) and one for special actions that executes either a loop like in 1942 or one of three special attacks that damage the plane. Unlike 1942, the player only has one life, with one refillable energy meter. Destroying a complete formation of red enemy planes will result in a power-up, such as a health boost or a temporary special weapons which replaces the default twin gun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/1943-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aerofgt.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters</name>
		<desc>Aero Fighters lets you choose from 8 planes, each with a distinctive character. Each character has a different mission base to suit their fighter, a huge range of power-ups and weapons, and a distinctive bomb feature for clearing the screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/aerofgt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>MC O'River</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./brvblade.zip</path>
		<name>Brave Blade</name>
		<desc>An extremely cool vertical shooter from 8ing/Raizing.
8ing/Raizing, the Brave Blade maker, released 12 different machines in our database under this trade name, starting in 1993.

Other machines made by 8ing/Raizing during the time period Brave Blade was produced include Magic Great Battle, Dimahoo, Great Mahou Daisakusen, Bloody Roar 2, Armed Police Batrider, Bloody Roar, Beastorizer, and Shippuu Mahou Daisakusen Kingdom-Grandprix.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/brvblade-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>8ing</developer>
		<publisher>Raizing</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./circusc.zip</path>
		<name>Circus Charlie</name>
		<desc>In the game there are six regular stages (plus an extra stage) of differing tasks that are to be completed by Charlie. Grabbing money bags, performing dangerous tricks, avoiding enemies, completing stages, etc., earns Charlie points. After the sixth stage is completed, the game starts over again but with a faster pace and more difficult (but exactly the same in terms of task to be completed) levels.
Charlie also races against time. Bonus points are awarded according to the time remaining, but running out of time will cost the player a life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/circusc-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Centuri</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ddonpach.zip</path>
		<name>DoDonPachi</name>
		<desc>Donpachi was a hit in arcades, and people felt that Cave were picking up right where Toaplan left off. Therefore, it's no surprise that a sequel to Donpachi would soon be in development. The feeling that the developers had when making Dodonpachi (lit. "Angry Leader Bee"), was to ignore the "Toaplanishness" of Donpachi, instead only putting in systems that Cave felt were the most interesting. This lead to a far more balanced and refined game than its predecessor. To sum up Dodonpachi in a single word, it would have to be...more. More enemies, more stages, more bosses, more systems, more dodging, more bullets, more...everything. The cause of this "more" feeling stems from a chance encounter with the Raizing game Battle Garegga that main programmer Tsuneki Ikeda experienced. The intense action and immediate difficulty of Battle Garegga left a strong impact on Ikeda, leaving him with the feeling that "We (Cave) have to surpass Battle Garegga. Ikeda knew that he couldn't make a game like Battle Garegga no matter how hard he tried, so if he wanted to surpass it, it would have to be done through different means, bullet dodging. Ikeda would later reveal in an interview that he told his team that "We won't lose in terms of bullets!" When released, Dodonpachi could have up to 245 bullets onscreen at once. Because of that decision, Dodonpachi went on to solidify the bullet-hell sub-genre. Dodonpachi would be released into Japanese arcades on February 5, 1997. The game introduced several of what would become the series mainstays: The Donpachi Squadron, Colonel Schwarlitz Longhena, and his "Final Brutal Weapon": Hibachi.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/ddonpach-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cave</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong is an arcade game released by Nintendo in 1981. It is an early example of the platform game genre, as the gameplay focuses on maneuvering the main character across a series of platforms while dodging and jumping over obstacles. In the game, Jumpman (since renamed Mario) must rescue a damsel in distress, Lady (now named Pauline) from a giant ape named Donkey Kong. The hero and ape later became two of Nintendo's most popular characters.
The game was the latest in a series of efforts by Nintendo to break into the North American market. Hiroshi Yamauchi, Nintendo's president at the time, assigned the project to a first-time game designer named Shigeru Miyamoto. Drawing from a wide range of inspirations, including Popeye, Beauty and the Beast and King Kong, Miyamoto developed the scenario and designed the game alongside Nintendo's chief engineer, Gunpei Yokoi. The two men broke new ground by using graphics as a means of characterization, including cut scenes to advance the game's plot, and integrating multiple stages into the gameplay.
Despite initial misgivings on the part of Nintendo's American staff, Donkey Kong proved a success in North America and Japan. Nintendo licensed the game to Coleco, who developed home console versions for numerous platforms. Other companies cloned Nintendo's hit and avoided royalties altogether. Miyamoto's characters appeared on cereal boxes, television cartoons, and dozens of other places. A lawsuit brought on by Universal City Studios, alleging Donkey Kong violated their trademark of King Kong, ultimately failed. The success of Donkey Kong and Nintendo's win in the courtroom helped position the company to dominate the video game market from its release in 1981, until the mid 1990s.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/dkong-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19810709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkong3.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 3</name>
		<desc>Stanley is a bugman. Donkey Kong has taken refuge in his greenhouse and it is now up to Stanley to stop the ape from stirring up any more insects that will soon destroy his flowers. Stanley saves the flowers by spraying bug spray on Donkey Kong.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/dkong3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19831005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkongjr.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Junior</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Junior must save his father from Mario by putting the key or keys in the stage into all of the locks. Mario attempts to stop Donkey Kong Junior by releasing the many animals he controls to knock Donkey Kong Junior off the vines and platforms. Donkey Kong Junior defeats Mario if the player completes the fourth stage by putting all six keys in their locks, making the floor disappear. Donkey Kong Junior catches Donkey Kong while Mario falls onto the ground.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/dkongjr-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19820810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./donpachi.zip</path>
		<name>DonPachi</name>
		<desc>In February of 1993, Japanese game developer Toaplan released Batsugun to Japanese arcades. The game would be met with high praise, and would later be cited as the game that defined many of the various tropes and characteristics that are present in every bullet-hell shmup created since. Sadly, Toaplan would close its doors soon after, leaving many developers suddenly out of work. One of these developers was a programmer named Tsuneki Ikeda, who with fellow now ex-Toaplan employees would found their own development studio, Cave Interactive Co. Ltd, more commonly known as Cave. As Cave was comprised of ex-Toaplan employees at that time, it makes sense that their inaugural game would be a Toaplan-style shooting game. Their first game is DonPachi (lit. "Leader Bee"),a "maniac shooter" in the vein of other Toaplan shmups, like Batsugun. DonPachi was first released in Japanese arcades in May of 1995, and in doing so, created a franchise that would see various releases and ports over the next eight years and across two console generations.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/donpachi-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cave</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./galaxian.zip</path>
		<name>Galaxian</name>
		<desc>Galaxian expanded on the formula pioneered by Space Invaders. As in the earlier game, Galaxian featured a horde of attacking aliens that exchanged shots with the player. In contrast to Space Invaders, Galaxian added an element of drama by having the aliens periodically make kamikaze-like dives at the player's ship, the Galaxip.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/galaxian-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19791001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunsmoke.zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<desc>Gun.Smoke is very similar to Commando, another Capcom game, but with several differences. Whereas Commando is a run and gun game, this game is a scrolling shooter in which the screen scrolls upward automatically and players only have three ways to shoot, using three buttons for left, right, and center shooting. However, a player can also change the way the gunman shoots through button combinations. A player can still die by getting shot or struck by enemies like in Commando but improve protection by getting special items, including a horse, for protection up to three hits; boots, for speed of movement; bullets, for faster shots; and rifles, for shot length. These items are found by shooting barrels and rifles, boots, and bullets can stock up to five.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/gunsmoke-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19851101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./punchout.zip</path>
		<name>Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Isn't it time you got in on the action?

Once again, Nintendo has created a smash hit —Punch-Out— a fast action dual-monitor video boxing game. Its been knocking out the competition week-after-week in earnings and player appeal across the nation.

With Punch-Out in your corner, you gain the added muscle of the
Champ!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/punchout-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./raidendx.zip</path>
		<name>Raiden DX</name>
		<desc>Vertical scrolling shoot-em-up that adds new features to its prequel Raiden II. Choose from three separate missions: Training special stage, Alpha levels 1-5 and Bravo levels 1-9. Collect various power-ups to increase your weaponry. Lots of secrets and bonuses including ratings based upon player performance</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/raidendx-image.jpg</image>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu</developer>
		<publisher>Fabtek</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./splatter.zip</path>
		<name>Splatter house</name>
		<desc>Splatterhouse is a sidescrolling beat 'em up video game in which the player controls Rick, a parapsychology student who is trapped inside West Mansion. After his resurrection by the Terror Mask, Rick makes his way through the mansion, fighting off hordes of creatures in a vain attempt to save his girlfriend Jennifer from a grisly fate. Players of this game will also recognize a number of western horror film influences, such as Friday the 13th and Evil Dead II.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/splatter-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./galaga.zip</path>
		<name>Galaga</name>
		<desc>The gameplay in Galaga '88 is built on the same premise as that of the original Galaga game, but is in many ways more complex and more difficult. The game is divided into a series of 29 Stages distributed through eight Worlds. The starship Galaga accelerates between Stages and Worlds and even to higher dimensions (go to the section on Dimensional Travel below to find out more).

With the exception of the third and eighth, each World culminates in a Challenging Stage. There are six such stages to engage in any full game, and each begins with the on-screen announcement "That's Galactic Dancin'!" and has its own YM2151-generated song to which the enemy formations dance. In any given Challenging Stage, both the design of the enemies and their dancing formations shall vary according to the player's current Dimension. As in Galaga, the objective is to destroy all forty enemies before they fly away off the screen. However, refraining completely from touching any controls for the duration of a Challenging Stage awards a "secret bonus" ranging in value from 10000 to 25000 points, and equal to the "special bonus" which would have been awarded for destroying all forty enemy aliens instead.

Galaga '88 introduces a variety of new enemies and behaviors. Most of these special enemies are worth varying amounts of bonus points when destroyed. Some enemies can combine into larger enemies which take multiple hits to destroy, while others arrive in eggs, explode in a shower of fireworks, grow with multiple hits, or sport armor which makes them invincible while in formation. Certain enemies drop small formations of tiny creatures that wiggle their way down the screen, and still others can act as escorts to incoming groups of enemies and then quickly dive at the player before leaving the game. Most stages also include various obstacles which appear once the enemy formation has been assembled. These can be destroyed with either one or several shots, and the first one on each stage will leave a "Warp Capsule".

At the start of the game, the player can select how many Galaga starships to start with (one or two), affecting their number of remaining lives. The game ends after the final boss is defeated (or when the player's last ship is destroyed or captured) - in the latter case, the player can continue the game for an additional credit. The Game Over screen shows the player's hit-miss ratio and a visual representation of their progress. If the player reaches Stage 27, the game also shows a picture of the final boss (damaged if defeated, but silhouetted if not). If the arcade operator has set the "continue" option to "on", the player also cannot continue if he is defeated on Stages 27-29.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/galaga-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bbakraid.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Bakraid</name>
		<desc>The capitalist nation of Randa has long had a history of excellence in the creation of aircraft, attracting the best of engineers in aerodynamics, artillery, and structuring from the world over. Once, even this interest had waned, until the creation of the air show Bakraid, in which the capabilities of the fighters could be demonstrated outside of simulations for all to see.
Around the time of the seventh Bakraid, a nearby nation, Deneb, had attained an expansionist attitude, forcibly subjugating and annexing several of its neighbors with the assistance of the Shtarterra Security Council. Recently, Deneb has asked to participate in Bakraid. Randa's defense council, perfectly aware that this is just a pretext for Deneb to get its and the SSC's engines of war into Randan borders and more easily prosecute their war from there, give their blessing. However, the council secretly contacts the other Bakraid participants, offering even more prize money than normal if they will perform in a special version of Bakraid--genuine war conditions. In other words, use their own top-of-the-line planes to shatter Deneb's schemes. In all, nine pilots accept this plan, and begin Bakraid two weeks early to catch Deneb unaware...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/bbakraid-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T035457</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bgaregga.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Garegga</name>
		<desc>Battle Garegga is a game with a divisive reputation. Many people regard it as one of the best shooters of all time. Others think that it's overrated and that the art style and rank system ruin what would have been some cool ideas. The general style, in addition to the bomb collection system, was heavily influenced by Taito's 1990 shooter Gun Frontier, to the point where Battle Garegga could be considered a spiritual successor.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/bgaregga-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raizing</developer>
		<publisher>Raizing</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T035827</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tps.zip</path>
		<name>TPS</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<hidden>1</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mappy.zip</path>
		<name>Mappy</name>
		<desc>The player guides Mappy the police mouse through the mansion of the cats called Mewkies (Meowky in the U.S. version) to retrieve stolen goods. The player uses a left-right joystick to move Mappy and a single button to operate doors. The mansion has six floors of hallways in which the stolen items are stashed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/mappy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bally Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T164355</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pacman.zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<desc>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde). One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/pacman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19801001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco, Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T165310</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./19xx.zip</path>
		<name>19XX: The War Against Destiny</name>
		<desc>19XX: The War Against Destiny is a vertical scrolling shooter arcade game made by Capcom in 1995 (copyrighted in 1996). The game is the 4th of a series of World War II vertical shooters made by Capcom. The story takes place before a fictional war (Hence, the 19XX) as a lone pilot tries to defeat an entire army/evil organization from starting another World War, which soon escalates to a nuclear apocalypse.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/arcadev/19xx-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T020322</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
