<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island II - Aliens in Paradise.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island II</name>
		<desc>In Adventure Island II the player takes the role of Master Higgins who has to save his cavegirl from aliens which also want to dominate the Earth. The basic gameplay elements are the same as in its predecessor Adventure Island: Master Higgins walks through the levels while fighting against various enemies. One hit results in his untimely death unless he carries one of the various power ups, e.g. weapons or a skateboard which improves his speed. He also needs to collect food to fill up his steadily decreasing starvation bar - death awaits if it hits zero.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Adventure Island II - Aliens in Paradise-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T142355</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga &amp; Galaxian.zip</path>
		<name>Arcade Classic 3: Galaga/Galaxian</name>
		<desc>This is a compilation of two classic arcade games on one pack:
•Galaga
•Galaxian</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Galaga &amp; Galaxian-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044218</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads in Ragnarok's World.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads in Ragnarok's World</name>
		<desc>Okay 'toads! Let's get EVEN! When the evil Dark Queen kidnaps both your best buddy and the best looking girl this side of the Mazallion Star Cluster -what are you gonna do about it? Are you gonna cry? Hide? Call the Starcops? No way! Because you're a BATTLETOAD and BATTLETOADS don't cry, hide, or call for help. BATTLETOADS get real MAD-and then they get EVEN!

So, strap on your Blaster, power-up the Toadster and get on downt o the Dark Queen's planet - but, watch out 'toad - this lady's bad, and she's got a whole mess of really nasty surprises lined up for you - like the Psyko Pigs, the Mutant Ratpack, Robo-Manus and the Saturn Toadtrap, to name but a few. You're gonna need all your fighting skills to defeat her - the Battletoad Butt, the Big Bad Boot and the Nuclear Knuckles. Hey, and don't forget to take along the Jet Turbo, the Space Board and the Speed Bike. Because you're gonna need 'em all, 'toad, if you're gonna rescue your friends and get the frog outta there with your green skin intact!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battletoads in Ragnarok's World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Adventure</name>
		<desc>The game's protagonist is Bonk, a strong caveboy who battles anthropomorphic dinosaurs and other prehistoric themed enemies. Bonk's mission is to rescue Princess Za (a small pink Pleisiosaur-type reptile) who has been kidnapped by the evil King Drool (a large, green, Tyrannosaurus-type dinosaur). In the Arcade version, Bonk is also assisted by a female version of himself.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bonk's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson, NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054155</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Legends.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania Legends</name>
		<desc>Every legend has a beginning. Now discover the beginning of the Castlevania Legend in Castlevania Legends for Game Boy. In this single-player adventure, you play as Sonia Belmont, the very first in the line of vampire hunting Belmonts. Use your whip to fend off the forces of darkness, as you work your way through six stages of non-linear gameplay. Explore the legendary areas of Castlevania, including the surrounding forest and the infamous clock tower. Don't forget to collect hearts from the torches that litter the stages to gain extra lives. Adjustable difficulty settings allow you to choose the skill level at which you want to play. At the end of it all, Count Dracula himself awaits. Can you defeat him and put the evil to rest for another 100 years?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania Legends-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra - The Alien Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Contra: The Alien Wars</name>
		<desc>Welcome to 2636 the year the notorious Red Falcon gets even-with an unprecedented alien onslaught orchestrated to push the Contra forces to their ultimate reaches. Plunge through a molten massacre on a high speed voyage to the guts of the archenemy alien. Check out the side and top perspectives that engulf you in a 3-D sensation. Pick off solar slimedogs while you scale over walls swing from girders and ropes whatever it takes to defeat Red Falcon's allies. Sweat through five gut-splitting stages including the Streets of the Neo City and the Mucho Grande Badlands.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Contra - The Alien Wars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054146</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong returns to Game Boy! This famous ape has kidnapped Pauline and climbed to the top of a perilous skyscraper. Challenged by many perils and unending puzzles, Mario must reach his arch rival. As he makes his way Mario will need to gather disappearing keys to unlock doors of hidden rooms. Donkey Kong devises evil tricks to confuse and trap him. Our heroic plumber has his hands full this time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T005854</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land 2.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land 2</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land 2 is the first sequel to Donkey Kong Land for the Nintendo Game Boy and was released in 1996.

The story mainly complies to its SNES counterpart; K. Rool kidnapped Donkey Kong, demanding the entire Banana Hoard as ransom, so it's up to Diddy Kong and Dixie Kong to rescue their kidnapped pal. A wild assortment of friendly animals like Rambi the Rhino, Squitter the Spider, Squawks the Parrot, Rattly the Rattlesnake and Enguarde the Swordfish help the two little monkeys in their adventurous mission. Each exciting level is filled with special traps, hidden items and dastardly Kremlings! Prepare yourself for the biggest Game Boy adventure yet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.81667</rating>
		<releasedate>19960116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land III.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land III</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land III is the last part in the Donkey Kong Land series and was released for the Game Boy by Nintendo in 1997.

Fame-and-fortune seekers have flooded Donkey Kong Country in search of the fabled Lost World. Dixie Kong &amp; Kiddy Kong rush through 36 Kong-sized levels of action and adventure. Use your animal friends - Squitter the spider, Squawks the parrot, Ellie the elephant, Enguarde the swordfish and Parry the parallel bird - to help you prove your adventuring skills and find the Lost World before someone else does!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.81667</rating>
		<releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Adventure</name>
		<desc>In the Empire of Glaive, a gladiator-slave is forced to fight evil monsters controlled by the Dark Lord. But when his best friend is mortally wounded, he learns of a secret pendant which will give him great power. As the hero, you must battle your way out of the Dark Knight's castle and search through a dangerous world for the girl who has the pendant. But you discover she has been captured by the Dark Knight's men. To free her, you must find the legendary sword and fight off the Dark Knight's beasts and overlords through deserts, snowfields, lakes, forests, and caves. Are you ready for the adventure of your life?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Final Fantasy Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T060204</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gargoyle's Quest - Ghosts'n Goblins.zip</path>
		<name>Gargoyle's Quest</name>
		<desc>Gargoyle's Quest Brings Big-Screen Action to Game Boy!

You are Firebrand - gargoyle and proud guardian of the Ghoul Realm. The Destroyers have returned to wipe out your planet... and they take no prisoners!

Use your breath of fire and your flying ability to combat the enemy. Fight heroically, and you'll recover stolen magic items that will strengthen you for your many battles.

Detailed Graphics set new standards for Game Boy
Fascinating new epic adventure story!

For 1 player only.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Gargoyle's Quest - Ghosts'n Goblins-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T041001</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>Plunge into a heart-wrenching race for survival! On a tropical island, a violent hurricane rips through the dinosaur preserve, trapping the tourists and freeing the most terrifying animals in prehistory! Two bigger-than-life ways to play: Be a dinosaur! As a Raptor, rampage across the island battling other beasts and eluding the traps and weapons of your human enemies. As Grant, the paleontologist, arm yourself with tranquilizer guns, and sleeping-gas grenades. Dodge the slashing jaws of the Tyrannosaurus Rex and the paralyzing spit of the Dilophosaurs! 16 mammoth megs of nerve-shredding action!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Dracula.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Dracula</name>
		<desc>His pearly fangs drive the girls wild, while his dead-of-the-party sense of humor makes them scream. He's Kid Dracula, star of the mythical Transylvania 92010, and the coolest living corpse ever to stake his claim on the Game Boy. If you thought Mario had a way with magic, you should see junior jugular's spellbinding powers, including the mesmerizing bat transformation. Poof! Nobody wings it better than Kid Drac.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kid Dracula-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T041133</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Block Ball.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Block Ball</name>
		<desc>Kirby's back with fast-paced, four-way action!

It's a breakaway bash in this wild new Kirby game of Block Ball! By destroying the blocks on the screen, you clear stages and obtain powers that help you in your final confrontation with King Dedede.

Paddles on all four sides of the screen make this an intense four-way action contest. Your quick reactions and your careful use of Kirby's powers will determine your ultimate fate!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Block Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19951214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land</name>
		<desc>The gluttonous King Dedede has stolen all of the food from the inhabitants of Dream Land for a midnight feast, so Kirby, a resident of Dream Land, goes to retrieve the food and stop Dedede. Kirby's Dream Land plays like other platformers of the 8-bit and 16-bit era of video games: Kirby must use various natural abilities and occasionally external abilities or items while heading toward the goal at the end of each level. Like many 1980s-era platformers, the player can accumulate points, with an extra life granted when the player has enough points. However, because Kirby lacks a save function, scores are not recorded. Also, there are no save files, so the player has to start over again when the Game Boy is turned off, if the player chooses to return to the title screen after a Game Over, or if the player resets the game. All levels are played on a two-dimensional plane, letting Kirby move only left, right, up, and down. Kirby can walk, jump, and fly. Kirby can also inhale objects and enemies, swallowing them or spitting them out as projectiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land 2.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land 2</name>
		<desc>The Rainbow Bridges have disappeared! Help Kirby solve the mystery. Search the seven Rainbow Islands while battling King DeDeDe and his horde of evil minions! Meet Rick the Hamster, Kine the Fish and Coo the Owl. Each holds important abilities that can multiply the magnitude of Kirby's powers. Earn the mysterious Rainbow Sword and prepare to face Kirby's most menacing rival ever - the evil Dark Matter!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170203T012715</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Star Stacker.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Star Stacker</name>
		<desc>Join Kirby as he stacks the falling stars with help from his friends, Rick the Hamster, Kine the Sunfish, and Coo the Owl. Watch out for King Dedede. He is out to stop you! With a few quick moves and some well-timed strategy, you can quickly outwit him and move on to the next challenging level. Kirby's Star Stacker features pure puzzle fun for everyone. From above, blocks rain down constantly. From below, whole lines appear with unrelenting clock-like regularity. Simply sandwich the stars between Kirby's pals and you'll soon be on your way to the high score.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Star Stacker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman II.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man II</name>
		<desc>The demented Dr. Wily is at it again! This time he's stolen the experimental Time Skimmer and skipped into the future. But Wait! Four of his strongest cyborgs have been left behind to squash the mighty Mega Man!

Time is of the essence as Mega Man and Rush blast past waves of maniacal metal monsters on the way to underground lair of Dr. Wily. Once there they must face Quint, the ferocious fiend from the future!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Biox</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman III.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man III</name>
		<desc>Battle at the Center of the Earth!

That sinister scientist Dr. Wily is at it again! Now, he and his renegade robots have purloined an off-shore oil rig and are drilling through the Earth's crust. It's up to Mega Man to shut down their scheme before Wily can harness the molten power of the Earth's core to fuel his latest metallic monstrosity!

Join Rush, Flip-Top and Mega Man as they battle wave after wave of mechanical maniacs as they search through Wily's fiendish fortress. Battle Snake Man, Spark Man, and six other robot masters as you near Wily's lair. Sneak inside and summon the power of the Mega Buster as you face the awesome power of Wily's ultimate creation!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman IV.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man IV</name>
		<desc>A huge celebration at the World Robot Expo is shattered by the sight of a flying saucer streaking across the sky. But instead of holding little green men, this saucer holds one very mad scientist! Armed with a mind control machine that transmits a sinister signal. Dr. Wily is ready to mesmerize all the robots of the city into an army of mindless metallic mercenaries!

Battling the effects of Wily's mind control machine, Mega Man and his robotic reenforcements, Rush and Beat must blast to molten metal an army of foes led by eight of Wily's greatest robot masters! And should Mega Man survive, Dr. Wily is waiting to unleash the heavy artillery with his latest creation, the awesome Wily Tank!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman V.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man V</name>
		<desc>They came from outer space!

From the cosmic reaches of outer space, comes mankind's greatest threat. Hordes of alien robots have swarmed down from the heavens all the Earth's weapons are powerless to stop their ravenous rampage. Now the only hope to stop these alien invaders lies with one man - Mega Man!

Blast off for new worlds of excitement as Mega Man launches an all-out attack on the alien armada! Rocket into battle and dodge the deadly rings of SATURN and face the molten menace of MERCURY! Search the galaxy for alien gems and construct the ultimate "Mega Arm" weapon and blast these invaders all the way back to Alpha Centauri!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman V-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man: Dr. Wily's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Dr. Wily's most challenging robot masters will be there when you pump up the GameBoy. And knowing the maniac he is, he's probably concocted a new one or two. Can you survive the eight empires before you break into Dr. Wily's lab? Well, if you experienced MegaMan before, you know it's no day at the beach. But good reason to get going on MegaMan in Dr. Wily's Revenge. Now.

* When the stompin' cyclops springs into action, you better step on it.
* The swooping copterheads just might be your greatest challenge yet.
* If the giant fan is blowing, only a ledge-jump will save you from the spikes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid II - Return of Samus.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid II: Return of Samus</name>
		<desc>A Sinister Planet Threatens the Galaxy!

Space Hunter Samus Aran returns to battle a planet crawling with evil creatures bent on universal domination in this bigger than ever sequel to the NES classic, Metroid.

Take control! Guide Samus through cavernous corridors, ancient ruins and alien traps. On the mysterious planet of the Metroids, you'll find artifacts of a lost civilization that grant amazing powers. Cut through creatures in a buzz-saw blur! Roll through hidden tunnels and climb sheer walls!

A battery back-up allows you to save your progress as you fight to the heart of the planet and search for the merciless Metroid leaders. If you are a cunning explorer, you'll earn the best of several super endings.

Enter this exciting Metroid sequel and experience the thrills of Game Boy like never before!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Metroid II - Return of Samus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mole Mania.zip</path>
		<name>Mole Mania</name>
		<desc>Join Muddy Mole in a race to destroy enemies and obstacles in an attempt to defeat the evil farmer, Jinbei. Blast strategic exits using black balls and tunnel your way to the next action-packed level. Help Muddy solve the incredible puzzles of Jinbei Land and reunite him with his beloved mole family. You'll dig the fast pace and challenging fun of Mole Mania!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mole Mania-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pax Softonica</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Operation C.zip</path>
		<name>Operation C</name>
		<desc>Operation C is an Action game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Operation C-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land</name>
		<desc>Journey with Mario to a land of giant crabs, Koopa Troopas, flying stone heads and hungry sharks!

Travel over land, in the air, and underwater. Mario makes his way through four treacherous worlds on his way to save the Princess!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Super Mario Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76</rating>
		<releasedate>19890421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins</name>
		<desc>In his greatest Game Boy adventure, Mario faces off against his evil rival Wario, who has captured Mario Land and turned it into his private playground.

To toss Wario off his ill-gotten throne, Mario must search all-new worlds for the six golden coins that unlock the gate to Mario's castle. A mob of monsters, old and new, seek to stop him. Along the way, through 6 zones, Mario can nab Power Mushrooms, Super Stars and Fire Flowers for extra power. And if he eats the Magic Carrot, he'll turn into a high-flying hare.

The battery pack saves your game in progress in this biggest Game Boy Mario adventure yet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.84444</rating>
		<releasedate>19921021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT III - Radical Rescue.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III: Radical Rescue</name>
		<desc>The whole sewer crew, except Michaelangelo, is captured in a most heinous hideout. Who could be behind this travesty? Who else. Shredder has returned as Cyber Shredder - half-man, half-machine and he‘s created this twisty-turny fun house" of Turtle torture. Use Turtle strategy and all new moves to help Michaelangelo rescue the gang from Cyber Shredder's Fortress.

-The Turtles are sporting some radical new maneuvers. Call on each unique skill to overcome specific obstacles. It helps to round up your scrambled cohorts in a certain order.

-Michaelangelo has helicopter hang time, Leonardo dusts concrete blocks, Raphael shells through tight spots and Donatello scales sheer walls.

-Fight through 5 rescue adventures. You'll need keen Turtle sense and all the pizza power you can scarf up to make It past bats, goons and hordes of robotic maniacs.

-Use the Fortress Map to navigate through places unseen and find valuable Items such as power ups, ID cards, keys an shanghaied Shell Backs.

-Who's the Boss you ask? How about Scratch, Dirtbag, Triceraton, Scale Tail and of course Cyber Shredder, as Turtle-hungry as they get.

-The Password feature lets you pick up your mission from the last Boss Beast you annihilated.

-To make it out of Shredder’s maze of mayhem, you'll need to be as sharp as a sai sword and as tough as a team of sumo wrestlers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/TMNT III - Radical Rescue-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>Tetris is a puzzle video game which was released in 1989 by Nintendo for the Game Boy. Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together and the formed line will disappear. If the pieces are not lined up correctly they eventually stack up to the top of the playfield and the game is over. Difficulty increases by dropping the pieces faster and faster over time. Tetris is a verifiable classic game, translated to well over 200 electronic and computer platforms. It takes 2 minutes to learn, but a lifetime to master!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9125</rating>
		<releasedate>19890614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Attack.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris Attack</name>
		<desc>In Tetris Attack, the player is presented with a playfield consisting of a virtual grid of squares, each of which can be occupied by a block. Blocks are stacked on top of one another and rise steadily toward the top of the playfield, with new blocks being added at the bottom. The player must arrange blocks in horizontal or vertical lines of three or more matching shapes by swapping blocks horizontally two at a time. As matching lines are formed, the blocks are cleared from the screen and any blocks above them fall into the gaps. The game is over when the blocks touch the top of the playfield, or another game-ending condition is met (such as reaching a time limit or clearing blocks below a set line). Clearing more than three tiles in a single move scores a Combo, while Chains are scored when falling blocks from one clear cause another clear to occur. Both of these events score extra bonus points, and in multiplayer Versus games, these also send "garbage blocks" to the other player's playfield.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - King Rock Treasure Island.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones: King Rock Treasure Island</name>
		<desc>The Flintstones: King Rock Treasure Island is an Action game, developed and published by Taito Corporation, which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Flintstones, The - King Rock Treasure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Babs' Big Break.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Babs' Big Break</name>
		<desc>BABS MAY BE A TOUGH ACT TO FOLLOW, BUT CATCHING UP WITH HER IS EVEN TOUGHER!

Babs dreams of making It BIG in the BIG City as a BIG Star. She slips away on an adventurous downtown journey to the Acme Theater. Montana Max wants to turn the theater into a spectacular safe to show off his money. so he's out to bring the curtain down on Babs. Yikes! It’s all up to Buster Bunny, Plucky Duck and Hamton to catch our favorite rising star before Monty catches her first! Join the zaniest star search to hit the Game Boy screen and see Babs in her most thrilling role yet. Here's what the fans have to say.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tiny Toon Adventures - Babs' Big Break-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trip World.zip</path>
		<name>Trip World</name>
		<desc>In the early 1990s Sunsoft was at its best, developing many fine platformers, several of which were even licensed properties. Its Batman games were almost all excellent, especially the Game Boy release, which combined Mario-style platforms and blockbusting with gunplay. Much of Sunsoft's NES catalogue is also fondly remembered, with titles such as Blaster Master, Journey to Silius and, despite its obscene difficulty, Mr. Gimmick / Gimmick! to name a few. Trip World for the Game Boy is another Sunsoft goodie, regularly featuring on lists for obscure or overlooked games and, in the US at least, lists for import exclusives. Released only in Japan and Europe in small quantities, a boxed copy of the original cartridge now sells for ludicrously high prices. At the time of writing, two unboxed copies were on eBay for around £115 / $180; Yahoo! Auctions Japan had nothing.

Trip World at first appears to be like any conventional platformer – perhaps a little too conventional. There's an intro showing the Maita Flower from atop Mount Dubious being stolen from an elderly Shabubu who is also kidnapped (a bunny-like creature not to be confused with the culinary shabu-shabu dish). Cue the old creature's grandson, Yacopu, to venture out, save his grandfather and retrieve the flower, thereby bringing peace back to the world. Players move across the screen, avoiding spike pits, jumping along collapsing platforms, and karate kicking enemies... Except the enemies don't seem to fight back. Very few of them in fact cause any damage at all, with only the bosses posing a genuine threat. Apart from the harmless enemies, it's all very standard. Yacopu can collect fruit items which imbue him with special powers: the ability to fire paralysing seeds that sprout from the skulls of enemies; a bouncy ball power-up; and a third which allows him to attack with his tail. These powers are timed and soon wear off, but in some stages it's possible to collect an additional power-up which, when combined with the first, grants something entirely new. The best of which causes Yacopu to sprout legs and gain the ability to fire instant-death projectiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Trip World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land II.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land II</name>
		<desc>What kind of no-good ruffians would break into my castle and steal my treasures?! It's that rotten Captain Syrup and that Black Sugar Gang! I'm looking out for bad guys and scavenging for coins as I track down my treasures. If I don't get them all the first time, that's OK. I can go back again and again until I find them all. Captain Syrup doesn't stand a chance against me!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Wario Land II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land - Super Mario Land 3.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land: Super Mario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Hey! Things are really cookin' on Kitchen Island! Wario's got a scheme to steal the pirates' treasure so he can have his very own castle! You help Wario get the treasure by smashing into the the magic pots! Each pot changes him into Dragon Wario, Bull Wario, or Jet Wario! With each change comes new powers!

Dozens of enemies try to stop Wario, but you have the power to beat them!

Be the bad guy!

Explore the many exciting levels of Kitchen Island!

Battery-backed memory saves your progress for many hours of fun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Wario Land - Super Mario Land 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8099999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19940121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Cookie is a fast-paced puzzle game. The player moves randomly placed cookies into rows and columns of cookies with similar patterns. When a row or column of the same cookies is successfully assembled, the line will disappear, and the player can begin to work on a new row or column. The "Yoshi" cookie is very special in both the 1-player and the 2-player game. Since this cookie is the key to both games, it should be used wisely.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Yoshi's Cookie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania II - Belmont's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II: Belmont's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Fifteen years after vanquishing the emperor of evil, Count Dracula, Christopher Belmont now faces a vampire swearing vengeance. Drac's back. And he's turned your son, Soleiyu Belmont, into a deadly demon to do his dirty deeds. Now not only do you have to rescue your kid from the Count's clutches, you have to first track him down in four creep packed Castles. Fortunately, you posses weapons like armor piercing Battle Axes, beast burning Holy Water, and the Legendary Mystic Whip. And you can increase your arsenal with power up items like Crystal Balls, Hearts, and Candles. Strap on your shield and step into the shadows. That is, if you're prepared for the dwellers of darkness.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania II - Belmont's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T020505</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Adventure, The.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: The Adventure</name>
		<desc>Castlevania: The Adventure, known as Dracula Densetsu (officially translated The Legend of Dracula) in Japan, is a platform game released for the Game Boy in 1989. It is the first Castlevania title for the system.

Set a century before the events of the original Castlevania, the player controls an ancestor of Simon Belmont named Christopher Belmont who goes on a quest to defeat Dracula.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania Adventure, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19891203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054138</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land is a Jump &amp; Run classic, developed by Rareware and released by Nintendo for the Game Boy in June 1995.

Cranky Kong, jealous of all the success Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong have had from Donkey Kong Country on the SNES, challenges the Kongs to beat another adventure on an 8-bit system (Game Boy). As King K. Rool agrees with Cranky and steals the bananas again, Donkey &amp; Diddy Kong set out to go throuth another adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044246</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerin' Harry - Ghost Building Company.zip</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Harry: Ghost Building Company</name>
		<desc>Harry and his spouse were walking down the street, while all of a sudden,
ghosts start to appear and the city gets demolished. A dark city, with a
haunted mansion in the middle, rises from the rumble and four ghost fuse to
become a large ghost and kidnaps Harry's spouse. You must save your spouse and
stop the evil Ghost Building Company.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Hammerin' Harry - Ghost Building Company-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tamtex</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Montana's Movie Madness.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures 2: Montana's Movie Madness</name>
		<desc>Here comes Montana Max the meanest movie maker to ever tarnish the silver screen. He's directed four new flicks that make Buster Bunny look like a villain! To defend his character Buster Bunny must leap into Max's movies and use attack moves like fast dash and freeze kick to change the endings before his career is finished.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tiny Toon Adventures - Montana's Movie Madness-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>In the South Pacific, Master Higgins lives peacefully wearing only a grass skirt and a cap. That is until the Evil Witch Doctor decides to capture the Princess Leilani and hold her as his own. It's up to Master Higgins to gather throwing axes, fireballs and skateboards in order to aid his noble quest.

The game is a side scroller, Master Higgins moves across the screen from left to right and finds his power-ups in giant eggs. This includes a skateboard which results in a great speed enhancement - until Master Higgins gets hit and loses his power. If he is not on a skateboard a hit means instant death. Another game mechanic is starvation which gets indicated through a meter which steadily decreases. If it hits zero the hero dies and the only way to fill it up is by collecting food on the way. Bosses await him at the end of levels, all the way to the Evil Witch Doctor himself.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Adventure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>13</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T153401</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery.zip</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery</name>
		<desc>Original and updated versions of four Game &amp; Watch hand held games!

Classic versions will take you back to the '80s and a simpler time in video games. Modern versions feature your favorite characters and will bring you to the present with improved play control and sound effects.

-Enjoy four different games!
Manhole - Don't let pedestrians fall.
Fire - Rescue the jumpers.
Octopus - Retrive the sunken treasure.
Oil Panic - Catch the dripping oil.

-New Interrupt Save feature lets you stop and restart anytime!

-Battery-backed memory saves all your scores!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Game &amp; Watch Gallery-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T033032</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Link's Awakening</name>
		<desc>A Game Boy fantasy adventure like no other!

Nintendo's fantasy adventure hero, Link of Hyrule, returns in this new epic quest...Link's Awakening. Link's newest challenge is set on the mysterious Koholint Island, a place where dreams and reality collide. As a castaway, Link must find a way to escape from the island and return to his beloved homeland of Hyrule.

But it won't be as easy as chartering a boat. The island's inhabitants have no knowledge of the outside world. One creature, a talking Owl, may know the solution to Link's dilemma, but first Link must tackle eight dungeons full of treacherous monsters and tricky taps. His goal: find the eight Instruments of the Sirens and awaken the omnipotent Wind Fish which rules the island.

Link will battle new enemies and make new friends in one of the most in-depth fantasy adventures for Game Boy yet!

A battery-backed memory will save up to three games so you never have to start your journey empty-handed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19930606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170307T230057</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
