<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island II - Aliens in Paradise.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island II</name>
		<desc>In Adventure Island II the player takes the role of Master Higgins who has to save his cavegirl from aliens which also want to dominate the Earth. The basic gameplay elements are the same as in its predecessor Adventure Island: Master Higgins walks through the levels while fighting against various enemies. One hit results in his untimely death unless he carries one of the various power ups, e.g. weapons or a skateboard which improves his speed. He also needs to collect food to fill up his steadily decreasing starvation bar - death awaits if it hits zero.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Adventure Island II - Aliens in Paradise-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T142355</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga &amp; Galaxian.zip</path>
		<name>Arcade Classic 3: Galaga/Galaxian</name>
		<desc>This is a compilation of two classic arcade games on one pack:
•Galaga
•Galaxian</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Galaga &amp; Galaxian-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044218</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads in Ragnarok's World.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads in Ragnarok's World</name>
		<desc>Okay 'toads! Let's get EVEN! When the evil Dark Queen kidnaps both your best buddy and the best looking girl this side of the Mazallion Star Cluster -what are you gonna do about it? Are you gonna cry? Hide? Call the Starcops? No way! Because you're a BATTLETOAD and BATTLETOADS don't cry, hide, or call for help. BATTLETOADS get real MAD-and then they get EVEN!

So, strap on your Blaster, power-up the Toadster and get on downt o the Dark Queen's planet - but, watch out 'toad - this lady's bad, and she's got a whole mess of really nasty surprises lined up for you - like the Psyko Pigs, the Mutant Ratpack, Robo-Manus and the Saturn Toadtrap, to name but a few. You're gonna need all your fighting skills to defeat her - the Battletoad Butt, the Big Bad Boot and the Nuclear Knuckles. Hey, and don't forget to take along the Jet Turbo, the Space Board and the Speed Bike. Because you're gonna need 'em all, 'toad, if you're gonna rescue your friends and get the frog outta there with your green skin intact!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battletoads in Ragnarok's World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Adventure</name>
		<desc>The game's protagonist is Bonk, a strong caveboy who battles anthropomorphic dinosaurs and other prehistoric themed enemies. Bonk's mission is to rescue Princess Za (a small pink Pleisiosaur-type reptile) who has been kidnapped by the evil King Drool (a large, green, Tyrannosaurus-type dinosaur). In the Arcade version, Bonk is also assisted by a female version of himself.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bonk's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson, NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054155</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Legends.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania Legends</name>
		<desc>Every legend has a beginning. Now discover the beginning of the Castlevania Legend in Castlevania Legends for Game Boy. In this single-player adventure, you play as Sonia Belmont, the very first in the line of vampire hunting Belmonts. Use your whip to fend off the forces of darkness, as you work your way through six stages of non-linear gameplay. Explore the legendary areas of Castlevania, including the surrounding forest and the infamous clock tower. Don't forget to collect hearts from the torches that litter the stages to gain extra lives. Adjustable difficulty settings allow you to choose the skill level at which you want to play. At the end of it all, Count Dracula himself awaits. Can you defeat him and put the evil to rest for another 100 years?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania Legends-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra - The Alien Wars.zip</path>
		<name>Contra: The Alien Wars</name>
		<desc>Welcome to 2636 the year the notorious Red Falcon gets even-with an unprecedented alien onslaught orchestrated to push the Contra forces to their ultimate reaches. Plunge through a molten massacre on a high speed voyage to the guts of the archenemy alien. Check out the side and top perspectives that engulf you in a 3-D sensation. Pick off solar slimedogs while you scale over walls swing from girders and ropes whatever it takes to defeat Red Falcon's allies. Sweat through five gut-splitting stages including the Streets of the Neo City and the Mucho Grande Badlands.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Contra - The Alien Wars-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054146</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong returns to Game Boy! This famous ape has kidnapped Pauline and climbed to the top of a perilous skyscraper. Challenged by many perils and unending puzzles, Mario must reach his arch rival. As he makes his way Mario will need to gather disappearing keys to unlock doors of hidden rooms. Donkey Kong devises evil tricks to confuse and trap him. Our heroic plumber has his hands full this time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T005854</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land 2.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land 2</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land 2 is the first sequel to Donkey Kong Land for the Nintendo Game Boy and was released in 1996.

The story mainly complies to its SNES counterpart; K. Rool kidnapped Donkey Kong, demanding the entire Banana Hoard as ransom, so it's up to Diddy Kong and Dixie Kong to rescue their kidnapped pal. A wild assortment of friendly animals like Rambi the Rhino, Squitter the Spider, Squawks the Parrot, Rattly the Rattlesnake and Enguarde the Swordfish help the two little monkeys in their adventurous mission. Each exciting level is filled with special traps, hidden items and dastardly Kremlings! Prepare yourself for the biggest Game Boy adventure yet!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.81667</rating>
		<releasedate>19960116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land III.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land III</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land III is the last part in the Donkey Kong Land series and was released for the Game Boy by Nintendo in 1997.

Fame-and-fortune seekers have flooded Donkey Kong Country in search of the fabled Lost World. Dixie Kong &amp; Kiddy Kong rush through 36 Kong-sized levels of action and adventure. Use your animal friends - Squitter the spider, Squawks the parrot, Ellie the elephant, Enguarde the swordfish and Parry the parallel bird - to help you prove your adventuring skills and find the Lost World before someone else does!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.81667</rating>
		<releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Adventure</name>
		<desc>In the Empire of Glaive, a gladiator-slave is forced to fight evil monsters controlled by the Dark Lord. But when his best friend is mortally wounded, he learns of a secret pendant which will give him great power. As the hero, you must battle your way out of the Dark Knight's castle and search through a dangerous world for the girl who has the pendant. But you discover she has been captured by the Dark Knight's men. To free her, you must find the legendary sword and fight off the Dark Knight's beasts and overlords through deserts, snowfields, lakes, forests, and caves. Are you ready for the adventure of your life?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Final Fantasy Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T060204</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gargoyle's Quest - Ghosts'n Goblins.zip</path>
		<name>Gargoyle's Quest</name>
		<desc>Gargoyle's Quest Brings Big-Screen Action to Game Boy!

You are Firebrand - gargoyle and proud guardian of the Ghoul Realm. The Destroyers have returned to wipe out your planet... and they take no prisoners!

Use your breath of fire and your flying ability to combat the enemy. Fight heroically, and you'll recover stolen magic items that will strengthen you for your many battles.

Detailed Graphics set new standards for Game Boy
Fascinating new epic adventure story!

For 1 player only.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Gargoyle's Quest - Ghosts'n Goblins-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T041001</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>Plunge into a heart-wrenching race for survival! On a tropical island, a violent hurricane rips through the dinosaur preserve, trapping the tourists and freeing the most terrifying animals in prehistory! Two bigger-than-life ways to play: Be a dinosaur! As a Raptor, rampage across the island battling other beasts and eluding the traps and weapons of your human enemies. As Grant, the paleontologist, arm yourself with tranquilizer guns, and sleeping-gas grenades. Dodge the slashing jaws of the Tyrannosaurus Rex and the paralyzing spit of the Dilophosaurs! 16 mammoth megs of nerve-shredding action!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Dracula.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Dracula</name>
		<desc>His pearly fangs drive the girls wild, while his dead-of-the-party sense of humor makes them scream. He's Kid Dracula, star of the mythical Transylvania 92010, and the coolest living corpse ever to stake his claim on the Game Boy. If you thought Mario had a way with magic, you should see junior jugular's spellbinding powers, including the mesmerizing bat transformation. Poof! Nobody wings it better than Kid Drac.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kid Dracula-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T041133</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Block Ball.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Block Ball</name>
		<desc>Kirby's back with fast-paced, four-way action!

It's a breakaway bash in this wild new Kirby game of Block Ball! By destroying the blocks on the screen, you clear stages and obtain powers that help you in your final confrontation with King Dedede.

Paddles on all four sides of the screen make this an intense four-way action contest. Your quick reactions and your careful use of Kirby's powers will determine your ultimate fate!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Block Ball-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19951214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land</name>
		<desc>The gluttonous King Dedede has stolen all of the food from the inhabitants of Dream Land for a midnight feast, so Kirby, a resident of Dream Land, goes to retrieve the food and stop Dedede. Kirby's Dream Land plays like other platformers of the 8-bit and 16-bit era of video games: Kirby must use various natural abilities and occasionally external abilities or items while heading toward the goal at the end of each level. Like many 1980s-era platformers, the player can accumulate points, with an extra life granted when the player has enough points. However, because Kirby lacks a save function, scores are not recorded. Also, there are no save files, so the player has to start over again when the Game Boy is turned off, if the player chooses to return to the title screen after a Game Over, or if the player resets the game. All levels are played on a two-dimensional plane, letting Kirby move only left, right, up, and down. Kirby can walk, jump, and fly. Kirby can also inhale objects and enemies, swallowing them or spitting them out as projectiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land 2.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land 2</name>
		<desc>The Rainbow Bridges have disappeared! Help Kirby solve the mystery. Search the seven Rainbow Islands while battling King DeDeDe and his horde of evil minions! Meet Rick the Hamster, Kine the Fish and Coo the Owl. Each holds important abilities that can multiply the magnitude of Kirby's powers. Earn the mysterious Rainbow Sword and prepare to face Kirby's most menacing rival ever - the evil Dark Matter!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Dream Land 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170203T012715</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Star Stacker.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Star Stacker</name>
		<desc>Join Kirby as he stacks the falling stars with help from his friends, Rick the Hamster, Kine the Sunfish, and Coo the Owl. Watch out for King Dedede. He is out to stop you! With a few quick moves and some well-timed strategy, you can quickly outwit him and move on to the next challenging level. Kirby's Star Stacker features pure puzzle fun for everyone. From above, blocks rain down constantly. From below, whole lines appear with unrelenting clock-like regularity. Simply sandwich the stars between Kirby's pals and you'll soon be on your way to the high score.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kirby's Star Stacker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19970401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman II.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man II</name>
		<desc>The demented Dr. Wily is at it again! This time he's stolen the experimental Time Skimmer and skipped into the future. But Wait! Four of his strongest cyborgs have been left behind to squash the mighty Mega Man!

Time is of the essence as Mega Man and Rush blast past waves of maniacal metal monsters on the way to underground lair of Dr. Wily. Once there they must face Quint, the ferocious fiend from the future!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Biox</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman III.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man III</name>
		<desc>Battle at the Center of the Earth!

That sinister scientist Dr. Wily is at it again! Now, he and his renegade robots have purloined an off-shore oil rig and are drilling through the Earth's crust. It's up to Mega Man to shut down their scheme before Wily can harness the molten power of the Earth's core to fuel his latest metallic monstrosity!

Join Rush, Flip-Top and Mega Man as they battle wave after wave of mechanical maniacs as they search through Wily's fiendish fortress. Battle Snake Man, Spark Man, and six other robot masters as you near Wily's lair. Sneak inside and summon the power of the Mega Buster as you face the awesome power of Wily's ultimate creation!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman IV.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man IV</name>
		<desc>A huge celebration at the World Robot Expo is shattered by the sight of a flying saucer streaking across the sky. But instead of holding little green men, this saucer holds one very mad scientist! Armed with a mind control machine that transmits a sinister signal. Dr. Wily is ready to mesmerize all the robots of the city into an army of mindless metallic mercenaries!

Battling the effects of Wily's mind control machine, Mega Man and his robotic reenforcements, Rush and Beat must blast to molten metal an army of foes led by eight of Wily's greatest robot masters! And should Mega Man survive, Dr. Wily is waiting to unleash the heavy artillery with his latest creation, the awesome Wily Tank!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman V.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man V</name>
		<desc>They came from outer space!

From the cosmic reaches of outer space, comes mankind's greatest threat. Hordes of alien robots have swarmed down from the heavens all the Earth's weapons are powerless to stop their ravenous rampage. Now the only hope to stop these alien invaders lies with one man - Mega Man!

Blast off for new worlds of excitement as Mega Man launches an all-out attack on the alien armada! Rocket into battle and dodge the deadly rings of SATURN and face the molten menace of MERCURY! Search the galaxy for alien gems and construct the ultimate "Mega Arm" weapon and blast these invaders all the way back to Alpha Centauri!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman V-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man: Dr. Wily's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Dr. Wily's most challenging robot masters will be there when you pump up the GameBoy. And knowing the maniac he is, he's probably concocted a new one or two. Can you survive the eight empires before you break into Dr. Wily's lab? Well, if you experienced MegaMan before, you know it's no day at the beach. But good reason to get going on MegaMan in Dr. Wily's Revenge. Now.

* When the stompin' cyclops springs into action, you better step on it.
* The swooping copterheads just might be your greatest challenge yet.
* If the giant fan is blowing, only a ledge-jump will save you from the spikes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Megaman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid II - Return of Samus.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid II: Return of Samus</name>
		<desc>A Sinister Planet Threatens the Galaxy!

Space Hunter Samus Aran returns to battle a planet crawling with evil creatures bent on universal domination in this bigger than ever sequel to the NES classic, Metroid.

Take control! Guide Samus through cavernous corridors, ancient ruins and alien traps. On the mysterious planet of the Metroids, you'll find artifacts of a lost civilization that grant amazing powers. Cut through creatures in a buzz-saw blur! Roll through hidden tunnels and climb sheer walls!

A battery back-up allows you to save your progress as you fight to the heart of the planet and search for the merciless Metroid leaders. If you are a cunning explorer, you'll earn the best of several super endings.

Enter this exciting Metroid sequel and experience the thrills of Game Boy like never before!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Metroid II - Return of Samus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mole Mania.zip</path>
		<name>Mole Mania</name>
		<desc>Join Muddy Mole in a race to destroy enemies and obstacles in an attempt to defeat the evil farmer, Jinbei. Blast strategic exits using black balls and tunnel your way to the next action-packed level. Help Muddy solve the incredible puzzles of Jinbei Land and reunite him with his beloved mole family. You'll dig the fast pace and challenging fun of Mole Mania!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mole Mania-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pax Softonica</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Operation C.zip</path>
		<name>Operation C</name>
		<desc>Operation C is an Action game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Operation C-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land</name>
		<desc>Journey with Mario to a land of giant crabs, Koopa Troopas, flying stone heads and hungry sharks!

Travel over land, in the air, and underwater. Mario makes his way through four treacherous worlds on his way to save the Princess!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Super Mario Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76</rating>
		<releasedate>19890421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins</name>
		<desc>In his greatest Game Boy adventure, Mario faces off against his evil rival Wario, who has captured Mario Land and turned it into his private playground.

To toss Wario off his ill-gotten throne, Mario must search all-new worlds for the six golden coins that unlock the gate to Mario's castle. A mob of monsters, old and new, seek to stop him. Along the way, through 6 zones, Mario can nab Power Mushrooms, Super Stars and Fire Flowers for extra power. And if he eats the Magic Carrot, he'll turn into a high-flying hare.

The battery pack saves your game in progress in this biggest Game Boy Mario adventure yet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.84444</rating>
		<releasedate>19921021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT III - Radical Rescue.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III: Radical Rescue</name>
		<desc>The whole sewer crew, except Michaelangelo, is captured in a most heinous hideout. Who could be behind this travesty? Who else. Shredder has returned as Cyber Shredder - half-man, half-machine and he‘s created this twisty-turny fun house" of Turtle torture. Use Turtle strategy and all new moves to help Michaelangelo rescue the gang from Cyber Shredder's Fortress.

-The Turtles are sporting some radical new maneuvers. Call on each unique skill to overcome specific obstacles. It helps to round up your scrambled cohorts in a certain order.

-Michaelangelo has helicopter hang time, Leonardo dusts concrete blocks, Raphael shells through tight spots and Donatello scales sheer walls.

-Fight through 5 rescue adventures. You'll need keen Turtle sense and all the pizza power you can scarf up to make It past bats, goons and hordes of robotic maniacs.

-Use the Fortress Map to navigate through places unseen and find valuable Items such as power ups, ID cards, keys an shanghaied Shell Backs.

-Who's the Boss you ask? How about Scratch, Dirtbag, Triceraton, Scale Tail and of course Cyber Shredder, as Turtle-hungry as they get.

-The Password feature lets you pick up your mission from the last Boss Beast you annihilated.

-To make it out of Shredder’s maze of mayhem, you'll need to be as sharp as a sai sword and as tough as a team of sumo wrestlers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/TMNT III - Radical Rescue-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>Tetris is a puzzle video game which was released in 1989 by Nintendo for the Game Boy. Geometric shapes fall from the top of a playfield to rest on the bottom; fit the pieces together and the formed line will disappear. If the pieces are not lined up correctly they eventually stack up to the top of the playfield and the game is over. Difficulty increases by dropping the pieces faster and faster over time. Tetris is a verifiable classic game, translated to well over 200 electronic and computer platforms. It takes 2 minutes to learn, but a lifetime to master!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9125</rating>
		<releasedate>19890614T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Attack.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris Attack</name>
		<desc>In Tetris Attack, the player is presented with a playfield consisting of a virtual grid of squares, each of which can be occupied by a block. Blocks are stacked on top of one another and rise steadily toward the top of the playfield, with new blocks being added at the bottom. The player must arrange blocks in horizontal or vertical lines of three or more matching shapes by swapping blocks horizontally two at a time. As matching lines are formed, the blocks are cleared from the screen and any blocks above them fall into the gaps. The game is over when the blocks touch the top of the playfield, or another game-ending condition is met (such as reaching a time limit or clearing blocks below a set line). Clearing more than three tiles in a single move scores a Combo, while Chains are scored when falling blocks from one clear cause another clear to occur. Both of these events score extra bonus points, and in multiplayer Versus games, these also send "garbage blocks" to the other player's playfield.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris Attack-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - King Rock Treasure Island.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones: King Rock Treasure Island</name>
		<desc>The Flintstones: King Rock Treasure Island is an Action game, developed and published by Taito Corporation, which was released in 1993.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Flintstones, The - King Rock Treasure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Babs' Big Break.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Babs' Big Break</name>
		<desc>BABS MAY BE A TOUGH ACT TO FOLLOW, BUT CATCHING UP WITH HER IS EVEN TOUGHER!

Babs dreams of making It BIG in the BIG City as a BIG Star. She slips away on an adventurous downtown journey to the Acme Theater. Montana Max wants to turn the theater into a spectacular safe to show off his money. so he's out to bring the curtain down on Babs. Yikes! It’s all up to Buster Bunny, Plucky Duck and Hamton to catch our favorite rising star before Monty catches her first! Join the zaniest star search to hit the Game Boy screen and see Babs in her most thrilling role yet. Here's what the fans have to say.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tiny Toon Adventures - Babs' Big Break-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trip World.zip</path>
		<name>Trip World</name>
		<desc>In the early 1990s Sunsoft was at its best, developing many fine platformers, several of which were even licensed properties. Its Batman games were almost all excellent, especially the Game Boy release, which combined Mario-style platforms and blockbusting with gunplay. Much of Sunsoft's NES catalogue is also fondly remembered, with titles such as Blaster Master, Journey to Silius and, despite its obscene difficulty, Mr. Gimmick / Gimmick! to name a few. Trip World for the Game Boy is another Sunsoft goodie, regularly featuring on lists for obscure or overlooked games and, in the US at least, lists for import exclusives. Released only in Japan and Europe in small quantities, a boxed copy of the original cartridge now sells for ludicrously high prices. At the time of writing, two unboxed copies were on eBay for around £115 / $180; Yahoo! Auctions Japan had nothing.

Trip World at first appears to be like any conventional platformer – perhaps a little too conventional. There's an intro showing the Maita Flower from atop Mount Dubious being stolen from an elderly Shabubu who is also kidnapped (a bunny-like creature not to be confused with the culinary shabu-shabu dish). Cue the old creature's grandson, Yacopu, to venture out, save his grandfather and retrieve the flower, thereby bringing peace back to the world. Players move across the screen, avoiding spike pits, jumping along collapsing platforms, and karate kicking enemies... Except the enemies don't seem to fight back. Very few of them in fact cause any damage at all, with only the bosses posing a genuine threat. Apart from the harmless enemies, it's all very standard. Yacopu can collect fruit items which imbue him with special powers: the ability to fire paralysing seeds that sprout from the skulls of enemies; a bouncy ball power-up; and a third which allows him to attack with his tail. These powers are timed and soon wear off, but in some stages it's possible to collect an additional power-up which, when combined with the first, grants something entirely new. The best of which causes Yacopu to sprout legs and gain the ability to fire instant-death projectiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Trip World-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land II.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land II</name>
		<desc>What kind of no-good ruffians would break into my castle and steal my treasures?! It's that rotten Captain Syrup and that Black Sugar Gang! I'm looking out for bad guys and scavenging for coins as I track down my treasures. If I don't get them all the first time, that's OK. I can go back again and again until I find them all. Captain Syrup doesn't stand a chance against me!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Wario Land II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land - Super Mario Land 3.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land: Super Mario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Hey! Things are really cookin' on Kitchen Island! Wario's got a scheme to steal the pirates' treasure so he can have his very own castle! You help Wario get the treasure by smashing into the the magic pots! Each pot changes him into Dragon Wario, Bull Wario, or Jet Wario! With each change comes new powers!

Dozens of enemies try to stop Wario, but you have the power to beat them!

Be the bad guy!

Explore the many exciting levels of Kitchen Island!

Battery-backed memory saves your progress for many hours of fun!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Wario Land - Super Mario Land 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8099999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19940121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<desc>Yoshi's Cookie is a fast-paced puzzle game. The player moves randomly placed cookies into rows and columns of cookies with similar patterns. When a row or column of the same cookies is successfully assembled, the line will disappear, and the player can begin to work on a new row or column. The "Yoshi" cookie is very special in both the 1-player and the 2-player game. Since this cookie is the key to both games, it should be used wisely.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Yoshi's Cookie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania II - Belmont's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II: Belmont's Revenge</name>
		<desc>Fifteen years after vanquishing the emperor of evil, Count Dracula, Christopher Belmont now faces a vampire swearing vengeance. Drac's back. And he's turned your son, Soleiyu Belmont, into a deadly demon to do his dirty deeds. Now not only do you have to rescue your kid from the Count's clutches, you have to first track him down in four creep packed Castles. Fortunately, you posses weapons like armor piercing Battle Axes, beast burning Holy Water, and the Legendary Mystic Whip. And you can increase your arsenal with power up items like Crystal Balls, Hearts, and Candles. Strap on your shield and step into the shadows. That is, if you're prepared for the dwellers of darkness.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania II - Belmont's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T020505</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Adventure, The.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: The Adventure</name>
		<desc>Castlevania: The Adventure, known as Dracula Densetsu (officially translated The Legend of Dracula) in Japan, is a platform game released for the Game Boy in 1989. It is the first Castlevania title for the system.

Set a century before the events of the original Castlevania, the player controls an ancestor of Simon Belmont named Christopher Belmont who goes on a quest to defeat Dracula.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Castlevania Adventure, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19891203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054138</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Land is a Jump &amp; Run classic, developed by Rareware and released by Nintendo for the Game Boy in June 1995.

Cranky Kong, jealous of all the success Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong have had from Donkey Kong Country on the SNES, challenges the Kongs to beat another adventure on an 8-bit system (Game Boy). As King K. Rool agrees with Cranky and steals the bananas again, Donkey &amp; Diddy Kong set out to go throuth another adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Donkey Kong Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044246</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerin' Harry - Ghost Building Company.zip</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Harry: Ghost Building Company</name>
		<desc>Harry and his spouse were walking down the street, while all of a sudden,
ghosts start to appear and the city gets demolished. A dark city, with a
haunted mansion in the middle, rises from the rumble and four ghost fuse to
become a large ghost and kidnaps Harry's spouse. You must save your spouse and
stop the evil Ghost Building Company.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Hammerin' Harry - Ghost Building Company-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tamtex</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Montana's Movie Madness.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures 2: Montana's Movie Madness</name>
		<desc>Here comes Montana Max the meanest movie maker to ever tarnish the silver screen. He's directed four new flicks that make Buster Bunny look like a villain! To defend his character Buster Bunny must leap into Max's movies and use attack moves like fast dash and freeze kick to change the endings before his career is finished.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tiny Toon Adventures - Montana's Movie Madness-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>In the South Pacific, Master Higgins lives peacefully wearing only a grass skirt and a cap. That is until the Evil Witch Doctor decides to capture the Princess Leilani and hold her as his own. It's up to Master Higgins to gather throwing axes, fireballs and skateboards in order to aid his noble quest.

The game is a side scroller, Master Higgins moves across the screen from left to right and finds his power-ups in giant eggs. This includes a skateboard which results in a great speed enhancement - until Master Higgins gets hit and loses his power. If he is not on a skateboard a hit means instant death. Another game mechanic is starvation which gets indicated through a meter which steadily decreases. If it hits zero the hero dies and the only way to fill it up is by collecting food on the way. Bosses await him at the end of levels, all the way to the Evil Witch Doctor himself.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Adventure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>13</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T153401</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery.zip</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery</name>
		<desc>Original and updated versions of four Game &amp; Watch hand held games!

Classic versions will take you back to the '80s and a simpler time in video games. Modern versions feature your favorite characters and will bring you to the present with improved play control and sound effects.

-Enjoy four different games!
Manhole - Don't let pedestrians fall.
Fire - Rescue the jumpers.
Octopus - Retrive the sunken treasure.
Oil Panic - Catch the dripping oil.

-New Interrupt Save feature lets you stop and restart anytime!

-Battery-backed memory saves all your scores!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Game &amp; Watch Gallery-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T033032</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Link's Awakening</name>
		<desc>A Game Boy fantasy adventure like no other!

Nintendo's fantasy adventure hero, Link of Hyrule, returns in this new epic quest...Link's Awakening. Link's newest challenge is set on the mysterious Koholint Island, a place where dreams and reality collide. As a castaway, Link must find a way to escape from the island and return to his beloved homeland of Hyrule.

But it won't be as easy as chartering a boat. The island's inhabitants have no knowledge of the outside world. One creature, a talking Owl, may know the solution to Link's dilemma, but first Link must tackle eight dungeons full of treacherous monsters and tricky taps. His goal: find the eight Instruments of the Sirens and awaken the omnipotent Wind Fish which rules the island.

Link will battle new enemies and make new friends in one of the most in-depth fantasy adventures for Game Boy yet!

A battery-backed memory will save up to three games so you never have to start your journey empty-handed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19930606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170307T230057</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Animated Series.zip</path>
		<name>Batman: The Animated Series</name>
		<desc>FROM TV SCREEN TO GAME BOY SCREEN COMES HEROIC CRIME FIGHTING ADVENTURE.

Everyone's tuning in to Batman - The Animated Series. Now, for the first time, this hit TV series becomes an intense video game adventure. The Dark Knight and his partner Robin fight Gotham City's most infamous fiends in five original episodes of sizzling crime fighting action. Batman's strategic use of the grappling hook is crucial for surviving the onslaught of evil enemies. And Robin relies on his hang-from-the-ceiling skills to escape certain doom. Both of our heroes possess fists of amazing strength and must try to find weapon power-ups scattered throughout the mayhem.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Batman - The Animated Series-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Arena Toshinden.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Arena Toshinden</name>
		<desc>Get Ready To Rumble!

The Toshin Daibukai tournament has arrived. Ten of the toughest fighters in the world are taking part in the most grueling slugfest known to man. To win, each combatant must be completely focused. One slip and their fate is sealed. Who will be crowned the champion? That is up to you. So get off your duff and get ready for the fight of your life with Battle Arena Toshinden!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battle Arena Toshinden-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19961231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Betop</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Pingpong.zip</path>
		<name>Battle PingPong</name>
		<desc>Battle Ping-Pong is a Game Boy game revolving around ping-pong (or table
tennis as it is generically called). One person on either side of a small table
with a net return a ball back and forth in a rally until the ball is either dead
in play or bounces off the table.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battle Pingpong-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>’TOAD-NAPPED!

While partying on Lost Vega, a deep-space leisure station, the three Battletoads—Zitz, Rash and Pimple—get pleasantly side-tracked by a Thallian Thorax Dancer. Unfortunately, the dancer soon reveals herself as the evil Dark Queen! The ‘toads fight valiantly against overwhelming odds, but are eventually overpowered. Rash and Pimple are taken prisoner, but luckily, Zitz makes it to the Toadster and burns space back to the Vulture and the Battletoads’ mentor, Professor T. Bird. So, Zitz, the Dark Queen’s ‘toadnapped your best buddies—what’re you gonna do about it? You’re gonna get real MAD, that’s what—then you’re gonna get EVEN! Once you get to Armagedda, the Dark Queen’s planet, you’ve got a long way to go—into caverns, across swamps and even through the belly of the dreaded Wurm. And ultimately, you’re gonna have to defeat the terrible, the towering, the truly ’toadsplatting Robo-Manus mutant! Have you got what it takes to be a bonafide Battletoad? We’ll soon see, one way or another…</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battletoads-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads Double Dragon - The Ultimate Team.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>The Ultimate Team!

When a battle cruiser the size of a city and called the Colossus smashes out of the moon, its laser cannon glowing menacingly, you can bet it ain’t gonna be makin’ no social calls…

You can bet it’s gonna be creating some bad n’ crazy mayhem on good ol’ planet Earth- ‘specially when you know that the dreaded Dark Queen and the shady Shadow Boss are on board just rarin’ to rock n’ roll…

The dastardly duo are about to unleash their most monstrous plan yet- from their secret lunar base they intend to launch an invasion that’ll make them master of the world…

Neutralized by deadly glooming rays, Earth’s forces are powerless… that is until the Dragons join the ‘Toads!

Take a toadacious trip with the dream ticket as those terrific twins Billy and Jimmy Lee team up with Zitz, Rash and Pimple against the combined might of the gruesome twosome and their mindless minions, Big Blag, Abobo, Robo-Manus and Roper, in a toadally terminal new adventure!

So let’s get mad, bad n’ crazy once again as the BATTLETOADS join DOUBLE DRAGON in THE ULTIMATE TEAM!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Battletoads Double Dragon - The Ultimate Team-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commando.zip</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando</name>
		<desc>SWING INTO ACTION AGAINST THE FORCES OF EVIL!

A ruthless army stands ready for war and the one man who can stop it has disappeared. Now, in a desperate fight for survival, the world tums to an elite group of men and women to put an end to the threat. More than simple soldiers, they are the Bionic Commandoes. Drop behind the lines with Rad Spencer as he infiltrates the Doraize military stronghold. Blast your way through enemy lines with your assault rifle and gather the information needed to rescue Super Joe. Tap enemy communications to
learn the dark secrets of director Wiseman and then come face to face with the awesome might of his mysterious Albatross Project!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bionic Commando-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Revenge</name>
		<desc>In the Game Boy version of this title, Bonk can turn into one of three unique heroes: Master Bonk, Hungry Bonk, or Stealth Bonk. Becoming Master Bonk dresses Bonk in a cape and provides him with Vulcan-esque ears, and gives him the ability to move faster and jump higher. Becoming Hungry Bonk gives Bonk an animalistic appearance with evil eyes and a mouth full of razor-sharp teeth, and gives bonk the ability to chew enemies to death, as well as providing him with a much stronger head-butt that can kill nearby foes. Becoming Stealth Bonk dresses Bonk in a striped jail outfit, and gives him the ability to enter special locked doors that lead to areas such as the bank, where Bonk can collect Smileys, the butcher's, where Bonk can eat more slabs of meat in hope for a different power-up, and jail, where Bonk loses a portion of his Smileys.

Grabbing one of many tulips scattered throughout the game carries Bonk to a special bonus stage where he can face off against Mechabonk -- a RoboCop-esque version of Bonk—in a best-of-three battle to "bonk" one another off the edge of a small stage. Winning two rounds provides Bonk with an extra life, while a loss transforms Bonk into Wounded Bonk, where Bonk resembles a mummy and takes twice as much damage as usual.

The game overall is very similar to games in the Mario series, providing linear, side-scrolling action, multiple power-ups, and several small boss confrontations leading up to a final boss. Its treatment of power-ups is similar as well: taking a hit while powered-up causes Bonk to take no damage but instead lose his power. For those who struggle with the game, the game offers passwords after game-overs so the player does not need to start over from the beginning.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bonk's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson, NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition.zip</path>
		<name>Bust-a-Move 2: Arcade Edition</name>
		<desc>Bust-A-Move 2 is a puzzle game that involves clearing or "popping" groups of bubbles by creating matches of three or more. A pointing device at the bottom of the screen is used to aim and launch a randomly generated bubble toward others of the same shade or pattern. Since launched bubbles can ricochet off walls, the challenge comes from estimating the angle you'll need to create potential matches. Clear each stage before the ceiling reaches the screen's bottom and you'll safely advance. The Game Boy version offers three play modes and a password save feature. You can challenge a series of 13 computer opponents, complete 100 puzzle levels, and race to clear 50 screens with the time attack option.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move 3 DX.zip</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move 3 DX</name>
		<desc>Bust-A-Move 3 DX is the same game as Bust-A-Move '99. Besides the obvious differences because of technical limitations of the platform, e.g. the bubbles have to differentiated from of their shades instead of colour, it also has less playing modes. Only the arcade mode (a port of the original arcade version with the main singleplayer campaign or the possibility to challenge an AI opponent) and the challenge mode (beating a series of 25 levels as fast as possible) are available. 

Regarding gameplay, this is a tile matching game. There are bubbles of varying shades at the top of the screen and the player controls a stationary cannon at the bottom of the screen. The cannon is loaded with one bubble at the time and the direction of the shot can be varied left and right. The goal is to clear the screen by matching bubbles of the same colour.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Bust-A-Move 3 DX-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daffy Duck - The Marvin Missions.zip</path>
		<name>Daffy Duck: The Marvin Missions</name>
		<desc>Shrinking rays and crushing platforms are commonly seen as the player tries to kill Martians that are standing in the way along with rock monsters and dragons. Lava won't instantly kill the player's character but falling into a bottomless pit will. In the end, Marvin the Martian must be destroyed in the final stage of the game.

The Game Boy version includes a secret "hard" difficulty level. Losing in this difficulty level will simply reset the game instead of bringing up the game over screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Daffy Duck - The Marvin Missions-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkwing Duck.zip</path>
		<name>Darkwing Duck</name>
		<desc>The kingpins of crime are at it again! The mysterious criminal organization F.O.W.L. has hatched a plan to take control of the peaceful city of St. Canard. Six of their most heinous henchmen are running rampant through the city and only the daring Darkwing Duck can bring them to justice. Join Darkwing as he explores the woods to weed out Bushroot's evil plan. Search the warehouses along the wharf for Mega Volt and pull the plug on an electrifying scheme. Track down all six of F.O.W.L.'s crafty criminals and then prepare yourself as Darkwing squares off against the sinister Steelbeak in his fiendish floating fortress!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Darkwing Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dexterity.zip</path>
		<name>Dexterity</name>
		<desc>A game that consists of a square floor covered in seven rows and eight columns of tiles (56 tiles in total). The goal of the game is to flip all of the light tiles into dark tiles. There are several enemies as the level advances. The game has a total of 30 rounds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Dexterity-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers who learned to fight on the cold, tough streets of the city. Their expert knowledge of the martial arts combined with their street smarts, has made them both formidable fighting machines. But now Billy is faced with his greatest challenge. Marian has been kidnapped by the Black Warriors, the savage street gang of the mysterious Shadow Boss! Using whatever weapons come to hand - knives, whips, bats, rocks, oil drums, even dynamite - Billy must pursue the gang through the slums, factories, and wooded outskirts of the city to reach the hideout for his final confrontation with the Shadow Boss... his brother Jimmy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Double Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon II.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon II</name>
		<desc>Billy and Jimmy Lee, the Double Dragons, are back to avenge the loss of Marion. In their quest to defeat the evil Shadow Warriors, Billy and Jimmy must complete nine missions, facing deadly street gangs, ninjas and huge mutant fighters. The duo must traverse through construction sites, alleyways and underwater hideouts complete with secret elevator shafts, spiked ceilings and razor-sharp mechanical claws. Can Billy and Jimmy contend with the enemies placed before them and ultimately save the world?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Double Dragon II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario.zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario</name>
		<desc>It's Dr. Mario for an intense new challenge! Mario throws multi-shaded vitamin capsules into a bottle that contains an ugly variety of nasty viruses. You can move, shift or spin the capsules as they fall. Arrange them to align with other capsules on top of a virus. If you can get 4 or more of the same shade in a row, POOF! They disappear! Destroy all of the viruses in the bottle and you progress to the next round where things get even more difficult. Dr. Mario, with germs that are fun to catch.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Dr. Mario-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales.zip</path>
		<name>DuckTales</name>
		<desc>DuckTales (わんぱくダック夢冒険 Wanpaku Dakku Yume Bōken?, lit. "Naughty Ducks Dream Adventures") is an action platformer video game developed and published by Capcom and based on the Disney animated TV series of the same name. It was first released in North America for the Nintendo Entertainment System in 1989 and was later ported to the Game Boy in 1990. The story involves Scrooge McDuck traveling around the globe collecting treasure and outwitting his rival Flintheart Glomgold to become the world's richest duck.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Duck Tales-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales 2.zip</path>
		<name>DuckTales 2</name>
		<desc>Huey runs to his uncle Scrooge McDuck with a torn piece of paper, which is actually a piece of a treasure map drawn by Fergus McDuck. Inspired to discover the hidden treasure left by Fergus, Scrooge starts an expedition to find the missing pieces, unaware that his rival Flintheart Glomgold is also after the lost treasure of McDuck.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Duck Tales 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Felix the Cat.zip</path>
		<name>Felix the Cat</name>
		<desc>The game involves the player controlling Felix the Cat as he sets out to defeat the evil mad Professor who has kidnapped Felix's lovely girlfriend, Kitty. The Game Boy version plays virtually the same as the NES version, but features fewer levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Felix the Cat-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soccer.zip</path>
		<name>Soccer</name>
		<desc>Soccer is a Sports game, developed by TOSE and published by Tonkin House, which was released in Japan 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Soccer-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose</developer>
		<publisher>Tonkin House</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetsons, The - Robot Panic.zip</path>
		<name>Jetsons: Robot Panic</name>
		<desc>Robots have attacked Orbit City and only George Jetson can stop them. With the help of his family, George will navigate through multiple levels filled with robots and hazards. Ultimately, he will have to defeat the robot leader to save the day in THE JETSONS: Robot Panic.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Jetsons, The - Robot Panic-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Act Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jungle Book, The.zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Jungle Book</name>
		<desc>Get down to the bare necessities of life... and escort Mowgli through the jungle to the safety of the human village. Fight the boggle-eyed snake, Kaa, and defeat Shere Khan the hungry tiger in this exciting adventure based on Disney's classic! It'll drive you ape crazy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Jungle Book, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park Part 2: The Chaos Continues</name>
		<desc>A year has passed. No one has set foot in Jurassic Park... until now. 

As Dr. Grant, you'll venture back to the island, where more dinosaurs than you could ever imagine await your return - including terrifying  new species you never seen before!

Only you have the power to send these prehistoric monsters back where they came from.

Only you can close the doors on Jurassic Park... for another 65 million years!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19941209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Icarus - Of Myths and Monsters.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Icarus: Of Myths and Monsters</name>
		<desc>A lighthearted adventure with mythical challenges. The "8-bit Summer" series continues with this classic action game from 1991. Angel Land is up to its halos in woes as mythical monsters are running rampant. Pit, the original Kid Icarus, must save the realm again. Armed with his trusty bow, he'll zap the bad guys and find the Three Sacred Treasures hidden by Palutena. Only after this grueling training will he be strong enough to take on the dark forces behind Angel Land's troubles. Pit will encounter old friends and new enemies - from helpful Centurions to the dreaded Eggplant Wizard - as he journeys from the depths of the underworld to the towers of the sky palace. Find hammers to shatter special walls and reveal helpful items. Collect hearts by fighting off Pit's foes. Train hard and battle harder. Pit's challenges make the labors of Hercules look like a walk in the park.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Kid Icarus - Of Myths and Monsters-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Krusty's Fun House.zip</path>
		<name>Krusty's Fun House</name>
		<desc>Hey, kids! Give a hoot! Help out your old pal Krusty the Clown! My official Krusty's Fun House is infested with rats! There are over 60 levels in this game, and they're all crawling with the little varmints! I've got my loyal cadets, Bart and Homer Simpson, Sideshow Mel, and Corporal Punishment to guard the rat traps, but I need you to lead the filthy rodents into those traps! Then we blow 'em up! We incinerate 'em! We laser-blast 'em! We electrocute 'em! We Krusterize the little stinkers! Hoo boy! Did I mention the snakes, aliens and flying pigs? Well, watch out for those riffraff! If you can't Krusterize 'em, at least avoid 'em... they're worse than the #@!*%! rats! Making Krusty's Fun House vermin-free is not a pretty task, kiddy cadets - but someone's gotta do it!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Krusty's Fun House-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Audiogenic Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes.zip</path>
		<name>Looney Tunes</name>
		<desc>This side-scrolling game allows the player to control different Looney Tunes characters and their different abilities to advance through the levels, seven in all. The player can use Daffy Duck (throwing a frisbee to defeat enemies with Mario-style gameplay), Tweety Bird (elude Sylvester throughout the level), Porky Pig (control a bi-plane to shoot down enemies), Taz (really only a bonus game in which he has to collect as many steaks as possible in 60 seconds), Speedy Gonzalez (elude ghosts and ghouls in a haunted mansion), Roadrunner (of course running from his arch enemy, Wile E. Coyote) and finally Bugs Bunny (gameplay similar to Daffy).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Looney Tunes-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SunSoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sun Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost World, The - Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>The Lost World: Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>SOMETHING HAS SURVIVED...

on the mysterious Isla Sorna, and it's your job to find out exactly what. You must infiltrate the island, collect vital information and thwart the efforts of the evil BioSyn team. A difficult enough task if the island wasn't infested with man-eating dinosaurs! Welcome to The Lost World: Jurassic Park, the largest adventure you'll ever fit in your pocket!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Lost World, The - Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>T*HQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mercenary Force.zip</path>
		<name>Mercenary Force</name>
		<desc>Over one hundred years ago during the mighty Shogun era, the Lord of Darkness sent his fearsome army to terrorize the Japanese countryside. Using the Dark Lord's powerful magic, his evil minions spread famine, plague, and pestilence wherever they went, leaving the peaceful population hopelessly oppressed. All who challenged the wicked Lord were mercilessly slain as a warning to all those who had any further thoughts of rebellion. Then one day while meditating, the great Shogun, Tokugawa, had a divine vision where he saw a small group of mighty warriors rise up to defeat the evil Lord. He immediately set out to recruit the five bravest and most skillful fighters in the land. After months of searching he was finally ready to put his dream into action. It was time to unleash the Mercenary Force.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mercenary Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Meldac</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mouse</name>
		<desc>The Great, Exciting Adventures of the World's Super Idol Mickey Mouse

Mickey Mouse's Great Adventures begin in Arbarus Castle! Rescue Mickey’s beloved girlfriend Minnie Mouse by defeating his hilarious enemies and by safely passing through the dangerous traps. A useful continue function lets you play with Mickey for an extended period of time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey Mouse-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse - Magic Wand.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mouse: Magic Wands</name>
		<desc>A great adventure with Magic Wands!
Hurry and rescue your friends from the wicked witch's castle!

Mickey Mouse and his friends have become lost while playing near the edge of the forest. Mickey's friends have been trapped in Yashja the wicked witch's castle. Hurry and rescue your friends, Mickey! Take the Magic Wands and begin your great adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey Mouse - Magic Wand-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse IV.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mouse IV: The Magical Labyrinth</name>
		<desc>It's the mouse everyone loves! Mickey must figure out the puzzle to escape. Help him fight enemies and solve the labyrinth's magical mystery!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey Mouse IV-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey's Chase.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey's Dangerous Chase</name>
		<desc>Mickey Goes After a Missing Present and the Culprit Who Swiped It!

Who's got Minnie's missing present? Big Bad Pete is the culprit! He swiped Minnie's present and spoiled the surprise. Now Mickey's after him, and the chase leads through some very dangerous places. Mickey meets barking bulldogs, slippery weasels, hairy tarantulas, and even worse critters. Tricks, traps, and collapsing escape routes make Mickey scurry. He scampers through his Hometown, into the Woods and up the Mountain. He chases Pete through a Factory and up to the Rooftops for a final showdown. Can you help Mickey stop Pete and get the missing present back? Better hurry!

-Mickey throws boxes at the bad guys while grabbing Stars and Prizes.

-A speedboat, jalopy, and bouquet of balloons add high fun to Mickey's chase.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey's Chase-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey's Ultimate Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey's Ultimate Challenge</name>
		<desc>Five Magical Puzzles
Full Of Family Fun!

"The sky is rumbling!
The sky is rumbling! What ever can it be?" cry the citizens of Beanwick.

"Is it a storm? Is it a monster? Is it the end of the Kingdom?" I don't know, but I'll find out, says Mickey, "if I have to search every room in the Castle of Beanwick to solve the mystery!"

In Mickey's Ultimate Challenge, volunteer as Mickey or Minnie to help the Kingdom of Beanwick solve the mystery of the rumblings in the sky. But, first you must prove worthy of the challenge--by thinking your way through a series of fiendishly clever puzzles, players from 4 to 104 can take full advantage of the game's interactive capabilities to put their critical thinking skills to the ultimate test. Five incredible locations!

Five brain-teasing challenges starring many of your favorite Disney characters. Solve them all for a chance to see what's really up, up there!

Is this all a dream? Play Mickey's Ultimate Challenge and decide for yourself!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey's Ultimate Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Designer Software</developer>
		<publisher>Hi Tech Expressions</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>Nothing, NOTHING can prepare you! The fierce kombatants of the #1 arcade smash gather for Mortal Kombat II, a battle to defeat the shape-shifting demon Shang Tsung and his ruthless master, Shao Kahn. Brutal special moves, Babalities, hidden surprises, outrageous finishing moves -- ALL yours to kommand. Let the Kombat Kontinue...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mortal Kombat II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nettou The King of Fighters '96.zip</path>
		<name>The King of Fighters: Heat of Battle</name>
		<desc>The battle of the dream teams '96 - READY! 27 of SNK's top fighting heroes face off for fisticuffs! Only King of Fighters lets you combine your favorite characters in exciting teams. Try out endless combinations and bop your way to the top with the toughest team of all! Over 2,900 possible team combinations using the Team Edit Function. It's too much!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Nettou The King of Fighters '96-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takara</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Chessmaster, The.zip</path>
		<name>The New Chessmaster</name>
		<desc>Say goodbye to lost pieces and slow opponents. THE NEW CHESSMASTER lets you play in one of 16 different skill levels from Newcomer to Grandmaster. A Teaching mode allows you to examine all possible moves more easily, letting you play out then reverse any scenario. You can pause your game anytime and return later without having to set up the board all over again. Play against the computer or a human adversary in the most inclusive chess package ever. Whether you're looking for a chess companion, a well-suited opponent, or a friendly instructor, THE NEW CHESSMASTER is the perfect solution.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/New Chessmaster, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Altron</developer>
		<publisher>Altron</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gain Shadow.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden Shadow</name>
		<desc>When a madman threatens to take over the entire world, our beloved hero Ryu must travel the globe to get to New York. Once he gets there, there are hazards and enemies hiding in each and every nook and cranny. If you think the "Big Apple" is dangerous in real life, you'll be amazed at the depths of evil employed by the big-city villains in this escapade. You'll have to hack, slash, and kick your way through the streets and all the way to one of the most dangerous bosses in videogame history. Another installment in the ongoing Ninja Gaiden series, Ninja Gaiden Shadow boasts intense graphics, a great storyline, and smooth gameplay. The world could really use a hero, and if you've got the skills and know-how, you could be it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Ninja Gain Shadow-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocket Bomberman.zip</path>
		<name>Pocket Bomberman</name>
		<desc>Pocket Bomberman (ポケットボンバーマン Poketto Bonbāman?) is a platforming action game first released for the Game Boy in 1997, and later as a launch title for the Game Boy Color in 1998.

Pocket Bomberman features gameplay that revolves around using bombs to box in enemies and blowing them to bits. Once all enemies are defeated, Bomberman has to go to the door at the end of the stage to complete the level. There is a total of 5 worlds and 25 levels. These worlds include a jungle world, an ocean world, a wind world, a cloud world, and a world with the name of "Evil". Each world has a boss fight at the end in which Bomberman must expose the boss's weak points and bomb the boss until it has no health left.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pocket Bomberman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Blue Version.zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Blue Version</name>
		<desc>You’ve finally been granted your Pokémon trainer’s license.  Now, it’s time to head out to become the world’s greatest Pokémon trainer.  It’s going to take all you’ve got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world.  Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu.  Face off against Blastoise’s torrential water cannons.  Stand strong when facing Pidgeot’s stormy Gust.  Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve.  Important - no single Pokémon can win it all.  Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?

* Collect up to 139 different Pokémon playing the Blue version.  Using the Game Link cable, trade with a friend who has the Red version to capture all 150.
* You’ll need to use both versions (Red and Blue) to collect all of the Pokémon.
* Test your training skills by battling against a friend using the Game Link cable.
* Save your Pokémon and game progress on the Game Pak memory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pokemon - Blue Version-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Red Version.zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Red Version</name>
		<desc>You’ve finally been granted your Pokémon trainer’s license.  Now, it’s time to head out to become the world’s greatest Pokémon trainer.  It’s going to take all you’ve got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world.  Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu.  Face off against Blastoise’s torrential water cannons.  Stand strong when facing Pidgeot’s stormy Gust.  Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve.  Important - no single Pokémon can win it all.  Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?

* Collect up to 139 different Pokémon playing the Red version.  Using the Game Link cable, trade with a friend who has the Blue version to capture all 150.
* You’ll need to use both versions (Red and Blue) to collect all of the Pokémon.
* Test your training skills by battling against a friend using the Game Link cable.
* Save your Pokémon and game progress on the Game Pak memory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Pokemon - Red Version-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19960227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>You take the part of a young adventurer attempting to save a beautiful princess. Time is ticking away, you'll have to move fast to escape your cell and evade the many cunning traps placed in your path. Non-stop action is combined with the exploration and puzzle-solving challenge of a top-flight adventure game. With hundreds of fantastic rooms to explore, you must use all your sword fighting skills to do battle with violent opponents and foil the Grand Vizier's despicable plans!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type</name>
		<desc>The galaxy is in deep peril: foul creatures from the evil Bydo Empire have warped across space to invade and conquer our planet! There is only one hope for victory. The Earth Defense League has chosen you to pilot R-9, a nuclear-powered space fighter that can cut through invading aliens faster than a light saber through butter. Fly R-9 through many exciting levels of high-powered action. Use your plasma gun to rip through armies of nasty creatures and their deadly machines. And when the going gets really tough, pick up Droid Units to make your ship even harder hitting!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/R-Type-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type II.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type II</name>
		<desc>The game is the sequel to R-Type, which was first released as an arcade game in 1987 and profoundly influenced later shooting games with its charge shots, unique weaponry, and grotesque enemies. Hudson Soft ported the later 4 levels of the original R-Type to the TurboGrafx-16 with the title R-Type II, but the Hudson release is unrelated to the game described in this article.

The player controls a ship called the R-9C (or R-9 Custom), which is an improved version of its predecessor game's ship; the R-9. The ship's design was changed slightly, and the wave cannon was given homing capabilities. Two new types of weapons (the Search Laser and Shotgun Laser) were added, bringing the total number of weapon types up to five. A new anti-ground unit bomb was also added to the missile inventory.

Though the number of levels was decreased from the prequel, the number of enemies, their durability, and the number of bullets they shoot were greatly increased. Enemy movements and terrain were also made trickier, bringing the game's difficulty up considerably. The same revival system is used as in the prequel, where the player is brought back to a checkpoint whenever their ship is destroyed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/R-Type II-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solar Striker.zip</path>
		<name>Solar Striker</name>
		<desc>You are locked in ferocious combat on an interstellar battlefield. Dodging and taking aim, alien rocketships stream past, circle, and attack. There are too many to count! Fire, fire, fire! The enemies' first wave is repelled. A moment's rest, and the attack begins again. Gather extra life and firepower from floating energy cells. Prepare to duel batwing fighters and insect spaceships, avoid churning energy fields, alien cruisers and more!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Solar Striker-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super R.C. Pro-Am.zip</path>
		<name>Super R.C. Pro-AM</name>
		<desc>Super R.C. Pro-Am is a racing video game that is similar to its predecessor, R.C. Pro-Am, for the NES. In the game, players race remote control cars on a series of tracks. It can be played solo, with two-players via the Game Link Cable, or with three or four players via the Four Player Adapter. The game features 24 different tracks of increasing difficulty, and the object is to finish in the top three in order to qualify to race in the next track. Players who do not finish in the top three may use a continue and retry the track; players get three continues, and the game ends when the player fails to finish in the top three and has no continues remaining.
Each track is different and range from standard ovals to tracks with many twists and turns. The game includes many obstacles, such as oil slicks that send players spinning, puddles of water that cause players to slide out of control, sand traps and "slow cones" that slow players down, large cones that bring players to a complete halt, and walls of tires that players bounce off. If a player hits an oil slick and then hits a wall while spinning, the player's car is temporarily destroyed, which loses time. The tracks also has items that help players along the way: "zippers" (a series of chevrons on the track) give players a speed boost, roll cages allow players to hit walls without being destroyed and allow them to crash opponents by forcing them into walls, and missiles and bombs temporarily destroy opponents' cars. Also on the track are spare parts which help improve performance—tires improve traction, batteries increase acceleration, and engines improve speed.
Players have the opportunity to upgrade their vehicles by collecting letters, which are distributed throughout the tracks. By spelling "Nintendo" with the letters, players upgrade to a better vehicle; players can upgrade from the "Racer" to the "Speed demon" and then to the Spiker, each of which performs progressively better than the previous vehicle. If players spell "Nintendo" while racing with the Spiker, then they win the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Super R.C. Pro-Am-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Tennis</name>
		<desc>The game features single-player and two-player modes for singles and doubles matches, with either competitive or cooperative gameplay. A computerized opponent's artificial intelligence can be set to different difficulty levels. Mario referees the matches.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19890529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Plus.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris Plus</name>
		<desc>THE all-time favorite puzzle game is back, with a new bonus puzzle adventure. You'll find Tetris in its classic form with its relentless rain of blocks. It's sure to provide hours of puzzle pleasure. The Puzzle mode lets you play in a whole new way. Help the Professor and his assistant Jo, as they travel to the lost cities of the world in search of treasure. Don't forget, you can always challenge a friend in the VS mode too!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Tetris Plus-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok - Battle of the Bionosaurs.zip</path>
		<name>Turok: Battle of the Bionosaurs</name>
		<desc>Turok: Battle of the Bionosaurs is an action platformer Game Boy adaptation of Turok: Dinosaur Hunter, developed by Bit Managers and published by Acclaim.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Turok - Battle of the Bionosaurs-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit Managers</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zool.zip</path>
		<name>Zool</name>
		<desc>Once every year, the games world is rocked by a game so stunning, so fast, so colorful, so big, so demanding, so mega, so awesome, so varied , so incredible, and so full of fabulous features and unexpected treats, that everybody just looks at it and says "THAT'S IT!" This year, ZOOL, THE NINJA FROM THE Nth DIMENSION, is definitely "IT!"</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Zool-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Tail.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Tail</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Dragon Tail-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ganso!! Yancha Maru.zip</path>
		<name>Ganso!! Yancha Maru</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Ganso!! Yancha Maru-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse II.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mouse II</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mickey Mouse II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TwinBee da!!.zip</path>
		<name>TwinBee da!!</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/TwinBee da!!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
</gameList>
