<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master - Enemy Below.zip</path>
		<name>Blaster Master: Enemy Below</name>
		<desc>Jason, brave hero of yesteryear, is roused from retirement by the news that mutant lifeeorms, thought to have been long since destroyed, are once again on the move, hollowing out subterranean niches in the image of their old haunts. The decision to reactivate Sophia seems to Jason nothing more than an inevitability. Back into the cold once more...

- Eight areas to explore, to find the keys and kill the sub human bosses
- Use the tank’s suction system to drive up walls and along ceilings
- Drive Sophia or go it alone with Jason.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Blaster Master - Enemy Below-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000924T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia - The Legend Returns.zip</path>
		<name>Lufia: The Legend Returns</name>
		<desc>The island of the Sinistrals, Doom Island, sank deep into the sea after the second Doom Island War.It was believed to be in an eternal sleep, but has once again begun silently beating, preparing to make its appearance in the sky for the third time. The evil Sinistrals have again been resurrected and released an unforseen terror on the land.A force has awaken witin you... a spiritual flow that draws you to a conflict that will save the world! The power of Maxim's legendary bloodline lives in you... The thread of destiny guides you through an adventurous journey looking for an unknown destination!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Lufia - The Legend Returns-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis</name>
		<desc>Take your game to the next level with mario Tennis™! Get advice from coaches, test your groundstrokes against 'The Wall,' then hit the courts to ace the competition and earn a spot on the varsity squad. Play your way to the top on your own in singles, or power up a partner for doubles competition. When you're good enough, you'll enter the Island Open, where you'll face the fiercast players around...and maybe even challenge the greatest player of all-Mario™!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mario Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Xtreme.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Xtreme</name>
		<desc>The future world is in turmoil. The peace keeping mother computer has been hacked and a virus runs rampant throughout the world. Only Mega Man X has the ability to traverse eight dangerous levels in cyberspace, battle huge bosses along the way and restore the mother computer to its normal state. When the going gets too intence, Mega Man X's pal, Zero can be summoned to help him out of the most dangerous situations. It's an X-treme situation that only Mega Man X can resolve!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Megaman Xtreme-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Xtreme 2.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Xtreme 2</name>
		<desc>Mega Man Xtreme 2 is an Action game, developed and published by Capcom,which was released in Japan in 2001.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Megaman Xtreme 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid</name>
		<desc>You are Snake, a government agent on a mission to regain control of a secret nuclear weapons base from terrorist hands. Lightly armed and facing an army of foes, Snake must avoid firefights in order to survive. If Snake can locate them he can utilize advanced hardware, ranging from silenced pistols to ground-to-air missiles. Enemies react to sight and sound - so stay quiet and stay in the shadows. State-of-the-art graphics: textures, transparencies, models and explosions. Taut, gripping story with multiple endings - a truly cinematic experience.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Metal Gear Solid-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shantae.zip</path>
		<name>Shantae</name>
		<desc>Genie-girl Shantae is the self-appointed guardian of a small fishing village, Scuttle Town. Living life in a lighthouse rather than a bottle, she's constantly on the lookout for danger. When the nefarious lady-pirate, Risky Boots catches wind of the treasure that was recently unearthed in the village, she launches an attack. To get Scuttle out of trouble, it's up to Shantae to prove that she's the rightful 'Guardian Genie' to the best of her dancing, buying and hair-whipping abilities. Now crack that whip!* Play on the Game Boy Advance system for enhanced color and to unlock hidden secrets!* Over 50 Locations and Mini-Games!* Learn 'Dance Magic' to transform Shantae and learn new attacks!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Shantae-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>WayForward</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. Deluxe.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. Deluxe</name>
		<desc>Bowser has once again taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and it's up to Mario to put an end to his sinister reign.Battle Bowser's vile henchmen through 32 different levels - all taken directly from the 1985 classic!Then move on to collect special Red Coins and Yoshi Eggs in the Challenge Mode.Or face off against a friend and race through 8 competition courses in the all-new VS Mode!This time there's a lot more to do than just save a Princess, so get ready for a brick-smashin', pipe-warpin', turtle-stompin' good time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Super Mario Bros. Deluxe-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Survival Kids.zip</path>
		<name>Survival Kids</name>
		<desc>Survival Kids is a Role-Playing game, developed by KCE Sapporo and published by Konami,which was released in Japan in 1999.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Survival Kids-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCE Sapporo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Ages.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Oracle of Ages</name>
		<desc>Using the legendary power of the Triforce, Link travels to a distant land known as Labrynna where Veran, the Sorceress of Shadows, has developed a scheme to alter Labrynna's past. Through trickery and deceit, Veran harnesses the power of Nayru, the Oracle of Ages, and travels 400 years into the past. Before the Sorceress of Shadows can complete her dark mission, Link must use the Harp of Ages to save the day.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Ages-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Seasons.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Oracle of Seasons</name>
		<desc>The land of Holodrum is slowly withering.Onox, the General of Darkness, has imprisoned the Oracle of Seasons and is draining the very life out of the land.With the seasons in tumult and the forces of evil running rampant, the world looks for a hero... and finds Link.His quest won't be easy - he'll have to master the seasons themselves if he's to turn back the evil tide.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Legend of Zelda, The - Oracle of Seasons-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land 3.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Trapped inside a magical music box, the invincible Wario is on a dangerous quest to help a mysterious figure recover its lost powers! Smash, bash and crash your way through more than two dozen gigantic levels in search of hidden keys, valuable treasures and mystical music boxes. Test your wits on puzzle after intricate puzzle and flex your muscles in action-packed boss fights! Be wary of Wanderin' Gooms, Hammer-bots, Mad Scienstein and more as you plunge into one of the largest, most dazzling adventures ever to hit Game Boy Color!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Wario Land 3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land II.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land II</name>
		<desc>What kind of no-good ruffians would break into my castle and steal my treasures?! It's that rotten Captain Syrup and that Black Sugar Gang! I'm looking out for bad guys and scavenging for coins as I track down my treasures. If I don't get them all the first time, that's OK. I can go back again and again until I find them all. Captain Syrup doesn't stand a chance against me!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Wario Land II-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1942.zip</path>
		<name>1942</name>
		<desc>1942... you and daring fighter pilot "Super Ace" are engaged in realistic, thrilling and challenging high-flying battles with the enemy. Over land, on the sea and in the air, your own skill and dexterity... combined with Super Ace's flying mastery, duel enemy pilots in fighter and bomber craft. 1942... it's airplanes taking off and landing on ocean-going aircraft carriers... disrupting enemy formations ready to attack... intercepting enemy air-warriors you must defeat by "blasting 'em out of the sky." Will it be victory? Or defeat? It's in your skillful hands!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/1942-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170214T054027</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior III.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
		<desc>Your father, the brave Ortega, is dead. He set off to destroy the Demon Lord Baramos but fell in glorious battle. Unless stopped, Baramos will unleash a torrent of evil that will destroy the world. You must stop Baramos and discover the legend of Dragon Warrior! Your journey starts on Aliahan. Only you decide where it ends...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Dragon Warrior III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening DX.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Link's Awakening DX</name>
		<desc>Link’s latest challenge is set on the mysterious Koholint Island, a place where dreams and reality collide.  As a castaway, Link must find a way to escape from the island and return to his beloved homeland of Hyrule.  This will not be an easy task.

The island’s inhabitants have no knowledge of the outside world.  One creature, a talking owl, may know the solution to Link’s dilemma.  Link must first tackle eight dungeons full of treacherous monsters and tricky traps.  His goal: find the eight Instruments of the Sirens and awaken the omnipotent Wind Fish which rules the island.

* Experience the adventure in color!
* Journey through a new dungeon (can only be accessed on the Game Boy Color system)!
* Take pictures and print them using the Game Boy Printer (sold separately)!
* Battery-backed memory saves up to three separate game files!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Legend of Zelda, The - Link's Awakening DX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery 2.zip</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery 2</name>
		<desc>Original and updated versions of five Game &amp; Watch hand held games! Classic versions will take you back to the '80s and a simpler time in video games. Modern versions feature your favorite characters, bringing you to the present with improved play control, color and sound effects.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Game &amp; Watch Gallery 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T033209</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery 3.zip</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery 3</name>
		<desc>Flash back to the '80s with original and updated versions of five Game &amp; Watch hand-held games!

Relive the birth of hand-held gaming in Classic Game &amp; Watch games. Then join your favourite Nintendo characters in Modern versions featuring improved play control, graphics, colour and sound!

Egg - Catch your eggs before they hatch!
Turtle Bridge - Carry the packages across the turtles' backs!
Green House - Protect your plants from the pesky pests!
Mario Bros. - Help Mario &amp; Luigi keep the factory flowing!
Donkey Kong, JR. - Grab the key and free DK!

-Save &amp; Quit feature lets you stop and restart your game anytime!
-Battery-backed memory saves all your scores!
-Collect stars to access new features and open hidden classic games!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Game &amp; Watch Gallery 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990408T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo, TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T033246</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystalis.zip</path>
		<name>Crystalis</name>
		<desc>CRYSTALIS for the Game Boy Color takes you to a post-apocalyptic world where an evil force named Dragonia threatens to take over. You must seek out the four powerful enchanted Swords of the Elements in order to defeat him. Explore a massive world, loaded with more than 70 enemies and 300 non-player characters to interact with in this action or RPG.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Crystalis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NST</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daiku no Gen-san.zip</path>
		<name>Daiku no Gen-san: Kachikachi no Tonkachi ga Kachi</name>
		<desc>Daiku no Gen-san: Kachikachi no Tonkachi ga Kachi is an action/platforming game developed by Biox and published by Gaps for the Game Boy Color platform. Daiku no Gen-san: Kachikachi no Tonkachi ga Kachi was never released outside of Japan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Daiku no Gen-san-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Biox</developer>
		<publisher>Gaps</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<desc>The best-selling Super NES game of all time is back! Remember blasting through levels in barrels and taking wild mine cart rides? All the jammin' jungle hi-jinks are back, along with DK's animal friends Rambi the Rhino, Squawks the Parrot, Enguarde the Swordfish and more! In addition to all the original levels, you get the chest-pounding fun of new bonus levels and 2-player games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Donkey Kong Country-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga - Destination Earth.zip</path>
		<name>Galaga: Destination Earth</name>
		<desc>All the other space pilots have been eliminated. Somehow you survived. The Galaga enemies are on the move. Now, you must fight or doom Earth to extinction. There's no time to plan strategies. Just find your targets and come out blasting. Battle wave upon wave of alien attack craft in this dazzling edition of the arcade classic. Use special weapons, retrieve captured craft to multiply your firepower and of course, rack up big points in the Challenge Stages. This is Galaga - Strap yourself in and come out firing!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Galaga - Destination Earth-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pipe Dream Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Hasbro Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts'n Goblins.zip</path>
		<name>Ghosts 'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>Capcom's arcade-turn-console action platformer Ghosts 'N Goblins is a true 2D classic. The game, which stars Sir Arthur, a knight on a mission to rescue Princess Guinevere, travels players through six huge 2D scrolling levels rained with obstacles, enemies and other infuriating hazards. It was all too easy to meet one's doom at the near end of a stage as the difficulty level is unforgiving and have to start all over, but because of the clever coin-munching design and atmospheric presentation, the drag to keep playing never loosened. It's still regarded as one of the greats. The GBC version, released in 2000, is a direct port of the NES game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Ghosts'n Goblins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Karate Joe.zip</path>
		<name>Karate Joe</name>
		<desc>There's a new boss in town, and his gangs are taking over the city. He's got thugs on every corner waiting to take you out. But you're not a run-of-the-mill videogame character. You're Karate Joe, and you're going to fight your way through 18 levels to free the city in this side-scrolling action-adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Karate Joe-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Octopus Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Rocket Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T015934</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Konami GB Collection Vol1.zip</path>
		<name>Konami GB Collection: Vol.1</name>
		<desc>Enjoy these classic Konami games on GameBoy.
4 great games to choose from!
More Konami classic games coming soon.

-Gradius
-Castlevania: The Adventure
-Konami Racing
-Contra</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Konami GB Collection Vol1-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Konami GB Collection Vol4.zip</path>
		<name>Konami GB Collection: Vol.4</name>
		<desc>Enjoy these classic Konami games on GameBoy.
4 great games to choose from!
More Konami classic games coming soon.

-Gradius II
-Castlevania II: Belmont's Revenge
-Yie Ar Kung-Fu
-Antarctic Adventure</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Konami GB Collection Vol4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Driller.zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Driller</name>
		<desc>Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mr. Driller-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Puzzle Challenge.zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Puzzle Challenge</name>
		<desc>In a rising pit of colored blocks, it's your task to continuously eliminate these tiles by switching two tiles' positions on the horizontal row. When three or more tiles link up in a up/down or left/right fashion, they disappear. Gravity kicks in and settles the rest of the tiles into the bin ? this can cause a chain reaction to occur since other blocks of the same color can fall into place next to each other. It's up to you to continuously work the bin to wipe out tiles by making combination connections and chain reactions. That's the game in a nutshell, but there are several modes of play that'll keep your fingers busy. In the game's Challenge mode, for example, you're up against a computer opponent and you'll have to make combos and chain reactions to send garbage blocks to his unseen screen -- but keep in mind your opponent's doing the same to you.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon Puzzle Challenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20001204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>The Grand Visir Jaffar seizes control of the throne while the Sultan is away. At the same time, a young prince from a far away land falls in love with the Princess, causing him to become Jaffar's enemy. Jaffar kidnaps the prince throwing him into the darkest part of the dungeon. The Princess now has one hour to make a choice: marry the evil Jaffar or die. Take the role of the young prince as he tries to escape from the dungeon. Each of the 12 game levels is a puzzle, and you have exactly 60 minutes to get through all of the levels. There are guards throughout the dungeon who are trying to stop you, but you can pick up a sword and use it to dispatch the guards. Break out of the dungeon and save the woman you love in PRINCE OF PERSIA.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Orb</developer>
		<publisher>Red Orb</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris DX.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris DX</name>
		<desc>Puzzle fans rejoice! The all-time puzzle favorite has returned! Tetris DX has everything you need to satisfy your puzzle appetite. Play MARATHON, the classic Tetris game. Try your hand at ULTRA or 40 LINES, two Tetris games with a twist. The VS. game will have you playing for hours!
It that's not enough, Tetris DX is fully compatible with the new Game Boy® Color system! With the Game Link® cable, you can exchange saved information from one system to another! That's right, battery-backed memory saves up to three game files. Now your high scores will live on forever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tetris DX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19981101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda - Hard Awakening DX.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Hard Awakening DX</name>
		<desc>Link’s latest challenge is set on the mysterious Koholint Island, a place where dreams and reality collide.  As a castaway, Link must find a way to escape from the island and return to his beloved homeland of Hyrule.  This will not be an easy task.

The island’s inhabitants have no knowledge of the outside world.  One creature, a talking owl, may know the solution to Link’s dilemma.  Link must first tackle eight dungeons full of treacherous monsters and tricky traps.  His goal: find the eight Instruments of the Sirens and awaken the omnipotent Wind Fish which rules the island.

* Experience the adventure in color!
* Journey through a new dungeon (can only be accessed on the Game Boy Color system)!
* Take pictures and print them using the Game Boy Printer (sold separately)!
* Battery-backed memory saves up to three separate game files!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Legend of Zelda - Hard Awakening DX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T193110</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./V-Rally - Championship Edition.zip</path>
		<name>V-Rally: Edition 99</name>
		<desc>Get all the bumps, jumps, thrills, and spills of off-road rally racing in your hands with V-RALLY EDITION '99 for the Game Boy Color. Choose between four real-world rally cars: Peugeot 306 Maxi, the Mitsubishi Lancer WRC, V-Rally Ford Escort WRC, and Subaru Impreza WRC. Then race on 40 courses in exotic locations like Indonesia, Safari, Corsica, New Zealand, Alps, United Kingdom, Greece, Argentina, Italy, and Sweden. The terrain of each track has an effect on your car's performance, and you must be careful because snow, dirt, and asphalt all react differently. In addition to the terrain, keep an eye out for obstacles like rocks, oil slicks, hills, and jumps. You can get all of the off-road action you could ever want with V-RALLY EDITION '99</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/V-Rally - Championship Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bit Managers</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asteroids.zip</path>
		<name>Asteroids</name>
		<desc>Your spaceship is trapped in a deadly asteroid belt. You will have to destroy the drifting asteroid boulders before they destroy your spaceship. But, watch out for enemy spacecraft. Fire your missiles to destroy the boulders and the enemy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Asteroids-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Syrox Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commando - Elite Forces.zip</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando: Elite Forces</name>
		<desc>You are the ultimate weapon. You are the perfect synthesis of human and machine - a Bionic Commando.Your latest mission - to rescue a fellow commando, Commando Joe - will take you deep into the heart of enemy territory. Use your Bionic Claw to grapple and swing through more than 20 levels of forest, deserts, mountains and futuristic cities Blast through dozens of unique with your Assault Rifle, Rocket Launcher and Flame Thrower as you seek to destroy the overlord Arturus, and save your homeland of Karinia from utter destruction.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bionic Commando - Elite Forces-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs Bunny in Crazy Castle 4.zip</path>
		<name>Bugs Bunny In Crazy Castle 4</name>
		<desc>Bugs Bunny returns in BUGS BUNNYS CRAZY CASTLE 4 for Game Boy Color! Thinking he has found the Carrot Castle, Bugs has once again entered the Crazy Castle. You must help him escape in this single-player action or puzzle game. This time, more than 60 rooms await Bugs, and he'll have to use all of his wits and skills to escape with his "hare" intact. Once again, the Crazy Castle is loaded with traps and hazards that will cut your carrot-collecting career short so make sure you don't get reacquainted with them the hard way. As CRAZY CASTLE fans are probably used to, several Warner Bros. cartoon characters are here to keep Bugs on his toes. You'll have to fight off Daffy Duck, Yosemite Sam, Foghorn Leghorn, Pepe Le Pew, Tweety, and the Tazmanian Devil with one of a variety of weapons, or make tracks to the nearest safe spot. A password save will chart your progress so that you don't have to start from scratch each time you play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Bugs Bunny in Crazy Castle 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jungle Book, The - Mowgli's Wild Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Walt Disney's The Jungle Book: Mowgli's Wild Adventure</name>
		<desc>In WALT DISNEY'S THE JUNGLE BOOK: Mowgli's Wild Adventure, you must guide Mowgli on an adventure to become King of the Jungle. Mowgli must work his way through more than 20 levels of adventure, using his superior intellect. Instead of beating up monkey guards, Mowgli can use a banana to lure them away from their posts. However, there will come a time when fighting is necessary, and the man-cub can use a number moves to get rid of the enemies including a butt-stomp and a vicious spin-attack. Since the game is optimized for the Game Boy Color, the environments look like they could have been taken right from the film. Help Mowgli survive to adulthood in WALK DISNEY'S THE JUNGLE BOOK: Mowgli's Wild Adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Jungle Book, The - Mowgli's Wild Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20001120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Golf</name>
		<desc>Forget buying expensive golf gear--Mario brings the game to you. Mario Golf features four complete 18-hole courses, 11 golfers, and precise play control. Create your own golfer and build up his or her experience and skill levels by competing in various tournaments and head-to-head matches. The more you play, the stronger and more accurate your golfer becomes. There are many different modes of play in Mario Golf, including a wide variety of minigames designed to challenge even the most level-headed swingers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Mario Golf-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Yellow Version.zip</path>
		<name>Pokémon Yellow</name>
		<desc>You've finally been granted your Pokémon trainer's license, and now you're on your way to becoming the world's greatest Pokémon trainer! The shockingly-cute Pikachu tags along behind you as you search the enormous world for monsters to train and evolve. Face off against Blastoise's torrential water gun. Stand strong when facing Pidgeot's stormy Gust. Develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Pokemon - Yellow Version-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type DX.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type DX</name>
		<desc>The World Government needs your help. A deep-space probe has uncovered the Bydo Empire's secret plans to mount an attack on Earth. A full-scale assault force would be detected by the Empire's long-range scanners, and any hope of surprise would be lost. Our only chance is for a single pilot in a lone R-Type fighter to penetrate the Bydo defense system and destroy the evil Empire before it can launch its attack. Tear through Bydo defenses as you blast enemies with your Fire Chain, Super Laser and Bubble Beam. Take the fight to a fevered pitch with two pulse-pounding rapid-fire modes on your Game Boy Color system.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/R-Type DX-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snoopy Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Snoopy Tennis</name>
		<desc>It's a tennis game, Charlie Brown! The PEANUTS gang have packed up their rackets and headed to the courts for some fun tennis action in SNOOPY TENNIS for Game Boy Color. Choose from an initial selection of four characters Snoopy, Charlie Brown, Linus, and Lucy and take to one of four courts: clay, hard, and two different grass courts. Five gameplay modes await you: in Normal mode you play a quick best-of-three or best-of-five match up against a computer or human opponent; Sudden Win gives you an instant victory if you gain two games on your opponent; in Point Race mode, you'll race to see how many points you can score in a minute; Special mode throws a variety of power-ups into the mix; and Championship mode has you battling several opponents in order to become champion and unlock four new characters and courts. In addition, three different difficulty levels allow players of all skill levels to enjoy the game. SNOOPY TENNIS is for Game Boy Color only.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Snoopy Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mermaid Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders.zip</path>
		<name>Space Invaders</name>
		<desc>Aliens are trying to take over the solar system, and you're the only one that can stop them. You are the best pilot on Earth, and you must defend all of the planets. After choosing your vehicle from the three that are available, it will stay at the bottom of the screen as a formation of aliens slowly moves down the screen. Your job is simple: blast the aliens out the sky. When they are decimated, you will move on to the next level. Fortunately, there are several power-ups available including electricity, solar flares, bubbles, shurikens, and others. As you progress through the game, new aliens with new formations will appear, not mention a boss character or two. If you are lucky enough to make it through all of the game levels, you will be able to play a version of the original arcade game released in the late '70s. Defend the Earth from tyranny in SPACE INVADERS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Space Invaders-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha: Warriors' Dreams</name>
		<desc>The challenge has been made and you're cast into the battle with nothing but cunning and skill on your side. The world's most powerful collection of warriors is now assembled in one incredible tournament. Armed with an arsenal of new martial arts moves, Super Combos and Alpha Counters, legendary Street Fighters, Ryu- Chun-Li and Ken collide with a lethal new combination of foes. Welcome to the most extreme one-on-one warfare ever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Dizzy's Candy Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Dizzy's Candy Quest</name>
		<desc>This is a puzzle solving game in which the player (as Dizzy from the Tiny Toons Cartoon) has to collect and return different types of candy to a friendly robot that needs the candy to free himself from Montana Max.

The game is divided in 5 worlds (The Studios, Ice World, City, Gogo Dodo's world, Looniversity) with varying numbers of sublevels.

Getting to the candy is made complicated by conveyor belts, trap doors and fans as well as dissolving bridges etc. To add to the trouble, clones of popular Tiny Toon characters (Plucky Hamton, Furrball etc.) are programmed to attack the player.

Extras can be collected for extra energy, time etc. The game is presented from a top down perspective. Estimated playtime approx. 30 hours.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tiny Toon Adventures - Dizzy's Candy Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Conspiracy Games</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toki Tori.zip</path>
		<name>Toki Tori</name>
		<desc>Join the courageous Toki Tori on his quest to recover his family of eggs in this brain teasing puzzle adventure exclusively for the Game Boy Color video game system. Explore mysterious new worlds like the Slime Cave, Creepy Castle, Forest Falls and Bubble Barrage... over 60 levels of exciting puzzle action in all. Armed with an arsenal of 10 different tools, Toki Tori must use his noggin' to overcome dangerous obstacles and face other exasperating challenges.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Toki Tori-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Two Tribes</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider - Curse of the Sword.zip</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: Curse of the Sword</name>
		<desc>Released in conjunction with the LARA CROFT: Tomb Raider film starring Angelina Jolie, Curse of the Sword is one of the more advanced titles ever created for the Game Boy Color. While averting a museum robbery, Lara is wounded ever so slightly by what seems to be a cursed sword. Now, her worst fears are beginning to come true, as a bizarre cult based out of New Orleans is plotting to steal her soul. Help the lovely and talented Ms. Croft save herself as you control her through worldly adventures of all sorts. An equal blend of puzzle solving and action, the game boasts a unique control system that allows for maximum character response. You'll be collecting keys and artifacts throughout the experience, each of which will help you to unlock doors and secrets. Graced by perfect animation and epic gameplay, TOMB RAIDER: Curse of the Sword is a welcome addition to the long line of brilliant TOMB RAIDER games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Tomb Raider - Curse of the Sword-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wendy - Every Witch Way.zip</path>
		<name>Wendy - Every Witch Way</name>
		<desc>She's been around for roughly 50 years, and Wendy the Good Little Witch finally has her own handheld video game. The laws of gravity have been upset, and Wendy is to blame! Help her trek through level after level of maddening obstacles and deadly enemies in order to set things right. There are hidden Moon Stones that Wendy must find in order to get things back to normal, but they're spread out over four vast levels of harrowing action. Packed with strange locations and tough mysteries to solves, WENDY: Every Witch Way features four bonus levels hat have you earning points by flying through the air on a broom, avoiding flying objects, and taking out would-be deterrents with a magic wand. Boasting detailed, cartoon-style graphics and some of the most original gameplay you've ever laid eyes on, WENDY: Every Witch Way is a truly magical experience for gamers of all ages.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Wendy - Every Witch Way-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WayForward Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>TDK Mediactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins DX.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins DX</name>
      <image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gbc/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins DX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
</gameList>
