<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./avsp.zip</path>
		<name>Alien vs. Predator</name>
		<desc>San Drad, California, has been overrun by the Aliens, and the cybernetically-enhanced Major Dutch Schaefer and Lieutenant Linn Kurosawa have been abandoned by their superiors and are cornered by a swarm of the Alien drones. Before they can be killed, a pair of the Predators appear and destroy the Aliens. The Predators offer an alliance with the two humans in order to stop the Alien infestation.

The players take control of up to three of four characters: Dutch, Linn, a Predator hunter, and a Predator warrior, and battle the Aliens through several environments. In the process, the characters discover that the Alien presence on Earth is the result of an experiment headed by a renegade General Bush of the U.S. Colonial Marines in conjunction with the Weyland-Yutani corporation. They destroy the Alien hive by crashing a military ship into San Drad, causing a huge explosion. The Predator warrior then gives his wrist blades to Dutch and Linn in recognition of their skills as warriors, before the Predators depart back into space.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/avsp-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./captcomm.zip</path>
		<name>Captain Commando</name>
		<desc>Captain Commando is set in a crime-ridden future in the year 2026, where a superhero named Captain Commando, assisted by his three faithful Commando Companions rise up to protect the Earth and all the Galaxy from a gang of super-powered criminals.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/captcomm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dstlk.zip</path>
		<name>Darkstalkers</name>
		<desc>The DarkStalkers have been unleashed! All the creatures from your darkest dreams have materialized to wage an eternal war for domination of the night. The fate of all humanity rests on who wins this epic struggle. You control the power of your favorite supernatural monster to combine their special attacks and unique abilities in a head to head fighting challenge. It's a fierce and brutal conflict for supremacy in the monster hit of the year!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/dstlk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ffight.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight</name>
		<desc>Final Fight can be played by up to two players simultaneously, with each player controlling a different character. Before the game begins, the player chooses between the three main characters, Guy, Cody, and Haggar, each with his own fighting style and attributes. Guy is the weakest but has faster attacks, Haggar is the strongest but also the slowest, and Cody has all-round attributes.

Final Fight consists of six stages or "rounds", as well as two bonus rounds. Each round takes place in a different section of Metro City such as the Slums and the Subway, with most rounds featuring more than one level. At the end of each round the player will face a boss character unique to that round.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/ffight-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ghouls.zip</path>
		<name>Ghouls 'N Ghosts</name>
		<desc>The gameplay for Ghouls n' Ghosts is eerily similar to that of Ghosts 'n Goblins. The player controls the knight Arthur, who must advance through a series of spooky levels and defeat a number of undead and demonic creatures in his quest to restore souls stolen by Lucifer, including the soul of his bride, Princess Guinevere. Along the way, Arthur can pick up a variety of weapons and armor to help him in his quest.

It is the sequel to Ghosts'n Goblins and the second game in the Ghosts'n Goblins series.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/ghouls-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hsf2.zip</path>
		<name>Hyper Street Fighter II: The Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>Hyper Street Fighter II: The Anniversary Edition is a competitive fighting game by Capcom that was originally released for the PlayStation 2 in 2003 in Japan and in 2004 in North America and Asia. Released to commemorate the 15th anniversary of the Street Fighter series, Hyper Street Fighter II is a modified port of Super Street Fighter II Turbo in which players can control any versions of the main characters from the five Street Fighter II games previously released for the arcades. Although, originally released as a home console game, an arcade port was released shortly afterwards in limited quantities, turning it into the sixth and final arcade iteration.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/hsf2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20031222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./msword.zip</path>
		<name>Magic Sword: Heroic Fantasy</name>
		<desc>Magic Sword fully titled as Magic Sword: Heroic Fantasy, is a side-scrolling fantasy arcade game released by Capcom in 1990. The game casts the player as a hero who must fight his way through a mystical tower in order to save the world. The player can use a sword, axe or magic, and can also rescue and recruit potential allies of various character classes, each of which has his or her own special abilities. Three years earlier, Capcom had released the similar Black Tiger in 1987.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/msword-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./msh.zip</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Play as your favorite Marvel character: Wolverine, Spider-Man, The Incredible Hulk, Captain America, Iron Man, Psylocke, Shuma-Gorath, Blackheart, Juggernaut or Magneto. Power up with an Infinity Gem - Grant your super hero healing power, super attacks and increased strength.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/msh-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19951031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mshvsf.zip</path>
		<name>Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter</name>
		<desc>Now you can choose your favorite heroes from the worlds of Street Fighter and Marvel Super Heroes to face off in a head-to-head battle for supremacy. Dive into the action to perform outrageous moves and link together amazing Chain Combos... then delight in their devastating results! Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter combines two incredible universes to create an entirely new legend of heroic proportions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/mshvsf-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19980618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mvsc.zip</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes is the fifth Marvel Comics-licensed fighting game by Capcom and the third game in the Marvel vs. Capcom series. In contrast to X-Men vs. Street Fighter and Marvel Super Heroes vs. Street Fighter, the game features characters from numerous Capcom franchises such as Mega Man and Strider, rather than just Street Fighter characters. The game takes place within the Marvel comic continuity, as Professor Charles Xavier calls out for heroes to stop him before he merges with the consciousness of Magneto and becomes the being known as Onslaught, the final boss. The game was developed in late 1997 and first released in January 1998.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/mvsc-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mtwins.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Twins</name>
		<desc>Mega Twins (Chiki Chiki Boys in Japan) is an arcade game, first released in 1990.

The game features twins who are attempting to re-take control of their land, Alurea, after a monster unexpectedly attacks, destroying everything in its path. The people of Alurea have lived in peace for a thousand years and have forgotten how to fight, yet the land's only survivors, the twin sons of the king, must take up the challenge and return their kingdom to its former glory.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/mtwins-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfa3.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3, the third game in the Alpha series, has a total of 31 fighters, the most in the series so far. New characters include old favorites E. Honda, Blanka, Vega, Cammy, T. Hawk, Dee Jay, Juni and Juli. Some of the newest fighters on the block include a former Final Fight character (Cody, who has been in jail since the last Final Fight game, or so his clothing suggests), Karin Kanzuki and Rainbow Mika. The major difference between this Alpha and the last two are the new play modes World Tour, Arcade, VS, Training and Entry.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sfa3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sf2hf.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II Turbo: Hyper Fighting</name>
		<desc>Hyper Fighting features faster playing speed compared to Champion Edition. As a result, the inputs for special moves and combos requires more precise timing. The faster play speed also allowed players to get into battle quicker, as well as to counterattack quicker. All of the fighters, with the exception of Guile and the four Grand Masters, were each given a new special move, with the exception of Chun-Li who was given two.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sf2hf-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sf2.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II: The World Warrior</name>
		<desc>GET READY TO RUMBLE!

From across the globe comes eight of the wildest fighters the world has ever known. Choose your champion, gather your courage and prepare to battle your opponents in a bare knuckle brawl. Face Ken and his devastating "Dragon Punch"! Watch the temperature rise as Dhalsim incinerates you with his mystical Yoga Flame! Hear your spine crack as Zangief smashes you to the pavement with his spinning pile driver! Cover your ears as Guile breaks the sound barrier with the awesome power of the Sonic Boom!

Annihilate your competition and claim the right to test your skills against the bone-crushing power of the Grand Masters! Can you survive? Can Anyone?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sf2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfiii3.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III: 3rd Strike</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter III 3rd Strike: Fight for the Future is a 2D competitive fighting game produced by Capcom originally released for the arcade in 1999. It is the second follow-up to Street Fighter III, following Street Fighter III 2nd Impact. Like its predecessors, it runs on the CP System III hardware. 3rd Strike increased the character roster by adding five new characters, including Chun-Li. It also added further refinements to the previous game's play mechanics and rules. It was ported to the Dreamcast, PlayStation 2, and Xbox. A downloadable online version titled Street Fighter III: 3rd Strike Online Edition was released on PlayStation Network and Xbox Live Arcade in August 2011.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sfiii3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19990512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ssf2t.zip</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo</name>
		<desc>Super Street Fighter II Turbo, released in Japan as Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge, is a competitive fighting game released for the arcades by Capcom in 1994. It is the fifth arcade installment in the Street Fighter II sub-series of Street Fighter games, following Super Street Fighter II. Like its predecessor, it ran on the CP System II hardware.

Super Turbo introduced several new play mechanics to the game system from the previous Street Fighter II installments, including the addition of powered-up Special Moves called Super Combos. It also introduced the hidden character of Akuma, who would go on to become a recurring character in later Street Fighter installments and other Capcom fighting games.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/ssf2t-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./willow.zip</path>
		<name>Willow</name>
		<desc>Willow is a platform game based on the 1988 film of the same name. It was developed by Capcom and released as an arcade and a NES game in 1989.

The evil witch queen Bavmorda is after the holy baby of the lands, Elora Danan, intent on destroying her. A young peaceful wizard called Willow Ufgood was selected to protect Elora. Later on, a brave warrior named Madmartigan joins Willow to fight the enemy rival General Kael.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/willow-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./xmvsf.zip</path>
		<name>X-Men vs. Street Fighter</name>
		<desc>X-Men vs. Street Fighter pits Marvel's mighty mutants against Capcom's legendary fighters in a slugfest of epic proportions. Now you can perform outrageous moves and link together amazing Chain Combos. X-Men vs. Street Fighter... the collision of two explosive universes in the world's most amazing fantasy fighter!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/xmvsf-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19960909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./xmcota.zip</path>
		<name>X-Men: Children Of The Atom</name>
		<desc>X-MEN UNLEASHED! It's here! Ultimate combat! Mutant mayhem! X-Power! Special moves! Mid-air action! Big characters! Sizzling graphics! Exactly like you played in the arcade! You will need all your mutant powers, all your speed, all your strength... for this is the ultimate combat! Have you got enough to defeat Magneto, Omega Red and the Sentinel? Are you tough enough for Wolverine, powerful enough for Cyclops, cool enough for Iceman... are you good enough to join the new breed of mutant heroes? X-Men Children of the Atom - the fighting game to end them all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/xmcota-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfa.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sfa-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170304T055104</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./sfz2al.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Zero 2 Alpha</name>
		<desc>Street Fighter Zero 2 Alpha en Japón, Asia y América del Sur, es un videojuego de lucha de la saga Street Fighter que salió en 1996 y es continuación directa de Street Fighter Alpha que a su vez se sitúa argumentalmente entre el primer y segundo Street Fighter, por eso se denominada con la coletilla Alpha o Zero en Japón, su país de origen. En Latinoamérica llegaron a los arcades con ese mismo nombre de Zero y traducido al español en algunos países.

Esta continuación no es una simple extensión del primer Alpha como sucedía con los Street Fighter II, Capcom en esta ocasión hizo un nuevo juego, con el mismo código gráfico pero sustancialmente mejorados y nuevos escenarios, sólo los sprites de los personajes que repiten del primer Alpha se mantienen, aunque con mejoras en la animación.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/sfz2al-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19960601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./vsav.zip</path>
		<name>Vampire Savior: The Lord Of Vampire</name>
		<desc>Jedah, one of the ancient Three Lords of Darkrealm has returned. You play as one of fifteen Darkstalkers. Beat Jedah and take your throne as the Lord of the Darkness.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/vsav-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T015933</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./nwarr.zip</path>
		<name>Night Warriors: Darkstalkers' Revenge</name>
		<desc>The Darkstalkers return and now crave the fury of a good night fight. In this head-to-head fighting challenge, creatures from your darkest nightmares battle for eternal control fo the night. Treacherous, classic favorites take on 4 new challengers for total domination. Donovan, the Dark Hunter. Huitzil, the Killer Machine. Hsien-Ko, the Chinese Ghost. And Pyron, the ultimate Alien ruler. The battle has never been as intense, with faster speeds, more captivating moves and even more incredible graphics. Night Warriors; the game of your dreams, and nightmares.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/nwarr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19950305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T015638</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
