<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./1942.zip</path>
		<name>1942</name>
		<desc>1942 is set in the Pacific theater of World War II. The goal is to reach Tokyo and destroy the entire Japanese air fleet. The player pilots a plane dubbed the "Super Ace" (but its appearance is clearly that of a Lockheed P-38 Lightning). The player has to shoot down enemy planes; to avoid enemy fire, the player can perform a roll or "loop-the-loop".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/1942-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19841201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1943.zip</path>
		<name>1943: The Battle of Midway</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the Pacific theater of World War II, off the coast of the Midway Atoll. The goal is to attack the Japanese Air Fleet that bombed the players' American Aircraft Carrier, pursue all Japanese Air and Sea forces, fly through the 16 levels of play, make their way to the Japanese battleship Yamato and destroy her. 11 Levels consist of an Air-to-Sea battle (with a huge battleship or an aircraft carrier as an End-Level Boss), while 5 levels consist of an all-aerial battle against a squadron of Japanese Bombers and a Mother Bomber that needs to be destroyed.
As in 1942, players pilot a P-38. Two buttons are used: one for regular attacks (with several weapons) and one for special actions that executes either a loop like in 1942 or one of three special attacks that damage the plane. Unlike 1942, the player only has one life, with one refillable energy meter. Destroying a complete formation of red enemy planes will result in a power-up, such as a health boost or a temporary special weapons which replaces the default twin gun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/1943-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ddonpach.zip</path>
		<name>DoDonPachi</name>
		<desc>Donpachi was a hit in arcades, and people felt that Cave were picking up right where Toaplan left off. Therefore, it's no surprise that a sequel to Donpachi would soon be in development. The feeling that the developers had when making Dodonpachi (lit. "Angry Leader Bee"), was to ignore the "Toaplanishness" of Donpachi, instead only putting in systems that Cave felt were the most interesting. This lead to a far more balanced and refined game than its predecessor. To sum up Dodonpachi in a single word, it would have to be...more. More enemies, more stages, more bosses, more systems, more dodging, more bullets, more...everything. The cause of this "more" feeling stems from a chance encounter with the Raizing game Battle Garegga that main programmer Tsuneki Ikeda experienced. The intense action and immediate difficulty of Battle Garegga left a strong impact on Ikeda, leaving him with the feeling that "We (Cave) have to surpass Battle Garegga. Ikeda knew that he couldn't make a game like Battle Garegga no matter how hard he tried, so if he wanted to surpass it, it would have to be done through different means, bullet dodging. Ikeda would later reveal in an interview that he told his team that "We won't lose in terms of bullets!" When released, Dodonpachi could have up to 245 bullets onscreen at once. Because of that decision, Dodonpachi went on to solidify the bullet-hell sub-genre. Dodonpachi would be released into Japanese arcades on February 5, 1997. The game introduced several of what would become the series mainstays: The Donpachi Squadron, Colonel Schwarlitz Longhena, and his "Final Brutal Weapon": Hibachi.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/ddonpach-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cave</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./donpachi.zip</path>
		<name>DonPachi</name>
		<desc>In February of 1993, Japanese game developer Toaplan released Batsugun to Japanese arcades. The game would be met with high praise, and would later be cited as the game that defined many of the various tropes and characteristics that are present in every bullet-hell shmup created since. Sadly, Toaplan would close its doors soon after, leaving many developers suddenly out of work. One of these developers was a programmer named Tsuneki Ikeda, who with fellow now ex-Toaplan employees would found their own development studio, Cave Interactive Co. Ltd, more commonly known as Cave. As Cave was comprised of ex-Toaplan employees at that time, it makes sense that their inaugural game would be a Toaplan-style shooting game. Their first game is DonPachi (lit. "Leader Bee"),a "maniac shooter" in the vein of other Toaplan shmups, like Batsugun. DonPachi was first released in Japanese arcades in May of 1995, and in doing so, created a franchise that would see various releases and ports over the next eight years and across two console generations.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/donpachi-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cave</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./galaxian.zip</path>
		<name>Galaxian</name>
		<desc>Galaxian expanded on the formula pioneered by Space Invaders. As in the earlier game, Galaxian featured a horde of attacking aliens that exchanged shots with the player. In contrast to Space Invaders, Galaxian added an element of drama by having the aliens periodically make kamikaze-like dives at the player's ship, the Galaxip.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/galaxian-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19791001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./raidendx.zip</path>
		<name>Raiden DX</name>
		<desc>Vertical scrolling shoot-em-up that adds new features to its prequel Raiden II. Choose from three separate missions: Training special stage, Alpha levels 1-5 and Bravo levels 1-9. Collect various power-ups to increase your weaponry. Lots of secrets and bonuses including ratings based upon player performance</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/raidendx-image.jpg</image>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu</developer>
		<publisher>Fabtek</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./galaga.zip</path>
		<name>Galaga</name>
		<desc>The gameplay in Galaga '88 is built on the same premise as that of the original Galaga game, but is in many ways more complex and more difficult. The game is divided into a series of 29 Stages distributed through eight Worlds. The starship Galaga accelerates between Stages and Worlds and even to higher dimensions (go to the section on Dimensional Travel below to find out more).

With the exception of the third and eighth, each World culminates in a Challenging Stage. There are six such stages to engage in any full game, and each begins with the on-screen announcement "That's Galactic Dancin'!" and has its own YM2151-generated song to which the enemy formations dance. In any given Challenging Stage, both the design of the enemies and their dancing formations shall vary according to the player's current Dimension. As in Galaga, the objective is to destroy all forty enemies before they fly away off the screen. However, refraining completely from touching any controls for the duration of a Challenging Stage awards a "secret bonus" ranging in value from 10000 to 25000 points, and equal to the "special bonus" which would have been awarded for destroying all forty enemy aliens instead.

Galaga '88 introduces a variety of new enemies and behaviors. Most of these special enemies are worth varying amounts of bonus points when destroyed. Some enemies can combine into larger enemies which take multiple hits to destroy, while others arrive in eggs, explode in a shower of fireworks, grow with multiple hits, or sport armor which makes them invincible while in formation. Certain enemies drop small formations of tiny creatures that wiggle their way down the screen, and still others can act as escorts to incoming groups of enemies and then quickly dive at the player before leaving the game. Most stages also include various obstacles which appear once the enemy formation has been assembled. These can be destroyed with either one or several shots, and the first one on each stage will leave a "Warp Capsule".

At the start of the game, the player can select how many Galaga starships to start with (one or two), affecting their number of remaining lives. The game ends after the final boss is defeated (or when the player's last ship is destroyed or captured) - in the latter case, the player can continue the game for an additional credit. The Game Over screen shows the player's hit-miss ratio and a visual representation of their progress. If the player reaches Stage 27, the game also shows a picture of the final boss (damaged if defeated, but silhouetted if not). If the arcade operator has set the "continue" option to "on", the player also cannot continue if he is defeated on Stages 27-29.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/galaga-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bbakraid.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Bakraid</name>
		<desc>The capitalist nation of Randa has long had a history of excellence in the creation of aircraft, attracting the best of engineers in aerodynamics, artillery, and structuring from the world over. Once, even this interest had waned, until the creation of the air show Bakraid, in which the capabilities of the fighters could be demonstrated outside of simulations for all to see.
Around the time of the seventh Bakraid, a nearby nation, Deneb, had attained an expansionist attitude, forcibly subjugating and annexing several of its neighbors with the assistance of the Shtarterra Security Council. Recently, Deneb has asked to participate in Bakraid. Randa's defense council, perfectly aware that this is just a pretext for Deneb to get its and the SSC's engines of war into Randan borders and more easily prosecute their war from there, give their blessing. However, the council secretly contacts the other Bakraid participants, offering even more prize money than normal if they will perform in a special version of Bakraid--genuine war conditions. In other words, use their own top-of-the-line planes to shatter Deneb's schemes. In all, nine pilots accept this plan, and begin Bakraid two weeks early to catch Deneb unaware...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/bbakraid-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T035457</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bgaregga.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Garegga</name>
		<desc>Battle Garegga is a game with a divisive reputation. Many people regard it as one of the best shooters of all time. Others think that it's overrated and that the art style and rank system ruin what would have been some cool ideas. The general style, in addition to the bomb collection system, was heavily influenced by Taito's 1990 shooter Gun Frontier, to the point where Battle Garegga could be considered a spiritual successor.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/bgaregga-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raizing</developer>
		<publisher>Raizing</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T035827</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aliens.zip</path>
		<name>Aliens</name>
		<desc>Hadley's Hope lost contact with the Weyland-Yutani staff, so the Colonial Marine troops of the USS Sulaco decided to send their team to investigate. Players take the role of either Lieutenant Ellen Ripley or Corporal Dwayne Hicks as they fight their way through Xenomorphs before killing their Queen, which is a stowaway in the Sulaco. Three of the levels also featured Newt, where the players must rescue her from the Aliens.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/aliens-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./blktiger.zip</path>
		<name>Black Tiger</name>
		<desc>Black Tiger, known in Japan as Black Dragon (Japanese: ブラックドラゴン Burakku Doragon), is a 1987 action game released for the arcades by Capcom.

A barbarian hero jumps and fights his way through a variety of colourful, enemy-packed levels. The sprawling, eight-way scrolling, two-dimensional levels are packed with hidden bonuses to encourage and reward exploration. Though a percentage of these bonuses consist of dubious and often self-evident "advice", most come in the form of "Zenny coins", currency that allows the player to buy such items as an upgrade to their weapons and armour, keys for treasure chests, and anti-poisoning potions. Special items that reveal coins, upgraded armour, full vitality, extra lives, extra time, or simply bonus points may be found by attacking certain walls. The player's vitality bar will also increase up to three times as a reward for reaching score benchmarks.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/blktiger-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bonkadv.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's adventure</name>
		<desc>Bonk's Adventure is a 2D platform video game developed by Red Company and Atlus that was released in 1989 in Japan and 1990 in North America for the TurboGrafx-16. In Japan it was released as PC Genjin (PC原人?) in 1989, a play on the Japanese name for the system, 'PC Engine'. The game was re-released for the TurboGrafx-16 in the U.S. in 1992 on the Gate of Thunder 4-in-1 game CD-ROM. The game was later ported to the NES, Game Boy, Amiga, arcade systems under different titles (FC Genjin, GB Genjin and BC Genjin). It is also available through Nintendo's Virtual Console service, on the PlayStation Store and there is a version for mobile phones in Japan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/bonkadv-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Kaneko</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./boogwing.zip</path>
		<name>Boogie Wings</name>
		<desc>Boogie Wings (known in Japan as The Great Ragtime Show) is a side-scrolling shooter arcade game released by Data East in 1992.

The player controls a biplane which can either shoot or hook enemies. The biggest characteristic of the biplane is the hook attached to its rear section. Enemies or objects that come in contact with the hook are dragged along by the plane. Dragged objects cause damage to anything they collide with, and the player can release the objects on the hook by pressing the hook button again. Dragged objects are destroyed when the player releases them from the hook, or if they collide enough times to break apart.

The ship's power gauge increases when the player taps the shot button rapidly, and filling up the gauge causes the plane to shoot a bolt of lightning that covers a large area of the screen. However, the plane overheats if the player taps the shot button too many times, so this attack must be used sparingly.

The game's graphics are highly detailed, and many of the backgrounds are likened to European towns and cities or World's fair-like scenes. Many of the game's background objects can also be destroyed or dragged around with the hook.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/boogwing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./charlien.zip</path>
		<name>Charlie Ninja</name>
		<desc>You control a cartoonish ninja-type character who must attempt to shoot all the enemies and defeat the boss at the end of each stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/charlien-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./chelnov.zip</path>
		<name>Chelnov</name>
		<desc>Atomic Runner is a side-scrolling shooter by Data East that was originally an arcade game, later being ported to the Genesis, the Sharp X68000 and eventually the Wii Shop. Its most distinctive feature is that the screen constantly auto-scrolls to the right and the protagonist runs forward automatically, except during boss fights.

Atomic Runner's base gameplay is similar to Contra, with weapon power-ups and limited platforming elements, though the automatic scrolling and near-constant forward movement also calls to mind shoot-em-ups like R-Type.

While the player character runs automatically and cannot move backward, he is able to jump, stop briefly, run faster, or turn around and run backwards in order to shoot behind him.

The game's protagonist, Chelnov, starts out as a scientist working happily alongside his father and sister. One day, his father is mortally wounded by an explosion in their home. As he dies, he reveals to Chelnov that the Deathtarians, a race claiming to have lived on Earth before humans, are responsible for the blast and have also kidnapped Chelnov's sister Chelmi.

Donning an armed, super-powered suit made by his father, Chelnov becomes the Atomic Runner and sets out to defeat the Deathtarians. However, he himself is captured and tortured by the Deathtarians. The game begins with his escape from the facility where he was being held.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/chelnov-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cotton.zip</path>
		<name>Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams</name>
		<desc>Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams is a scrolling shooter arcade game, released on Sega's Sega System 16B Arcade system board in 1989. It is the first in the Cotton series of videogames. It was ported to both the Sharp X68000 and the NEC TurboGrafx-CD in 1993. The TurboGrafx-CD version was released on Super CD-ROM and features an enhanced redbook audio soundtrack and voice acting on the Japanese release. The game was later ported to Sony PlayStation under the title Cotton Original in 1999. The PlayStation release combines the enhanced digital CD-ROM soundtrack of TurboGrafx-CD release and the gameplay/graphics of the original Arcade version. A version was ported to the Neo Geo Pocket Color in 2000. Due to hardware limitations the Neo Geo Pocket Color features less detailed graphics and sound compared to previous versions, however it is still a faithful version of the original in terms of gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/cotton-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dmnfrnt.zip</path>
		<name>Demon Front</name>
		<desc>The gameplay is similar to Metal Slug and other run and gun games. It lacks the vehicles that were an element of Metal Slug.

In addition, there are some unique features in the game. Each of the four characters brings along a pet, which can be sent to attack enemies or used as a shield. There are three buttons: Shoot, jump, and shield. Holding the shoot button charges your pet, and when released the pet launches a stationary devastating attack for a few seconds. The shield button converts the pet into a shield that is permanent - until you press the button again or it takes enough damage to disappear. Melee attacks and pet attacks release hearts which boost your shield power.

Characters include Jake and Sara, two regular humans from Earth. Dr. J, a scientist, and Maya an ape. All characters largely play the same.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/dmnfrnt-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>International Games System</developer>
		<publisher>International Games System</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./desertbr.zip</path>
		<name>Desert Breaker</name>
		<desc>Desert Breaker is an overhead run-and-gun, a sort of game which often falls into the genre of vertical shoot-em-ups. However, they differ from conventional shooters in that they allow you to go at your own pace and shoot in multiple directions instead of always moving and firing north.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/desertbr-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dietgo.zip</path>
		<name>Diet Go Go</name>
		<desc>Diet Go Go was produced by Data East in 1992.

Data East released 149 different machines in our database under this trade name, starting in 1980.

Other machines made by Data East during the time period Diet Go Go was produced include Mutant Fighter, Boogie Wings, Aaron Spelling, Hook Pinball, Lethal Weapon 3, Death Brade, Checkpoint, Wolf Fang, Joel Silver, The Pinball, and Joe &amp; Mac - Ikusae Genshizin.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/dietgo-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./eswat.zip</path>
		<name>E-SWAT: Cyber Police</name>
		<desc>Players control Duke Oda, a member of the Cyber Police force in the city of Liberty who tries to clear the streets of crime, terminate the most wanted criminals and put them behind bars. There are 15 stages to complete, which takes the player through Liberty streets, car yards, stadiums, restaurants, the CBD, and boat docks. There are bosses on some stages. During each stage, the player picks up ammunition with varying amounts. For example, on some levels, ammo may be worth 10 bullets, while in others, there may be 60 bullets.

Bosses attack in several ways. Note that the bosses are not just people. The player also battles an ape, a tiger, a monster truck in "Eagles Stadium", and cyborgs. Once these first three bosses are defeated, the player's rank rises to captain, followed by assistant chief, and finally to chief.

Once the chief rank has been achieved, the player is given a cyber suit, which is described by the game as a "long-range supersonic powered suit" which contains two Turbo-Booster Thrusters, and provides extra ammunition and protection. This suit is used for the rest of the game. At this point, the player will have to arrest criminal masterminds.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/eswat-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19890323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunbird.zip</path>
		<name>Gunbird</name>
		<desc>Gunbird uses anime-styled character as the player's chosen craft. A story plays out in between levels and before boss fights, telling a tale of how the protagonists are trying to collect pieces of a magic mirror to make a wish.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/gunbird-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunbird2.zip</path>
		<name>Gunbird 2</name>
		<desc>Seven warriors are challenged to head on a quest to find three powerful elements of Sun, Moon and Stars. Whoever brings the elements to the Potion God will be rewarded the legendary Almighty Potion and all its magical powers.[3]

Through gameplay cutscenes (and endings) it appears that the zany, uproarious (and at times rather adult) humor has considerably increased since the original Gunbird. The game has numerous similarities to the Parodius series, including the final boss in the game, a cartoon elephant playing a trumpet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/gunbird2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hcastle.zip</path>
		<name>Haunted Castle</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula sleeps for a long hundred of years. During this time, peace exists at the village and Dracula is nothing but a mere legend.

However, one day a young couple named Simon and Serena were celebrating their wedding at the village's church.

The couple were enveloped with happiness, as the wedding bells rang, their future seemed blessed...

Suddenly, the empty sky was covered with dark clouds and with a rolling thunder that shook the earth, Dracula has once again awakened. Asking for the beautiful girl's blood, he flew down during the middle of the wedding and suddenly took the bride with him.

Now in order to save Serena, Simon heads to the demon castle</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/hcastle-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./jjsquawk.zip</path>
		<name>J. J. Squawkers</name>
		<desc>J. J. Squawkers doesn't have much of story, other than brief crawl text telling the villagers fell into spells of some sort. The short intro where two birds get attacked with the house exploding to pieces is apparently why they're going on rampage to beat up everything in their eyes, so fair enough.

You play as these two angry birds named Ani Karasukun and Ototo Karasukun (altogether standing for "crow brothers" in Japanese, by the way). Along with basic ability to run and jump, they have standard projectiles attack to shoot out the enemies or destroy the objects. Your default weapon at the beginning is a handful of tomatoes. You can exchange them with better weapons by picking up the item dropped by specific enemies; available weapons include pumpkins, watermelon seeds, screws and springboards with red sneakers. Each weapon differs from others about its usefulness; for instance, screws are thrown in straight direction until they meet obstacles or the end of screen, making it easy to deal with enemies far away. On the other hand, watermelon seeds can't reach such a long distance, but they're thrown in several shots simultaneously spread in various angles, effective against the multiple enemies approaching in wide range.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/jjsquawk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Athena</developer>
		<publisher>Athena</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kidniki.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Niki: Radical Ninja</name>
		<desc>One day in Feudal Japan, Kid Niki, the most radical of ninjas, is training at his Ninja School. Suddenly, a passing bird is struck down by an arrow and lands at Niki's feet. Attached is a note explaining that Niki's girlfriend, Princess Margo, has been kidnapped by the evil Stone Wizard. With the cry of "Will help you!" Niki bursts through the wall of his school and sets off on his quest to save Margo.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/kidniki-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19861002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kungfum.zip</path>
		<name>Kung-Fu Master</name>
		<desc>Kung-Fu Master, known in Japan as Spartan X, is a 1984 beat 'em up arcade game developed and published in Japan by Irem. It was later published in North America by Data East. The Japanese version was based on the Jackie Chan movie Wheels on Meals, known as Spartan X in Japan, and credited "Paragon Films Ltd., Towa Promotion", who produced the film upon which it was based. The game is considered by many to be the first beat 'em up video game, and contains elements of Bruce Lee's Game of Death.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/kungfum-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./loht.zip</path>
		<name>Legend Of Hero Tonma</name>
		<desc>An Irem Arcade side-scrolling platformer, featuring the titular hero Tonma. His main weapon is a fireball that can be upgraded multiple times.

Legend of Hero Tonma is a 1989 Irem Arcade platformer, known for its difficulty, brightly colored graphics and its rarity in the US. The game was converted to the TurboGrafx-16 in 1993 (based on the 1991 PC Engine version) making it one of the last games to be released for the system in the US. It was later added to the Wii's Virtual Console in 2007.

The game is graphically similar to Wonder Boy, but is also structured similarly to Ghouls n' Ghosts. The player must pass through areas filled with enemies, trying to survive long enough to upgrade their fireballs to the point where it becomes far easier to cope.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/loht-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mcatadv.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Cat Adventure</name>
		<desc>A cat encounters many obstacles and enemies while traveling through various terrains.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/mcatadv-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wintechno</developer>
		<publisher>Wintechno</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mysticri.zip</path>
		<name>Mystic Riders</name>
		<desc>Mystic Riders is a 2D side-scrolling shoot'em up game set in a fantasy world, similar in style to Cotton. The player controls a child witch riding on a broomstick. Gameplay is very typical - the player flies right, shoots enemies like ghosts, grim reapers, bats, dragons, gargoyles etc., and collects bonuses and power-ups. The witch can charge shoot to deal more damage. The game has six levels and a multiplayer mode for 2 players.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/mysticri-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./nspirit.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Spirit</name>
		<desc>A ninja-based action game that has the player leading Moonlight through numerous enemy-riddled levels on a quest to exact revenge against his father's murderer. To accomplish this task Moonlight is armed with a katana, shurikens, bombs, and a sickle and chain weapon. Each weapon offers its own advantages and must be used at certain times to overcome specific obstacles or opponents. 

The game's coin-op origins are evident in the fact that that the home versions do not have passwords or saves. To compensate for this, however, adjustable difficulty settings were added.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/nspirit-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./osman.zip</path>
		<name>Osman</name>
		<desc>It is the late 21st century, and the world has come under the control of a single federal government. One day a new threat known as Abdullah the Slaver appears, causing widespread terror and panic. The fear in men's hearts incites the abandonment of all economic activity. The federal government, which is the foundation of capitalism and modern civilization, has become nothing less than an insidious idea that corrupts the foundations of society itself. It destroys the idiosyncrasies and variations among national viewpoints, stifling them in the name of "freedom" and its own internal ideals.

Judicial Affairs Director Jack Layzon alone grasps the situation, fearing the worst. He summons the lone assassin who had mastered the 'secret style'...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/osman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pang.zip</path>
		<name>Pang</name>
		<desc>The Buster brothers must finish a round-the-world quest to destroy bouncing balloons that are terrorizing several of Earth’s landmarks and cities. The fight to save the Earth begins on Mt. Fuji, Japan where the brothers must pass all three stages before moving on to the next location.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/pang-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./puckman.zip</path>
		<name>Puck-Man</name>
		<desc>The original Japanese Version of Pac-Man. The player controls Puck-Man through a maze, eating Puck-dots (also called pellets). When all Puck-dots are eaten, Puck-Man is taken to the next stage. Between some stages one of three intermission animations plays. Four enemies (Akabei, Pinky, Aosuke and Guzuta) roam the maze, trying to catch Puck-Man. If an enemy touches Puck-Man, a life is lost and the Puck-Man itself withers and dies. When all lives have been lost, the game ends. Puck-Man is awarded a single bonus life at 10,000 points by default.

Near the corners of the maze are four larger, flashing dots known as power pellets that provide Puck-Man with the temporary ability to eat the enemies. The enemies turn deep blue, reverse direction and usually move more slowly. When an enemy is eaten, its eyes remain and return to the center box where it is regenerated in its normal color. Blue enemies flash white to signal that they are about to become dangerous again and the length of time for which the enemies remain vulnerable varies from one stage to the next, generally becoming shorter as the game progresses. In later stages, the enemies go straight to flashing, bypassing blue, which means that they can only be eaten for a short amount of time, although they still reverse direction when a power pellet is eaten; in even later stages, the ghosts do not become edible (i.e., they do not change color and still make Puckman lose a life on contact), but they still reverse direction.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/puckman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19800522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./raiden.zip</path>
		<name>Raiden</name>
		<desc>In the year 2090, Earth has suddenly become the target of deranged aliens. Following the invasion, a new cutting-edge weapon, the Raiden Supersonic Attack Figther, based on the destroyed alien craft, is created for humanity's hope for survival.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/raiden-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu</developer>
		<publisher>Fabtek</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./shadoww.zip</path>
		<name>Shadow Warriors</name>
		<desc>Ninja Gaiden (NINJA 外伝?) is a series of video games by Tecmo featuring the ninja Ryu Hayabusa as its protagonist. The series was originally known as Ninja Ryukenden (忍者龍剣伝 Ninja Ryūkenden?, lit. "Legend of the Ninja Dragon Sword") in Japan. The word "gaiden" in the North American Ninja Gaiden title means "side-story" in Japanese, even though the Ninja Gaiden series is not a spinoff of a previous series. The original arcade version and first two NES games were released as Shadow Warriors in PAL regions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/shadoww-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19881001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./spang.zip</path>
		<name>Super Pang</name>
		<desc>The world has come under attack and it is up to you as a Super Buster Brother to ensure that the world is cleared of all bouncing bubbles. Every time you shoot a bubble, it breaks into two smaller ones. But be careful! If a bubble touches you, you're history! Whether you play in the Panic Mode or the Tour Mode, the challenges will keep you on your toes! In the Panic Mode, bubbles large and small pour down for 99 levels of exhilaration. In the Tour Mode, you will travel the world in search of new and explosive bubble bottles. Enjoy the action, but be alert! As you progress through the levels, the game becomes more exciting as the bubbles bounce faster and faster.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/spang-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./swatpolc.zip</path>
		<name>Swat Police</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/swatpolc-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ESD</developer>
		<publisher>ESD</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ninjak.zip</path>
		<name>The Ninja Kids</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/ninjak-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./uccops.zip</path>
		<name>Undercover Cops</name>
		<desc>Dr. Clayborn and his henchmen have taken control of the city! Commissioner Gordon (no, Batman is not in the game) makes one last plea for help and calls three of New York's Finest undercover cops : Bubba, an ex-professional football player; Flame, a former Miss America; and Claude, a retired philosophy teacher. They must fight every lackey and vanquish Dr. Clayborn in order to restore law and order to the city. Very fun beat 'em up where almost anything can be used as a weapon; fish, rocks, i-beams, cars, etc.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/uccops-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./wboy.zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy</name>
		<desc>Wonder Boy (also known as Super Wonder Boy for its Sega Mark III release in Japan and Revenge of Drancon for its Game Gear release in North America) is a 1986 video game published by Sega and developed by Escape (now known as WestOne Bit Entertainment, not to be confused with Westone).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/wboy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kikcubic.zip</path>
		<name>Kickle Cubicle</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/kikcubic-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./uccopsar.zip</path>
		<name>Undercover Cops Alpha Renewal</name>
		<desc>Dr. Clayborn and his henchmen have taken control of the city! Commissioner Gordon (no, Batman is not in the game) makes one last plea for help and calls three of New York's Finest undercover cops : Bubba, an ex-professional football player; Flame, a former Miss America; and Claude, a retired philosophy teacher. They must fight every lackey and vanquish Dr. Clayborn in order to restore law and order to the city. Very fun beat 'em up where almost anything can be used as a weapon; fish, rocks, i-beams, cars, etc.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/fba/uccopsar-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pgm.zip</path>
		<name>PGM (Polygame Master) System BIOS</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
</gameList>
