<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda (GST).zip</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda (GST)</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T022110</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (Patched).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (Patched)</name>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T191733</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1943 - The Battle of Midway.zip</path>
		<name>1943: The Battle of Midway</name>
		<desc>The game is set in the Pacific theater of World War II, off the coast of the Midway Atoll. The goal is to attack the Japanese Air Fleet that bombed the players' American Aircraft Carrier, pursue all Japanese Air and Sea forces, fly through the 16 levels of play, make their way to the Japanese battleship Yamato and destroy her. 11 Levels consist of an Air-to-Sea battle (with a huge battleship or an aircraft carrier as an End-Level Boss), while 5 levels consist of an all-aerial battle against a squadron of Japanese Bombers and a Mother Bomber that needs to be destroyed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/1943 - The Battle of Midway-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T023720</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hudson's Adventure Island.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island</name>
		<desc>You just found out that Princess Leilani was kidnapped by the Evil Witch Doctor and taken to Adventure Island in the South Pacific.

You land on Adventure Island without weapons or food. The island is thick with tropical forest, mountains and caves. Hidden on the island are your skateboard, axe, food and other helpful tools you must find by exploring the island.

Better find the weapons and food quickly because you will need them to fight the Witch Doctor's spiders, snakes, bats and demons. The Evil Witch Doctor has set lots of traps for you before you can face him one on one. Are you up for the challenge?! Can you live through Adventure Island to save Princess Leilani?!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hudson's Adventure Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170219T023736</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hudson's Adventure Island II.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island II</name>
		<desc>Soar into action with Adventure Island II. That Evil Witch Doctor's just snatched your favorite lady. And you've got to battle your way past EIGHT treacherous islands to get her back.
Combat prehistoric monsters -- some of the creepiest, fire-spitting critters ever to slither across a video screen! Survive molten volcanoes. Dodge giant scorpions and king cobras. And the action gets even crazier with a new vertical/horizontal scroll, while stage select lets you control play.
So sharpen your axe, slip on a leopard skin, and take off for ADVENTURE ISLAND II. It's gonna be a wild ride!!!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hudson's Adventure Island II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.73333</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170203T234252</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Dino Riki, The.zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Dino Riki</name>
		<desc>Somewhere in the land of dinosaurs, a hero known as Dino-Riki sets out to battle against the beasts of the ancient times and prove man's right to survival amongst evolution. You control Dino-Riki from a top-down perspective as the screen scrolls towards the top. Dino Riki must shoot the enemies in his way as well as leap over pits and avoid obstacles. His chances improve when he obtains weapon power-ups such as fireballs or boomerangs. Angel Wings also help and let Dino Riki fly above the ground. At the end of each level, Dino-Riki faces off against a boss creature.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Adventures of Dino Riki, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Lolo 3.zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Lolo 3</name>
		<desc>The journey continues! The game preferred by the best and the brightest is back with a brand new installment. See if you qualify!

Seventeen levels, one hundred rooms. Play as either Lolo or Lala. Underwater levels with new challenges. Lolo's Grandpa teaches you the tricks of the game. New tactics, techniques and characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Adventures of Lolo 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Dracula.zip</path>
		<name>Akumajou Special: Boku Dracula-kun</name>
		<desc>The self-proclaimed Demon King, Kid Dracula, has awoken from a long sleep, only to discover that the demon Galamoth has challenged him. Swiping his father's cape, it is then up to Kid Dracula to set out on an adventure to destroy the monster, and retake his throne. After battling through dangers and demons, Kid Dracula defeats Galamoth. This causes him to become famous throughout the land, with all the monsters in Transylvania showing up at his castle wanting to be his friend.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kid Dracula-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170203T013521</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alfred Chicken.zip</path>
		<name>Alfred Chicken</name>
		<desc>Super-Hero with a Bionic Beak! Whoa... Alfred needs your help! The Evil Meka-Chickens have raided the hen house and stolen Alfred's chick, Floella, and all the little egg-a-roonies! Now, these turkeys say they'll scramble the eggs. It's nothing to crow about! An egg-xasperated Alfred Chicken struts off to pluck his loved ones from the dangers of the Meka-Chickens' world. Remember, while Alfred is a super-hero wannabe, he's still a ruffled-feather chicken... you gotta help!

Egg-splore way out worlds and warp space. Fight fowl feasting fiends. Find fine feathered friends. Make Meka-Chickens mincemeat. After you play this game, who you think is "Chicken" will never be the same!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Alfred Chicken-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Twilight Games</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arkanoid.zip</path>
		<name>Arkanoid</name>
		<desc>It's a real block-buster!

Use your special Vaus controller to shatter the walls of the space system in 33 amazing rounds of a fight for survival!

Control the action of your adventure with the high speed controller included. Use with Arkanoid now... use with other great Taito games to come.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Arkanoid-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Balloon Fight.zip</path>
		<name>Balloon Fight</name>
		<desc>The player controls the unnamed Balloon Fighter with two balloons attached to his back. Repeatedly pressing the A or B buttons causes the Balloon Fighter to flap his arms and rise into the air. If a balloon is popped, the player's flotation is decreased, making it harder to rise. A life is lost if both balloons are popped by enemy Balloon Fighters, if the player falls in the water, gets eaten by the large fish near the surface of the water, or is hit by lightning.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Balloon Fight-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banana Prince.zip</path>
		<name>Banana Prince</name>
		<desc>Confront the Great King’s evil forces on the action stages! Power-up on the dice game stages!

The Banana Prince and his peaceful Banana Kingdom is suddenly under attack by the evil Great King and his army  of peppers.  They leave the kingdom devastated and take off with their holy Banana. The courageous Prince swears revenge and justice for his kingdom by bringing the Great King down and returning the sacred Banana. And so begins the story of the young Banana Prince as he sets out on a long journey in what will be  his greatest heroic adventure.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Banana Prince-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KID</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Barker Bill's Trick Shooting.zip</path>
		<name>Barker Bill's Trick Shooting</name>
		<desc>Barker Bill is your host. Join him and assistant Tricksie for arcade-style Trick Shooting! Get out your Zapper video gun. Blast floating balloons before they drift away. But, don't hit the friendly dog - he'll get mad! Rack up points by shooting spinning plates tossed by Barker Bill and Tricksie. They are happy when you make a shot, but scold you when you miss! Shoot around window panes to knock falling targets out of the picture! Take aim at tomatoes, eggs and watermelons before they land on poor Tricksie's head! So, set your sites for a day at the carnival with Tricksie and Barker Bill!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Barker Bill's Trick Shooting-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman Returns.zip</path>
		<name>Batman Returns</name>
		<desc>Frigid winter winds swept over an already chilled Gotham City. Random street crimes were running at an all-time high, despite the holidays. Down below, in the city's frozen sewers, Oswald Cobblepot, known as The Penguin, planned more mayhem and schemed the take over of the fightened metropolis. His loyal army of missle-packing Penguin Commandos and the bizarre Red Triangle Circus Gang are energized by the evil genius of the web-footed orphan. A desperate call to Batman goes up. Partner with Batman to salvage Gotham City from The Penguin's cold-hearted plot. Guide him in swift, life-like moves from dark alleys to rooftops in vivid scenes based on the hit movie, "Batman Returns." Control his combat style, and help conduct relentless interrogations of The Penguins many allies. Use the Batcave computer to input clues, analyze evidence, and review enemy bios. You're in charge of weapons, too. Stock Batman's Utility belt with enough heat to match the diverse fighting styles of The Penguin and cold-blooded, sewer-dwelling minions. Gotham City is in trouble.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Batman Returns-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - Return of the Joker.zip</path>
		<name>Batman: Return of the Joker</name>
		<desc>The seedy underworld is crawling with criminals. Even worse - the JOKER is back on top of 'em all! Law and order means nothing... until now! Because BATMAN is here - and the action is hotter than ever! Ear-crunching sound effects. Pulse-quickening music. Graphics that are as hot as 16-bit. And this time, BATMAN hits fast and hard. Flying, leaping, and sliding to attack! And striking at the heart of the JOKER. The CAPED CRUSADER has a totally new arsenal at his command: Batarang, Crossbow, Sonic Neutralizer. He's even got a superfueled jetpack. And even more powerful weapons at the touch of a button. BATMAN has got to use all of his power. Because this world is a very dark place, and you never know where the JOKER is hiding!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Batman - Return of the Joker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Video Game.zip</path>
		<name>Batman: The Video Game</name>
		<desc>He's totally new. Totally tough. And he'll stop at nothing to make sure justice prevails! From the dark streets of GOTHAM CITY to the deepest corners of the criminal underworld comes the CAPED CRUSADER as you've never seen him before. Incredibly strong. Armed to the teeth. And ready to put his life on the line for the sake of all, on a search-and-destroy mission to end the Joker's reign of terror. He leaps, he flies, he dodges enemy fire and delivers it right back... with a vengeance. This is no kid stuff. This is as real as video gaming gets. If you liked what you saw in the movie, you're gonna love what you see here. Because this time around, BATMAN is all business, and he won't let anything stand in his way!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Batman - The Video Game-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6166699999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19891222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>After her defeat by the Galactic Corporation at the battle of Canis Major, the evil Dark Queen and her renegade space troops retreat to the outer reaches of the universe, hiding out in dark spaces between the stars. Meanwhile, on board the spaceship Vulture, Professor T. Bird and the trio of Battletoads - Rash, Zitz and Pimple - are escorting the Princess Angelica back to her home planet, where her father, the Terran Emperor, awaits her safe arrival. Along the way, Pimple, the biggest Battletoad, takes Angelica out for a cruise in the Toadster to a nearby Leisure Station, but the Dark Queen ambushes them before they can get there, and they are kidnapped and carried away to Ragnarok's World, the Dark Queen's planet. Professor Bird sends remaining Battletoads down on Ragnarok to save Pimple and Angelica, but it will be a hard battle against planet's dangerous environments, traps and Dark Queen's troops. They have to go a long way from the planet's rough surface to deep caves and landed Gargantua and ultimately to the Tower of Shadows, where the Dark Queen awaits.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Battletoads-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.575</rating>
		<releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon</name>
		<desc>When a battlecruiser the size of a city and called the Colossus smashes out of the moon, its laser cannon glowing menacingly, you can bet it ain't gonna be makin' no social calls... You can bet it's gonna be creating some bad n' crazy mayhem on good ol' planet Earth - 'specially when you know that the dreaded Dark Queen and the shady Shadow Boss are on board just rarin' to rock n' roll... The dastardly duo are about to unleash their most monstrous plan yet - from their secret lunar base they intend to launch an invasion that'll make them masters of the world... Neutralized by deadly glooming rays, Earth's forces are powerless... That is, until the Dragons join the 'Toads! Take a toadacious trip with the dream ticket as those terrific twins Billy and Jimmy Lee team up with Zitz, Flash and Pimple against the combined might of the gruesome twosome and their mindless minions Big Blag, Abobo, Robo-Manus and Roper, in a toadally new adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master.zip</path>
		<name>Blaster Master</name>
		<desc>You've fallen down a hidden manhole into a world of creatures so terrifying they'd scare the rats away. You can panic and perish, or blast your way through an endless maze of tunnels, searching for the secret passages to your escape. And that's the easy part. Because the Masters of the Caverns lay waiting - prehistoric creatures so powerful, so gigantic, they literally fill your screen! So load your arsenal and get ready for BlasterMaster.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Blaster Master-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.73333</rating>
		<releasedate>19880617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble Part 2.zip</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble: Part 2</name>
		<desc>A new breed of heroes! Cubby and Rubby, descendants of the famous Bubby, must battle the Skull Brothers and their army of fiends to rescue a friend in danger. Fortunately, our dinosaur heroes can blow bubbles that will destroy their foes. They will rain fire, floods and tornado!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Bubble Bobble Part 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ITL</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bucky O'Hare.zip</path>
		<name>Bucky O'Hare</name>
		<desc>BUCKY'S GONNA NEED A LOT OF LUCK FROM HIS RABBIT'S FOOT!

Today's newest renegade space hero, Captain Bucky O'Hare, faces his greatest challenge. His crew, Dead Eye Duck, Blinky, Jenny the Aldeberan Cat and the genius earth boy Willy DuWitt, have been captured by the Toad Empire. Now you must play the role of Bucky, blasting past the fiercest toads in the Aniverse. It's an intense arcade action battle with eight hare-raising levels. Luckily, when you rescue a crew member you can assume their identity and take advantage of their unique fighting skills, like Jenny's Super Mind Blast and Willy's Laser Cannon... WE INTERUPT THIS PACKAGE FOR A SPECIAL BULLETIN FROM TOAD HEADQUARTERS!

Greetings, warthead. This is the Toad Air Marshall, coming to you live from the Toad Magma Tanker. I'm here to smash an ugly rumor goin' around that says you're thinking about becoming Bucky O'Hare in a futile attempt to rescue the captured crew of the Righteous Ingignation.

Fool! Those lunkhead traitors are guided by the elite Storm Toad Troopers in four toad prisons hidden throughout the planetoid belt, from the Way-Cool Ice Planet to the Burnin' Hunk of Lava Star. So don't even mess with us toads, you wart for brains hare-ball. 'Cause it you do, I'll have to blast ya Toad Battle Cruisers and Double Bubble High Speed Toad Armada Tanks. That ain't the worst of it, pal! Once I've got your pointy ears in my sights, I'll drop the big bomb with Crater Centipedes, Robosnakes and triple threat Triborgs that your laser-guided Wart Remover doesn't have a shot against.

Face it rabbit. Try to croak us toads, and you'll be one unlucky Bucky!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Bucky O'Hare-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<desc>If you think it's scary on the outside, wait'll you see the basement! You're in for the longest night of your life. Ghosts, goblins, demons, wolves, bats - creatures lurking around every corner. As you descend deeper and deeper, they get thicker and thicker. Better stick close to the cavern floor - it's your only chance of finding a weapon or two. You're gonna need 'em. Because when you finally meet the Count, you know he'll be going for the jugular. So keep your courage up and your stake sharp. And say your prayers!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Castlevania-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>6</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170208T230105</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania III: Dracula's Curse</name>
		<desc>Led by the immortal Count Dracula, the greatest army of evil ever assembled is poised to bury mankind in a Tomb of Terror. Destroying this legion of Swamp Dragons, Slasher Skeletons and Forces of the Undead will be the supreme challenge for the mightiest of warriors. Your place in history is 100 years before Simon Belmont's birth. Dracula is young at heart, and it will take more than a stake to penetrate his evil. Luckily, you command the role of Trevor - Simon's forefather and the origin of the Belmont Warlord Chromosones. Trevor has a power never before seen by human eyes - the power to transform into three different spirits: Grant DaNasty, the ferocious Ghost Pirate. Sypha, the Mystic Warlord. And Alucard, Dracula's forgotten son. You must perfectly time Trevor's body transformations to match up his different fighting spirits against Ultimate Evils. Trevor also has the strength and wisdom to command the Battle Axe, Invisibility Potion and Mystic Whip. But the most important weapon Trevor has is your cunning to choose the correct Paths of Fate and your bravery to lead him past 17 possible levels of never-ending doom, including the Haunted Ship of Fools, the Sunken City of Poltergeists, the Clock Tower of Untimely Death and Curse Castle. Never before have so many dangers confronted you at one time. And if by some miracle you triumph, you'll no longer be a mere mortal. You'll be a legend who'll live forever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.72</rating>
		<releasedate>19921222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Overflow Darkness.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Overflow Darkness</name>
		<desc>In a small village in Transylvania the Belmont clan lived to protect the world from Dracula's curse. Simon succeeded in his task... but something went wrong. Ten years after he defeated Dracula a group of cultists rose Dracula and his Castle! It's up to Simon to go back and slay the Count!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Castlevania - Overflow Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dr. Mario</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170208T055157</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers.zip</path>
		<name>Chip 'N Dale Rescue Rangers</name>
		<desc>Chip and Dale, those pint-sized but courageous Disney detectives, have received another desperate call for help: The evil Fat Cat has kidnapped Gadget... his sinister goal - to take over the city!! Join the Rescue Rangers on their exciting search through the darkest depths of slimy sewers to the electrifying heights of live telephone wires! Play alone or with a friend to locate Fat Cat's headquarters and thwart his diabolical scheme! Fat Cat's Bad Guys: Can you escape them or do you stand and fight? Deadly Attacking Killer Bees: Can you out run them or do you let them bite? Rabid Robot Rats and Mechanical Dogs: Are you saved from their savage jaws or do you bite them back?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers 2.zip</path>
		<name>Chip 'N Dale Rescue Rangers 2</name>
		<desc>Chip and Dale, those tiny but daring detectives, have learned of some terrifying news: The notorious criminal cat has escaped from prison and he's stolen the Urn of the Pharaoh. The Rescue Rangers must once again assemble to help crack the case of the missing urn and return the feline felon, Fat Cat, back to the slammer. Join Chip and Dale and the rest of the Rangers in their wacky new adventure. Help them explore the dangerous levels of the downtown restaurant and meet the exploding personality of Water Rabbit. Aid them on their escape through the freezing floors of the giant refrigerator. Search the ghostly walls of the haunted warehouse and find the final clue to unravel the secret headquarters of Fat Cat.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Circus Charlie.zip</path>
		<name>Circus Charlie</name>
		<desc>You are Charlie, a member of a circus troupe. Your job is to please the crowd by performing five death-defying stunts..</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Circus Charlie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Soft Pro</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Clash at Demonhead.zip</path>
		<name>Clash at Demonhead</name>
		<desc>Clash at Demonhead is an open-ended platformer. The player takes control of Billy "Big Bang" Blitz, who is capable of running, jumping, and shooting. He is initially armed with a handgun, though various upgrades can be purchased from a shop. He later gains the ability to perform various powers by collecting Force, including shrinking, teleportation to previously-visited areas, flight, healing, and invincibility. The player chooses levels from a world map that consists of over forty routes. Various objectives must be met to complete the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Clash at Demonhead-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra.zip</path>
		<name>Contra</name>
		<desc>The universe teeters on the brink of total annihilation at the hands of the vile alien warmonger, Red Falcon. Earth's only hope rests with you, a courageous member of the Special Forces elite commando squad. Your mission: Battle deep into the deadly Amazon jungle, where the Red Falcon and his galactic henchmen have transformed ancient Mayan temples into awesome monuments dedicated to mass destruction. A multitude of weapons, from rapid-fire machine guns to high-tech lasers are at your disposal as you sweat blood, fighting past 3-D mazes, underground security systems, and tropical forests surrounded by giant waterfalls and alien cannons. This is the ultimate test for the ultimate guerilla warrior. And if you survive, Earth survives!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Contra-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7428600000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19870220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra Force.zip</path>
		<name>Contra Force</name>
		<desc>Commandos Burn, Smith, Beans and Iron are a special forces team who have seen more than their fair share of action. Neo City is their post, now that a terrorist group known as D.N.M.E. is bombarding its citizens with a typhoon of a crime wave. The C-Force has been asked to stop them, no matter what. Take command solo or team up with a comrade in 2-player mode. Even if you go it alone, you can call on a backup soldier for spot support. Tap into your special forces training to devise unique battle plans and attack patterns, select weapons, and decide which soldier's individual strengths are best suited for the dirty deeds going down. You can switch commandos whenever the situation calls for it. Endure all 5 grueling missions, swarming with traps and terrorists, that take place in a warehouse, on a battleship, at a construction site, aboard a helicopter, and at C-Force headquarters. Encounter secret passageways, hidden rooms, aerial angle views and more. Every man is a walking arsenal with heavy-duty weaponry including rocket launchers, flame throwers, bazookas, rifles, land mines and time bombs. This mission is no cakewalk, but if it was, they wouldn't have given it to you. Hit it with all you've got!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Contra Force-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crisis Force.zip</path>
		<name>Crisis Force</name>
		<desc>The denizens of Atlantis have arisen after a slumber of 10,000 years, and only Asuka and Maya can save the world from destruction in their Aurawing aircraft!  Crisis Force was Konami's last shoot-'em-up game for the Famicom, and it pushes the hardware to its absolute limits.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Crisis Force-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystalis.zip</path>
		<name>Crystalis</name>
		<desc>You must save the world from evil magic by finding the four powerful swords that form Crystalis.

After the apocalypse, magic returns to Earth.

A blessed group of good-intentioned sorcerers have used their new magical powers to rebuild the Earth, but an evil sorcerer named Dragonia has combined his supernatural forces with man-made technology to devastate the rebuilt Earth. It is your mission to recover four mystical swords, and combine them to form the ultimate blade: the Sword of Crystalis. This legendary weapon is the only tool which can put an end to Dragonia's black reign.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Crystalis-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkwing Duck.zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Darkwing Duck</name>
		<desc>The kingpins of crime are at it again! The mysterious criminal organization F.O.W.L. has hatched a plan to take control of the peaceful city of St. Canard. Six of their most heinous henchmen are running rampant through the city and only the daring Darkwing Duck can bring them to justice! Join Darkwing as he explores the woods to weed out Bushroot's evil plan. Search the warehouses along the wharf for Mega Volt and pull the plug on an electrifying scheme. Track down all six of FOWL's crafty criminals and then prepare yourself as Darkwing squares off against the sinister Steelbeak in his fiendish floating fortress!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Darkwing Duck-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Mermaid, The.zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Little Mermaid</name>
		<desc>Ariel, the little mermaid who became human, and Eric, prince of the land, are head over fins in love. But Ariel's friends are in deep trouble! Ursula, the evil Witch of the Sea, has cast a spell on all watery creatures. If Ursula's not stopped, she'll take over the ocean! To save her friends, Ariel dives into the sea, becoming a mermaid again. But the water is full of jellyfish, lobsters, eels, and blowfish. Ariel quickly snares the fierce fish, while diving and leaping to escape danger. At Ursula's palace, the wicked witch attacks with her most treacherous tricks. Can Ariel defeat her in time to save the sea? It's the catch of the year! Swim to Ariel's favorite music, including the Academy Award-winning Under the Sea. Gasp as Ariel tackles slithery eels, snarling sharks, walruses and the amazing Soldierfish. Find out if Ariel can ever return to Eric. Your whole family will fall hook, line, and sinker for The Little Mermaid!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Little Mermaid, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doki Doki Panic!.zip</path>
		<name>Doki doki panic (fds conversion)</name>
		<desc>This game is an FDS conversion for NES
The game takes place inside a book. The book's story tells of the land of Mu, where the quality of dreams determined the quality of the weather the next day. Because of this, the Mu citizens invented a dream machine so they could always have good dreams. One day, an evil toad named Mamu (whose name was changed to Wart for Super Mario Bros. 2) invaded the land and twisted the dream machine into a nightmare machine. However, the Mu people learned of his weakness to vegetables, and used them to defeat him.

The book had found its way into an Arabian family. Their pet monkey, Rusa, gives the book to twins Poki and Piki. However, the twins quarrel and end up ripping out the last page of the book, causing its ending to be erased. Mamu, freed, reaches through the pages and grabs the twins, pulling them into the book. Rusa gets the twins' parents, Mama and Papa, their brother, Imajin, and sister, Lina, and they enter the book to rescue them</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Doki Doki Panic!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Can you save Mario's girl from the clutches of Donkey Kong? Donkey Kong has kidnapped Mario's girlfriend Pauline and taken her to the top of a construction site. It's up to you to help Mario save Pauline before time runs out. But it won't be easy. Donkey Kong will do everything in his power to stop you. He'll throw barrel bombs, flaming fireballs and anything else he can get his hands on. So if you're looking for action, don't monkey around. Get the original Donkey Kong from the Nintendo Arcade Classics Series!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Donkey Kong-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.78</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 3.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 3</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong is at it again! This time he's loose in the greenhouse. And he's got company: a swarm of very pesky bees! It's up to you to get Donkey Kong out of the greenhouse and exterminate the bees... without hurting the flowers. But that's easier said than done! Because Donkey Kong has plenty of coconuts to hurl at you, and those bees know just where to sting you so it hurts. But, if you keep your wits about you, you'll score lots of points and have lots of laughs in the best Donkey Kong of them all... DONKEY KONG 3!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Donkey Kong 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840704T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon II - The Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon II: The Revenge</name>
		<desc>The Double Dragons - Billy and Jimmy Lee - are back to avenge the loss of Marion! In their quest to defeat the evil Shadow Warriors, the martial arts duo are challenged in 9 incredible missions, facing ruthless street gangs, nunchaku-toting ninja and giant mutant warriors! The non-stop action winds its way through construction sites, alleyways and underwater hideouts complete with secret elevator shafts, spiked ceilings and razor-sharp mechanical claws! And in a bonus mission, never before seen, the duo's worst fear becomes reality as they fight the ultimate battle between good and evil. A battle where not only their lives are at stake, but the fate of the entire world!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Double Dragon II - The Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.675</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Technos Japan</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Buster.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Buster</name>
		<desc>In the beginning, a prince named Clovis was born the son of the kingdom's chief bodyguard to the royal Lawrence family. As a young child, Clovis was very mischievous and undisciplined, so his father thought it might be best to place him under the care of a monk who lived in the woods far from the kingdom. Under the monk's care, Clovis began to learn various aspects of knowledge, including how to be a superior swordsman. When word reached the monk that King Lawrence's 16-year-old daughter Celia had been abducted and held by a fearsome dragon, who wished to break the kingdom's spirit and coerce the kingdom to do his bidding, Clovis felt a sense of duty to chase after the dragon and rescue Celia in the name of his father. In order to save his sister, he trained daily with the monk and learned to withstand injury, whether cut by swords or burned by flame, and still be just as capable a fighter as ever.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Dragon Buster-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior III.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
		<desc>Dragon Warrior III is noted for greatly expanding upon the original Dragon Warrior and Dragon Warrior II. The game uses basic console role-playing game conventions, such as leveling up by gaining experience points and equipping items. Battle is turn-based like the other games in the series.
Dragon Warrior III features a class system, in which each character has a certain class. While the Hero always keeps the Hero class, the other characters can choose among the following: Soldier (Warrior in the GBC version), Fighter, Pilgrim (Cleric), Wizard (Mage), Merchant (Dealer), Goof-Off (Jester), Sage, and Thief which was available only in the later versions. The choice of class greatly affects the character's stats and spells he or she can learn. Furthermore, upon reaching experience Level 20, a character has the option of changing classes at the temple of Dhama, found halfway through the game. The game starts with just the Hero in the party, who then is able to recruit a party of three at the local tavern. Unlike most Dragon Quest parties, aside from the Hero, the party is not made up of characters involved in the story. Although only four characters can be in the party at a time, extra members of the party can be kept at the tavern, allowing room for new recruits. Another innovation is an arena where the player can place bets on the outcome of monster battles.
The remakes incorporated some interface changes from later games in the series, such as simplified door opening; the bag, which replaced bank item storage; the item sorting "Tidy Item" and "Tidy Bag" commands; and the "Full HP" command, which can be used outside of combat to automate the process of casting healing and status restoring spells.
While the earlier Dragon Quest games were also non-linear, Dragon Quest III was the most substantial example of open-world gameplay among the early Dragon Quest games. It also allowed the player to swap characters in and out of the party at will, and another "major innovation was the introduction of day/night cycles; certain items, characters, and quests are only accessible at certain times of day."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Dragon Warrior III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5333300000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Hunt.zip</path>
		<name>Duck Hunt</name>
		<desc>In Duck Hunt, players use the Nintendo Zapper Light Gun and attempt to shoot down either ducks or clay pigeons in mid-flight.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Duck Hunt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19840421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales.zip</path>
		<name>DuckTales</name>
		<desc>Bless me bagpipes! When will that thrillseeker, Scrooge McDuck, ever quit? Never one to turn away from adventure, Uncle Scrooge has taken on his greatest challenge - to discover the legendary Five Lost Treasures and become the "Richest Duck in the World!" Join Scrooge and the DUCKTALES gang: gung-ho flying ace, Launchpad; the nephews, Huey, Dewey and Louie; and little Webby, on their search. Together they must trek through the treacherous Amazon Jungle, down into the diamond mines of Africa, and even to the moon! Are you "Duck" enough to join them on their adventure? Come along to Duckburg Headquarters and see for yourself!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Duck Tales-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.775</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales 2.zip</path>
		<name>DuckTales 2</name>
		<desc>Scrooge McDuck is hot on the trail of the richest adventure ever. Pieces to the map of the Lost Treasure of McDuck have been scattered across the globe, and Scrooge must find them before the greedy Flintheart Glomgold grabs them. It's going to be a race to the finish as both of them try to find the treasure and become the richest duck in the world! Join Scrooge and his nephews as they explore the ancient pyramids of Egypt and do battle with swash-buckling pirates in the Bermuda Triangle. Help them search the haunted halls of an ancient Scottish castle and scale the watery heights of Niagara Falls. Aid Scrooge in his quest for the secret of the island of Mu and you'll gain the final clue to unravel the hidden location of the Lost Treasure of McDuck!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Duck Tales 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.56667</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthbound Zero.zip</path>
		<name>EarthBound Zero</name>
		<desc>Mother is a 1989 Japanese role-playing video game developed by Ape and published by Nintendo for the Famicom (Nintendo Entertainment System). The game is modeled on Dragon Quest series gameplay but is set in a late 20th century United States, unlike its fantasy genre contemporaries. Mother follows the young Ninten as he uses his great-grandfather's psychic powers to fight hostile, formerly inanimate objects and other enemies. The game uses random encounters to enter a menu-based, first-person perspective battle system. It is the first game in the Mother series. Writer and copywriter Shigesato Itoi pitched the game concept to Shigeru Miyamoto when visiting Nintendo for other business. Though Miyamoto denied the proposal at first, he eventually gave Itoi a development team. The game was released in Japan on July 27, 1989. A North American version was localized into English but abandoned as commercially unviable. A copy of this prototype was later found and circulated on the Internet as EarthBound Zero.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Earthbound Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ape</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Esper Dream.zip</path>
		<name>Esper Dream</name>
		<desc>Esper Dream 2: Aratanaru Tatakai is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Esper Dream-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KONAMI</developer>
		<publisher>KONAMI</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Esper Dream 2 - Aratanaru Tatakai.zip</path>
		<name>Esper Dream 2: Aratanaru Tatakai</name>
		<desc>Esper Dream 2: Aratanaru Tatakai is a Role-Playing game, developed and published by Konami, which was released in Japan in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Esper Dream 2 - Aratanaru Tatakai-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KONAMI</developer>
		<publisher>KONAMI</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike.zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike</name>
		<desc>Whether the player chooses to race solo or against computer-assisted riders, he/she races against a certain time limit. The goal is to qualify for the Excitebike (the championship) race by coming in at third place or above in the challenge race (preliminary race). The times to beat are located on the stadium walls (for first place) and in the lower left corner (for third place). In any race, the best time is 8 seconds ahead of third place. When the player places first, then they get a message: "It's a new record!" Additional points are earned by beating the previously-set record time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Excitebike-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.74</rating>
		<releasedate>19841130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo Research &amp; Development 1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fantasy Zone.zip</path>
		<name>Fantasy Zone (Tengen)</name>
		<desc>Imagine the wildest, wackiest place in the Universe and you've got Fantasy Zone! As Opa-Opa, a living spaceship, you'll marvel at the incredible landscapes filled with the strangest creatures. Watch out! They may look cute and innocent, but they're Menons, nasty aliens that have overrun the eight planets that make up Fantasy Zone. Your job is to clear each world of Menons. Every time you zap one, it turns into a coin. Collect enough coins and you can buy power-up items like deadlier weapons and mightier engines. At the end of every planet lurks a super-powerful boss. Find a way to blast past these monsters in order to continue your exciting journey in the Fantasy Zone!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Fantasy Zone-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JoWood</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faxanadu.zip</path>
		<name>Faxanadu</name>
		<desc>Unlock doors of legend on your journey through Faxanadu!

You are the elves’ last hope. Outside the town walls lurk monsters with the power to destroy anything in their path. Inside the walls, water and time are running out. Soon the ancient elf town of Eolis will vanish into eternity. Only you can save Eolis. No one else dares to venture beyond the walls, onto the World Tree, where towns and fortresses precariously await the whims of fate at the hands of the Evil.

You are searching for the water source and for an antidote to the poison that makes the water undrinkable. To find them you’ll need gold and food and magic, speed with a sword … and luck.

Every town holds a new mystery, every fortress a new danger. Merchants will sell you magic and valuable tools, but it’s up to you to figure out what you need. Long, secret mantras help you slip through the mists, but will you survive the next challenge?

This is Faxanadu, the legend, the adventure – the incredible journey on the World Tree.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Faxanadu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19871117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Felix the Cat.zip</path>
		<name>Felix the Cat</name>
		<desc>The game involves the player controlling Felix the Cat as he sets out to defeat the evil mad Professor who has kidnapped Felix's lovely girlfriend, Kitty. The Game Boy version plays virtually the same as the NES version, but features fewer levels.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Felix the Cat-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy 3.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>The Gulgan thus prophesied: "The earthquake was only the beginning. The great tremors that swallowed the crystals, the light of our world, only to spawn monsters from the depths of the scarred land, are nothing but harbingers of what has yet to come. Something is coming...fathomless, ominous, and full of sorrow... But hope is not yet lost. Four souls will be blessed with light, and so it shall begin...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Final Fantasy 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Freedom Force.zip</path>
		<name>Freedom Force</name>
		<desc>Players assume the role of an anti-terrorist gunman who must kill terrorists without shooting any of their hostages. The game has different levels, including an airport that has been taken over by the terrorists and a city street. The game does have some blood, but it lacks gore; a small red splotch will appear on the chest of the targets that are hit.
The screen scrolls from left to right, with terrorists or hostages popping out of windows and doors. Unlike other shooters, the powerups (being either energy, ammo or weapons) are obtained by shooting the lower-right box when an item appears there.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Freedom Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sun Corporation of America</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga - Demons of Death.zip</path>
		<name>Galaga</name>
		<desc>The objective of Galaga is to score as many points as possible by destroying insect-like enemies. The player controls a starfighter that can move left and right along the bottom of the playfield. Enemies swarm in groups in a formation near the top of the screen, and then begin flying down toward the player, firing bombs at the fighter. The game ends when the player's last fighter is lost, either by colliding with an enemy or one of its bullets, or by being captured.
Galaga introduces a number of new features over its predecessor, Galaxian. Among these is the ability to fire more than one bullet at a time, a count of the player's "hit/miss ratio" at the end of the game, and a bonus "Challenging Stage" that occurs every few levels, in which a series of enemies fly onto and out of the screen in set patterns without firing at the player's ship or trying to crash into it. These stages award a large point bonus if the player manages to destroy every enemy.
Another gameplay feature new to Galaga is the ability for enemies to capture the player's fighter. While the player is in control of just one fighter, a "boss Galaga" (which takes two shots to kill) periodically attempts to capture the fighter using a tractor beam. If successful, the fighter joins the enemy formation. If the player has more lives remaining, play resumes with a new fighter. The captured fighter flies down with the enemy that captured it, firing upon the player just like normal enemies, and can be shot and destroyed. The player can free the fighter by destroying the boss Galaga while in flight, causing the captured fighter to link up with the player's current fighter, doubling his or her firepower but also making a target twice as large.
Galaga has an exploitable bug that can cause the attackers to stop firing bullets at the player, due to a coding error. In addition, similar to the famous "Split-Screen bug" in Pac-Man, a bug exists in Galaga in which the game "rolls over" from Level 255 to Level 0. Depending on the difficulty setting of the machine, this can cause the game to stall, requiring that the machine be reset or power-cycled in order to start a new game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Galaga - Demons of Death-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.66667</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gargoyle's Quest II - The Demon Darkness.zip</path>
		<name>Gargoyle's Quest II</name>
		<desc>The Law of the Claw!

Before Man ruled the world there were the monsters of Etruria. One such beast Firebrand the Gargoyle. must act to
restore the magic that quickly fades from the Ghoul Realm. Join him on his perilous journey as he looks for the origin of a mysterious dark beam of light. 

This epic quest features a hero with leathery wings and the claws of a lion. Breathe fire at hideous creatures that hunger for your essence. Dodge magical assaults. deadly traps and cunning opponents that will stop at nothing to protect their ghastly secret! See if you have what it takes to solve riddles while battling for your very life!

-State-of-the-art Graphics with incredible Music and Sound!
-Collect magical items to boost your awesome powers!
-From the sensational hit that set the standard for Game Boy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gargoyle's Quest II - The Demon Darkness-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts'n Goblins.zip</path>
		<name>Ghosts 'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>The beautiful princess is kidnapped. Her lover, the Knight in shining armor, armed with five different weapons to fight the enemy, sets out to rescue the beautiful princess. The Knight, aided by your skill, must pass through seven different guarded gates, fighting and destroying demons, dragons, giants and zombies. There are hidden characters, too! Some friends, some foes. Ghosts 'N Goblins is exciting... challenging you and the Knight to rescue the princess, amid great danger, escaping Hades, land of the enemies!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ghosts'n Goblins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19860919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gremlins 2 - The New Batch.zip</path>
		<name>Gremlins 2: The New Batch</name>
		<desc>Gizmo is trapped inside Clamp Centre by the evil Gremlins. Your mission? Help him battle his way to the control center and rid the city forever of the Gremlin menace! It's not going to be easy. You'll have to use cunning and wits to survive with only the weapons you find inside Clamp Centre... matches, a flashlight, tomatoes, and a homemade bow and arrow. But, if you're lucky, the door to Mr. Wing's Magic Shop may mystically appear... and let you buy some very special - and powerful - items to help you. This game has all the traps, mazes, and lightning quick moves to push your skill to the limits. And it has graphics that seem to come alive on the screen. Gremlins. Stopping them is not going to be easy. Don't say we didn't warn you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gremlins 2 - The New Batch-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gumshoe.zip</path>
		<name>Gumshoe</name>
		<desc>Jennifer's been kidnapped! Now's your chance to prove you're a sharp-shooting detective by helping Jennifer's father find the five diamonds that will pay her ransom. You'll use your Zapper light gun to blow away anything that gets in your way. But even with the Zapper, this case will be hard to crack. Because not only are the diamonds hard to find, but you only have 24 hours to find them! What's more, you'll have to think fast and shoot even faster, because ferocious monsters, diving airplanes and hungry man-eating sharks will stop at nothing to prevent you from getting to the diamonds. Think you're a sharp-shooting detective? Well, you better be. Because if you're not, it's curtains for you in this quick-on-the-trigger Nintendo Light Gun game!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gumshoe-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19860606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun Nac.zip</path>
		<name>Gun-Nac</name>
		<desc>The most happening place in the universe is the trendy, upscale solar system of IOTA Synthetica, part of the Galactic Federation of artificial stars. It's as far from dirty old Earth as can be... But don't sign up to go yet! A strange cosmic energy field with a major attitude has engulfed the system, and the most outrageous things are happening. Ordinary inanimate objects are coming to life - harmless little animals are becoming rabid giants - and the freaked-out residents are under attack! The only Galactic Commander who can handle this ordeal is the eccentric renegade called Gun-Nac. He can oust this aura that's threatening the destruction of comfortable artificial life as we know it. But where in the universe is he? He could be as far away as Earth, searching for a new Game Pak. Commander Gun-Nac, if you read this, call H.Q., A.S.A.P., O.K.? We N.E.E.D. you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gun Nac-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19901005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun.Smoke.zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<desc>Gun.Smoke is very similar to Commando, another Capcom game, but with several differences. Whereas Commando is a run and gun game, this game is a scrolling shooter in which the screen scrolls upward automatically and players only have three ways to shoot, using three buttons for left, right, and center shooting. However, a player can also change the way the gunman shoots through button combinations. A player can still die by getting shot or struck by enemies like in Commando but improve protection by getting special items, including a horse, for protection up to three hits; boots, for speed of movement; bullets, for faster shots; and rifles, for shot length. These items are found by shooting barrels and rifles, boots, and bullets can stock up to five.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gun.Smoke-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerin' Harry.zip</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Harry</name>
		<desc>Hammerin' Harry is a 2D Platformer game, developed and published by Irem, which was released in Europe in 1992.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hammerin' Harry-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19911115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hogan's Alley.zip</path>
		<name>Hogan's Alley</name>
		<desc>Despite being rather short on story and depth, this game was nevertheless fairly popular. The game flashes three "cardboard cut-outs" of a mixture of bad guys and innocent civilians. The player needs to react quickly and shoot the thugs while sparing the bystanders and other friendlies (such as police officers). The game gets more difficult and faster as it progresses</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hogan's Alley-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19840612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Holy Diver.zip</path>
		<name>Holy Diver</name>
		<desc>Randy, the hero, is setting out to retrieve the five emblem seals belonging to the King Crimson Family in an attempt to expell the greatest evil, the Black Slayer.  He will have to battle through the horde of evil and dark creatures at Black Slayer's command however, making his mission near impossible!  However, he can counter their Black Magics as he gains the use of new, Holy Magics as well as some much needed equipment!  So, set out with courage, hope, and a little luck, or the darkness will surely dominate!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Holy Diver-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ice Climber.zip</path>
		<name>Ice Climber</name>
		<desc>The first player controls Popo, a boy wearing a blue Eskimo parka, while the second player controls Nana, a girl wearing a pink Eskimo parka. The only tool they carry is a wooden mallet to carve openings in the ice above and to club enemies. Each mountain level consists of eight layers of colorful ice and a bonus stage. Standard, dull ice blocks pose no threat other than an easily disposed of barrier and platform. Square ice blocks with higher detail are indestructible forcing the player to take another path</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ice Climber-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19850130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170204T004846</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu.zip</path>
		<name>Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu</name>
		<desc>Jackie and his sister, Josephine, are tough on tyrants. As China's supreme kung fu champs, they guard their country against the Prince of Sorcerers, who lurks just beyond the Great Wall. It comes as no surprise when this fiend and his ghouls try yet again to seize China for themselves. But this time they're clever, casting a spell over Josephine which causes her to vanish into thin air! Jackie is in shock! How can he save his country without his sister? The two have been an unbeatable team! Meanwhile, a demon horde led by the Sorcerer storms the Great Wall and prepares to establish a fierce empire. At the urging of his revered Master, Jackie must now battle the dreaded Sorcerer and rescue Josephine. Maybe he can learn a little magic on his own, because he's going to need all the help he can get!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170204T004936</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jajamaru Gekimaden EN.zip</path>
		<name>Jajamaru Gekimaden: Maboroshi no Kinmajou</name>
		<desc>JaJaMaru Gekimaden is an action role-playing game, with gameplay similar to The Legend of the Zelda. Players control the protagonist character through towns, dungeons, and a world map. Each different type of map features top-down exploration. When moving through a dungeon, the protagonist will gradually recover health. The protagonist can equip different types of weapons and items that he can buy or find and use them during combat. Dungeons are made up of several rooms with enemies inside. Occasionally, an enemy will drop money when defeated, which can be used to buy items or heal health points at an inn.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Jajamaru Gekimaden EN-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900529T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jajamaru no Daibouken.zip</path>
		<name>JaJaMaru no Daibouken</name>
		<desc>JaJaMaru no Daibouken (じゃじゃ丸の大冒険?, "JaJaMaru's Great Adventure") is a Family Computer video game that was released exclusively for a Japanese market in 1986.

The concept of the game is that the player controls a red ninja as he progress through a series of Japanesque levels defeating evil spirits that have spread across the land. The player can even ride his faithful frog if he can recover it from hiding.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Jajamaru no Daibouken-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Journey to Silius.zip</path>
		<name>Journey to Silius</name>
		<desc>In the ruins of Silius, intergalactic terrorists - and their deadly arsenal of weapons - are waiting for you. Are you prepared to face an endless onslaught of flying war robots, humanoid laser cannons, bone crushing traps, and the seemingly invincible Master Ship? Still want to make the journey? If you do, it will take all your skills to reach the final battle with the terrorist's supreme leader, the merciless, all-powerful Skeletal Android. Journey to Silius. It's level upon level of gigantic supercharged graphics, thundering sound effects and danger at every turn. Go ahead. We dare you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Journey to Silius-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19900810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park.zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<desc>This game can be played in two modes, either as Dr. Alan Grant or as a Velociraptor. Playing as each provides the user with an alternative story and level design. The climax of the game mirrored the unused climax of the film, in which Grant must defeat a pair of Velociraptors by causing the Tyrannosaurus rex skeleton in the Visitors Center to collapse on top of them. Grant himself is the final boss in the same location for the raptor storyline: your dinosaur character must cause the bone structure to collapse via specifically placed kicks to cause Grant to flee. A sequel was released using a new game engine and new artwork (with some of the original art as well), entitled Jurassic Park: Rampage Edition. In it, Grant's helicopter (that he just escaped on in the first game) crashes. Now he must deal not only with dinosaurs, but InGen as well. A new raptor must also make it off the island.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Jurassic Park-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kabuki - Quantum Fighter.zip</path>
		<name>Kabuki Quantum Fighter</name>
		<desc>The setting - Earth, the future. The defense computer protecting the entire planet has been invaded by a constantly mutating, evolving virus. One lone volunteer has the courage to face the virus on its own ground. Converted to raw data and transferred into the circuits of the computer, the molecular structure of this brave warrior is transformed by the as-yet untested Image Transfer System. Into the circuits of the computer steps an unlikely hero - the Quantum Fighter! Six levels of challenging action, unequalled game control, and a surprising arsenal of weapons!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment, Inc</developer>
		<publisher>HAL</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kick Master.zip</path>
		<name>Kick Master</name>
		<desc>The King and Queen are dead, Princess Silphee kidnapped, and the King's Knights destroyed. Belzed, an evil wizard, wants the Kingdom of Lowrel for his own, and has hidden Silphee deep in his lair. Only Thonolan remains, the youngest, most talented Kick Master ever born. If he were any less powerful, he'd never survive. He must use every ounce of his fighting strength and summon up all of his magical skill to overcome Belzed's army of fanatics. For the adventure of a lifetime - and the salvation of Lowrel - come challenge fate with Thonolan!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kick Master-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kid</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kickle Cubicle.zip</path>
		<name>Kickle Cubicle</name>
		<desc>The Kingdom's covered with ice! And it's likely to stay that way unless Kickle saves the day! The Wicked Wizard King came to the Fantasy Kingdom and covered the Four Lands with ice. Now, armed with his freezing breath, Kickle sets out to save his friends. Join Kickle as he attempts to rescue the kingdom from this puzzling predicament of perpetual winter.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kickle Cubicle-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19900629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Icarus - Angel Land Story.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Icarus</name>
		<desc>Far away in a kingdom called "Angel Land," the evil goddess Medusa has stolen the Three Sacred Treasures and imprisoned the goddess of light, Palutena. As Kid Icarus, your mission is to find the treasures, destroy Medusa and rescue Palutena from the depths of the Palace in the Sky. To find the treasures you'll travel through ruins collecting weapons and storing power for use in combat against creatures of Medusa's army. Use your bow and arrow to ward off gatekeepers of the Underworld, Overworld and Skyworld as you strive towards your battle against Medusa. Will you survive to restore Palutena's light and return it to "Angel Land?" Only you know!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kid Icarus - Angel Land Story-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.73333</rating>
		<releasedate>19861218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Niki - Radical Ninja.zip</path>
		<name>Kid Niki: Radical Ninja</name>
		<desc>KID NIKI is truly AWESOME! This rad and bad punk dude is out to rescue his spike-haired girlfriend, Princess Margo, from the clutches of the Stone Wizard. Armed with a razor-sharp sword, this miniature madman slices his rivals down to size!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kid Niki - Radical Ninja-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19871002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Adventure</name>
		<desc>What would Dream Land be without dreams? A nightmare! The Dream Spring, source of all dreams, has dried up, taking with it all the blissful dreams of Dream Land. It's up to Kirby, the bombastic blimp, To return happy naps to the inhabitants of Dream Land! Kirby's appetite for adventure is as big as ever as he eats his way through a feast of all-new enemies! In this adventure, he can also steal the abilities of the bad guys he scarfs down! With this new power, Kirby can perform 20 new tricks that will help him make his way through the nightmare infested Dream Land! Kirby's Adventure features brand new worlds to explore with the same fun action-packed feel that made Kirby's Dream Land for Gameboy a hit!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kirby's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.625</rating>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T061545</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Krazy Kreatures.zip</path>
		<name>Krazy Kreatures</name>
		<desc>Here they come. And there they go. They just keep coming, you gotta make 'em go away. When you signed on as an intergalactic immigration officer you figured it was an easy way to make some money. You were wrong. Transporting wave after wave of weird wild life from all over the universe is anything but easy. You gotta line 'em up to move 'em out. Up and down, left and right, or diagonally you gotta make the clumps of critters move out faster than they move in. If the room fills to capacity, that's it, the entire system will be shut down. One of the most exciting games of the year, it's more fun than a barrel full of creatures!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Krazy Kreatures-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>American Video Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>American Video Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Krusty's Fun House.zip</path>
		<name>Krusty's Fun House</name>
		<desc>Hey, kids! Give a hoot! Help out your old pal Krusty the Clown! My official Krusty's Fun House is infested with rats! There are over 60 levels in this game, and they're all crawling with the little varmints! I've got my loyal cadets, Bart and Homer Simpson, to guard the rat traps, but I need you to lead the filthy rodents into those traps! Then we blow 'em up! We incinerate 'em! We laser-blast 'em! We electrocute 'em! We Krusterize the little stinkers!!! Hoo boy!
Did I mention the snakes, aliens and the flying pigs? Well, watch out for those riffraff! If you can't Krusterize 'em, at least avoid 'em... they're worse than the #@!*%l rats! Making Krusty's Fun House vermin-free is not a pretty task, kiddy cadets-but someone's gotta do it!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Krusty's Fun House-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Audiogenic</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kung Fu.zip</path>
		<name>Kung Fu</name>
		<desc>You'll need lightning fast reactions to knock out the Knife Thrower, stop the Stick Fighter, and trip up the evil Tom Tom Brothers in this action-packed martial arts contest! Are you sure you're tough enough? Because it'll take all your strength and skill to master the moves in KUNG FU, beat your opponents, and rescue the fair Sylvia who's held captive on the top floor! The action is non-stop, and just when you think you've got your enemies licked there's always a Giant, a Snake, or a fire-breathing Dragon to contend with in KUNG FU!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kung Fu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19851001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo under license by IREM</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Laser Invasion.zip</path>
		<name>Laser Invasion</name>
		<desc>A summer offensive in the year 1999. Never in your military career have you been in such a hot spot, as the world's most threatening power, Sheik Toxic Moron, deploys his arsenal of TechnoScorch Weapons. To achieve total victory over 4 intense levels, you must possess numerous skills, including precision reflexes for air combat, a cut throat mentality for land assaults, the brains to gather secrets from underground informants, and a keen sense for surviving 3-D battle mazes. If you've got the guts to match those skills, then prepare for action. Because it'll really heat up the second you blast across the Sheik's firing line, piloting the world's most advanced super weapon - the Mach 4 Laser Invasion Helijet, which can go from hovering to a six "G" vertical climb in a heartbeat. From the moment you activate your Vulcan Cannons and Sidewinder Missiles, you'll take dead aim on an insane assault, featuring Anti-Copter Rocket Launchers, High-Altitude Bombers and Aerial Mines. But the battle's just begun, and there's no time to kill between firefights!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Laser Invasion-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of the Wizard.zip</path>
		<name>Legacy of the Wizard</name>
		<desc>Long, long ago, an evil dragon terrorized the forest until it was imprisoned by a powerful wizard. Now, years later, the dragon has revived and it's up to you to use the power of the wizard's descendants, the Draslefamily, to defeat the dragon once again.
The whole family takes part in this action adventure as the parents, children and even the family pet search huge dungeons for gold, keys, magic, hidden crowns and finally the magical sword that can destroy the dragon.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Legacy of the Wizard-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Nemo - The Dream Master.zip</path>
		<name>Little Nemo: The Dream Master</name>
		<desc>Little Nemo receives a royal invitation to visit the castle in Slumberland. Is he dreaming? It seems the princess is looking for a new playmate. When he arrives he is told that King Morpheus has been kidnapped. Nemo sets off on a wild adventure to rescue the good king and restore peace to the land. Anything can happen in this realm of imagination. Little Nemo even learns how to get a ride from the local creatures so he can pass through the roughest parts of Slumberland. Rescue the King of good dreams and thwart the Master of Nightmares!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Little Nemo - The Dream Master-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Ninja Brothers.zip</path>
		<name>Little Ninja Brothers</name>
		<desc>Start out on a journey. You are spirited Ninja boys, Jack and Ryu. Now, go out on your journey to save the once merry world, Chinaland!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Little Ninja Brothers-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Samson.zip</path>
		<name>Little Samson</name>
		<desc>The Imperial Forgy has been invaded by Ta-Keed the Prince of Darkness! Only the owners of the Magic Bells can stop his forces from destroying the realm. Led by the mountaineering youth, Samson, a force of unlikely heroes sets out to banish evil forever! Become a fire-breathing dragon, a living statue of solid stone or a nimble and crafty mouse. Soar the skies and belch fire balls as Kikira the Dragon Lord! Crush enemy troops with fists of granite as Gamm the Rock Lord! Scurry past dangerous monsters while setting time bombs as K.O. the mouse! These creatures join Little Samson to form a unique and powerful alliance as the last hope for the Imperial Forgy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Little Samson-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takeru</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maniac Mansion.zip</path>
		<name>Maniac Mansion</name>
		<desc>The game takes place in the mansion of the Edison family: Dr. Fred, Nurse Edna, and their son Weird Ed. Living with the Edisons are two large, disembodied tentacles – one purple and the other green. The player starts out by selecting two of six characters to accompany protagonist Dave Miller. The intro sequence shows that a meteor crashed near the mansion 20 years earlier. The sentient meteor took control of the family and caused Dr. Fred to begin conducting human experiments while plotting to take over the world. After the introduction, Dave and his two companions prepare to enter the mansion to rescue his cheerleader girlfriend, Sandy Pantz, whom Dr. Fred has kidnapped.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Maniac Mansion-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mappy.zip</path>
		<name>Mappy</name>
		<desc>Mappy is a 1983 arcade game by Namco. In the United States, it was distributed by Bally/Midway. Mappy is a side-scrolling platform game that features cartoon-like animals, primarily cats and mice. The game's main character itself is a mouse. Mappy runs on Namco Super Pac-Man hardware, modified to support horizontal scrolling. The name "Mappy" is likely derived from mappo, a Japanese slang term (slightly insulting) for a policeman.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mappy-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19841114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man</name>
		<desc>It's MEGA MAN versus the powerful leaders and fighting forces of Monsteropolis - that strange multi-layered land of robot-like humanoids created by the wrongly-performed experiments with human beings by Dr. Wily. Mega Man - the chosen defender of the human race. For he dares to single-handedly penetrate Monsteropolis' seven separate societies to stop the rapid expansion of strange misrepresentations of humans.

Mega Man's goal is monumental. He must infiltrate seven separate heavily-guarded empires. By himself, he must break down and destroy the following empire leaders: Cutman, Gutsman, Iceman, Bombman, Fireman, Elecman, and Dr. Wily. The action involves Mega Man armed only with laser beam weapons, encountering strangely-configured humanoids. They're atop, in and out of fortified prison-like structures strengthened with thick walls. Hidden amid gun turrets embedded in concrete uprights, even in subterranean passages below icefields. WOW!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19871217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 2.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 2</name>
		<desc>He's Back! And this time the evil Dr. Wily (once the supreme power in the universe) has created even more sinister robots to mount his attack. But as MegaMan, you've also grown in power and ability. Can you save mankind from the evil desires of Dr. Wily? Each of the eight empires is ruled by a different super-robot. You must defeat each enemy on his own turf, building up weapons as you go. Only after all are destroyed will you go head-on with the mastermind himself, the evil Dr. Wily.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 3.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 3</name>
		<desc>It's robot rebellion, and nobody's safe! Least of all, Mega Man! This time the superpowerful cyborg takes on a horde of metal maniacs who've had it with being obedient! And they use every android-annihilator ever invented to make you believe it! Mega Man goes berserk, blasting through a galaxy of mining stations in search of energy crystals. But it takes more than guts to battle the phenomenal robot masters who control these worlds. It's a wrenching job, the worst - and the best - that Mega Man's faced so far!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170203T013918</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 4.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 4</name>
		<desc>For a year the city has been quiet, but a new robotic terror has gripped the city! That scheming scientist, Dr. Cossack has arrived in town with eight new metal maniacs who are bigger and badder than anything Dr. Wily dreamed of. It's going to be a cybernetic showdown as the streets of the city erupt with the sizzling sounds of molten metal! Armed with the new Mega Buster, Mega Man runs, jumps and dodges his way through mazes of metallic munchkins on his way to the Siberian citadel of Dr. Cossack for the final cataclysmic clash!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170215T000418</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 5.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 5</name>
		<desc>Protoman has gone berserk! Destroying half the city was not enough. Now, he has snatched Dr. Light and is holding him and the entire city hostage. Speeding to the rescue is Mega Man and his modified Mega Buster, but eight of Protoman's cybernetic soldiers plan to send Mega Man to the scrap heap for good! Feel the weight of the world on your shoulders as you battle Gravity Man! Chip away at the rock-like defenses of Stone Man and bring him crumbling down! Hit the surf and sail up against the tidal power of Wave Man! Help Mega Man defeat all eight of Protoman's robots and then get ready for the fight that pits brother against brother in the battle of the century!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man 5-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 6.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 6</name>
		<desc>From the United States, Canada and Japan they came. The world's premier designers and their finest robotic warriors traveled to do battle in the First Annual Robot Tournament. But what began as a game suddenly took a terrifying twist! On the eve of the Grand Championship, the sponsor of the event announced that the entire tournament was just an elaborate scheme to get his hands on the world's most powerful robots! Now faced with an army of metallic mercenaries, Mega Man must fight a ferocious new foe - The Mysterious Mr. X!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mega Man 6-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T005444</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear</name>
		<desc>Outer Heaven leader CaTaffy has activated the ultimate super weapon: Metal Gear! Responding to the crisis, covert unit "Fox Hound" is called into action, and that's where you come into play. Trained in hand-to-hand combat and skilled in every weapon known to man, you're Fox Hound's lethal fighting machine, code named "Solid Snake". But on this mission you better be sly as well, to surprise heavily-armed enemies, busting 'em up quietly and rescuing their hostages before alarms are triggered. Plus you gotta maintain radio contact with Commander South, who'll feed you crucial info on Metal Gear's whereabouts. To survive, capture sub-machine guns, Barettas, grenade launchers, and plastic explosives, until you find and destroy Metal Gear, ending CaTaffy's reign of terror!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Metal Gear-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6799999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19870707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Storm.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Storm</name>
		<desc>Battle station cyberg's massive computer that keeps peace throughout the solar system is no longer user friendly. It's gone wildly out of control. The LaserGun it operates has already destroyed Neptune. Earth is its next target. As a high-tech hot shot, you must enter Cyber's core and activate the system's self-destruct mechanism. Mankind is reyling on your know-how and toughness to see this thing through. But time is running out...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Metal Storm-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid</name>
		<desc>It's you against the evil Mother Brain in the thrilling battle of Metroid!

You’re inside the fortress planet Zebes.  The planet of endless secret passageways where the Metroid are multiplying.  Left alone the Metroid are harmless.  But in the wrong hands they could destroy the galaxy.  It’s up to you to prevent the Mother Brain that controls Zebes from using the Metroid for evil purposes.  But that won’t be easy.  You’ll have to use your spacesuit to absorb valuable energy for your search to gain the use of power items like the Ice Beam, Wave Beam, High Jump Boots and Varia.  If you survive, it will be you and your acquired powers against the Mother Brain.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Metroid-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7125</rating>
		<releasedate>19860806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mousecapade.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mousecapade</name>
		<desc>"Help! Help!" echos a mysterious voice. Mickey Mouse, the famous world explorer, has heard the cries of one of his friends and he's off on a rescue mission... This adventure starts in a zany Fun House. Join Mickey and Minnie as they turn it inside out looking for their missing friend. A mischievous creature may fly off with Minnie, and you'll have to get her back. Now that Minnie is safe, you must help our heroes make it across a vast ocean - on foot! Even the feisty flying fish can't stop Mickey from his search, but what about the cantankerous crocodile waiting at the shore? Enter the world of fantasy, mystery and excitement with Mickey and Minnie as you solve the mystery of Mickey's missing friend!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mickey Mousecapade-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19870306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Machines.zip</path>
		<name>Micro Machines</name>
		<desc>Yo dudes, it's Micro Machines - the official video game! We believe this is the most competitive racing game yet produced. Amazing playability! Featuring a very competitive two-player option. 27 cunningly devised circuits - under bridges, through oil patches, power-sliding around corners - trying to beat the other drivers and become the Micro Machines Champion! Choose your vehicle and go! Feel the power, feel the traction - excellent! Performance sports cars, Formula 1 racing cars, Power boats, Combat tanks, Helicopters, Highway Warriors, 4 x 4's, Monster trucks, and Turbo Wheels - Absolutely Brilliant!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Micro Machines-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Camerica</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mighty Final Fight.zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Final Fight</name>
		<desc>The Mad Gear Gang has spread crime and violence throughout the streets of Metro City. Only one man has enough guts to take the streets back from them, Mayor Mike Haggar. Now the Mad Gear Gang has kidnapped his daughter Jessica to bring him under their control. But they've made one mistake: Haggar's furious and he wants someone's head! Guy and Jessica's boyfriend, Cody, are joining Haggar to clean up the slime-filled streets and rescue Jessica. Along the way you'll find food to replenish your health, or better yet, search for weapons to knock the living daylights out of your enemies. So join Haggar and his friends as they try to free the city from the evil clutches of the Mad Gear Gang!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mighty Final Fight-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19931111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moon Crystal.zip</path>
		<name>Moon Crystal</name>
		<desc>As Ricky Slater, the player must rescue Ricky's family and confront the evil forces of Count Crimson, who wields the powerful Moon Crystal!  Owing much inspiration to Prince of Persia, this game boasts colorful graphics and vivid animations coupled with non-linear exploration and gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Moon Crystal-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hect</developer>
		<publisher>Hect</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gimmick!.zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Gimmick</name>
		<desc>A young girl receives a doll named Yumetarou (ゆめたろー) for a birthday present. She quickly favors the new doll over her previous five toys, who felt abandoned and unloved. While she was sleeping, they suddenly came to life and took her to another dimension. Yumetarou, as the protagonist, must track down his new owner and retrieve her from the toys' world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Gimmick!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Ghostbusters II.zip</path>
		<name>New Ghostbusters II</name>
		<desc>The world-wide hit movie is now available on the Nintendo Entertainment System! Capture the ghost that haunted New York City in this comedy-action-adventure. Six stages in all, including a Courtroom, the Subway, the Art Museum and more!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/New Ghostbusters II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL</developer>
		<publisher>HAL</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightshade - The Claws of Sutekh.zip</path>
		<name>Nightshade</name>
		<desc>The shadows of doom grow long as the ancient Egyptian villain Sutekh envelops Metro City with a wave of crime. But Sutekh's seedy underworld is about to be infiltrated by a superhero unlike any the world has ever seen. A superhero who can melt into the darkness like a phantom. By day this brave new crimefighter is a common ordinary citizen. But when night falls, he is cloaked in a secret identity to seek out and destroy the dark forces that lurk on midnight streets. Who is this man the press calls Nightshade? Only you can answer that... for he is you! Every night you solidify your superhero status, patrolling 100 of the city's darkest corners. Here you'll find thieves, muggers, and other alley scum that you must either deal with or destroy for clues. But be warned. You're not the only night stalker. For as you hunt Sutekh, Sutekh hunts you with the human printing press, the closing wall of spikes, deadly jackal pits, and the chilling freeze ray. Of course the ultimate key to destroying Sutekh is your popularity. For it's a power source that gives you the wit to decipher clues and the strength to pulverize villains and rescue innocent bystanders. Remember, if this heroic prowess ever diminishes, you'll no longer control the night. You'll be consumed by it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Nightshade - The Claws of Sutekh-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
		<desc>Ryu Hayabusa of the Dragon Ninja Clan receives a letter from his father, saying that he was leaving for a duel with an unknown warrior. Should he not return, Ryu was to go to America and seek a man named Walter Smith. Ryu honors his father's last request, and travels to America. While there, he is kidnapped by a CIA agent and given a statue of a hideous beast.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ninja Gaiden-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.73636</rating>
		<releasedate>19881209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Episode II - The Dark Sword of Chaos.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden II: The Dark Sword of Chaos</name>
		<desc>Dynamic action scenes! Split your body into three, destroy all enemies with the Invincible Fire Wheel and other new Ninja fighting techniques! Ninja Gaiden II gives you the feel of real Ninjutsu! Exciting cinema display format! Ninja Gaiden II uses the same Cinema Display Format as the original. The fiendish plot unfolds in a movie-like sequence. Action, drama, revenge. Just wait till you get to the end!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ninja Gaiden Episode II - The Dark Sword of Chaos-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden Episode III - The Ancient Ship of Doom.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden III: The Ancient Ship of Doom</name>
		<desc>Thrilling new cinema screen! Follow the story of Ryu's epic adventure through Tecmo's movie-like Cinema Screen Animation. As you complete each level, a new part of the story unfolds. Exciting new powers and weapons! Over the years Ninja Ryu's fighting skills have improved to include fantastic new powers and weapons. Action-packed Ninja adventure! Can you get Ryu through his most challenging adventure as he battles the hideous ancient forces of darkness to save mankind? The Ultimate Ninja Challenge!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ninja Gaiden Episode III - The Ancient Ship of Doom-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Noah's Ark.zip</path>
		<name>Noah's Ark</name>
		<desc>Noah has been commanded by God to put two of each animal aboard his ark to save them from the flood. However unhappy people from around the world have captured different animal species, preventing Noah from doing his job. Noah will need to visit these different locations and free the animals from the people holding them captive.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Noah's Ark-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Source Research &amp; Development</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parodius.zip</path>
		<name>Parodius</name>
		<desc>One day, our octopus friend gets into a fight to the death with his old rival, the bug. Our octopus wins and people start to call him Mr. Parodius. On his paid vacation he goes to the countryside to enjoy a little farming. Returning to our ready-made octopus pot, he reads the "People of the Universe" newspaper and nearly falls off his chopping board in surprise. There now is a picture of the mysterious Great Octopus with the Earth in his arms.
"F...father?," he stutters. It was his father, who had disappeared just two years before never to return home.
So Octopus sets out on a search for the truth and with his companions begins to travel the world!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Parodius-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Blade.zip</path>
		<name>Power Blade</name>
		<desc>22nd CENTURY WARRIOR! When New Earth's Master Computer is attacked by aliens, only NOVA, lord of the ancient Power Blade, can hope to battle through to Control Center and restore the Database!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Power Blade-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19920123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Blade 2.zip</path>
		<name>Power Blade 2</name>
		<desc>Time to sharpen the blade! NOVA is suddenly called to take action against a cyborg army. The Delta Foundation has developed a line of fighting robots that pose a threat to national security. NOVA has been picked to eliminate the danger by destroying the Delta Foundation - all five locations. Fortunately, he will be using different suits which give him the ability to walk on ceilings, swim long distances, and fly - not to mention the latest top secret suit. And of course, NOVA will be wielding the ancient Power Blade, a weapon of art and science. He must draw on all his skills and cunning to defeat these near-perfect fighting machines!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Power Blade 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<desc>The Grand Vizier Jaffar has thrown you into a dark dungeon and plans to marry the girl of your dreams in an hour. You're not going to let that happen are you? Try to escape from the dungeon, take out Jaffar's guards, find your way through the Sultan's palace and defeat Jaffar himself. Now go, you've got 60 minutes!

Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer with run and jump gameplay. Your hero must avoid deadly traps, solve some simple puzzles and engage in sword fights with the guards. The player has an infinite amount of lives, but has to restart at the beginning of a level each time he dies, and must complete the game within an hour. An especially noteworthy aspect of the game is the very fluent animation of your character.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Prince of Persia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Motive Time</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R.C. Pro-Am II.zip</path>
		<name>R.C. Pro-Am II</name>
		<desc>If you're into racing, but you're tired of racing big, unwieldy cars, then you should check out R.C. PRO-AM II for the Nintendo Entertainment System. You'll be in control of the remote-controlled cars that you remember from your childhood, complete with antennae to pick up your signal. There are 24 tracks covering a wide variety of terrain. If you're good enough to win a race, you can go to the R.C. Model Shop and upgrade your car's components to turn it into an unbeatable racing machine. You'll also have access to power-ups and weapons, adding a new element of strategy to the racing formula. Whether by yourself or with up to three friends, R.C. PRO-AM II delivers intense racing action miniature style!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/R.C. Pro-Am II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.675</rating>
		<releasedate>19921015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./S.C.A.T. - Special Cybernetic Attack Team.zip</path>
		<name>S.C.A.T.: Special Cybernetic Attack Team</name>
		<desc>It's the year 2029 and humanity faces certain extinction! An alien force led by the Supreme Commander Vile Malmort is positioned to destroy the earth.
The President had little time to act. He assembled the greatest scientists from around the globe to stop this menace. From their laboratory came mankind's last hope - the members of S.C.A.T.
The Special Cybernetic Attack Team has one goal: the utter destruction of the alien fleet. "They've sent an armada to conquer us. We've sent two warriors from S.C.A.T... It should be a fair fight."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/S.C.A.T. - Special Cybernetic Attack Team-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Ninja.zip</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Ninja</name>
		<desc>It's the year 2029 A.D. and a madman controls the largest city in America. When reports have reached the Emperor Garuda, he feels an inner chill, for he knows the invaders are Ninja!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Shadow of the Ninja-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19901211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shatterhand.zip</path>
		<name>Shatterhand</name>
		<desc>Imagine packing the power of 100 strategic missiles in every punch. Imagine needing every single megaton just to hold your own against a cybernetic army of metallic monstrosities. That's the guts of SHATTERHAND, the game that redefines hand-to-hand combat in the 21st century... along with all the standards for single-player action games for the NES. Seven levels of programmed adventure - you choose the action! State-of-the-art graphics featuring 8-direction scrolling! "Anti-gravity" levels force you to fight upside-down! Armed "satellite robots" assist you in battle. No arms on Earth can withstand the power in your hands!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Shatterhand-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Splatter House - Wanpaku Graffiti.zip</path>
		<name>Splatterhouse: Wanpaku Graffiti</name>
		<desc>Revived by his girlfriend's grief and a flash of lightning, Rick must chase down the Pumpkin king and save his beloved Jennifer once and for all!  A parody of the bloody horror beat-'em-up Splatterhouse, Wanpaku Graffiti assumes a much cuter appearance but retains the same fast-paced action of the original.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Splatter House - Wanpaku Graffiti-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Now Production</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Force.zip</path>
		<name>Star Force</name>
		<desc>Moving in the darkness of the cosmos is a evil and mysterious planet named GORDESS. Everyone gave up fighting against GORDESS because of it's awesome power, until one day a soldier riding a space patroller challenged GORDESS to fight! Join forces with STAR FORCE and travel across the galaxy in order to defeat GORDESS.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Star Force-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19871101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tehkan</developer>
		<publisher>Tehkan</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Startropics.zip</path>
		<name>StarTropics</name>
		<desc>Find out just how resourceful you can be in this classic game, with its mixture of adventure and RPG elements. Step into the shoes of Mike Jones, a teenage star pitcher from Seattle who has come to the tropics to visit his famous archeologist uncle, Dr. Jones. After being told that his uncle has been abducted, Mike begins a perilous quest in order to rescue him and figure out the mysterious plot behind his disappearance.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Startropics-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo IRD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Startropics 2 - Zoda's Revenge.zip</path>
		<name>StarTropics II: Zoda's Revenge</name>
		<desc>The story begins with Mike Jones, the protagonist, receiving a telepathic message from Mica, the princess of the Argonians, whom Mike had rescued in the previous game. She tells Mike how to solve a cipher that he and his uncle, referred to as Dr. J, found on the side of the Argonians’ space pod. Mike goes to see Dr. J, and together, they solve the cipher and read it aloud. This causes Mike to be flung into the past. He arrives in the Stone Age. After helping a tribe of cave men retrieve their children from a flesh-eating wild boar, he finds an object, which Mica telepathically identifies as a Tetrad ("Block" in the Virtual Console version). He must travel to different eras throughout Earth’s history and retrieve the rest of the Tetrads.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Startropics 2 - Zoda's Revenge-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super C.zip</path>
		<name>Super C</name>
		<desc>After losing a confrontation against Super Commandos Mad Dog and Scorpion, the juices of destruction drip from the spiked tongue of the vile alien warmonger - Red Falcon. Now, he's coming back stronger than ever, with a sinister plan that includes having his intergalactic warriors seep into the brains of the U.S. Army. To support his disguised forces of doom, he's recruited Jagger Froid, a demented alien from the Black Hole Galaxy. He's also shuttled in The Babula Destructoid Mechanism with its Beam of Death. With torrential terror about to rain down upon civilization, Earth's only hope rests with you, Scorpion, and your pal, the Dogster. And if your spread guns, lasers, flame throwers and mega shells fail to destroy Red Falcon's eight levels of terror, including radioactive lava fields, it's all over but for the shouting, the screaming and the cries from a disintegrating world!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super C-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.73333</rating>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 3.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>Fight monsters and mini-bosses, avoid ghosts and the burning sun.  Make your way through water and quicksand.  Dodge cannon balls and bullets and rescue the King’s wand!

In Super Mario Bros. 3 there are more warps, more chances at extra lives, and new special suits!  The raccoon suit lets you fly and knock out blocks.  The frog suit helps you out-swim the deadly fish.  There are suits for every occasion!

Store up flowers and mushrooms to use later on.  Play game-show type bonus rounds!  Go back to that last screen and get a mushroom!  Pause to take a break, then continue where you left off!

Super Mario Bros. 3 is fun to play alone, or team up with a buddy to prolong the adventure!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super Mario Bros. 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.78947</rating>
		<releasedate>19881023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>7</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170215T000913</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Brothers 2 JAP.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Brothers 2</name>
		<desc>Originally released in Japan as Super Mario Bros.® 2, this game has previously made only brief cameo appearances in the Western hemisphere. Mario fans will appreciate the familiar look and feel of the game, while finding that its updated game play creates an entirely new challenge. No longer content just to wear different-colored overalls, Mario and Luigi also possess different skill sets (Mario can stop quicker, while Luigi can jump higher). In addition to the classic enemies already known to fans worldwide, there are also Poison Mushrooms, backward Warp Zones, and the occasional wind gust (which can help or hinder your progress) to take into account. And if that’s somehow not enough, expert players can go looking for the game’s secret worlds. So get ready to put your Mario skills to the ultimate test, and save the Princess again. Just don’t be surprised if she’s in another castle!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super Mario Brothers 2 JAP-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T233053</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican.zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican</name>
		<desc>The lost colony of Alterra is a completely man-made lifeworld abandoned long ago in a nearby galaxy. Alterra is actually five colonies in one. Each self-contained habitat has been separately bio-engineered by a powerful ecosystem generation network known as a Multiple Organism Unit Link. MORGUL, for short. Early colonists used MORGUL to render Alterra inhabitable. But a cataclysmic quake severed all system interface functions, and MORGUL murderously rebelled. The few colonists lucky enough to escape told a grim tale of a higher intelligence gone berserk.

For generations, mankind sought a return to Alterra. Finally, genetic science created a saviour: Turrican, a mutant warrior, bio-engineered for the task of planetary reclamation. In the meantime, MORGUL has diligently twisted Alterran life forms to his brutal, destructive purposes. Thus, Turrican's challenges consist in eliminating hostile organisms from Alterra's five multi-level worlds and, finally, destroying the three faces of MORGUL.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super Turrican-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tale Spin.zip</path>
		<name>TaleSpin</name>
		<desc>Strap on your seat belt! Here's rollicking fun with Baloo Bear and his cargo plane, the Mini-Sea Duck. He's out delivering goods to all the people in the cape. But Don Karnage and his goofy band of pirates are hot on Baloo's tail wind, trying to swipe the cargo! It's high-flying adventure as Baloo dodges and shoots through the clouds and over skyscrapers. It's low-flying fun as he zips through a haunted house where hats and gloves join the chase. Alligators and natives rumble in the jungle. Cave dogs bash Baloo with bones. Submarines transform into helicopters. Baseballs as big as boulders give Baloo a rocky ride! Baloo's got 8 trips to make so he's got to be a frisky flyer. Grab your goggles, and don't smack into a bubble. It could mean trouble!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Tale Spin-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III: The Manhattan Project</name>
		<desc>Surf's up, dude! The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles make a little getaway to the Sunshine State. Until Shredder makes a major getaway with the entire island of Manhattan! His power hungry plot gets even more bogus when April O'Neil becomes part of the heist. What a relaxing vacation.

Not! Those mondo mutants must make waves to get back home to save April and Manhattan, and send Shredder on a one way trip to geeksville! So unless you want Shredder to ninja-kick sand in your face and make off with your best girl and your hometown, you better get busy. Squashing him once and for all will be no holiday.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.675</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tennis.zip</path>
		<name>Tennis</name>
		<desc>Whether it's singles or doubles you'll love the non-stop action of this amazingly real tennis game!

   Slam a serve, fire a blazing backhand, smash a forehand volley - you call the shots in Nintendo TENNIS!  Nintendo lets you choose an opponent from five different skill levels.  So as your game improves, so does your playing partner!  Plus, you can actually gauge the speed of your serve!  The better your timing, the faster it moves across the net.  You'll have hours of fun rushing the net, playing the baseline or roaming the court.  With Nintendo's state-of-the-art graphics and realistic game play, you'll really believe you're at center court!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Tennis-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6799999999999999</rating>
		<releasedate>19851001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle of Olympus, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Battle of Olympus</name>
		<desc>This is an ancient story - a time when men and gods lived together. The peaceful village of Elis was the home of the fairest maiden and a gentle yet brave young man named Orpheus. Helene and Orpheus swore eternal love to each other. But alas, one day, Helene fell victim to the fangs of a venomous serpent and was turned to stone. Your adventure will take you through ancient Greece on a classic mythological quest. It may be easy to defeat the snakes and centaurs that inhabit most of the cities but how will you defeat Hydra? Or the terrible three-headed dog, Cerberus? You'll need to use all of your adventuring skills to find the magic items that will allow you to rescue your beloved Helene.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Battle of Olympus, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - The Rescue of Dino &amp; Hoppy.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones: The Rescue of Dino &amp; Hoppy</name>
		<desc>It's prehistoric pandemonium as your favorite cave family, the Flintstones, get a visit from the 30th century. The clever scientist, Dr. Butler, needs some dinosaurs for the Orbit City Zoo, and he's invented a time machine to capture Dino and Hoppy. Can Fred find all the pieces that the Great Gazoo needs to build a time machine of his own? Can he make a jump into the future with the help of Wilma, Barney and Betty and rescue his prehistoric pals? Who says history has to be boring?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Flintstones, The - The Rescue of Dino &amp; Hoppy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19920807T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak!.zip</path>
		<name>The Flintstones: The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak!</name>
		<desc>Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm have wandered away from home and it looks like Fred and Barney found them. Unfortunately, an active volcano stands in the way. Now, Fred and Barney must travel across the pre-hysterical world of Bedrock to rescue the kids! Fred swings a mean club and Barney's sling carries a nasty sting in this adventure for the whole family. Scale the side of a cliff, use crocodiles as trampolines, and leap into action as Bedrock's most famous citizens go looking for their children. Collect the hidden five fabled fire gemstones to pay a greedy Pterodactyl to return Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm to their homes!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Flintstones, The - The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sol</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goonies, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Goonies</name>
		<desc>The Goonies is a side-scrolling action-adventure game from Konami that was first released on the Japanese Famicom in 1986 and quickly ported to the Sharp X1, MSX and PC-8801. A Famicom Disk System followed a couple years later: this version was only made available via the Disk Writer service. The game finally saw its US debut with the Arcade adaptation Vs. The Goonies from the PlayChoice-10 range.

The game was followed by a sequel that diverges from the movie's story and is better known to US audiences. The game is not to be confused with the 1985 Datasoft game for the C64, Atari 8-Bit and Spectrum which was closer to The Lost Vikings with its co-operative puzzles.

Gameplay:
The game features Mikey as he runs around various stages based on locations from the movie - the closed restaurant that the Fratellis use as a hideout, the caverns beneath the restaurant and One-Eyed Willy's pirate ship - saving his friends and recovering keys. In order to progress, Mikey must find three keys and the captive Goonie on each stage. As well as bats, rats and other hostile wildlife, Mikey is being pursued by the three Fratelli family members: they cannot be defeated, but can be stunned temporarily.

Mikey can find power-ups that help him proceed. The most important of these are bombs which destroy walls marked by skulls and reveal keys and captive Goonies behind them. Permanent bonuses like headphones (which prevents Mikey being hurt by Jake Fratelli's opera singing) and a backpack (which allows Mikey to carry two bombs at once) can also be found, but only once and each in a specific stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Goonies, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian Legend, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Guardian Legend</name>
		<desc>In The Guardian Legend, the player controls the female guardian of Earth, a "highly sophisticated aerobot transformer". The player's mission is to infiltrate Naju, a large planet-like object which aliens sent hurtling towards the Earth. While inside, the player must activate ten safety devices in order to initialize Naju's self-destruct mechanism and destroy the alien world before it reaches Earth. Five hostile tribes of alien lifeforms are vie for control of territories within Naju,and the player needs to fight through them to successfully activate the switches and escape.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Guardian Legend, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Irem, Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jungle Book, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Jungle Book</name>
		<desc>A 2D platformer based on the 1967 animated Disney movie and released on multiple platforms. It was one of four Virgin Interactive platformers based on Disney movies, along with The Lion King, Aladdin and Pinocchio.

Walt Disney's The Jungle Book is a side-scrolling platformer based on the Disney film of the same name. As Mowgli, the player must make their way from Mowgli's home in the jungle to the human village. Along the way, he faces various dangers such as pitfalls, fruit-throwing monkeys, and spitting snakes. The ultimate objective is to defeat Shere Khan, a cunning tiger who hunts humans.

Virgin Interactive developed the game for multiple consoles, including the Game Boy, NES, SNES, Genesis, Sega Master System and Game Gear. It was part of a series of Disney licensed platformers they created in the mid-90s.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Jungle Book, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lone Ranger, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Lone Ranger</name>
		<desc>Evil arch villain Butch Cavendish has been a burr on your saddle ever since he did in your dad. Now he's kidnapped the President just to lure you to your doom, and there's nothing but a trail of doom between you. In fact, kemosabe, there's eight wild west stages of pistol packin' danger to run, shoot, and gallop through, including first person 3-D stages that put peril in a whole new perspective. So hop on your fiery horse Silver, track down that cad Cavendish, and rescue the President. Or with the speed of light and a cloud of dust you'll wind up a mere tumbleweed in time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Lone Ranger, The-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic of Scheherazade, The.zip</path>
		<name>The Magic of Scheherazade</name>
		<desc>Magic of Scheherazade is a mixture of action- and turn-based combat RPG styles. Wandering through Arabia, you'll encounter enemies whom you'll fight in real time, using various weapons. You'll also be attacked by enemies with whom you'll engage in strategic, party-vs.-party combat. You can choose from three character classes: Fighter, Saint, and Magician. Each class has its own special abilities that you'll use in battles as well as during your exploration of the game world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Magic of Scheherazade, The-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures</name>
		<desc>These Tiny Toons have big problems. That's right. The arch enemy of Acme Acres, Montana Max, has kidnapped the ever-so-popular Babs Bunny. Now the furry female's fate rests in the paws of Buster Bunny and his crime fighting pals - Dizzy Devil, Furrball and Plucky Duck. Four kooky buddies with their own special talent. Buster can bounce over bad guys with the best of them. Furrball uses his feline claws to climb walls. Dizzy Devil prefers to spin through them. And Plucky can glide through the air and swim like a fish. Choose which partner you want at the beginning of each level before you face-off against time and goofballs gone bad in 6 zany wonderlands. So you better get jumping or it will be curtains for our playful pals!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Tiny Toon Adventures-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures 2 - Trouble in Wackyland.zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures 2: Trouble in Wackyland</name>
		<desc>There is a new amusement park in Acme Acres, and everyone has been invited to visit by a "Secret Admirer".
There are five areas which the player can explore, each one starring a different character. Plucky rides a bumper car. Hamton rides a tricky train trip. Babs rides the rollercoaster. Furrball dodges Sweetie as he goes for a wild log ride. And Buster faces the thrills and chills of the Funhouse.
Each ride costs a certain amount of tickets, but as the player racks up points on the various rides, more tickets are earned. Eventually, when enough tickets have been earned, they can be saved until the player has enough to afford the entrance fee to the Funhouse, where Buster Bunny must then navigate numerous obstacles before squaring off with the "Secret Admirer", who turns out to be Montana Max.
Just like in the first game, Roderick Rat is there to try to interfere, plus other villain characters. Other Tiny Toon characters also make appearances in varying degrees.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Tiny Toon Adventures 2 - Trouble in Wackyland-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./To the Earth.zip</path>
		<name>To the Earth</name>
		<desc>In the year 2050 the Earth has been attacked by the villainous Raggosians and it is your job to save the planet! You will need to pilot your ship, The Tempest, to the planets Uranus, Saturn, Jupiter, and Earth in order to retrieve certain minerals which can be used to fight the Raggosians. The Raggosians will be trying to stop you from reaching these destinations, though, so you need to use the Nintendo zapper to fight back. Numerous (and very fast!) enemy ships will fly by on the screen and attempt to destroy your ship. You need to shoot the ships and incoming missiles before your ship takes too much damage. From time to time a comet will fly by, and if you shoot this a temporary barrier will be formed that protects your ship from enemy fire. Occasionally you can also earn a smart bomb which appears in the bottom of the screen and destroys all enemies if shot. Each level ends with a large boss which will take multiple hits to destroy.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/To the Earth-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cirque Verte</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TwinBee.zip</path>
		<name>TwinBee</name>
		<desc>TwinBee is a cartoon-themed vertical-scrolling shoot 'em up game originally released by Konami as a coin-operated video game in 1985 in Japan. It was the very first game to run on Konami's Bubble System hardware. TwinBee was ported to the Family Computer and MSX in 1986 and has been included in numerous compilations released in later years. The original arcade game was released outside Japan for the first time in the Nintendo DS compilation Konami Classics Series: Arcade Hits. A mobile phone version was released for i-mode Japan phones in 2003 with edited graphics.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/TwinBee-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19860104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vice - Project Doom.zip</path>
		<name>Vice: Project Doom</name>
		<desc>Vice: Project Doom is a game that features side-scrolling platform sequences, overhead driving modes and rail-shooter stages. In driving stages Hart's vehicle can accelerate or slow down and fire his weapon straight ahead. During side-scrolling sequences, Hart can jump, duck, climb or use his selected weapon. Weapons that can be selected include a Katana sword, a pistol and a grenade-type weapon. These weapons feature limited ammunition with the exception of the katana. Power-ups include ammunition, coins, and health. In rail-shooting stages, similar to Operation Wolf, Hart can shoot enemies with his gun or throw grenades and pick up items by shooting at them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Vice - Project Doom-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wai Wai World.zip</path>
		<name>Wai Wai World</name>
		<desc>The player starts the game as Konami Man and can switch between Konami Man and Konami Lady. If two players are gaming, then one will play as Konami Man and the other as Konami Lady. Both players are not able to switch characters until they rescue at least one character from one of the six levels. The player must play through six different selectable levels that take place in different Konami games. Subsequently the player uses a key to save that game's star character, who then becomes playable. Each character has different abilities to begin with as well as ones they can eventually gain. The player ventures through these first six levels in a sort of non-linear fashion with gameplay very similar to the original Castlevania games. After these stages are completed, the player plays through a scrolling space shooter stage and then a linear final stage.

The player will also regularly visit the lab of Dr. Cinnamon (from the TwinBee series), who will give the player the game's character profiles and refill energy when needed. Through his lab, the player can also talk to Saimon, Dr. Cinnamon's brother, who can resurrect any defeated characters at the cost of 100 bullets per character during the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Wai Wai World-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario's Woods.zip</path>
		<name>Wario's Woods</name>
		<desc>It's up to Toad to keep the woods safe in this new Super NES puzzle action!

Toad is back in his very own big adventure in this game with the challenge of Tetris. It's up to you and Toad to keep peace in the Mushroom Kingdom - and that means outfoxing the wicked Wario!

Monsters, goblins and bombs fall from the sky faster and faster as Wario fires them into the woods. Toad must scramble to catch and line up the falling puzzle pieces to eliminate Wario's evil hold. If you loved Tetris, this puzzle action game is for you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Wario's Woods-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5333300000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19941215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Gunman.zip</path>
		<name>Wild Gunman</name>
		<desc>You palm sweats as you grip your Zapper™ light gun. The Outlaw's eyes flash. He yells "Fire!" And suddenly you're in the middle of a Wild West shootout! Get the Outlaw before he gets you, and you'll win a reward! But watch out - the more you win the tougher it becomes, because this gunman has some very nasty friends. You can take on one outlaw, two outlaws - or the whole wild gang. And you up to the action? Because it's fast and furious in this quick -on- the-trigger Nintendo Light Gun game!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Wild Gunman-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6333300000000001</rating>
		<releasedate>19851001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Willow.zip</path>
		<name>Willow</name>
		<desc>Long ago, in a time of magic and sorcery, an evil sorceress named Queen Bavmorda ruled the land under a reign of terror.
A baby has been born who, legend foretells, will destroy the wicked ruler but the Queen vows the slay the child first. Now the villagers of Nelwyn must band together to assist Willow, the child's chosen protector.
As Willow, you must travel through mysterious forests and villages - first evading the Queen and her demons, then plotting to end her reign of terror. You will accumulate an arsenal of swords, shield, and most importantly magic, which are necessary for your final confrontation. Outnumbered by the Nockmaar Army, you must rely on inner strength and determination to destroy the evil Queen - before it's too late!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Willow-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xevious - The Avenger.zip</path>
		<name>Xevious: The Avenger</name>
		<desc>The player uses an 8-way joystick to pilot a combat aircraft called a Solvalou, which is armed with a forward-firing Zapper for aerial targets and a Blaster which fires an unlimited supply of air-to-surface bombs for ground targets. The game, presumably set in Peru, was noted for the varied terrain below, which included forests, airstrips, bases, and mysterious Nazca Line-like drawings on the ground</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Xevious - The Avenger-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yie Ar Kung-Fu.zip</path>
		<name>Yie Ar Kung Fu</name>
		<desc>Oolong has spent his entire life training for the Martial Arts Championship. The Championship has attracted masters of different disciplines, all fighting to be named champion. In Yie Ar Kung-Fu, Oolong must use his own fighting moves and face masters of the throwing shuriken, nunchaku, bo, chain, and more to fulfill his destiny. Will you fight like a tiger or run away in shame?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Yie Ar Kung-Fu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie.zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<desc>Cookie chaos for Mario and Yoshi! Mario and Yoshi are filling in at the Cookie Factory and they need your help! Fresh baked cookies roll out of the ovens. It's up to Mario to sort and stack 'em before they pile too high! Line up a row of the same kind of cookies either vertically or horizontally, and they vanish! Clear the screens to move on to a new level of cookie chaos. Yoshi appears from time to time to stir things up. Play for a high score or head-to-head against a friend. The mouth-watering madness doesn't let up! And be sure to keep some cookies close by, 'cause you'll get the munchies during this lip-smacking good time!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Yoshi's Cookie-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys.zip</path>
		<name>Ys: Ancient Ys Vanished</name>
		<desc>Once long ago, the Kingdom of Y's fell under a reign of evil. But the Goddesses of Y's saved the Kingdom from ruin. Their feats were written in 6 magical books and hidden until the time the Goddesses would be needed again. A thousand years later, that time has come. You are Adol, a wanderer. An evil sorcerer named Dark Dekt is planning diabolical magic. And the Seer Sara is desperately looking for a swordsman to help her find the vanished 6 books of Y's. Now arm yourself and prepare for an adventure into the unknown. Where caverns and towers are filled with creatures and hoards of treasure. Where the strangest people have clues to tell you. Where your skill in combat depends on your reflexes. If you succeed, you'll have the power to call down the Goddesses. Fail, and Dark Dekt will rule the Kingdom under a reign of terror forever!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ys-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zen - Intergalactic Ninja.zip</path>
		<name>Zen: Intergalactic Ninja</name>
		<desc>IF YOU LIKE FIGHTING DIRTY, YOU'RE GONNA DIG ZEN!

The greatest environmental disaster in human history is about to hit your backyard. But you're not backing down, because you're Zen, a cold-blooded Ninja warrior who's come to Earth to clean the clock of Lord Contaminous and his crud-loving cronies.

But wasting these slimeballs won't be easy. Because they'll spew forth the most hazardous graphics ever to wreak havoc on your NES. We're talking horizontal, vertical and 3/4 view scrolling that will give you a whole new perspective on acid rain, oil spills and ozone-ravaging smog. And wait till you see the fluid character movements. They're hotter than a uranium-oozing nuclear meltdown!

There are 12 total levels, each with its own ecological enemies, toxic traps and pollution-fighting objectives. You'll battle oil rig fires, trying to save trapped workers. Use your Photon-Stick to zap gaseous garbage men on a high-speed plutonium mining car ride. Vertical jump through two separate screens to reach a venomous vixen who's single-handedly scorching the rainforests. And spin kick Smogger, a smoked-out scum of the Earth.

Finally, try to survive a rescue mission stage. Rack up points in the bonus recycling level. And slash through 6 subgames that will lead you to the feet of Lord Contaminous, who you must dispose of before he trashes every living thing on the face of the Earth.

For 1 Ninja Master.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zen - Intergalactic Ninja-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930307T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./8 Eyes Castlevania.zip</path>
		<name>8 Eyes Castlevania</name>
		<desc>CONTROL MAN AND BIRD IN A FIGHT FOR THE EIGHT JEWELS OF POWER!

After hundreds of years of chaos, mankind has finally emerged from the ruins of nuclear war. This world of the distant future has once again fluorished under the guidance of the Great King, who harnessed the power of the 8 Eyes to rebuild the planet.

These strange jewels of power were formed at the eyes, or centers, of the eight nuclear explosions which nearly destroyed the Earth. In the wrong hands, the 8 Eyes could cause untold destruction...And now, they have been seized by the Great King's eight Dukes, in a desperate bid to gain control of the world for themselves. They have banished the King to the nuclear wastelands, and already their squabbling threatens to plunge the world into war once again!

The task of retrieving the 8 Eyes falls to you, Orin the Falconer, the bravest and mightiest of the King's Guardsmen. With your fighting falcon, Cutrus, you must penetrate each of the eight Dukes' castles. There you will face the Dukes' soldiers, and battle strange nuclear mutants such as living skeletons, giant wasps, and mud men. You must defeat the monstrous Boss of each castle to retrieve the Jewel of Power he guards.

Then, to complete your quest, return the 8 Eyes to the Altar of Peace to await the return on the Great King, so that he may finish the rebuilding of Earth. Your reward will be the the eternal gratitude of all mankind!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/8 Eyes Castlevania-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Taxan</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Densetsu.zip</path>
		<name>Akumajou Densetsu</name>
		<desc>The year is 1476, and Count Dracula has started to ravage Europe with an army of monsters. The Belmont family of vampire hunters, once exiled from Wallachia, are called into action by the Church. They feared the Belmonts' "super-human" power, but with Dracula menacing to swallow Europe in darkness, they are left with no choice but to call Trevor Belmont, current wielder of the Vampire Killer Whip.

Joining Trevor Belmont in his mission to defeat Dracula are three new playable characters: Sypha Belnades, a young sorceress with poor physical attack power but powerful elemental magic spells at her disposal; Grant Danasty, a pirate with the ability to climb on walls and change direction in mid-jump (a rare ability in earlier games of the series); and Alucard, Dracula's son, a dhampir with the ability to shoot fireballs and transform into a bat. Trevor can be accompanied by only one companion at a time. If he chooses to take on another he must abandon his current companion. The player can "spiritually transform" between Trevor and his ally with the "select" button. Both Trevor and whoever is accompanying him share the same health meter. The ending of the game differs depending on which companion Trevor has with him at the time, or if he does not take another character with him at all.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Akumajou Densetsu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19891222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170210T003737</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Armana no Kiseki.zip</path>
		<name>Armana no Kiseki</name>
		<desc>an FDS game with Indiana Jones style</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Armana no Kiseki-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170304T012242</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hudson's Adventure Island III.zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island III</name>
		<desc>Jeannie Jungle Kidnapped by Space Aliens!
What’s a hero to do? A mysterious flying saucer just made off with Master Higgins’ girlfriend and it’s up to him to save her! But first he must defeat scores of mutated monsters across eight uncharted islands! Fly a dive-bombing pterodactyl or ride under the waves on a sea serpent in search of the missing Jeannie Jungle!

Battle your way through all new dangers and challenges on the biggest Adventure Island yet! Find secret treasure chambers, surf through killer waves and grab all the bonus items you can handle as you master each realm! Action, adventure and more await you in this thrilling addition to the Adventure Island saga!

-A new dinosaur friend joins Master Higgins’ team of wild reptiles!
-Collect Power Crystals to gain temporary in vulnerability!
-Hours of entertainment for the whole family to enjoy!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hudson's Adventure Island III-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T061213</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commando.zip</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando</name>
		<desc>Bionic Commando takes place ten years after an unspecified World War between two warring factions. The game follows a commando who must infiltrate an enemy base and foil the enemy's plot to launch missiles.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Bionic Commando-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19881206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Adventure</name>
		<desc>The game's protagonist is Bonk, a strong caveboy who battles anthropomorphic dinosaurs and other prehistoric themed enemies.  Bonk's mission is to rescue Princess Za (a small pink Pleisiosaur-type reptile) who has been kidnapped by the evil King Drool (a large, green Tyrannosaurus-type dinosaur).  In the Arcade version, Bonk is also assisted by a female version of himself.  Bonk attacks enemies by "bonking" them with his large, invincible forehead.  Bonk starts the game with three hearts' worth of health, which are depleted to blue as Bonk takes damage and three extra lives.  Bonk's health can be restored in increments by collecting fruits and vegetables.  Bonk can also collect pieces of meat as power-ups; these lend him special abilities and make him stronger.  There are three stages of power-up: his normal self, a second stage during which he can stun enemies by pounding on the ground and a third stage where he becomes temporarily invulnerable.  Meat can be found in two varieties: big meat and small meat.  The effects of meat are additive but wear off over time.  A small meat gives Bonk the second stage of meat power but will eventually decay into the first stage of meat power, and then back into regular Bonk.  Eating a small meat while in stage two will put Bonk into the third, invincible stage of meat power.  And eating either size of meat while in the third stage of meat power-up will reset the timer on Bonk's meat power.  Bonk can occasionally collect red heart power-ups that refill an entire heart worth of health, or even more rarely, a large red heart which restores all of Bonk's missing health.  There are also two rare, blue heart power-ups in the game which will increase Bonk's maximum health by one heart.  Bonking an enemy will typically knock it backward and slightly into the air.  Defeating an enemy yields points and also releases a small "smiley" power-up.  Bonk's smileys are totaled at the end of each stage after defeating the boss of that stage.  The player is given additional points and a caveman type congratulation based on how many smileys were collected.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Bonk's Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company, Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>NEC Home Electronics</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania II - Simon's Quest.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II: Simon's Quest</name>
		<desc>Castlevania was a cakewalk compared to this bloody curse. You thought you had the Prince of Darkness defanged - eh, Simon Belmont? Well think again, 'cause according to a damsel in distress, evil Count Dracula has left a horrifying curse in his wake. And the only hope you have of ending the terror is to destroy his missing body parts! Talk about your frightening quest, searching a maze of mansions, graveyards and dark, eerie forests - each guarded by man-eating werewolves, fire-throwing zombies and other devilish demons. Your grim chances are kept alive in Transylvania, where cowardly villagers offer clues to the whereabouts of Dracula's remains. And where you'll purchase magic weapons, including silver knives and flame whips. But beware the night. For when the sun disappears, Dracula's curse grows deadlier. And your chances grow dimmer and dimmer.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170211T191721</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cocoron.zip</path>
		<name>Cocoron</name>
		<desc>Tapir, an enigmatic blue wizard in spotted pajamas from the Dream World, sends the player on a quest to rescue princess Rua. But things quickly become more complicated and the player soon has to rescue other characters along the way, such as Santa Claus, the king of Trump castle and the blue fairy Cocoron. Tapir can manipulate people's dreams and this ability gives Cocoron an unique twist - the player can assemble his own character by combining one of the eight available heads to one of the eight available bodies (which both include several designs to choose from, resulting in literally hundreds of combinations! ). More than a mere physical appearance, each part also defines the character's attributes, such as his health, speed, how high he can jump and so forth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Cocoron-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>K2</developer>
		<publisher>Takera</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Don Doko Don 2.zip</path>
		<name>Don Doko Don 2</name>
		<desc>Similar to the original Don Doko Don, the player controls a bearded dwarf wielding a hammer to flatten enemies and throw them. But unlike the original, this version is a side-scroller. The game consists of five stages, plus the final boss battles. The player's goal is to reach the end of each stage, defeat a boss, and collect a bag,(antidote ingredient,) to advance to the next.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Don Doko Don 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2.zip</path>
		<name>Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2: Donuts Ike ha Oosawagi</name>
		<desc>Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2: Donuts Ike ha Oosawagi (けろけろけろっぴの大冒険2 （ドーナツ池はおおさわぎ！！）?) is a Japan-exclusive action video game video game for children that was released on the Family Computer console in 1993.

This video game has Sanrio's character searching for lost children who have been kidnapped by monsters. Essentially a standard Super Mario Bros. clone, the player controlling the cartoon frog has to leap around platforms jumping on baddies or killing them with his croak weapon. Each bonus level involves matching characters from the Sanrio franchise in a format similar to the card game Concentration. Intermission screens show the progress of the character throughout the game.

Levels range from the forest to a seaside setting.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kero Kero Keroppi no Daibouken 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Character Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cat Ninden Teyandee.zip</path>
		<name>Kyatto Ninden Teyandee</name>
		<desc>Players take the role of the three main cats and otasuke (rescue team) members, who can be switched to at any time and have special abilities to progress through the game. The game features most of the characters in the series as well as an additional villain, a mysterious scientist named Dr. Purple (Dr. パープ).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Cat Ninden Teyandee-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid_Rogue_Dawn.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid: Rogue Dawn</name>
		<desc>A rogue human agent trained and manipulated by Ridley from a young age. She was taken as a child from a Federation colony obliterated by Ridley’s faction where she was initially just another test subject slated to undergo horrific experiments. Ridley decided to instead manipulate and mold her into a weapon, his first human servant, and dark agent. Primed yet untested she is sent out on her “zero” mission to retrieve a newly discovered biological specimen in the possession of a Federation research crew orbiting planet SR388 and prove her worth. Her name is Dawn Aran.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Metroid_Rogue_Dawn-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20170114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Grimlock Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking.net</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T005614</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse 3 - Yume Fuusen.zip</path>
		<name>Mickey Mouse 3: Yume Fuusen</name>
		<desc>Mickey Mouse is working part-time selling balloons in order to buy a present for Minnie, whose birthday is a few days away. He gets news from Pluto that Minnie cannot wake up. He sets off to visit her, only to find that she has been trapped in a nightmare. Now, Mickey must journey into Minnie's mind in order to free her from the nightmare.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mickey Mouse 3 - Yume Fuusen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mitsume ga Tooru.zip</path>
		<name>Mitsume Ga Tooru</name>
		<desc>To learn about his roots, Sharaku must investigate the mysterious ruins that a long lost civilization called the Three-Eyed Ones bequeathed to him. In his worldwide search, which takes both he and Chiyoko Wato to locations like Arizona, Easter Island, and Mexico, Sharaku deciphers ancient scriptures and uses gadgets he invents to help solve (or start) problems and mysteries.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mitsume ga Tooru-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Tomy</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radia Senki - Reimei Hen.zip</path>
		<name>Radia Senki: Reimmeihen</name>
		<desc>The story revolves around a hero who awakens in a field, without any memories of who he is or where he comes from. After befriending a magician named Darus and rescuing Princess Lefis of Ark from her crashed airship, he learns that the nations of Samara and Ark have been conquered by tyrants named Nova and Gadiss respectively. The hero is launched into a quest to protect the Princess, free the people from the villains' reign, and discover his identity.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Radia Senki - Reimei Hen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19911115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Romancia.zip</path>
		<name>Romancia</name>
		<desc>This game is also known as Dragon Slayer Jr., is an action-adventure game developed by Nihon Falcom in 1986 for the PC-8801, PC-9801, MSX, and Sharp X1 computers. A later Famicom version was developed by Compile and published by Tokyo Shoseki. An enhanced remake was released for Windows in 1999 by Unbalance. It is the third in the Dragon Slayer series, preceded by Xanadu and followed by Dragon Slayer IV. Romancia is a simpler and brightly colored game in comparison to the other Dragon Slayer titles, hence the name "Dragon Slayer Jr."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Romancia-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Tokyo Shoseki</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Saiyuuki World 2.zip</path>
		<name>Saiyuki World 2: Tenjokai no Majin</name>
		<desc>"Saiyūki World 2: Tenjōkai no Majin" is an action platformer, akin to many games at the time. The protagonist is Sun Wukong, the King Monkey, one of the most popular characters in the Chinese culture.

After completing the first stage, the player can play the other six in any order. Each of the stages revolve around elements, such as fire and water. After each stage, the player gains a new weapon, much like in the original Mega Man series, which was extremely popular at the time. The game was released with thematic and graphical changes as "Whomp 'Em" for North American audiences.  "Saiyūki World 2: Tenjōkai no Majin" (as well as Whomp 'Em) and the prior Saiyuki World (which was an adaptation of Wonder Boy in Monster Land) are based on the Journey to the West novel.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Saiyuuki World 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Saiyuuki World.zip</path>
		<name>Saiyuuki World</name>
		<desc>Saiyuuki World is an Action game, developed by NMK and published by Jaleco Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 1988.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Saiyuuki World-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NMK</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret Ties.zip</path>
		<name>Secret Ties</name>
		<desc>Secret Ties is an Action game, developed by Graphic Research and published by Vic Tokai, which was cancelled before it was released.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Secret Ties-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer>Graphic Research</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 2.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<desc>Mario’s back!  Bigger and badder than before!  This time it’s a fierce action-packed battle to free the land of Subcon from the curse of the evil Wart.  It’s up to you, along with Mario, Luigi, Toad and the Princess, to fight your way through bizarre multi-level worlds and find him!  This time you’ve got a brand new kind of power - plucking power - and now anything you find can be a weapon.  But beware!  You’ve never seen creatures like these!  Shyguys and Tweeters!  Ninji and Beezos!  And you’ve never had an adventure like this!  Only cunning and speed can save you now…</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super Mario Bros. 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19881001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T005726</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda (DX).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda DX</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the Legend of Zelda.  Where the only sound you’ll hear is your own heart pounding as you race through forests, lakes, mountains and dungeonous mazes in an attempt to restore peace to the land of Hyrule.  Along the way you’ll be challenged by Tektites, Wizzrobes and an endless array of ruthless creatures who’ll stop at nothing to prevent you from finding the lost fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom.  But don’t despair.  With a little luck and a lot of courage, you’ll conquer your adversaries, unite the Triforce fragments and unravel the mystery of the Legend of Zelda!

* Explore the vast Overworld terrain of the land of Hyrule and discover hidden treasures.
* Explore the mystical labyrinths of the Underworld and ward-off ruthless enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Legend of Zelda (DX)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T022058</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Zone.zip</path>
		<name>Time Zone</name>
		<desc>Oh, no! On the way to meet your girlfriend Haruka, our intrepid little hero has gotten ambushed by that nefarious, time-traveling villain, Professor Time. Now it's time to join him as he crosses time and space to save her from his evil clutches.

In this run and jump action game, you'll find yourself flung anywhere from prehistoric times to the far future and back again, defeating anything from dinosaurs to samurai to aliens just to get her back.

Your main weapon — your ever-sturdy baseball cap. Just toss it forward and let it simply boomerang back or jump as it boomerangs back to let it fly around you for a short amount of time. And if you're lucky enough to collect enough chimes, you'll get to witness the awesome destructive power and invincibility of the skateboard.

Combined that with a host of hazardous obstacles so prevalent in platformers and you've got yourself into quite a pickle trying to tackle Professor Time. Pursue and flog him with your cap so that the hero and Haruka can live happily ever after.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Time Zone-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19911025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EIM</developer>
		<publisher>Sigma Ent. Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type EX.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type EX+</name>
		<desc>Hack of Magic Dragon of teh Famicom with graphics similar to those on the real R-Type game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/R-Type EX-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<genre>Hack</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra Japan.zip</path>
		<name>Contra Japan</name>
		<desc>The universe teeters on the brink of total annihilation at the hands of the vile alien warmonger, Red Falcon. Earth's only hope rests with you, a courageous member of the Special Forces elite commando squad. Your mission: Battle deep into the deadly Amazon jungle, where the Red Falcon and his galactic henchmen have transformed ancient Mayan temples into awesome monuments dedicated to mass destruction. A multitude of weapons, from rapid-fire machine guns to high-tech lasers are at your disposal as you sweat blood, fighting past 3-D mazes, underground security systems, and tropical forests surrounded by giant waterfalls and alien cannons. This is the ultimate test for the ultimate guerilla warrior. And if you survive, Earth survives!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Contra Japan-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T015219</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Getsufuu Maden.zip</path>
		<name>Getsu Fuuma Den</name>
		<desc>In the distant future of 14672 A.D., the first year of the Demon Age, the demon lord Ryoukotsuki escaped from hell and plotted to conquer the surface world ruled by the three Getsu brothers. The Getsu brothers fought against Ryoukotsuki, each wielding one of the three spiritual Pulse Blades that have been passed within the clan for generations. However, the brothers were ultimately defeated by the demon and only Fuuma, the youngest of the three, survived. Vowing to avenge his slain brothers, Fūma ventures into Kyouki-tou to recover the three stolen Pulse Blades and summon the spirits of his brothers to defeat Ryoukotsuki.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Getsufuu Maden-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!.zip</path>
		<name>Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>It's a right jab, a left hook, an uppercut - it's Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! where you'll get the chance to compete against boxers from around the globe. Punch your way through 13 bouts in the minor, major and world circuits against tough contestants like Piston Honda, Glass Joe, Super Macho Man and many, many more! Defeat all your opponents and meet the ultimate challenge against the World Heavyweight Champion Mike Tyson in the greatest fight of all - The Dream Bout! Knockout Tyson and you can become WVBA (World Video Boxing Association) Champ!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19871001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Takahashi Meijin no Boukenjima 4.zip</path>
		<name>Takahashi Meijin no Bouken Jima IV</name>
		<desc>Takahashi Meijin no Bouken Jima IV is an Action game, developed by Hudson Soft and published by Hudson, which was released in Japan in 1994.

Last Adventure Island game for NES.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Takahashi Meijin no Boukenjima 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda (automap).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the Legend of Zelda.  Where the only sound you’ll hear is your own heart pounding as you race through forests, lakes, mountains and dungeonous mazes in an attempt to restore peace to the land of Hyrule.  Along the way you’ll be challenged by Tektites, Wizzrobes and an endless array of ruthless creatures who’ll stop at nothing to prevent you from finding the lost fragments of the Triforce of Wisdom.  But don’t despair.  With a little luck and a lot of courage, you’ll conquer your adversaries, unite the Triforce fragments and unravel the mystery of the Legend of Zelda!

* Explore the vast Overworld terrain of the land of Hyrule and discover hidden treasures.
* Explore the mystical labyrinths of the Underworld and ward-off ruthless enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Legend of Zelda (automap)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xexyz.zip</path>
		<name>Xexyz</name>
		<desc>The game centers around the main character of Apollo (no relation to the Greek sun god) who progresses through the game in an alternating format that switches between platform, side-scrolling action (similar to the Super Mario Bros. series) and side-scrolling shooter action (similar to Konami's Gradius series). The goal of the series is, stereotypically, to destroy an evil boss — Goruza — rescue a princess — in this case, Princess Maria — and save the planet.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Xexyz-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19880826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170306T042912</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys II - Ancient Ys Vanished - The Final Chapter.zip</path>
		<name>Ys II: Ancient Ys Vanished – The Final Chapter</name>
		<desc>A bright light shot up from Darm Tower in the end of the first Ys, and Adol Christin is awakened by a young girl who finds him lying on the ground. She introduces herself as Lilia and tells Adol he is in the land of Ys. Finally he was able to establish a connection between his world and this mysterious land! But finding the gateway to Ys is not enough: Adol must stop an evil entity that his archenemy Dark Fact served. And his foes already know where he is.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ys II - Ancient Ys Vanished - The Final Chapter-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III - Wanderers From Ys.zip</path>
		<name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<desc>As Adol, hero of Ys Book I &amp; II, your most fearsome new adventure is about to begin! The curse of the monster Demanicus terrorizes your friend Dogi's homeland. Chaos rules as blood-thirsty creatures threaten innocent lives. Only you have the courage and strength to defeat them! Gather your fiercest swords and deadly amulet to battle these horrific creatures with a thrilling new action view. Survive the fiery depths of Alcaino. Conquer the terrifying Nekevil. But stay alert, brave Adol! The fury of Demanicus awaits your final epic struggle!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ys III - Wanderers From Ys-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19891020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Advance Communication</developer>
		<publisher>Victor</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda II - Journey of a Day.zip</path>
		<name>Zelda II: Journey of a Day</name>
		<desc>The land of Hyrule is in chaos.  As Link, you’ll be sent on a treacherous journey to return six precious Crystals to their origins in six stone statues.  Only by defeating the guardians of the six palaces will you gain passage to the seventh palace, take on the ultimate challenge that awaits you, and wake the Princess Zelda from her sleeping spell.  On your way, helpful villagers you encounter will offer clues and secret messages invaluable in your quest.  As you guide Link through the levels of Hyrule, close-ups and overviews will enhance your video vision.  Are you up to the challenge?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zelda II - Journey of a Day-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170306T042653</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda II - Shadow of Night.zip</path>
		<name>Zelda II: Shadow of Night</name>
		<desc>The land of Hyrule is in chaos.  As Link, you’ll be sent on a treacherous journey to return six precious Crystals to their origins in six stone statues.  Only by defeating the guardians of the six palaces will you gain passage to the seventh palace, take on the ultimate challenge that awaits you, and wake the Princess Zelda from her sleeping spell.  On your way, helpful villagers you encounter will offer clues and secret messages invaluable in your quest.  As you guide Link through the levels of Hyrule, close-ups and overviews will enhance your video vision.  Are you up to the challenge?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zelda II - Shadow of Night-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda II - The Adventure of Link.zip</path>
		<name>Zelda II: The Adventure of Link</name>
		<desc>The land of Hyrule is in chaos.  As Link, you’ll be sent on a treacherous journey to return six precious Crystals to their origins in six stone statues.  Only by defeating the guardians of the six palaces will you gain passage to the seventh palace, take on the ultimate challenge that awaits you, and wake the Princess Zelda from her sleeping spell.  On your way, helpful villagers you encounter will offer clues and secret messages invaluable in your quest.  As you guide Link through the levels of Hyrule, close-ups and overviews will enhance your video vision.  Are you up to the challenge?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zelda II - The Adventure of Link-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda - The Legend of Link.zip</path>
		<name>Zelda: The Legend of Link</name>
		<desc>Various ancient legends have been recorded of a young boy clothed in green, wielding the mythical master sword, sealing away all evil throughout the land. His ventures, passed down through generations have become legend. The hero of legend, had many different forms. He saved many kingdoms, restoring peace in all the lands. This is but one of the legends, of which the people speak…</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zelda - The Legend of Link-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20141005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>infidelity</developer>
		<publisher>infidelity</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Jajamaru.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Jajamaru: Ginga Daisakusen</name>
		<desc>Ninja Jajamaru: Ginga Daisakusen is an Action game, developed and published by Jaleco Entertainment, which was released in Japan in 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Ninja Jajamaru-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170306T044529</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Over Horizon.zip</path>
		<name>Over Horizon</name>
		<desc>Over Horizon is a Shoot-'Em-Up game, developed by Pixel and published by Hot-B, which was released in Europe in 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Over Horizon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pixel</developer>
		<publisher>Takara</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros..zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Do you have what it takes to save the Mushroom Princess?  You’ll have to think fast and move even faster to complete this quest!  The Mushroom Princess is being held captive by the evil Koopa tribe of turtles.  It’s up to you to rescue her from the clutches of the Koopa King before time runs out.  But it won’t be easy.  To get to the Princess, you’ll have to climb mountains, cross seas, avoid bottomless pits, fight off turtle soldiers and a host of black magic traps that only a Koopa King can devise.  It’s another non-stop adventure from the Super Mario Bros.!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Super Mario Bros.-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170215T000611</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./8 Eyes.zip</path>
		<name>8 Eyes</name>
		<desc>CONTROL MAN AND BIRD IN A FIGHT FOR THE EIGHT JEWELS OF POWER!

After hundreds of years of chaos, mankind has finally emerged from the ruins of nuclear war. This world of the distant future has once again fluorished under the guidance of the Great King, who harnessed the power of the 8 Eyes to rebuild the planet.

These strange jewels of power were formed at the eyes, or centers, of the eight nuclear explosions which nearly destroyed the Earth. In the wrong hands, the 8 Eyes could cause untold destruction...And now, they have been seized by the Great King's eight Dukes, in a desperate bid to gain control of the world for themselves. They have banished the King to the nuclear wastelands, and already their squabbling threatens to plunge the world into war once again!

The task of retrieving the 8 Eyes falls to you, Orin the Falconer, the bravest and mightiest of the King's Guardsmen. With your fighting falcon, Cutrus, you must penetrate each of the eight Dukes' castles. There you will face the Dukes' soldiers, and battle strange nuclear mutants such as living skeletons, giant wasps, and mud men. You must defeat the monstrous Boss of each castle to retrieve the Jewel of Power he guards.

Then, to complete your quest, return the 8 Eyes to the Altar of Peace to await the return on the Great King, so that he may finish the rebuilding of Earth. Your reward will be the the eternal gratitude of all mankind!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/8 Eyes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>Taxan</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jr..zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
		<desc>Mario has gone mad! He's turned the tables on Donkey Kong and locked him in a cage. It's up to you, as Donkey Kong Jr., to rescue your father by stealing Mario's set of keys. But it won't be easy. You'll have to fight off ape-eating Snapjaws, jump onto moving islands and break through a jungle of vines to get to the keys that will free Donkey Kong. Can you handle the action? Because this off-the-wall monkey business will have you going bananas!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Donkey Kong Jr.-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Buster II.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Buster II: Yami no Fuuin</name>
		<desc>The main hero named Carl is a dragon slayer who wields a bow and arrow. He has to pass 6 stages and reach the Dragon Castle to retrieve the sword which the hero of the original Dragon Buster, Clovis, used as a weapon.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Dragon Buster II-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170202T021711</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaiketsu Yanchamaru 2.zip</path>
		<name>Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 2: Karakuri Land</name>
		<desc>Kaiketsu Yancha Maru 2: Karakuri Land is an Action game, developed and published by Irem, which was released in Japan in 1991.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kaiketsu Yanchamaru 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaiketsu Yanchamaru 3.zip</path>
		<name>Kaiketsu Yancha maru 3: Taiketsu! Zōringen</name>
		<desc>The princess has been kidnapped again, this time by a pair of menacing-looking figures. Locked in a tower, she manages to write a plea for help on a scrap of paper and then sends a paper airplane out of her prison. Miraculously, it reaches her boyfriend Yanchamaru who, being the upstanding samurai that he is, immediately sets out to save her.

Kaiketsu Yanchamaru 3 is the final sequel to Kid Niki and is a significant departure from the first two games. Not only does the game feature full four-way scrolling and large maps to explore, but Yanchamaru himself sports a completely new look and numerous new abilities. His trademark spinning sword now seems to more closely resemble a bō, and Yanchamaru can now use it to shoot waves of energy at foes, bounce on the end, spin in place, and even launch off of walls and corners. Taking a cue from Mega Man, he also now has the ability to slide through narrow spaces and underneath dangerous spikes.

Each stage contains numerous keys and locked doors. Any key will open any door, and it is possible to complete a stage without even finding all the keys and doors. The final door in each stage leads to the boss room. After clearing each stage, your performance is tallied, and depending on what you did, bonuses such as points or lives are given.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Kaiketsu Yanchamaru 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Khaos</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic John.zip</path>
		<name>Magic John</name>
		<desc>John is hired as an apprentice magician by Pong. He is training when some strange people attack and kidnap his girlfriend, Yuu. John goes on a quest to find out where they came from and why they wanted Yuu. Afterwards, John discovers Yuu's kidnapping was a feint to force Yuu's father, a renowned scientist, out of hiding. John must not only save Yuu's father, but ultimately battle an evil king who plans to lead a subterranean army in a battle against the people of John's world.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Magic John-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Doropie.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Kid's Doropie</name>
		<desc>The year is 1999. When the Akudama Empire attacks the Earth with his army of robots. No conventional weapon in existence is efficient against this opponent. The robots are, however, totally vulnerable to magic. An hired mercenary, Kagemaru, summons the only non-sealed witch, Doropie, to stop the Akudama Empire's offence. The imperial army, led by an old nemesis of Doropie, Empress Elysia, does not surrender though. Elysia captures Kagemaru and blackmails Doropie into breaking her seal and setting her free. It seems that the mercenary lost his life, and Doropie sets out to stop the now-free Empress. After the battle, the dying Empress Elysia confesses the reasons behind the invasion and apologizes. The imperial warship explodes shortly thereafter, but not before Doropie escapes it. She is contacted by Kagemaru, who apparently has survived the wounds that Elysia inflicted on him. Doropie comes back to Earth shortly afterwards.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Magical Doropie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Bros..zip</path>
		<name>Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Mario and Luigi are doing some underground plumbing when all sorts of weird creatures come flying out of the pipes. Turtles, crabs - even fighterflies - attack the helpless Mario Bros. It's up to you to kick, punch, and knock out these sewer pests before time runs out! But beware. Just when you think you got rid of them, they come back for more! Play against the computer, or with a friend - either way, this is one underground classic you'll want to play time and time again!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mario Bros.-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid [mOTHER].zip</path>
		<name>Metroid: mOther</name>
		<desc>Metroid: mOther is a hack of the original Metroid aiming to fully update sound and graphics to resemble Super Metroid. Space Pirates attack a Galactic Federation-owned space research vessel and seize samples of Metroid creatures. As a last resort, the Federation decides to send a lone bounty hunter to penetrate the Pirates' base. Samus Aran is chosen for the mission.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Metroid [mOTHER]-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20140422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>dACE</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mother 25th Anniversary Edition.zip</path>
		<name>Mother 25th Anniversary Edition</name>
		<desc>Mother: 25th Anniversary Edition aims to make Mother much more enjoyable for both Earthbound fans and those playing it for the first time. All enemy graphics, NPC sprites and tiles are be redrawn from scratch to be more faithful to the clay models. The goofy enemies are goofier and the creepy enemies are creepier. A shiny new font and title screen was added, too!

The overworld has been tweaked to be much less bleak and repetitive, so it’s harder to get lost. There is more scenery, areas are more colorful and confusing areas like Duncan’s factory have been simplified. On the other hand, tiny areas like the Cemetery or Snowman have been expanded.

There are also a lot of changes under the hood. Enemies will yield slightly more exp and the encounter rate has been readjusted. The “Dangerous Foe” battle theme is used less often and party members will be met at a higher level. DragonDePlatino’s goal in creating this hack was to make Mother less challenging, but still quite difficult.

And last but not least, this hack uses Tomato’s official Mother 1 + 2 translation, adapted for the NES. Over 1400 lines of text have been altered to create connections with the rest of the series, improve clarity and shorten reading time. This hack will also feature much quicker battle text courtesy of vince94. Battles progress almost twice as quickly!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Mother 25th Anniversary Edition-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20141105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Starmen</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hebereke.zip</path>
		<name>Hebereke</name>
		<desc>Hebereke (へべれけ?) is a video game series developed by Sunsoft that was released primarily in Japan, with a few releases in Europe and one release in North America. It was one of the company's main franchises during the 1990s. Hebe, the main character of the series, became Sunsoft's main mascot during this period, appearing on the company's logo in several games and commercials. The series features a comical, yet surreal setting and characters. The title of the series comes from a Japanese colloquialism for drunkenness. The series covers several different genres from platforming to puzzle, though they are all set in the same fictional universe.

The first Hebereke game for the Nintendo Entertainment System was released in the PAL region under the title of Ufouria: The Saga, which changed the names of the main characters, while two of them had their looks changed. A North American release was planned, but canceled; however, the PAL region version was later added to the Wii Virtual Console in North America. A later set of games for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System were also released under the Hebereke title, which retained the original names and looks from the Japanese version.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Hebereke-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wai Wai World 2 - SOS!!.zip</path>
		<name>Wai Wai World 2: SOS!! Parsley Jou</name>
		<desc>Wai Wai World is in trouble, as the evil Waruumon has kidnapped Princess Herb! Luckily, Dr. Cinnimon has created a hero that can stop him. Rikkuru! Can he save the princess, by traveling through all of Wai Wai world??</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Wai Wai World 2 - SOS!!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Hunter.zip</path>
		<name>Zombie Hunter</name>
		<desc>Zombie Hunter is a Role-Playing game, developed by Lenar and published by Hi-Score Media Work, which was released in Japan in 1987.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Zombie Hunter-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lenar</developer>
		<publisher>Hi-Score Media Work</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II: The Arcade Game</name>
		<desc>Yo! After being treated like garbage by the Ninja Turtles, Shredder has trained a new, more merciless breed of Foot Soldiers to inflict his revenge: A clan of over 700 Taekwondo turtle terminators who have once again captured April O'Neil to use as turtle bait. Fortunately you don't have to face these freaks of torture alone. For the first time ever, two dudes or dudettes can join forces and double-team Shredder, kicking shell while covering each others tails.

But to survive you've gotta fight through 8 action-packed arcade levels, including Vinnie's Valet "Stalking" Lot and the Soho Sewer System, plus two new never-before-seen shell-squashing stages! Each of these deathtraps is reinforced by lethal electro zappers, laser beams, freezer burners or enemies such as Scorpion Robots, Stone Warriors and Baxter Stockman. Shredder has also hired the all-powerful Tora and Shogun, two alien bounty hunters who have never known defeat.

Even though Master Splinter has prepared the turtles well for battle, teaching them radical new attack moves, it doesn't mean this war to save April and turtlekind will be a piece of cake or even a slice of pizza. Because with the forces of revenge on his side and the bounty boys in town, it's payback time for Shredder!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.76667</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170307T225139</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris.zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<desc>A random sequence of tetrominoes (sometimes called "tetrads" in older versions)—shapes composed of four square blocks each—fall down the playing field (a rectangular vertical shaft, called the "well" or "matrix"). The objective of the game is to manipulate these tetrominoes, by moving each one sideways and rotating it by 90 degree units, with the aim of creating a horizontal line of blocks without gaps. When such a line is created, it disappears, and any block above the deleted line will fall. With every ten lines that are cleared, the game enters a new level. As the game progresses, each level causes the tetrominoes to fall faster, and the game ends when the stack of tetrominoes reaches the top of the playing field and no new tetrominoes are able to enter. In certain versions, the game can also end if the player is able to get all the way to level 15.

All of the tetrominoes are capable of single and double clears. I, J, and L are able to clear triples. Only the I tetromino has the capacity to clear four lines simultaneously, and this is referred to as a "tetris". (This may vary depending on the rotation and compensation rules of each specific Tetris implementation. For instance, in the Super Rotation System used in most recent implementations, called "Easy Spin" in Tetris Worlds, certain rare situations allow T, S and Z to 'snap' into tight spots and clear triples.)</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Tetris-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.725</rating>
		<releasedate>19880715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet-Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170307T225121</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yume Penguin Monogatari.zip</path>
		<name>Yume Penguin Monogatari</name>
		<desc>Penta, a cute blue penguin, has a tragic flaw - he really enjoys eating. As a result, his girlfriend Penko left him for another fashionable penguin called Ginji because, she thinks, he has become too chubby for her liking. And yet, she decides to give him a second chance - if he manages to lose all this weight and keep it off, then she will give all her love and attention to him. But the covetous Ginji doesn't share the same sentiments and will do everything in his power to stop the poor flightless seabird before he slims down.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/nes/Yume Penguin Monogatari-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T175725</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
