<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-cvdp.cso</path>
		<name>Castlevania The Dracula X Chronicles</name>
		<desc>The legendary action game Castlevania: Rondo of Blood (the "lost" chapter never seen before outside of Japan) is reborn on the PSP system with incredible 3D graphics and timeless side scrolling gameplay in Castlevania: The Dracula X Chronicles. Gamers take up the Vampire Killer whip as Richter Belmont as they seek to destroy the maniacal Dracula once and for all in this pivotal piece of the ongoing Castlevania saga. Castlevania: The Dracula X Chronicles also includes unlockable versions of the original Rondo of Blood and Symphony of the Night games, delivering incredible gameplay and value while updating two of the most beloved video games of all time for a new generation of gamers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-cvdp-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20070823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>konami</developer>
		<publisher>konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T173255</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./a-daxter.cso</path>
		<name>Daxter</name>
		<desc>Daxter is centered around the world of the lovable orange ottsel made popular in the Jak and Daxter franchise. The story unfolds as Daxter searches for Jak, who was imprisoned during the events that led to the start of "Jak II." Daxter, now on his own in an unfamiliar place, quickly realizes that being small and furry won't help his chances of survival. To help stamp out a mysterious metalbug infestation, Daxter takes on a job as a pest exterminator, enabling him to explore parts of Haven City in an effort to collect the clues that will lead him to Jak. Daxter allows gamers to play from his perspective offering a distinctive set of moves with agile abilities that allows players to climb walls, creep up on enemies, fit in small places and maneuver vehicles. Taking a job as a pest exterminator, to fight an ongoing invasion of metal-bugs, Daxter comes equip with gadgets to rid the city of these metal nuisances. Get close up and personal by using your flimsy bug swatter to squash an army of attacking insects or your spray gun to hover around a variety of environments while picking up various upgrades.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/a-daxter-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pa-ffiiiu.cso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<desc>1,000 years ago, the War of the Magi occurred. People remember it as one of the most horrible tragedies in history. Since the War of the Magi, magic has been all but forgotten, technology began to grow, and people returned to seemingly normal lives. The only true worry people had was the Empire, whose leaders were looking to revive the great force once known as "magic".</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/pa-ffiiiu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20061115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hr-prinny2.cso</path>
		<name>Prinny 2: Dawn of Operation Panties, Dood!</name>
		<desc>Prinny 2 is a side scrolling hack and slash action game. Players will control demonic penguins, Prinnies, who are known as the "weakest monsters in the Netherworld." Players can run, jump, slash, execute special skills, and ride tanks or jets to battle enemies. The Prinnies' mission is to find Demon Lord Etna's stolen panties! If they fail... Etna will turn THEM into panties! As an extra bonus, a whole new main character and story become available after you complete the main game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/hr-prinny2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20110111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-prin.cso</path>
		<name>Prinny: Can I Really Be the Hero?</name>
		<desc>Prinny will be the most heart-pounding and challenging side-scrolling action game ever. Players will control an unlucky penguin dude called a Prinny and slash their way through various Netherworlds. For this tough-as-nails action game, you're given 1000 units to accomplish your mission, but even with those 1000 units you will have to use everything you find on the battlefield to survive. Lift and throw objects, stomp enemies, even pilot tanks and planes to bombard whatever gets in your way!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-prin-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nippon Ichi Software</developer>
		<publisher>NIS America</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-rcsm.cso</path>
		<name>Ratchet &amp; Clank: Size Matters</name>
		<desc>Ratchet &amp; Clank: Size Matters (known as Ratchet &amp; Clank 5 in Japan) is a 2007 platformer video game developed by High Impact Games and published by Sony Computer Entertainment for the PlayStation Portable and PlayStation 2. The game is the first Ratchet &amp; Clank title on the PSP handheld. Development company High Impact Games was spawned from the original Ratchet &amp; Clank developer, Insomniac Games. The story is about Ratchet and Clank as they are interrupted from their vacation to search for a kidnapped girl and encounter a forgotten race known as the Technomites</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-rcsm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T170423</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pa-shouu.cso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill Origins</name>
		<desc>The renowned Silent Hill survival horror series makes its handheld gaming debut with a brand new adventure that reveals many of the series' most hallowed secrets. Assuming the role of Travis Grady, a lone truck driver trapped in Silent Hill while making a routine delivery, players must escape the city's horrific inhabitants and confront the strange hallucinations that have haunted Travis since childhood. Taking full advantage of the PSP system's graphics, sound, and portability, Silent Hill Origins sets a new standard in handheld gaming terror.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/pa-shouu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Group</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T170940</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pa-3rdu.cso</path>
		<name>The 3rd Birthday</name>
		<desc>Hideous creatures descend on Manhattan. Ground reports from the squad tasked with containing the pandemonium refer to these life forms as the Twisted. An investigatory team known as the CTI is formed within the year.
The Overdive system emerges as a means of opposition, but only one viable candidate exists -- Aya Brea. A gift as she awakens from a lost past on this, the occasion of her third birth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/pa-3rdu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hexa Drive</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./b-ysiiiu.cso</path>
		<name>Ys I &amp; II Chronicles</name>
		<desc>Ys I &amp; II consists of enhanced remakes of the first two games released in the Ys series, Ys I: Ancient Ys Vanished and Ys II: Ancient Ys Vanished – The Final Chapter. 
In both games the player controls a red-haired swordsman named Adol Christin. In the first game he must seek out the six Books of Ys. These books contain the history of the ancient, vanished land of Ys, and will give him the knowledge he needs to defeat the evil forces currently sweeping the land of Esteria.
In Ys II Adol is transported to the floating civilization of Ys, and begins a quest to unravel the secrets of the land, and finally rid it and Esteria of evil. All English translations of Ys II were part of a compilation; no standalone version has been localized.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/b-ysiiiu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20110221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T171900</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./b-ys7uu.cso</path>
		<name>Ys Seven</name>
		<desc>The kingdom of Altago is rebuilding their kingdom around a newfound peace after years of war against the merciless armies of Romn. The classic adventuresome duo, Adol and Dogi, arrive in the harbor of Altago City, and quickly find themselves in a scuffle with the Dragon Knights, the kingdom's military police body, when attempting to save a local girl from harassment by one of their commanding officers. Upset by the interruption and subsequent humiliation, the commander arrests Adol and Dogi, charging them with espionage. The king of Altago, having known of the duo's pending arrival from an old trusted friend, quickly releases the pair from prison and summons them to his chambers. He tells the men about an ancient shrine that was uncovered after a recent earthquake, and asks for their help in investigating this mysterious new find. Adol and Dogi oblige, unaware that they are about to take the first steps on a long journey to save all of Altago from long-forgotten ancient forces, and to reunite the estranged five tribes who serve and protect the Five Great Dragons deified beings who may well be the world's last hope. Ys Seven is the latest installment in the long-running Ys series which first debuted on PC in 1987. This is the first iteration to be built specifically for the PSP system, taking full advantage of the widescreen format and hardware. The battle system consists of a three-member battle party with enemies engaged on the field map in real-time for fast-paced combat. Old fans of the series and new players alike will be immersed into the rich vibrant world containing over 30 hours of gameplay.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/b-ys7uu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100817T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T171806</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./d-y6aon.cso</path>
		<name>Ys: The Ark of Napishtim</name>
		<desc>The story begins after Adol's ship is attacked by a fleet of Romun ships. Forced to sail into an unknown area, they encounter a large storm. Adol is swept off the vessel while trying to rescue a fellow sailor and washed ashore by the vortex that surrounds the Canaan Islands. He is found, unconscious, by the daughters of the chieftain of the nearby Rehda village, Olha and Isha. The girls take him to their village and lay him to rest in their father's house. Adol hears them talking about him and wakes up briefly, afterwards going back to sleep because of his exhaustion. His adventure then begins.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/d-y6aon-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T171349</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pspking-ytoif.cso</path>
		<name>Ys: The Oath in Felghana</name>
		<desc>Ys: The Oath in Felghana is a re-imagined remake celebrating the 20th anniversary of the classic third game from the long-running Ys series, Ys III: Wanderers From Ys. Its rebirth on PSP includes a complete graphical overhaul, fully revamped gameplay, intense 3D action, and additional story elements culminating with full voice-overs during story sequences. Other additional features include a rearranged soundtrack, adjustable difficulty levels, and an art gallery, all ensuring that this beautifully re-imagined classic can be enjoyed equally by Wanderers veterans and series newcomers alike.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/pspking-ytoif-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20101102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170312T170251</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-ff2u.cso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy II</name>
		<desc>FINAL FANTASY II is highly anticipated follow-up to the original FINAL FANTASY, released in Japan in 1988. The game features the bitter and beautiful tale of four war-orphaned heroes who become embroiled in a conflict between the hostile Empire of Palamecia and the rebel resistance. By eschewing conventional leveling for a proficiency system that allows players to tailor their characters' growth and incorporating a key term memory system that makes dialogue integral to gameplay, this game sparked the spirit of innovation for which the series has become known. This release also contains the bonus dungeons added to later editions of the game--the Soul of Rebirth and the Arcane Labyrinth.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-ff2u-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SquareSoft</developer>
		<publisher>SquareSoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170313T235137</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./b-popfsu.cso</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia: The Forgotten Sands</name>
		<desc>Prince of Persia: The Forgotten Sands is the next chapter in the fan-favorite Sands of Time universe. Visiting his brother's kingdom following his adventure in Azad, the Prince finds the royal palace under siege from a mighty army bent on its destruction. When the decision is made to use the ancient power of the Sand in a desperate gamble to save the kingdom from total annihilation, the Prince will embark on an epic adventure in which he will learn to bear the mantle of true leadership, and discover that great power often comes with a great cost.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/b-popfsu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20100518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170314T230652</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./d-mmpwu.cso</path>
		<name>Mega Man Powered Up</name>
		<desc>Mega Man ...like you've never seen him!

The diabolical Dr. Wily is bent on world domination, and only Mega Man can stop his evil Minions. With a spiffy new look and amazing new powers, Mega Man is better than ever in his wildest adventure yet!

For the first time ever, play as any of the powerful bosses! Take control! Build &amp; explore your own levels. Use Infrastructure Mode to send your creations to Mega Man users around the world and test their skill.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/d-mmpwu-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170315T001159</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./a-ugandg.cso</path>
		<name>Ultimate Ghosts 'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>An exclusive PSP edition of Capcom's legendary platforming game, directed by the original's creator Tokurou Fujiwara. The game makes use of a 3D graphics engine, giving depth to the visuals, but plays in a side-scrolling perspective and similar art design to stay true to the original. Your goal is to work your way through side-scrolling stages, defeating enemies and using your best platforming skills. The game lets you build up your skills as you progress. You start off with just a basic jump, but eventually gain a double jump and even the ability to fly. You'll also earn lots of magic spells along the way. The game promises a greater number of spells and weapons than ever before. New for Goku Makaimura is non-linear gameplay. You're no longer on a fixed path from start to end. The levels include branching points and even warp points. By using a warp point, you can warp back to previous levels and collecting items that you might have missed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/a-ugandg-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170315T002547</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ggl-ccff7u.cso</path>
		<name>Crisis Core: Final Fantasy VII</name>
		<desc>Seven years prior to the events of FINAL FANTASY VII, the Shinra Company is finalizing construction of its base and symbol of prosperity: the enormous city of Midgar. When Genesis, a prominent SOLDIER 1st Class in Shinra's private army disappears with his contingent, young prodigy Zack is given the task of seeking him out. The story continues where it all began in an enthralling prelude to one of gaming's greatest sagas.

-The exciting prequel to FINAL FANTASY VII uncovers the origin and secrets behind some of the most popular characters in SQUARE ENIX history.
-Home console-quality graphics on a portable platform. Stunning, state-of-the-art visuals bring the FINAL FANTASY VII universe to life on the PSP &amp; reg; system.
-A blend of action and RPG elements provide for a completely new FINAL FANTASY VII experience. The fast-paced real-time battle system is the latest evolution of classic FINAL FANTASY gameplay</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/ggl-ccff7u-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20080325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170314T235203</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./d-mmmhx.cso</path>
		<name>Mega Man: Maverick Hunter X</name>
		<desc>Get ready for X-treme adventure!

When Sigma leads a group of Reploids in a revolt against mankind, it's up to X and Zero to protect world from ruin.

The revolutionary Mega Man X side scrolling game is recreated wih 3D graphics, remixed music, and special unlockable features.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/d-mmmhx-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060131T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170316T003748</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-sfdm.cso</path>
		<name>Syphon Filter - Dark Mirror</name>
		<desc>Assume the role of Gabe Logan, a highly-trained Precision Strike Operative, commanding a black box United States Agency that legally doesn't exist. Gabe finds himself dealing with a beautiful woman from his past who harbors a shocking secret while he battles the Red Section, a para-military group in possession of Project Dark Mirror, a next-generation weapon of mass destruction. Using Precision Strike Tactics, advanced vision technology, and the latest in high-tech weaponry, Logan and his team perform surgical strike missions - too sensitive for a military response, too dangerous for civilian intelligence forces. Through the role of Gabe, players will have to be quick to strategize, as he is responsible to infiltrate, recon and execute decisively. Once inserted, Logan is his own authority - he must make life and death decisions, quickly choosing which course of action to take.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-sfdm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170316T011702</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-khbbs.cso</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts: Birth by Sleep</name>
		<desc>Birth by Sleep is an action roleplaying game that introduces a gameplay aspect called the Command System, which allows players to customize a Command Deck with techniques and abilities that they can perform at will, called Deck Commands. Performing ordinary attacks and Commands fills a gauge displayed above the command deck that, when certain requirements are fulfilled, activates a Command Style that changes the player's basic attack command with the "Surge" command, which racks up powerful combos depending on what Command Style is activated. Filling the gauge with certain requirements a second time causes the character to change into an even higher level Command Style, which replaces the "Surge" command with the more powerful "Storm" command.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-khbbs-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God-of-War.cso</path>
		<name>God of War: Chains of Olympus</name>
		<desc>The game is set in Ancient Greece and loosely based on its mythology. The player controls Kratos, a Spartan warrior in the service of the Olympian Gods. Kratos is guided by the goddess Athena, who instructs him to find the Sun God Helios, as the Dream God Morpheus has caused the remaining gods to slumber in Helios' absence. With the power of the sun, Morpheus and Persephone, the Queen of the Underworld, with the aid of the Titan Atlas, intend to destroy the Pillar of the World and in turn Olympus. God of War: Chains of Olympus is chronologically the second chapter in the series, which focuses on vengeance as its central theme.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/God-of-War-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170314T235902</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2ch-hamher.iso</path>
		<name>2ch-hamher</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T004231</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lumine-Dynarox.iso</path>
		<name>Lumine-Dynarox</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T004440</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-gama.iso</path>
		<name>psy-gama</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T004640</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-lru.iso</path>
		<name>psy-lru</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T005220</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-ff1u.iso</path>
		<name>psy-ff1u</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T060825</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-scbd.iso</path>
		<name>psy-scbd</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T061937</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pa-sacus.iso</path>
		<name>pa-sacus</name>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170318T144851</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-codrtv.cso</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Roads to Victory</name>
		<desc>Call of Duty: Roads to Victory is a 2007 World War II first-person shooter for the PlayStation Portable. It was released on March 13, 2007. It is the third portable installment of the franchise, first being on the N-Gage and the second on the Pocket PC.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-codrtv-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170320T152908</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-resr.cso</path>
		<name>Resistance: Retribution</name>
		<desc>Set in the weeks after Resistance: Fall of Man, Resistance: Retribution follows the story of former British Marine James Grayson. After a personal tragedy - he is forced to kill his own brother inside a Chimeran conversion center - Grayson goes on a vendetta to destroy every conversion center he can find. Eventually Grayson learns that his efforts have been futile... in Western Europe the Chimera have evolved a new method of converting humans to aliens. The European resistance - the Maquis - enlist Grayson's help, and he joins Cartwright and Parker in Operation Overstrike. The war to retake the European continent has begun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-resr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170320T152604</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pa-sacus.cso</path>
		<name>Secret Agent Clank</name>
		<desc>Clank's on a mission. His best buddy, Ratchet, has been framed by a ruthless enemy and jailed for a crime he did not commit. Not only that, but Ratchet's maximum security prison is full of the universe's most dangerous criminals most of whom are lining up to personally 'welcome' Ratchet into his new cell. Luckily for Ratchet he's got Clank on the outside, and luckily for Clank he's the kind of brainy little robot who is cool under pressure and knows a thing or two about tracking down a mysterious enemy. That's why, as Secret Agent Clank, he's hot on the trail of clues to unravel the mystery and secure Ratchet's release from jail. Unleash Clank's cutting edge array of weapons and gadgets, such as Cufflink Bombs, Tie-a-Rangs, Spy Sunglasses and the ever helpful Holo-Disguise Monocle. Launch into a variety of gameplay styles from all-out action to cunning stealth and brain-busting puzzle solving. Drive state-of-the-art super spy vehicles including speedboats, snowboards and sports cars. Play as Clank, Ratchet and even Captain Qwark to gather enough evidence to set Ratchet free and discover who framed the innocent Lombax.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/pa-sacus-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20080617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Impact Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCEA</publisher>
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psy-scbd.cso</path>
		<name>Soul Calibur: Broken Destiny</name>
		<desc>With Soul Calibur: Broken Destiny's huge roster of warriors, players can battle as one of many returning favorites or new fighters for some nail biting brawls. Blow away the competition using finely tuned and enhanced mechanics including Critical Finishes, Soul Crushes and Equipment Destruction. Adding depth to the combat, an all new single player mode has been developed that not only challenges a player's reflexes but also improves their fighting skills. Soul Calibur: Broken Destiny also allows gamers to engage in local wireless battles, allowing them to challenge a friend using the PSP systems ad hoc networking. Furthermore, an almost limitless character customization feature returns with even more possibilities to create a personalized fighter. Adrenaline pumping combat has never been so accessible.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/psy-scbd-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20090901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco Bandai</developer>
		<publisher>Namco Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170320T153155</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ff_type_zero-engpatched.cso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Type-0</name>
		<desc>Type-0 is part of the Fabula Nova Crystallis subseries, a set of games sharing a common mythos which includes Final Fantasy XIII and Final Fantasy XV. The gameplay is reminiscent of Crisis Core: Final Fantasy VII, with the player taking direct control of characters and taking them on missions and large-scale battles.

The game focuses on the stories of Class Zero, a group of twelve magic-endowed students from the Peristylium, a magical academy in the country of Suzaku. One day, the Milites Empire launches an assault on the other nations of Orience, seeking to control their respective crystals. When Suzaku is attacked, Class Zero are called into action and become entangled in both the efforts to push back and defeat the forces of Milites, and reveal the secret behind the war and the existence of the crystals.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/psp/ff_type_zero-engpatched-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170320T193102</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
