<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./btoads.zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<desc>After her defeat by the Galactic Corporation at the battle of Canis Major, the evil Dark Queen and her renegade space troops retreat to the outer reaches of the universe, hiding out in dark spaces between the stars. Meanwhile, on board the spaceship Vulture, Professor T. Bird and the trio of Battletoads - Rash, Zitz and Pimple - are escorting the Princess Angelica back to her home planet, where her father, the Terran Emperor, awaits her safe arrival. Along the way, Pimple, the biggest Battletoad, takes Angelica out for a cruise in the Toadster to a nearby Leisure Station. However, the Dark Queen ambushes them before they can get there, and they are kidnapped and carried away to Ragnarok's World, the Dark Queen's planet. Professor Bird sends the remaining Battletoads down on Ragnarok to save Pimple and Angelica, knowing it will be a hard battle against the planet's dangerous environments, traps and enemy forces. They have to go a long way from the planet's rough surface to deep caves and landed Gargantua and ultimately to the Tower of Shadows, where the Dark Queen herself awaits.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/btoads-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bloodbro.zip</path>
		<name>Blood Bros.</name>
		<desc>Blood Bros. is a 1990 arcade game developed and published by TAD Corporation in Japan and Europe, while it was later published in North America by Fabtek. It is a spiritual sequel to Cabal, with almost identical mechanics. A bootleg of this game is known as West Story.

In 'Blood Bros., two blood brothers, a cowboy and an Indian, team-up to hunt down "the most wanted outlaw in Dodge City," Big Bad John. The gameplay mechanics are extremely similar to TAD Corp.'s earlier machine, Cabal, however this game did not seem to appear as a trackball-controlled variant.

The player's characters are seen from behind. Some screens feature protective walls (which can get damaged and shattered by enemy fire). The players have limitless ammunition for their primary gun, but a limited number of sticks of dynamite, with which they must fend off enemy troops. An enemy gauge at the bottom of the screen depletes as foes are destroyed and certain structural features of the screen (usually the ones that collapse when destroyed, rather than simply shattering) are brought down. At the successful completion of a level by fully depleting the enemy gauge, all the remaining buildings onscreen collapse and the player progresses to the next stage, reprising the amusing "victory dance walk" into the horizon from Cabal. Boss fights, however, start from the beginning if a player dies.

Power-ups appear from time to time, being released from objects destroyed onscreen or special characters who may run across, such as the small Indian Chief figure or warthogs. Points and weaponry can also be dispensed from the tin can, if you shoot it into the air and juggle it with subsequent shots. Some power-ups give special weapons with increased firepower, others grant extra dynamite or additional points. Two players could play this game, cooperatively, simultaneously.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/bloodbro-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TAD Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>TAD Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bucky.zip</path>
		<name>Bucky O'Hare</name>
		<desc>This video game is based on the cartoon television series Bucky O'Hare and the Toad Wars under license from Hasbro, Inc. While it is generally classified as a scrolling fighting game, utilizing a Final Fight-esque landscape, the player's character is also armed with a laser gun, adding in elements of a scrolling shooter. However, if the character is extremely close to an enemy, he will throw out his fists to attack - a precursor to the characters featured in Metal Slug, who use knives in close combat.

Much like the cartoon, Bucky O'Hare features colorful animation, and voice actors from the series were hired to participate in the game's cut scenes.

The player chooses from five protagonists: Bucky O'Hare, the heroic rabbit captain of the space ship Righteous Indignation; Jenny, an "Aldebaran cat" and telepath; Dead-Eye Duck, a four-armed mallard; Willy, a kid from earth that replaced their engineer, and Blinky, a one-eyed android. As in the television series, the characters must stop the Toad Empire from invading extraterrestrial planets and enslaving their peoples; to do so they must shoot their way through an army of brainwashed toads to destroy their evil leader, a computer program known as "Komplex" and release the "Interplanetary Life Force."

The enemies, among them Al Negator, Toadborg, Total Terror Toad, a "Cyborg Spider", the various varieties of Toad Storm Troopers, the Toads' Air Marshall, and "Komplex-2-Go" who featured in the comic book and cartoon series continuities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/bucky-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gng.zip</path>
		<name>Ghosts'n Goblins</name>
		<desc>Ghosts'n Goblins is a platform game where the player controls a knight, named Sir Arthur, who must defeat zombies, ogres, demons, armored giants, dragons, and other undead creatures in order to rescue Princess Prin Prin, who has been kidnapped by Satan, King of Demon World. Along the way the player can pick up new weapons, bonuses and extra suits of armor that can help in this task.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/gng-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunforc2.zip</path>
		<name>Gun Force II</name>
		<desc>Gun Force was an obscure Contra-like game you might have seen at the arcades back in the day. It was "feed me all your quarters" hard and pretty much unplayable, but contributed one exciting new element: you could jump into war vehicules and used them against the enemy. Most of you probably didn't even know that it had a sequel. Gun Force 2 was one of the last arcade games (if not the last one) from Irem Corp., published in 1994. When looking at the screenshots, the game's similarity to Metal Slug becomes evident immediately. Yes, Metal Slug is an evolution of this game, as the staff members are actually the same. When Irem Corp. ceased activity, a group of its staff members got together and founded Nazca Corp. They revived their last idea, pumping it up and calling it Metal Slug on the Neo Geo system.

Gun Force 2 is easier and even more enjoyable than Metal Slug. You won't need a dozen quarters to finish it. It's much friendlier and more replayable, but there's less to see and find through out the whole game, as it's just not as technically complex as its modern brother.

Your character is equipped with two guns at the same time that can aim in any direction, at a slightly different angle each. Different weapons are available but only one of your guns can be upgraded, with the other one always keeping the basic shot. There aren't any bombs or grenades, though. Our hero can jump, crouch and hang from ceilings and wires, and also use one of eleven (yes, eleven) war vehicules. This is why Gun Force 2 is so cool. Engaging the enemy with bipedal walkers, jeeps, tanks, and even a Gundam-like flying suit provides such a fuzzy and trigger-happy feeling. Your objective in every level is to rescue hostages for higher scores, which was also later taken over by Metal Slug. Luckily, they are sexy half-dressed cuties instead of Robinson Crusoe's look-a-likes, but they won't leave any rewards or power-ups behind.

Plot-wise, Metal Slug and Gun Force are not related, although you fight off mutants, soldiers and aliens in both games. But technically they are almost identical, utilizing the same graphic design and color palette for backgrounds, explosions and vehicles. There's lots of metal and shrapnel flying everywhere following the extremely well animated explosions (which, interestingly enough, also causes slowdown here). The characters are less cartoonish than Metal Slug. They look more menacing and cool, except for the goofy looking hero, who looks like his arms are going to fall off from carrying those two huge guns. All of the sprites are fluidly animated, with huge mechanical bosses and mini-bosses that perform various attack sequences, with the ability to destroy parts of the background too. The music is just repetitive and bland, but what's interesting is that some of it was first used in another Irem game. They are remixed versions of stages 1, 3 and 4 of Air Duel. Some weapon samples and sound effects are exactly the same as in Metal Slug.

Gun Force 2 looks nothing like its predecessor. The graphic design, playability and animation has completely changed and it's improved in every point. An excellent last arcade jewel from Irem even if you are not a Metal Slug fan, and if you are, do yourself a favor and catch up on the game's roots. You shouldn't miss this.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/gunforc2-image.jpg</image>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunforce.zip</path>
		<name>Gunforce</name>
		<desc>GunForce: Battle Fire Engulfed Terror Island or simply titled as GunForce, is a side-scrolling action shooting game produced by Irem for the arcades in 1991. The game was later ported by Bits Studios and published by Irem to the Super Famicom exclusively in Japan in 1992.

Outside of Japan, it later received a sequel titled GunForce II, originally known in Japan as Geo Storm.


The player is armed with a gun that fires rapid-fire bullets. Each direction it shoots can be fixed toward it so the player doesn't have to hold the joystick toward it. Players may find motorcycles to speed across enemy territory faster in addition to helicopters and cable cars. After scoring over any high score, whether they win or lose, players can enter their name into the high score list after the game over screen is "achieved". A strict time limit keeps the game going at a steady pace throughout; the consequence involves losing a life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/gunforce-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mario.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Bros.</name>
		<desc>Mario Bros.  is an arcade game published and developed by Nintendo in 1983. It was developed by Shigeru Miyamoto. 

Mario Bros. features two plumbers, Mario and Luigi, having to investigate the sewers of New York after strange creatures have been appearing down there. The objective of the game is to defeat all of the enemies in each phase. The mechanics of Mario Bros. involve only running and jumping. Unlike future Mario games, players cannot jump on enemies and squash them, unless they were already turned on their back. Each phase is a series of platforms with four pipes at each corner of the screen (in the old version along with an object called a "POW" block in the center). Both sides of every phase feature a mechanism that allows the player to go off-screen to the left and appear on the right and vice versa.
The player gains points by defeating multiple enemies consecutively and can participate in a bonus round to gain more points. Enemies are defeated by kicking them over once they have been flipped on their back. This is accomplished by hitting the platform the enemy is on directly beneath them. If the player allows too much time to pass after doing this, the enemy will flip itself back over, changing in color and increasing speed. Each phase has a certain number of enemies, with the final enemy immediately changing color and increasing its speed to maximum. There are three enemies in all: the Shellcreeper, which simply walks around; the Sidestepper, which requires two hits to flip over; and the Fighter Fly, which moves by jumping and can only be flipped when it is touching a platform. Players may also make use of the above-mentioned "POW" block, which flips any enemy touching a platform or the floor when a player hits it from below. This item can be used three times before it disappears. Coins appear whenever enemies are defeated and may be collected for bonus points.
As the game progresses, elements are added to increase the difficulty. Fireballs either bounce around the screen or travel directly from one side to the other, and Slipices can freeze platforms, causing Mario and Luigi to skid. In addition, icicles start to form under the platforms and fall loose. Bonus rounds give the players a chance to score extra points by collecting coins without having to deal with enemies; the "POW" block regenerates itself on each of these screens.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mario-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830714T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mk.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<desc>The series takes place in a fictional universe that consists of six surviving realms which, according to in-game backstories, were created by the Elder Gods. The Mortal Kombat: Deception manual described the six realms as: "Earthrealm, home to such legendary heroes as Johnny Cage, Sonya Blade, Liu Kang, and Jax, and also under the protection of the Thunder God Raiden; Netherrealm, which fiery depths are inhospitable to but the most vile, a realm of demons and shadowy warriors; Outworld, a realm of constant strife and where Emperor Shao Kahn claims this realm as his own; Seido, The Realm of Order, whose inhabitants prize structure and order above all else; The Realm of Chaos, whose inhabitants do not abide by any rules whatsoever, where constant turmoil and change are worshipped here; and Edenia, which is known for its beauty, artistic expression, and longevity of its inhabitants."</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mk-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19921008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mk2.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<desc>Following his failure to defeat to Liu Kang in the first Mortal Kombat game, the evil sorcerer Shang Tsung begs his master, Shao Kahn, to spare his life. He tells Shao Kahn that the invitation for Mortal Kombat cannot be turned down, and if they hold it in Outworld, the Earthrealm warriors must attend. Kahn agrees to this plan, and even restores Tsung's youth. He then extends the invitation to Raiden, who gathers his warriors and takes them into Outworld. The new tournament is much more dangerous, as Shao Kahn has the home field advantage, and an Outworld victory will allow him to subdue Earthrealm.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mk2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mystwarr.zip</path>
		<name>Mystic Warriors: Wrath of the Ninjas</name>
		<desc>The game's controls consists of an eight-way joystick and two buttons for attacking and jumping. Like in Sunset Riders, the player can jump between higher or lower levels, as well as slide. The player character attacks primarily by shooting an unlimited supply of shurikens/daggers, or using his/her weapon at close range. The game includes some improvements that were not included in Sunset Riders, such as the ability for players to change characters after they lose a credit as well as a life gauge that allows the player to sustain up to four hits from enemy attacks before losing a life.

The player must defeat box-carrying enemies in order to obtain power-up items. These includes a shuriken power-up that can increase the player's shooting power by up to two levels (which differ between characters), food (sushi, tempura, udon, sukiyaki) that will replenish the player's life gauge, a blue orb with the kanji shinobi (忍?) that will surround the player with a barrier for a limited period, a yellow orb with the kanji chikara (力?) that will destroy all on-screen enemies, and various kinds of jewelry for extra points.

There are a total of nine stages in the game, in which its own boss awaiting to challenge the player. Like in Sunset Riders, each player will be graded at the end of stage by how much they shot the boss; the player with the highest hit percentage will receive bonus points</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mystwarr-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./popeye.zip</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<desc>The object of the game is for Popeye to collect a certain number of items dropped by Olive Oyl, depending on the level — 24 hearts, 16 musical notes, or 24 letters in the word HELP — while avoiding the Sea Hag, Brutus and other dangers. The player can make Popeye walk back and forth and up and down stairs and ladders with a 4-way joystick. There is a punch button, but unlike similar games of the period, no jump button. Conversely, Brutus can jump down a level and also jump up to hit Popeye if he is directly above.

Despite the feature of a punch button, Popeye cannot attack Brutus directly. Instead, the button is used for the following:

Punching destroys items that could hurt Popeye such as bottles, vultures and skulls.
Each level has a can of spinach; punching these cans will give Popeye invincibility and he can knock out Brutus just by running into him, although after a few seconds Brutus will swim back out and be ready for action again.
In Round 1 (the dock scene) of each three-round cycle is a punching bag, which Popeye can use to knock loose a nearby barrel from its position near the top of the playing field. If the barrel falls onto Brutus' head, the player earns bonus points (based on where Brutus was attacked) and renders Brutus harmless for several seconds.
Other licensed Popeye characters in the game are Olive Oyl, Swee'Pea, and Wimpy, though they are mostly decorative and do not add heavily to the gameplay. Wimpy appears in Round 2 (the street scene) on one end of the seesaw in the lower left corner of the field, to act as a counterweight. Swee'Pea floats high above, with bonus points to be earned if Popeye can spring off the see-saw and touch him.
Popeye loses a life if he is hit by Brutus or any thrown/flying object, or if he fails to catch a dropped item before it reaches the bottom of the screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/popeye-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rtypeleo.zip</path>
		<name>R-Type Leo</name>
		<desc>R-Type Leo is a 1992 horizontally scrolling shooter arcade game developed by Nanao and published by Irem. Only released in Japan it is the fourth game in the R-Type series.[1]</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/rtypeleo-image.jpg</image>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./robocop.zip</path>
		<name>RoboCop</name>
		<desc>RoboCop is a 1988 run and gun/beat 'em up hybrid arcade game developed and published by Data East with permission from Ocean Software. Other reworked versions appeared for home computers and video game consoles, most of them handled by Ocean, as well as a NES version ported by Sakata SAS and published by Data East. It has more recently appeared on mobile phones.

The games capture the spirit of the RoboCop film to some degree, as it involves killing generic criminals and enemy bosses, like the dangerous ED-209. Being quite popular, RoboCop was followed by several sequels (most of them handled by Ocean), including RoboCop 2, RoboCop 3, and RoboCop versus The Terminator which was developed for, but never released in arcades, and was later ported to several other consoles including the Sega Mega Drive, Super NES, Nintendo Game Boy, Sega Game Gear, and even as a final generation title for the Sega Master System in Europe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/robocop-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./robocop2.zip</path>
		<name>RoboCop 2</name>
		<desc>Based upon the movie sequel of the same name. You play RoboCop whose mission is to find and destroy cyborg drug dealer Cain, the corrupt RoboCop-II while following your directives to serve the public trust, protect the innocent and uphold the law.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/robocop2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ssriders.zip</path>
		<name>Sunset Riders</name>
		<desc>You're a brave bounty hunter pursuing outlaw scum like Simon Greedwell, Paco Loco, and Chief Scalpen. Each bad guy has a big reward on his head. And they're helped by hordes of bandits, gunslingers and horse thieves, so pack loads of lead. Track those rotten skunks through an Indian village, on a steaming locomotive, and down the mean streets of lawless Reechforem Gulch. Occasionally, dynamite is at your disposal, as well as weapon power-ups. But cattle stampedes and sneaky traps could end your adventure in a cloud of dust. Oh, and be sure to carry ointment for your saddle sores because you'll ride horseback in a galloping bonus stage filled with handy items. Ultimately, you must make villainous Sir Richard Rose eat sagebrush. Do so and you'll have lots of money and the townsfolk kissing your boots.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/ssriders-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tmnt.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<desc>Yo! After being treated like garbage by the Ninja Turtles, Shredder has trained a new, more merciless breed of Foot Soldiers to inflict his revenge: A clan of over 700 Taekwondo turtle terminators who have once again captured April O'Neil to use as turtle bait. Fortunately you don't have to face these freaks of torture alone. For the first time ever, two dudes or dudettes can join forces and double-team Shredder, kicking shell while covering each others tails. But to survive you've gotta fight through 8 action-packed arcade levels, including Vinnie's Valet "Stalking" Lot and the Soho Sewer System, plus two new never-before-seen shell-squashing stages! Each of these deathtraps is reinforced by lethal electro zappers, laser beams, freezer burners or enemies such as Scorpion Robots, Stone Warriors and Baxter Stockman. Shredder has also hired the all-powerful Tora and Shogun, two alien bounty hunters who have never known defeat. Even though Master Splinter has prepared the turtles well for battle, teaching them radical new attack moves, it doesn't mean this war to save April and turtlekind will be a piece of cake or even a slice of pizza. Because with the forces of revenge on his side and the bounty boys in town, it's payback time for Shredder!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/tmnt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tmnt2.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Turtles In Time</name>
		<desc>Sunday evening. You're sitting around the sewer watching your main reported, April O'Neil do a live remote from the Statue of Liberty. Then it happens. A humungoso flying android screams out of the sky and rips Lady Liberty from her foundation, sending hundreds of freaked out tourists into the harbor below. "No way!" cries Raphael. "Way," replies Donatello. And the crazy quantum chase is on! Journey through multiple levels of enormous graphics, the largest and craziest talking Turtles ever with eons of bodacious battlegrounds, from prehistoric to futuristic galaxies. Get ready for the 3-D jab and toss that sends enemies flying right in your face. Mondo body slams and pizza power bonuses make you more Turtle than ever before. You better believe you're going to need it. Shredder's out for Turtle hide. And he's got all the time in the world to get it.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/tmnt2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./simpsons.zip</path>
		<name>The Simpsons</name>
		<desc>A jewel heist gone wrong sees Mr Burns's sidekick, Smithers, kidnapping Maggie and making his escape. Between one and four players take on the role of either Homer, Marge, Lisa, or Bart in this colorful, horizontally-scrolling beat-em-up from Konami. Each Simpsons character possesses an attacking move specific to them; Marge is armed with a vacuum cleaner, Lisa has a skipping rope, Bart has his skateboard, and Homer fights with his fists. The players must battle their way through a variety of Simpsons-themed levels - such as Springfield and Krustyland - fighting goons, thugs, zombies, drunks, firemen, and several Simpsons regulars. Many Simpsons characters that don't appear as enemies have 'cameo' scenes in the game (Otto working at a burgerstand in Krustyland, for example). The archetypal 'boss' character awaits the players at the end of every stage. The game ends with a final showdown with the evil Mr. Burns in his luxurious mansion.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/simpsons-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./toki.zip</path>
		<name>Toki</name>
		<desc>Toki, known in Japan as JuJu Densetsu is a 1989 shoot 'em up platformer arcade game, or a "run and gun" developed and published in Japan by TAD Corporation and published in North America by Fabtek. It features elements of tongue-in-cheek humor combined with the action. The player takes control of an enchanted ape who must battle hordes of jungle monsters with energy balls from his mouth (described humorously as "monkey-spit" or "monkey-vomit" by some gamers). The ultimate goal is to destroy the evil wizard who cast a spell on you; therefore transforming yourself from an ape back into a human, and rescuing the kidnapped princess. The game was ported to several video game consoles and home computers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/toki-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./moo.zip</path>
		<name>Wild West C.O.W.-Boys of Moo Mesa</name>
		<desc>In the 1800's, a mysterious comet hits the U.S. southwest, transforming the local cattle and animals into their own version of the old west called Moo Mesa, complete with several lawmen dealing with bizarre outlaws.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/moo-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19921119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./xmen.zip</path>
		<name>X-Men</name>
		<desc>In X-Men Arcade, Cyclops, Colossus, Dazzler, Nightcrawler, Storm and Wolverine unite to use their special powers to save mankind from the Brotherhood of Evil Mutants and other terrible threats. Players are charged with fighting off hundreds of Sentinels - along with Super Villains such as Pyro, the Blob, Wendigo, Nimrod, the White Queen, Juggernaut and Mystique - as they battle their way to Island M to take down the Master of Magnetism, Magneto, and save Kitty Pryde and Professor Xavier.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/xmen-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kinst.zip</path>
		<name>Killer Instinct</name>
		<desc>Killer Instinct is a fighting game developed by Rare and published by Midway and Nintendo. It was released as an arcade game in 1994. The game's plot involves an all-powerful corporation called Ultratech organizing a fighting tournament. The story was adapted in a limited comic book series published under the short-lived Acclaim Comics imprint.
Killer Instinct features several gameplay elements unique to fighting games of the time. Instead of fighting enemies in best-of-three rounds bouts, each player has two life bars. The player that depletes the other player's life bars first wins the match. The game also introduced "auto-seconds", which allows players to press a certain sequence of buttons to make characters automatically perform combos on opponents. Also featured in the game are "combo breakers"; special moves that can interrupt combos.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/kinst-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19941128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Rareware Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170315T225625</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aerofgt.zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters 2</name>
		<desc>The game is played with two buttons, with the A button firing bullets from the plane and the B button launching a special bomb attack which uses a bomb from a limited stock of bombs. Power bullets can be obtained by destroying buildings and armored enemy planes. There are 2 types of Power bullets: "P" Power bullets, that increases the plane's firepower by one level, and "F" Power bullets, that increases the plane's firepower to the maximum level instantly. The maximum level only lasts for a limited amount of shots.

When certain ground enemies and buildings are destroyed, money bonuses appear which give a random amount of points each. When the player reaches the end of the stage, the player has to face a boss ship.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/aerofgt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./baddudes.zip</path>
		<name>Bad Dudes Vs. DragonNinja</name>
		<desc>The game starts in New York City, where President Ronnie has been kidnapped by the nefarious DragonNinja. The game's intro begins with the following introduction: "Rampant ninja related crimes these days... Whitehouse is not the exception...". As soon as that occurs, a Secret Service agent asks two street-smart brawlers, named Blade and Striker: "President Ronnie has been kidnapped by the ninjas. Are you a bad enough dude to rescue Ronnie?". 

After hearing that, the Bad Dudes pursue the DragonNinja through the city streets, highway, sewers, transport train, forest, cave and into the secret ninja base in order to save President Ronnie.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/baddudes-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19880801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./brvblade.zip</path>
		<name>Brave Blade</name>
		<desc>An extremely cool vertical shooter from 8ing/Raizing.
8ing/Raizing, the Brave Blade maker, released 12 different machines in our database under this trade name, starting in 1993.

Other machines made by 8ing/Raizing during the time period Brave Blade was produced include Magic Great Battle, Dimahoo, Great Mahou Daisakusen, Bloody Roar 2, Armed Police Batrider, Bloody Roar, Beastorizer, and Shippuu Mahou Daisakusen Kingdom-Grandprix.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/brvblade-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>8ing</developer>
		<publisher>Raizing</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cabal.zip</path>
		<name>Cabal</name>
		<desc>Cabal offers one player and two-player-simultaneous modes of gameplay. Each player assumes the role of an unnamed commando trying to destroy several enemy military bases. There are 5 stages with 4 screens each. The player starts with a stock of three lives and uses a gun with limitless ammunition and a fixed number of grenades to fend off enemy troops and attack the base. The commando is seen from behind and initially starts behind a protective wall which can be damaged and shattered by enemy fire. To stay alive, the player needs to avoid enemy bullets by running left or right, hiding behind cover, or using a dodge-roll. An enemy gauge at the bottom of the screen depletes as foes are destroyed and certain structures (which collapse rather than shatter) are brought down. When the enemy gauge is emptied, the level is successful completed, all of the remaining buildings on screen collapse, and the player progresses to the next stage. If a player is killed, he is immediately revived at the cost of one life or game overs if he has no lives remaining. Boss fights, however, restart from the beginning if the only remaining player dies.

From time to time, power-ups are released from objects destroyed on screen. Some power-ups give special weapons such as an extremely fast-firing machine gun or an automatic shotgun with a lower firing rate and larger area of effect. Others grant extra grenades or additional points.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/cabal-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TAD Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Fabtek</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cninja.zip</path>
		<name>Caveman Ninja</name>
		<desc>Players control Joe and Mac, two cavemen who fight against enemy cavemen and dinosaurs using projectile weapons. The object of the game is to help Joe and Mac rescue their "Cave Babes" from huge dinosaurs on six different stages.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/cninja-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./circusc.zip</path>
		<name>Circus Charlie</name>
		<desc>In the game there are six regular stages (plus an extra stage) of differing tasks that are to be completed by Charlie. Grabbing money bags, performing dangerous tricks, avoiding enemies, completing stages, etc., earns Charlie points. After the sixth stage is completed, the game starts over again but with a faster pace and more difficult (but exactly the same in terms of task to be completed) levels.
Charlie also races against time. Bonus points are awarded according to the time remaining, but running out of time will cost the player a life.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/circusc-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Centuri</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./contra.zip</path>
		<name>Contra</name>
		<desc>In Contra, the player controls one of two armed military commandos named Bill and Lance, who are sent on a mission to neutralize a terrorist group called the Red Falcon Organization that is planning to take over the Earth.

The main character is equipped with a rifle with an unlimited amount of ammunition. The player can also jump, move and fire in eight directions, as well as move or jump simultaneously while firing. A single hit from any enemy, bullet, or other hazard will instantly kill the player character and discard the current weapon.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/contra-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./cosmccop.zip</path>
		<name>Cosmic Cop</name>
		<desc>Cosmic Cop (also known as Armored Police Unit Gallop).  Gallop is one of Irem's most unpopular shooters, and many haven't even heard of it. The game can easily be compared to R-Type 2 - it has smooth animation, a similar style of graphics, crazy huge bosses and that "look how many times I can kill you before you learn the pattern"-attitude. The first time you see it, and if you like old school shooters, you will be thinking "How the hell is it possible to have missed a game like this? Awesome graphics, big sprites, lots of frames, post-apocalyptic scenery... It needs to be played now!"

The Armed Police Unit Gallop is out on the streets chasing and taking down "mad cars", dangerous war vehicles that are terrorizing the city. Your job as representative of the law is to engage them in your armored police ship. There's really nothing new with the gameplay. In addition to your standard weapon, you get a side weapon that shoots together with your main one, which can be a ground bomb, a straight shooting missile, or a ground-based torpedo. You won't get a bomb that kills everything on the screen, but instead a homing laser that locks to the nearest unlucky vessel and does some nice drilling damage on its armor. This laser will run out when the gauge at the bottom of the screen is depleted, and has two levels to upgrade to for more power.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/cosmccop-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./demonwld.zip</path>
		<name>Demon's World</name>
		<desc>Demon's World, released in Japan as "Horror Story", is a platformer arcade game that was developed by Toaplan and published by Taito in 1989. This game is multi-regional, meaning that it can be configured for different regions via the DIP switches. These settings change the legal warnings, can display the Taito licensing message and can change the title between the English version (Demon's World) and the Japanese version (Horror Story).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/demonwld-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>Toaplan</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkong.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong is an arcade game released by Nintendo in 1981. It is an early example of the platform game genre, as the gameplay focuses on maneuvering the main character across a series of platforms while dodging and jumping over obstacles. In the game, Jumpman (since renamed Mario) must rescue a damsel in distress, Lady (now named Pauline) from a giant ape named Donkey Kong. The hero and ape later became two of Nintendo's most popular characters.
The game was the latest in a series of efforts by Nintendo to break into the North American market. Hiroshi Yamauchi, Nintendo's president at the time, assigned the project to a first-time game designer named Shigeru Miyamoto. Drawing from a wide range of inspirations, including Popeye, Beauty and the Beast and King Kong, Miyamoto developed the scenario and designed the game alongside Nintendo's chief engineer, Gunpei Yokoi. The two men broke new ground by using graphics as a means of characterization, including cut scenes to advance the game's plot, and integrating multiple stages into the gameplay.
Despite initial misgivings on the part of Nintendo's American staff, Donkey Kong proved a success in North America and Japan. Nintendo licensed the game to Coleco, who developed home console versions for numerous platforms. Other companies cloned Nintendo's hit and avoided royalties altogether. Miyamoto's characters appeared on cereal boxes, television cartoons, and dozens of other places. A lawsuit brought on by Universal City Studios, alleging Donkey Kong violated their trademark of King Kong, ultimately failed. The success of Donkey Kong and Nintendo's win in the courtroom helped position the company to dominate the video game market from its release in 1981, until the mid 1990s.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/dkong-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19810709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkong3.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 3</name>
		<desc>Stanley is a bugman. Donkey Kong has taken refuge in his greenhouse and it is now up to Stanley to stop the ape from stirring up any more insects that will soon destroy his flowers. Stanley saves the flowers by spraying bug spray on Donkey Kong.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/dkong3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19831005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./dkongjr.zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Junior must save his father from Mario by putting the key or keys in the stage into all of the locks. Mario attempts to stop Donkey Kong Junior by releasing the many animals he controls to knock Donkey Kong Junior off the vines and platforms. Donkey Kong Junior defeats Mario if the player completes the fourth stage by putting all six keys in their locks, making the floor disappear. Donkey Kong Junior catches Donkey Kong while Mario falls onto the ground.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/dkongjr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19820810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./elvactr.zip</path>
		<name>Elevator Action Returns</name>
		<desc>Elevator Action Returns, released as Elevator Action II in North America, is a side-scrolling action game by Taito originally released for the arcades in 1994 as a sequel to the 1983 arcade game Elevator Action</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/elvactr-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./goldnaxe.zip</path>
		<name>Golden Axe</name>
		<desc>An evil entity known as Death Adder has captured the King and his daughter, and holds them captive in their castle. He also finds the Golden Axe, the magical emblem of Yuria, and threatens to destroy both the axe and the royal family unless the people of Yuria accept him as their ruler. Three Warriors set out on a quest to rescue Yuria and avenge their losses at the hands of Death Adder. The first is a battle axe-wielding dwarf, Gilius Thunderhead, from the mines of Wolud, whose twin brother was killed by the soldiers of Death Adder. Another is a male barbarian, Ax Battler, wielding a two handed broadsword looking for revenge for the murder of his mother. The last is a long-sword-wielding Tyris Flare, an amazon, whose parents were both killed by Death Adder.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/goldnaxe-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./gunsmoke.zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<desc>Gun.Smoke is very similar to Commando, another Capcom game, but with several differences. Whereas Commando is a run and gun game, this game is a scrolling shooter in which the screen scrolls upward automatically and players only have three ways to shoot, using three buttons for left, right, and center shooting. However, a player can also change the way the gunman shoots through button combinations. A player can still die by getting shot or struck by enemies like in Commando but improve protection by getting special items, including a horse, for protection up to three hits; boots, for speed of movement; bullets, for faster shots; and rifles, for shot length. These items are found by shooting barrels and rifles, boots, and bullets can stock up to five.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/gunsmoke-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19851101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hharry.zip</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Harry</name>
		<desc>Hammerin' Harry, or Daiku no Gen-san ("Gen the Carpenter"), is a side-scrolling platformer and the first game in Irem's Hammerin' Harry/Daiku no Gen-san series. 

Harry/Gen takes on the Rusty Nail Construction Company after it destroys his home as part of their construction work. Harry's main weapon is an enormous mallet that he uses both for offense and defense: he can hold it out in front and above to shield himself from projectiles. Harry/Gen can also find power-ups to give himself more health or temporarily strengthen his hammer. 

The game was originally released in the arcade before being ported to the NES and Famicom later the same year. This port was only available in Japan and Europe.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/hharry-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hook.zip</path>
		<name>Hook</name>
		<desc>Hook is a side-scrolling, weapon based beat'em up, based on the movie with the same title. Up to four players control Peter Pan or one from the Lost Boys: Ace, Pockets, Thudbutt or Rufio, fighting against Captain Hook and his pirates. Gameplay is similar to other games, like Golden Axe - the heroes go to the right, and kill enemies with their weapons and magic.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/hook-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./horizon.zip</path>
		<name>Horizon</name>
		<desc>A horizontal side scrolling shooting game with 3 swim lanes to create different depth to play.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/horizon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./inthunt.zip</path>
		<name>In the Hunt</name>
		<desc>In the Hunt is a horizontal scrolling shooter arcade game by Irem. It was released in 1993 and later ported to the Sega Saturn, the PlayStation and Windows 95 for the PC by Kokopeli.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/inthunt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./liquidk.zip</path>
		<name>Liquid Kids</name>
		<desc>Liquid Kids is a single player platform game that features Hipopo, a platypus (referred to as a hippo) who must fight his way through a large number of enemy-packed levels in search of his missing girlfriend - rescuing other platypuses along the way. Hipopo is armed with water bombs which can be thrown at enemies to soak and damage them. Once soaked, the enemies can then be kicked and destroyed completely. Enemies left unkicked however will dry out and recover after a short period of time.

The level design presents moving platforms, collapsible floors, boats and water-wheels all making an appearance. Small plants also appear on certain levels which can be "watered", causing them to grow and creating new platforms. Appropriately enough for a game which features water as the main weapon, many of the enemies and the later levels have a fire thematic. He can also collect cakes and other items to gain more points.

Hipopo makes a cameo appearance in Arkanoid vs. Space Invaders (2017).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/liquidk-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mgcrystl.zip</path>
		<name>Magical Crystals</name>
		<desc>A cute top-down action game where you control a wizard that must rescue fairies who are trapped inside of crystals.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mgcrystl-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaneko</developer>
		<publisher>Kaneko</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mappy.zip</path>
		<name>Mappy</name>
		<desc>The player guides Mappy the police mouse through the mansion of the cats called Mewkies (Meowky in the U.S. version) to retrieve stolen goods. The player uses a left-right joystick to move Mappy and a single button to operate doors. The mansion has six floors of hallways in which the stolen items are stashed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mappy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bally Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mpatrol.zip</path>
		<name>Moon Patrol</name>
		<desc>Moon Patrol is an arcade game originally released in 1982 by Irem and later licensed for release in North America by Williams (Midway). It is a side-scrolling shooter that puts players at the controls of a six-wheeled moon rover that can jump and shoot. The goal is to move through the entire course as quickly as possible while shooting enemies for additional points. Cannons are mounted on the front and top of the vehicle, and both fire simultaneously when the fire button is pressed. Rocks, mines, and pits in the course prevent you from just holding to the right for maximum speed. Rocks and mines can be shot, but pits must be jumped. Some enemies fire shots that create new pits in the course, forcing players to react quickly.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mpatrol-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./mk3.zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 3</name>
		<desc>Weary of continuous losses in tournament battle, Shao Kahn, who lost to Liu Kang in the Outworld tournament in the previous game, enacts a 10,000-year-old plan. He would have his Shadow Priests, led by Shang Tsung, revive his former Queen Sindel, who unexpectedly died at a young age. However, she would not be revived in the Outworld, but in Earthrealm. This would allow Shao Kahn to cross the boundary lines and reclaim his queen. When Sindel is reincarnated in Earthrealm, Shao Kahn reaches across the dimensions to reclaim her, and as a result, Earthrealm gradually becomes a part of Outworld, instantly stripping billions of their souls. Only a few are spared, as Raiden protects their souls. He tells them that Shao Kahn must be stopped, but he cannot interfere; due to his status, he has no power in Outworld, and Earthrealm is partially merged with Outworld. Shao Kahn has unleashed extermination squads to kill any Earthrealm survivors. Also, Raiden's protection only extends to the soul, not to the body, so his chosen warriors have to fight the extermination squads and repel Shao Kahn. With his final defeat, every human on Earthrealm is restored.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/mk3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway Games</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./nbbatman.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Baseball Bat Man</name>
		<desc>Some of the most prized treasures from the Baseball Hall of Fame have been stolen, and the Commissioner of Baseball needs YOU to get them back! But is there more to this quest than meets the eye? Who is really behind the theft?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/nbbatman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19930917T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./punchout.zip</path>
		<name>Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>Isn't it time you got in on the action?

Once again, Nintendo has created a smash hit —Punch-Out— a fast action dual-monitor video boxing game. Its been knocking out the competition week-after-week in earnings and player appeal across the nation.

With Punch-Out in your corner, you gain the added muscle of the
Champ!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/punchout-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rambo3a.zip</path>
		<name>Rambo III</name>
		<desc>Rambo 3 (Rambo III) was released by Taito in 1989.  Rambo 3 was a rail shooter game that featured Rambo and Colonel Trautman as playable characters.  It was based on the Sylvester Stallone movie of the same name, whereby Rambo went about the business of rescuing Colonel Trautman, who had been taken hostage in Afghanistan while helping defend the Mujahedeen from the Soviet invasion.  From a third-person perspective, Rambo would have to blast through contingents of enemy soldiers using various weapons with crosshairs, as well as fight tank bosses at the end of each level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/rambo3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./shinobi.zip</path>
		<name>Shinobi</name>
		<desc>Shinobi is a side-scrolling action game produced by Sega originally released for the arcades in 1987. In Shinobi, the player controls a modern day ninja named Joe Musashi who goes on a mission to rescue his kidnapped students from a group of terrorists. Shinobi was later adapted by Sega to their Master System game console, followed by conversions to other platforms such as the Nintendo Entertainment System, PC Engine, and various home computers, as well as downloadable emulated versions of the original arcade game for the Wii and Xbox 360. The success of Shinobi inspired the development of various sequels and spin-offs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/shinobi-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./scontra.zip</path>
		<name>Super Contra</name>
		<desc>Super Contra is a run and gun video game released by Konami in 1988. It is the sequel to the original Contra. 

A year after the battle with the Red Falcon Organization, Bill and Lance are sent on another mission. This time, the alien forces have taken over an allied military base, possessing most of its troops. Bill and Lance must not only fight against their former comrades-in-arms, but also a new mutated form of the same alien creatures they fought during their previous mission.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/scontra-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19880108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./spnchout.zip</path>
		<name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
		<desc>This is a boxing game where you attempt to defeat five different champions, Bear Hugger, Dragon Chan, Vodka Drunkenski, Great Tiger and Super Macho Man. If you defeat all five, you become the champion and defend your title against the same five characters.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/spnchout-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./edrandy.zip</path>
		<name>The Cliffhanger - Edward Randy</name>
		<desc>A fast moving platform game in which the player controls the Indiana Jones-esque and unfortunately named 'Edward Randy'. The levels are an inventive mix of standard platform action and 3-D scrolling levels; the latter usually having the player driving a jeep and repelling the enemy attacks. The game is based on the archetypal Hollywood action blockbuster and features a filmic score to back up the on-screen action. The player's only weapon is a whip - another nod to the Indiana Jones character - which can be used to both attack enemies and as a 'rope', to enable the player to reach distant platforms.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/edrandy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./umk3.zip</path>
		<name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3</name>
		<desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 is a fighting video game in the Mortal Kombat series, developed and released by Midway to arcades in 1995. It is an update of 1995's earlier Mortal Kombat 3 with an altered gameplay system, additional characters like the returning favorites Kitana and Scorpion who were missing from Mortal Kombat 3, and some new features.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/umk3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./wb3.zip</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair</name>
		<desc>Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair is a side-scrolling action game developed by Westone Bit Entertainment that was originally released for the arcades by Sega in 1988. It is the third game in the Wonder Boy series and the last one released for the arcade. A console adaption was made by Hudson Soft, released in 1989 in Japan for the PC Engine CD and the subsequent North American release on the TurboGrafx-CD dropped the 'Wonder Boy III' title. It was also converted and released by Sega for the Mega Drive in Japan and Europe in 1991. Both the TurboGrafx-CD and Mega Drive versions have been re-released for the Wii Virtual Console.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/wb3-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19881116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./primrage.zip</path>
		<name>Primal Rage</name>
		<desc>Primal Rage is a one-on-one fighting game featuring dinosaurs and giant apes as the fighters. The graphics are done with digitized stop-motion animation. Gameplay is similar to Mortal Kombat in that it is viewed from a side perspective, and features deadly finishing moves at the end of the match.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/primrage-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Time Warner</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./yiear.zip</path>
		<name>Yie Ar Kung-Fu</name>
		<desc>In Yie Ar Kung-Fu, a fighter named Oolong must defeat a variety of martial arts masters unarmed to win the title of "Grand Master" and honor the memory of his father, who was killed while fighting the current champion.

Each opponent has a unique appearance and fighting style. Some rivals are also armed, with weapons including nunchaku, throwing stars and a club. Combinations of buttons and joystick movements enable the player to perform different types of attacks in jumping, crouching and standing positions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/yiear-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./slyspy.zip</path>
		<name>Sly Spy</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/slyspy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./splatter.zip</path>
		<name>Splatterhouse</name>
		<desc>The place was called the West Mansion; but, to all those who had known the legend, it was known as "Splatterhouse". It was once the home of the famed parapsychologist, Doctor West - and there was a research laboratory in the house (where he had conducted some of his most gruesome experiments). It was even said that it was in this house that he created the most hideous creatures that ever walked the face of the Earth, but no-one knew for sure; he had not been seen or heard from in years, and no-one who had ever gone into the mansion had survived to tell the tale. Rick and his girlfriend, Jennifer, were parapsychology majors at their local university - and they were both very interested in the works of Dr. West, as he was the most famous parapsychologist in the world.

One day, they decided to visit the abandoned mansion, as part of a project they were working on in school; as they walked towards that mansion, it started to rain. They entered - all went dark. Lightning cracked through the sky; there was a frantic scuffle. Then a scream - and suddenly Jennifer had gone. Rick's unconscious body was covered with blood; hours later, he awoke to a fantastic horror. He was alone, and also drenched with blood, but the most terrifying thing of all was that a hideous mask was covering his face - he had read tales of this mask (known as the "Terror Mask"), in Dr. West's writings. It was said to possess ancient spiritual powers; as his only hope, Rick must now depend on this mask, to grant him the strength and courage to find Jennifer. He has a total of seven stages to clear - and each one is gorier than the last.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/splatter-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rambo3.zip</path>
		<name>Rambo III</name>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tps.zip</path>
		<name>TPS</name>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<hidden>true</hidden>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rthunder.zip</path>
		<name>Rolling Thunder</name>
		<desc>Rolling Thunder is a side-scrolling action game produced by Namco originally released in as a coin-operated arcade game which ran on the Namco System 86 hardware. Rolling Thunder was released for various computer platforms in 1987 and the Nintendo Entertainment System in 1989. The original arcade game has been included in various classic game compilations.

The player takes control of "Albatross", a member of the WCPO's (World Crime Police Organization) "Rolling Thunder" espionage unit. Albatross's mission is to save a missing agent named Leila Blitz from a secret society named Geldra located in New York City. Albatross must travel through two different segments or "stories", both comprised of five stages, for a total of ten game stages. On each stage, Albatross can enter doors, to hide and take cover from enemies, as well jump over to higher or lower floors with rails, including stairs. Albatross begins this game armed with a standard-issue pistol, which can be substituted with a fully automatic assault rifle that allows for continuous firing by holding down the firing button. Albatross can gain ammunition for either weapon, by entering doors which are marked "bullets" or "arms". Despite the presence of a life meter, Albatross can only take two physical hits from the enemy: a single hit drains half of the meter, and he will be killed instantly when struck by a projectile attack such as enemy bullets or lasers. (However, all bullets can be blocked by your own).</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/rthunder-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./smashtv.zip</path>
		<name>Smash TV</name>
		<desc>Smash TV is a 1990 arcade game created by Eugene Jarvis and Mark Turmell for Williams. Home versions were developed for various platforms and most were published by Acclaim Entertainment.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/smashtv-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Williams</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bonkadv.zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's adventure</name>
		<desc>Bonk's Adventure is a 2D platform video game developed by Red Company and Atlus that was released in 1989 in Japan and 1990 in North America for the TurboGrafx-16. In Japan it was released as PC Genjin (PC原人?) in 1989, a play on the Japanese name for the system, 'PC Engine'. The game was re-released for the TurboGrafx-16 in the U.S. in 1992 on the Gate of Thunder 4-in-1 game CD-ROM. The game was later ported to the NES, Game Boy, Amiga, arcade systems under different titles (FC Genjin, GB Genjin and BC Genjin). It is also available through Nintendo's Virtual Console service, on the PlayStation Store and there is a version for mobile phones in Japan.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/bonkadv-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19891102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Kaneko</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./charlien.zip</path>
		<name>Charlie Ninja</name>
		<desc>You control a cartoonish ninja-type character who must attempt to shoot all the enemies and defeat the boss at the end of each stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/charlien-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Mitchell Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./osman.zip</path>
		<name>Osman</name>
		<desc>It is the late 21st century, and the world has come under the control of a single federal government. One day a new threat known as Abdullah the Slaver appears, causing widespread terror and panic. The fear in men's hearts incites the abandonment of all economic activity. The federal government, which is the foundation of capitalism and modern civilization, has become nothing less than an insidious idea that corrupts the foundations of society itself. It destroys the idiosyncrasies and variations among national viewpoints, stifling them in the name of "freedom" and its own internal ideals.

Judicial Affairs Director Jack Layzon alone grasps the situation, fearing the worst. He summons the lone assassin who had mastered the 'secret style'...</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/osman-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19960501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./nslashers.zip</path>
		<name>Night Slashers</name>
		<desc>The dead have risen from their graves, and monsters and mutants prey upon what's left of the living. Three monster hunters have joined together, using their knowledge of the occult to slay the undead scourge.

During the course of the game, players fight through hordes of attacking zombies and mutants, as well as other enemies such as werewolves and elementals. Bosses also include monsters such as a mummy, a golem and a mad scientist. Players fight these enemies and bosses to stop the evil plans of King Zarutz from turning our planet into a worldwide kingdom for the dead.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/nslashers-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./aliensyn.zip</path>
		<name>Alien Syndrome</name>
		<desc>Two players control two soldiers named Ricky and Mary, who must fight their way through large eight-way scrolling levels rescuing their comrades who are being held by aliens. After they have rescued a certain number of hostages the exit opens and they can pass through it in order to fight the end-of-level guardian. If this monstrosity is defeated, they move onto the next stage. As well as two player simultaneous gameplay, Alien Syndrome features pick-ups which assist the player including better weapons and maps of the current level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/aliensyn-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./captaven.zip</path>
		<name>Captain America and the Avengers</name>
		<desc>Captain America and the Avengers is an arcade game released by Data East in 1991. It features the Marvel Comics characters The Avengers in a side-scrolling brawling and shooting adventure to defeat the evil Red Skull.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/captaven-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bayroute.zip</path>
		<name>Bay Route</name>
		<desc>Bay Route is a platform "Run and gun" arcade game developed by Sunsoft and published by Sega in 1989. Players control a soldier and shoot terrorists, collect power-ups, and defeat bosses to advance levels. Players can select one of four configurations on their gun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/bayroute-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./boomrang.zip</path>
		<name>Boomer Rang'r</name>
		<desc>A caveman runs around tossing his boomerang at enemy cavemen and prehistoric creatures. Pick up potions to spell out BOOMER RANG'R to move to next level. For even more fun, kill a dinosaur rider and mount his dinosaur!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/boomrang-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./calibr50.zip</path>
		<name>Caliber .50</name>
		<desc>Caliber .50 is a 1989 scrolling shooter arcade game developed by SETA Corporation.
Players control a United States Air Force pilot who was taken as a prisoner of war in Vietnam in 1972. The pilot must escape the prison compound by battling enemy soldiers with guns and grenades. Various power-ups are available that give the player use of various other weapons including a machine gun and flamethrower. Enemy vehicles such as a plane can also be commandeered.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/calibr50-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seta</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./deadconx.zip</path>
		<name>Dead Connection</name>
		<desc>Dead Connection is an arcade game released by Taito in 1992. The game takes place on September 5, 1953 "in a big city somewhere".

It features a group of detectives who set out to fight a crime family. The game has a strong Film noir vibe, shown through the appearance of the detectives and the featuring of a female protagonist. Each stage is preceded by a short cinematic interlude that explains the transition between the game's different locales.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/deadconx-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./elevator.zip</path>
		<name>Elevator Action</name>
		<desc>The player assumes the role of a spy who infiltrates a building filled with elevators. He must collect secret documents from the building and traverse the 30 levels of the building using an increasingly complex series of elevators. The player is pursued by enemy agents who appear from behind closed doors. The player must outwit them via force or evasion. Successful completion of a level involves collecting all the secret documents and traversing the building from top to bottom. In the lower floors of the building, the elevator systems are so complex that some puzzle-solving skills are needed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/elevator-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./fastlane.zip</path>
		<name>Fast Lane</name>
		<desc>In this driving/maze game, you control a vehicle who must drive through the entire maze to progress. There is another vehicle who tries to stop you so to aid your progress, you must drive through the beach ladies in order to gain power-ups which you can use on the other vehicle.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/fastlane-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ironhors.zip</path>
		<name>Iron Horse</name>
		<desc>Side scrolling platform cowboy train-robber game. Select between fists, pistols or a whip and then work your way down the steam train killing the bad guys and collecting money and special weapons. Cowboy music score.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/ironhors-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./junglek.zip</path>
		<name>Jungle King</name>
		<desc>The player controls a Tarzan-like jungle man who must swing across vines in the forest, swim through a crocodile-infested river, jump and duck rocks while climbing a hill and rescue his woman from a pair of barbaric cannibals.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/junglek-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kikikai.zip</path>
		<name>KiKi KaiKai</name>
		<desc>KiKi KaiKai is an overhead multi-directional shooter game that requires the player to move in four directions through various levels while attacking harmful enemies as they approach from off screen. As Sayo-chan, the player can attack by either throwing her special o-fuda scrolls in eight separate directions, or by swinging her purification rod directly in front of her. These techniques can be upgraded by finding special paper slips left by defeated enemies that will either enhance their power or improve their range. Sayo can be damaged by coming in contact with an enemy, and can only be hit once before she is knocked out and must resume the level from a preset continuation point. At the end of each level, the player must face a powerful boss monster that takes several attacks to defeat and is more difficult than normal enemies.

Several hidden items can be found by attacking objects with Sayo's purification rod, and can be used to either enhance her attack or grant the player points. Once a certain number of points are gained, the player will gain another life and have an additional chance to complete a level. When all of the player's lives are exhausted, a "number match" screen appears with a random 3-digit number in 50-base increments (100, 150, 200, 250, and so on). If the last three digits of the player's total score match the number displayed, they are granted a free game; if not, the game ends.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/kikikai-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19861001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kurikint.zip</path>
		<name>Kuri Kinton</name>
		<desc>El jugador controla a un policía chino que ha recibido la misión de infiltrarse en una base subterránea para rescatar a un oficial de policía de alto rango y a su hija, los cuales han sido secuestrados por una banda.1 El juego consiste en dar patadas y puñetazos a numerosos enemigos,2 pudiendo usar también barridos y patadas voladoras.1 El juego comienza en un corredor subterráneo poblado por soldados con armadura y luchadores que lanzan shurikens.3 El jugador debe seguir la flecha que indica hacia dónde hay que avanzar según se va adentrando en las cavernas y encuentra un mayor número de enemigos.3 Un jefe experto en artes marciales guarda el final de cada nivel y puede eliminar rápidamente al personaje jugador si no se lucha con cuidado.2

El jugador tiene una única vida en el juego, representada por una barra de salud que se reduce según se reciben ataques de los enemigos en el personaje-jugador.2 Si la barra se vacía por completo, el juego termina y un querubín dorado se eleva desde el cuerpo del personaje. Si el jugador continúa la partida, el querubín desciende de nuevo y vuelve a entrar en el cuerpo del personaje, que se pondrá de un salto en pie.3</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/kurikint-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19881001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./valkyrie.zip</path>
		<name>Legend Of Valkyrie</name>
		<desc>Legend of Valkyrie is an Action game, developed and published by Namco, which was released in Japan in 1989.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/valkyrie-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19891220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./madgear.zip</path>
		<name>Mad Gear</name>
		<desc>LED Storm, known as Mad Gear in Japan, is an arcade game released in 1989. The acronym "LED" stands for "Laser Enhanced Destruction". It is a vertical scrolling racing game. The player races across various courses, and can force other cars off the road or jump on top of them.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/madgear-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19891001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./metamrph.zip</path>
		<name>Metamorphic Force</name>
		<desc>The Evil King has risen from the dead to rule the world once more. The Greek goddess Athena has summoned the souls of four ancient guardians and bestowed their power upon four heroes to stop the evil once again. These guardians wield the ability to shift into anthropomorphic beasts to fight their enemies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/metamrph-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ninjemak.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja emaki</name>
		<desc>Ninja Emaki was produced by Nichibutsu in 1985.

Nichibutsu released 80 different machines in our database under this trade name, starting in 1979.

Other machines made by Nichibutsu during the time period Ninja Emaki was produced include Cop 01, Pastel Gal, MagMax, Dangar Ufo Robo, Youma Ninpou Chou, Roller Jammer, Tube Panic, Dacholer, Rug Rats, and Nichibutsu Hustler.

Game Play

A lot like Commando, but the game has a much more interesting landscape. Pick up scrolls that will give you a variety of high-powered weapons to fight your opponents. Boss stages are fairly challenging.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/ninjemak-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nichibutsu</developer>
		<publisher>Nichibutsu</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pandoras.zip</path>
		<name>Pandora's Palace</name>
		<desc>Taking on the role of a Roman emperor, replete with white robe and olive leaf head ornament, the player must make his or her way from the top left of the screen to the bottom right, via careful navigation of a variety of poles and moving platforms. Enemies can push the player character into fires or over the edge of platforms if they are not carefully avoided.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/pandoras-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./pirates.zip</path>
		<name>Pirates</name>
		<desc>Pirates was produced by NIX in 1994.

In the early '90s there was this arcade game called "Blood Bros".
This little fly-by-night company called Nix apparently decided to clone it, except to differentiate they gave it a pirate theme. So now, a male and female pirate get Engrishy orders from some pirate captain ("Treasure map is in pirate power! You brave and strong!"), and off they go to find pieces of this map that apparently leads to fabulous booty.

Their approach in this is to simply blow the hell out of numerous small towns, stopping only when their thirst for devastation is slaked (you never actually see them pick up a map piece). The view is from behind your pirate warriors, and the joystick moves them left and right while simultaneously maneuvering the reticule you use to aim your shots. You also have a limited supply of bombs you can lob, and a slide that makes you briefly invincible.

Since it clones a good game, the action here is actually reasonably fun, if a bit repetitive. The goal seems to be to blow up every possible structure on each screen, then kill enough pirates until your Bloodthirst Meter is satisfied. The thing that separates it from Wild Guns is the total zaniness of the design. Aside from blowing the crap out of whole town for no good reason, you see a lot of bizarre characters pop up, and everything in the field of play is fair game. In the first level, a barmaid randomly wanders out dispensing beers to everyone, then starts showing off her juggling skills for you ... shoot her down in cold blood and you get a 2000 point bonus. You get a similar bonus for brutally gunning down some society dame that wanders into the battle lost. Sometimes a cow will just wander across the screen at random - fill him full of lead for bonus weapons and bombs. Weapon upgrades include double automatic pistols and what appears to be a machine gun. And at the end of every three-level set you face bosses that include an airship, and even a Giant Enemy Crab.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/pirates-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nix</developer>
		<publisher>Nix</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./psychic5.zip</path>
		<name>Psychic 5</name>
		<desc>Excellent vertical maze type game. You can control five different characters, each with their own special powers. You need to change between them to complete each level. Features the ability to win a FREE game. If you hit the witch with the hammer you can fly through walls for a limited time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/psychic5-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./rockrage.zip</path>
		<name>Rock'n Rage</name>
		<desc>It's another sold out show for one of the world's greatest rock bands - but this night is far from ordinary! A strange force from another dimension has eyes for the band's sexy lead singer Sheena, and has chosen this night to make its move. And to ensure that it has Sheena all to itself, it's taking Sheena through various periods in history. With Sheena gone, her band could be history! It's up to two of Sheena's bandmates, John and Rick, to save their singing eye candy before disaster strikes!

Rock'n Rage is a 8-way scrolling fighter in which John and Rick must battle through five time periods to save the lead singer of their band from a cruel fate. During game play, our two intrepid rockers can break pots to find note guns that allow them to attack from a distance, and point items that increase players' current score. In addition to looking for a way out of the time period, John and Rick must also watch out for a special character (unique to each time period) that when found will give them a force field. At the exit to each time period, a boss awaits.

Players can rock alone, or team up with a buddy to save Sheena.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/rockrage-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./stlforce.zip</path>
		<name>Steel Force</name>
		<desc>Steel Force is a 2D top down arcade shooter, similar in style to Alien Breed, but much more action-oriented. The main hero, a Federation soldier fights against space pirates - he must kill various enemies and find the exit in limited time. He can find ammunition, health packs and various power ups along the way.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/stlforce-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ecogames S.L.</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Devices SRL Italy</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./s1945iii.zip</path>
		<name>Strikers 1945 III</name>
		<desc>Year 1999, fall. The countless super minimum machine group 'nano-machine', which came flying, invaded the principal weapon and military terminals of each country from outer space and began multiplication. This weapon group which is automated with the 'nano-machines' repeated attack with non discrimination and the metropoles of each country were in a devastating state. A fear of the extensive nuclear warfare with the strategy nuclear missile error morphism hit the world!!! Barely the unit of each country which prevents the invasion of the 'nano- machine' is summoned because of the unmanned weapon eradication maneuvers. So, fighting with the weapons of the entire world was not enough. The Strikers start the attack on the enemy center! By the way of the time of half a century, new legend of special force STRIKERS now starts!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/s1945iii-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./thedeep.zip</path>
		<name>The Deep</name>
		<desc>Similar to the classic Depthcharge, the player controls a profile view warship on the water surface, while most of the screen shows the depth of the sea, with elaborate backgrounds and populated by divers enemies. Two players can play simultaneously with two ships. As the screen scrolls continuously to the right, the ship can move back and forth and unclip lens depth charges from the bow or stern, that explode on contact. Ammunition are limited but are automatically recharged over time. The opponents include various types of submarines that arrive from both sides and firing missiles and mines to the surface; the bullets of the player and the enemy can destroy each other. They also face the end boss level in the form of huge underwater structures. The power-ups are capsules that go back to the surface.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/thedeep-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wood Place</developer>
		<publisher>Wood Place</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./thundfox.zip</path>
		<name>Thunder Fox</name>
		<desc>Thunder Fox is an arcade game created by Taito. It was released in arcades in 1990 and for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis in 1991. It was later released on various consoles such as the Xbox and PlayStation 2 in Taito Legends, a compilation of Taito classics.

The gameplay for Thunder Fox is similar to other popular side scrolling action games like Namco's Rolling Thunder, and Sega's Shinobi. There are three buttons for each player - Attack, which normally is used to make Thunder and Fox (the game's heroes) stab with their knives. Jump, and a Weapon button which fires or throws a weapon acquired by the heroes. What makes this game unique is that the game gives players the opportunity to allow players to use their obtained weapons (save for the hand grenades) as melee weapons which helps conserve ammunition for when it's needed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/thundfox-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tinklpit.zip</path>
		<name>Tinkle Pit</name>
		<desc>The player contols Pitt and Patti, who must walk around the mazes, collecting items and avoiding enemies. They have the power to drop their Tinker power balls, which are both invulnerable to the enemies, and move around by pressing the Line button, therefore creating a line between them and their power balls. Releasing the button makes their power balls come back to them; the enemies are killed by having the power balls slam into them. There are also pieces of popcorn which can be picked up around the mazes - and pressing the Popcorn button, Pitt and Patti can throw them at the enemies, and they shall bounce off the walls until they hit one (or evaporate if they have not done so by the end of the stage). 

Killing all enemies in a maze advances the player to the next stage; however, in the event of one enemy remaining, he will make for the nearest corner of the maze, say "Bye-bye!", and disappear - which will detract from the "Pursuit Bonus" that the players will receive after they defeat Mao at the end of the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/tinklpit-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nimco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./viostorm.zip</path>
		<name>Violent Storm</name>
		<desc>In The 1990s, World War III has at last expired. The people are left to pick up the pieces and rebuild their civilizations. However, vicious gangs that prey on these defenseless citizens are obstructing the reconstruction.

The main protagonists are Boris, Wade and Kyle, vigilantes who protect the feared and helpless. Their largest problem is the corrupt, incorrigible, ruthless and lethal gang known as "The Geld Gang". They have commissioned every type of person imaginable. Purple-haired, leather-clad, chain-wielding, lead-pipe swinging, masked, martial art, orange-mohawked and men so strong and immune to pain they use manhole covers as shields.

One day, when the trio is patrolling the streets, alert, ready and able to help those in need, they see a woman named Sheena (a friend of theirs) waving at them walking across the street out of a supermarket with groceries. A moment later, Lord Geld's right-hand man, Red Freddy, snatches her away while riding on his purple hog. Now, the three braves must save Sheena from the grips of Lord Geld.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/viostorm-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>3</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./viprp1.zip</path>
		<name>Viper Phase 1</name>
		<desc>By the year 2050, mankind begins the colonization of multiple solar systems in search for habitable planets. However, while the colonists establish original cultures and scientific studies, many of them began feuding with each other and battles broke out among them and the Earth. One rebel faction in particular rose to great power and made Earth their primary target. Earth's response was Operation Viper Phase 1: to combat the rebels using advanced space fighters built from downed enemy ships.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/viprp1-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950511T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEIBU KAIHATSU INC.</developer>
		<publisher>Fabtek</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./xybots.zip</path>
		<name>Xybots</name>
		<desc>Xybots is a 3-Dimensional, 3rd-person perspective shoot-em-up for 1 or 2 players. Taking on the role of either 'Major Rock Hardy' or 'Captain Ace Gunn' (in the 2-player game), players must shoot their way through a huge, multi-level underground city - made up of a series of mazes - and destroy the evil 'Xybot' robot warriors that have invaded the planet and established their underground fortress. The players' on-screen counterparts walk 'into' the screen and players must manually rotate the maze's viewpoint left and right when changing direction in order to be able to look in the direction they are moving. 

Each level has at least one exit that must be reached in order to progress to the next (some levels have extra hidden exits that 'warp' players to later levels). Players can find energy pods to restore energy levels, keys to open doors, and golden coins. Some of the levels also feature transporters that connect different parts of the same level.

At the end of each level, players can enter a shop where supplies and power-ups can be purchased with any coins they have collected. Some supplies, such as 'Shield' or 'Speed' are permanent, whereas others are only temporary and must be replenished.

A map of each level is displayed at the top of the screen. For some levels, all enemies, objects and walls are shown. On later levels, however, the map may only display the enemy robots and/or objects; with the maze walls and layout only becoming visible once a player has 'looked' at a wall section. Xybots' gameplay feels highly reminiscent of a 3-Dimensional "Gauntlet" (with good reason, see TRIVIA for more details). The game also uses a split-screen display to allow for two-player simultaneous play; something of an innovation for 1987.

Like the "Gauntlet" games on which Xybots is based; the game is endless and play will continue until all lives are lost and players no longer wish to use the 'Continue' option.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/xybots-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19871101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./noboranb.zip</path>
		<name>Noboranka</name>
		<desc>This game is a vertical scrolling shoot 'em up where the player controls a character that has to climb a tree and shoot bug-like enemies. The story is that the princess has been kidnapped by the villains of the Insect World, and Zippy Bug has to rescue her. After shooting the enemies, they drop fruits that the player can collect for extra points, and skulls that are deadly if touched. The player is able to fly for a short time, and every time this is done, one of the letters from the 'I Love You' at the bottom of the screen is used up. The letters regenerate over a small period of time.

There are also other items, such as the key, which surrounds the player in a bubble and makes him invulnerable to 1 hit. Another item is a ring which seems to instantly replenish all of the used up 'I Love You' letters. One other item is the hammer, which allows the player to wipe out all the enemies off the screen. There is a boss at the end of each level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/noboranb-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./outrun.zip</path>
		<name>Out Run</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/outrun-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./swcourt.zip</path>
		<name>Super World Court</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/swcourt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./battlnts.zip</path>
		<name>Battlantis</name>
		<desc>A vertical shoot-em-up. Protect the castle by moving a bowman horizontally across the bottom of the screen, shooting upwards at the assorted fantasy warriors who are advancing in waves. The game includes boss waves and has nice music.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/battlnts-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./chqflag.zip</path>
		<name>Chequered Flag</name>
		<desc>An overhead-view racing game featuring rotational sprite scaling. The player races over a series of twisting courses, trying to reach the finish line before the timer expires.

Chequered Flag includes a Pit-stop facility, a feature that had appeared a year earlier in Taito's 'Continental Circus'. Should the player's car sustain too much damage, a pit-stop must be made to implement repairs. A 'damage meter' at the bottom of the screen shows the severity of the damage; highlighting what car components are in need of repair; Engine, Front Tires, Rear Tires and Brakes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/chqflag-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./jackal.zip</path>
		<name>Jackal</name>
		<desc>The Jackal unit is an elite group of four soldiers that have undergone a harsh training regiment to survive in any environment. The team is composed of Colonel Decker, Lieutenant Bob, Sergeant Quint and Corporal Grey. They have been given a mission to drive two armed jeeps into hostile territory in order to rescue and extract POWs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/jackal-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19860627T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./jailbrek.zip</path>
		<name>Jail Break</name>
		<desc>Move your character, a policeman, through the streets firing on escaped convicts.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/jailbrek-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./junofrst.zip</path>
		<name>Juno First</name>
		<desc>Juno First is a shoot 'em up originally developed and published by Konami Corporation for Arcades. The game was later published by Mylstar Electronics (US arcades), Datasoft Inc. (Atari 8-bit, PC Booter, and Commodore 64), and Sony Computer Entertainment Japan (MSX).

Juno First is a top down, vertical scrolling shooter in which there is a limited amount of time to defeat the enemies in each wave.

The players spaceship starts out with a laser that has a longer reach than the enemy weapons. The enemies start out firing a few bullets at the ship but the amount enemy fire rapidly increases as players progress through to the next waves.

Certain enemies fire tracking missile-like projectiles that can shoot additional bullets.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/junofrst-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kicker.zip</path>
		<name>Kicker</name>
		<desc>Shao-lin's Road, released in certain markets as Kicker, is a 1985 beat 'em up video game released by Konami. The game was commercially successful, becoming a chart hit in the arcades. It was ported to several early home computers and has also been featured in classics compilations Konami Arcade Classics in 1998 and Konami Classics Series: Arcade Hits in 2007, and was released for Microsoft's Game Room in 2010.

Players take control of Wanpyou (renamed Kicker in Kicker, renamed Lee in other ports), who has just mastered the secret of Chin-style Shaolin martial arts. He then encounters the triad Yamucha Gang, also responsible for the assassination of his master Raochuu, and is trapped within their Jaken Temple. He attempts to escape and enact revenge with his new-found skills.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/kicker-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./megazone.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Zone</name>
		<desc>This game has flavors of several different video games rolled into one. It is mostly like Xevious, being an overhead shooter against a plethora of enemies, each with a unique characteristic. Unlike Xevious, however, that only allowed you to travel in one straight path, Mega Zone periodically allows you to choose different paths. For most of the game, the player's ship flies along a river. When the river forks, the player has the option of following either fork.

The game also has elements of Scramble, in that the player fights through numerous zones in the struggle to reach the end. Where Scramble has a progress bar at the top, Mega Zone gives the player a map, and shows the player the progress along the map between lives. The main enemies of Mega Zone are giant robot eyeballs. Easily enough destroyed, they still pose a menace. Smaller eyeballs leave teardrops when destroyed, which when picked up, give bonus points and wipe out all enemies on the screen.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/megazone-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19831001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./timeplt.zip</path>
		<name>Time Pilot</name>
		<desc>Time Pilot is a multi-directional scrolling shooter and free-roaming aerial combat arcade game designed by Yoshiki Okamoto, released by Konami in 1982, and distributed in the United States by Centuri. Debuting in the golden age of video arcade games, it is a time travel themed game that allowed the player's plane to freely move across open air space that can scroll indefinitely in all directions.

The Killer List of Videogames included Time Pilot in its list of top 100 arcade games of all time.

The player assumes the role of a pilot of a futuristic fighter jet, trying to rescue fellow pilots trapped in different time eras. The player must fight off hordes of enemy craft and defeat the mother ship (or "boss") present in every level. The background moves in the opposite direction to the player's plane, rather than the other way around; the player's plane always remains in the center.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/timeplt-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Centuri</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./tp84.zip</path>
		<name>Time Pilot '84</name>
		<desc>Time Pilot '84: Further Into Unknown World is an eight-way scrolling shoot 'em up, released in 1984 by Konami. It is the sequel to Time Pilot. The player pilots a craft over many time periods. Unlike the original which told the year of each level, the new time periods are designated by new enemies and different colors.

There are a large number of enemy types in the game. They each have varying movement patterns, difficulty, and point values. The first button is used to fire a standard shot, which can destroy green-colored enemies. The second button is used to fire missiles, which can destroy the silver-colored enemies. You need to lock on to a silver enemy to fire missiles at it. Destroying enough green enemies brings out a large silver "boss" enemy that must be dispatched before advancing to the next level.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/mame/tp84-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
