<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Astro Boy - Omega Factor.zip</path>
		<name>Astro Boy: Omega Factor</name>
		<desc>Join Astro, the robotic superhero with a human mind, in a quest to reunite the robotic race with humans. Astro uses his seven super abilities to face off against the likes of Atlas, Blue Knight, and more than 40 other characters. The game brings classic 2D gaming to the Game Boy Advance along with an original seven-episode story. Playing as Astro Boy, you'll learn about justice, compassion, evil, courage, and the history of Astro Boy--all while building Astro's Omega Factor and strengthening his character and superhuman abilities.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Astro Boy - Omega Factor-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040817T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170213T044104</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow</name>
		<desc>The year is 2035 and Soma Cruz is about to witness the first solar eclipse of the 21st century when he suddenly blacks out -- only to awaken inside a mysterious castle. As Soma, you must navigate the castle's labyrinths while confronting perilous monsters at every turn. But beware, you must escape before the evil consumes you!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Aria of Sorrow-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>8</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T004940</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Circle of the Moon.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Circle of the Moon</name>
		<desc>Count Dracula has been resurrected and evil will reign supreme unless he is stopped. As Nathan Graves, you'll hunt down the count and use your whip and a variety of special items to destroy his minions. Battle your way through Dracula's castle and rid the world of evil once and for all!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Circle of the Moon-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEK</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170216T233828</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CT Special Forces.zip</path>
		<name>CT Special Forces</name>
		<desc>As part of the Counter-Terrorist Special Forces unit, you have all the necessary means for putting an end to the threat of terrorism. Your team comprises highly trained soldiers who can do anything from dressing in camouflage to initiating surgical strikes on the enemy. In both ground missions and air combat, you'll plunge into 12 levels that span jungles, cities, mountains, and deserts. You can equip your team with various state-of-the-art weapons, including assault rifles and rocket launchers. Multiplayer mode lets you team up with a friend to complete missions.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/CT Special Forces-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>LSP</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CT Special Forces - Back to Hell.zip</path>
		<name>CT Special Forces: Back to Hell</name>
		<desc>Despite their latest failures, the CT Special Forces unit is called upon once again to diffuse increased terrorist activity around the globe. Armed with high-tech weaponry and equipment, you must thwart the plans of terrorist groups and ensure peace in several regions of the world. You'll have access to an array of vehicles and weapons, including shotguns, bazookas, sniper rifles, and more. CT Special Forces 2 lets you prove your combat skills in a variety of single-player and multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/CT Special Forces - Back to Hell-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20040629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LSP</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DK - King of Swing.zip</path>
		<name>DK: King of Swing</name>
		<desc>The normally quiet jungle is abuzz with excitement, because it's time for the ceremony to choose the king of the jungle! Or at least it would be if King K. Rool hadn't stolen the special medallion meant for the winner. Donkey Kong and his friends must swing their way through the jungle to get the medallion back and, along the way, rescue Diddy, Dixie, and Funky Kong from King K. Rool's minions. A unique control system lets you swing through the trees and spin to build up momentum for a mighty leap. Innovative level design combines elements of platform and puzzle games: Grab gears and spin to crank doors open. Watch out for bolts that loosen as you spin, or you might find yourself falling flat. You'll need steady hands to make the leap-of-faith that takes you to the treetops.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/DK - King of Swing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paon Corporation</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics Advance.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics Advance</name>
		<desc>The world of Final Fantasy returns to Game Boy Advance.Final Fantasy Tactics Advance is a deeply diverse strategy and tactics game with battles, missions, swords, and magic.Players assume the role of young Marche Radiuju in the humble burg of St. Ivalice.Alone in a foreign world, Marche befriends a motley crew of low-level monks, mages, archers, and soldiers.The only hope you have of finding your way home is to turn your ragtag group of misfits into a finely tuned fighting force.As you gain experience and reputation, your job options grow as well as the rewards.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fantasy Tactics Advance-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight One.zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight One</name>
		<desc>Classic arcade action is unleased on the Game Boy&amp;reg; Advance system in Final Fight One. There's trouble in Metro City. The members of the Mad Gear Gang have kidnapped the mayor's daughter Jessica and the clock is ticking. The mayor, an ex-street fighter himself, calls in the big guns to help, enlisting the iron fist team of Cody and Guy. Now, it's a race against time to scour the city, defeat an army of the Mad Gear Gang's minions, and rescue Jessica before it's too late!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Final Fight One-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sun-Tec</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun.zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun</name>
		<desc>In a dark time, an epic adventure begins as evil slowly envelops the world! The forces of darkness are pursuing the lost art of Alchemy, and as they draw ever closer to their foul purpose, mankind's future hangs in the balance. You and your companions are the last hope: armed with noble weapons, mysterious Psynergy and a host of elemental creatures, you must find a way to stem the evil tide. Your ordinary life is over, as a Golden Sun rises above you and forever broadens your horizon!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - The Lost Age.zip</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: The Lost Age</name>
		<desc>It is the dawn of a new age...And the heroes of Golden Sun have been abandoned. Now, the world is falling into darkness. A new band of adventurers is the world's final hope...but they may also be its doom. Pursued by the heroes of the original Golden Sun, they must race to complete their quest before the world becomes lost to the ages.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Golden Sun - The Lost Age-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20030414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunstar Future Heroes.zip</path>
		<name>Gunstar Future Heroes</name>
		<desc>Gunstar Super Heroes is the sequel to the classic Genesis game Gunstar Heroes. You can play as Red or Blue as you battle through six levels, employing one of three different weapon types. Each character has a slightly different story and balance, adding variety to the 2D platformer gameplay. Gunstar Super Heroes features large bosses and pseudo-3D effects that maximize the graphics capabilities of the Game Boy Advance.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Gunstar Future Heroes-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King Kong - The Official Game of the Movie.zip</path>
		<name>King Kong: The Official Game of the Movie</name>
		<desc>Solve challenging puzzles as you play Jack, Ann, and Carl. Battle planes, tanks, and more as the colossal beast King Kong. Survive savage creature battles deep in the perilous jungle. Includes Bonus Map.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/King Kong - The Official Game of the Movie-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20051121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3 Upper.zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<desc>Capcom unleashes the biggest and brightest star in the Street Fighter&amp;reg; universe on the Game Boy&amp;reg; Advance system. Street Fighter Alpha 3 stars over 31 characters and is loaded with multiple modes of play, seamless animation and 3 different fighting styles for every character. Street Fighter Alpha 3 puts arcade fighting in the palm of your hand!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Street Fighter Alpha 3 Upper-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Crawfish Interactive</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ghouls N Ghosts.zip</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
		<desc>As dauntless knight Arthur you are caught up in the most dangerous of quests! A spell has been cast upon the kingdom. Your fair maiden, Princess Prin Prin has been snatched up by the evil emperor. Only as Arthur can you get her back from the creatures of the undead that haunt the land. Test your courage and skill to the limit. You must keep up the quest. On your journey, your mightiest weapon of all awaits you... MAGIC!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Ghouls N Ghosts-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20020923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Affect</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Advance.zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance</name>
		<desc>Mario's Game Boy Advance debut gives gamers two games in one: an enhanced version of Super Mario Bros. 2 and an action-packed four-player version of the original Mario Bros. arcade game.First released for the original NES in 1988, Super Mario Bros. 2 makes its debut on the Game Boy Advance with new enemies, improved graphics, and tougher challenges.Mario, Luigi, Peach, and Toad adventure through seven fantasy worlds on a quest to save the day, though they have little more than vegetables for defense.New challenges include collecting red coins and finding Yoshi's hidden eggs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Mario Advance-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter II Turbo - Revival.zip</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II Turbo: Revival</name>
		<desc>Capcom's timeless Street Fighter&amp;reg; masterpiece conquers the Game Boy&amp;reg; Advance system. Choose from over 16 brawlers from the Street Fighter universe and execute special moves, and super combos to wreak havoc on your opponent and become the best street fighter in the world. Lightning fast animation, unbelievable graphics and Capcom's signature gameplay make Super Street Fighter II Turbo the most respected fighting game of all time.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Super Street Fighter II Turbo - Revival-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of Mana.zip</path>
		<name>Sword of Mana</name>
		<desc>Fans of Secret of Mana have waited over ten years for a successor to Square's SNES role-playing game, and now it's here.Sword of Mana shares the art style and action-oriented gameplay of its predecessor, but boasts a huge game environment, a new gripping storyline, and a deep class and upgrade system.You'll choose between playing a man or a female hero and slay enemies to upgrade your abilities.Sword of Mana blends its fast action and depth with classic RPG style and fun.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Sword of Mana-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land 4.zip</path>
		<name>Wario Land 4</name>
		<desc>Hey! You! Yeah, you! Listen up when Wario's talking to you! I just read about this legendary Pyramid of Gold, and you're gonna help me go explore it. There's lots of treasure in there for the taking, and I want it all. I'm sure there are gonna be all kinds of weird enemies and big, bad bosses in there, so if you don't think you can hack it, put the game down now. I don't want any losers making me jump into bottomless pits, you hear me?</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Wario Land 4-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20011118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance.zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Harmony of Dissonance</name>
		<desc>Nearly fifty years has past since Simon Belmont rescued the land from the curse of Dracula. Now, Simon's descendant Juste Belmont, must acquire the relics of Dracula to unravel the disappearance of his childhood friend Lydie. The castle's enchanting mysteries and danger await all those who dare enter.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Castlevania - Harmony of Dissonance-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami TYO</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CT Special Forces - Bioterror.zip</path>
		<name>CT Special Forces 3: Navy Ops</name>
		<desc>Game Boy Advance brings CT SPECIAL FORCES 3: NAVY OPS to fans of vertical action combat game play. A special military unit called the Special Intervention Forces has but a single mission- to do away with all terrorist organizations and other menacing threats. The latest threat has to do with the fact that the enemy has in their possession a biochemical weapon that alters human DNA. They have used this chemical to strengthen hostility and athletic genes to produce an original species of insurgent. The Counter Terrorist Special Intervention Forces are the only ones who possess the strength and skill to crush this new adversary. Each player is responsible for controlling his or her member of the CT Special Forces, as each mission becomes increasingly difficult. In the latest threat of terrorism, the need for underwater soldiers has become a necessity. With scuba diving skills, the player can explore several underwater regions. Combat takes place in both the water and on land, so the game presents the player with a number of vehicle and weaponry options. Each skill is the most sophisticated available and designed to seek out and destroy the enemy. The game takes the player through 20 levels that test, challenge and drive the Special Forces towards victory. Fans of combat action games with a patriotic tone must try this intense game.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/CT Special Forces - Bioterror-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LSP</developer>
		<publisher>LSP</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League.zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League</name>
		<desc>Dr. Mario/Puzzle League are recreations of two of Nintendo's most popular puzzle creations. Though Dr. Mario has already been released on the GBA as a Classic NES Series title, the version included in the dual-pack is enhanced specifically for the Game Boy Advance hardware instead of a straight emulation of the original NES title. Puzzle League was originally brought to life as Tetris Attack, but then rebranded on the Game Boy Color as Pokemon Puzzle Challenge a few years back. The GBA version is also enhanced for the GBA's much more capable graphics hardware.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Dr. Mario &amp; Puzzle League-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Ball - Advanced Adventure.zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball: Advanced Adventure</name>
		<desc>Join Goku® in his very first epic adventure as he defends the earth from the relentless Red Ribbon Army. Start down his path to power, and help turn an ordinary boy into the ultimate champion.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Dragon Ball - Advanced Adventure-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20060606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Go! Go! Beckham! - Adventure on Soccer Island.zip</path>
		<name>Go! Go! Beckham! Adventure on Soccer Island</name>
		<desc>Go! Go! Beckham! Adventure on Soccer Island is an Action game, developed by Denki and published by Rage Software, which was released in Europe in 2002.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Go! Go! Beckham! - Adventure on Soccer Island-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denki</developer>
		<publisher>Rage Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hajime no Ippo - The Fighting!.zip</path>
		<name>Hajime No Ippo - The Fighting!</name>
		<desc>Boxing game based on the Japanese anime of the same name.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Hajime no Ippo - The Fighting!-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20021213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>ESP</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters EX2.zip</path>
		<name>King of Fighters EX 2: Howling Blood</name>
		<desc>The latest portable fighting masterpiece in one of the greatest series of all time!</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/King of Fighters EX2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc.zip</path>
		<name>Rayman 3</name>
		<desc>Rayman 3 (Game Boy Advance) is a portable version of the console game of the same name which was released for the Game Boy Advance in 2003. It is the first handheld Rayman game to feature multiplayer modes which made use of the Game Boy Advance/GameCube link cable, to link to the GameCube version. It is a 2D side-scrolling game with elements from Rayman, Rayman 2, and Rayman 3, though it is mostly centered around the story of Rayman 2. It is thought that it was originally developed as a Game Boy Advance version of Rayman 2, and that its Rayman 3 elements were added late in its development so that it could be marketed as a Game Boy Advance version of Rayman 3.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Rayman 3 - Hoodlum Havoc-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20030304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scurge - Hive.zip</path>
		<name>Scurge: Hive</name>
		<desc>What does not destroy you makes you stronger... Eclipse transports players to a world teetering between salvation and oblivion. After a recent attack on a bioresearch facility a new life form has awakened with no memories or sense of identity. Unravel the mystery of Aletha’s origin as she discovers her role in the facility's research. With seemingly limitless potential, Aletha must absorb the mysterious force known as bioenergy from defeated enemies in order to evolve, escape and survive.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Scurge - Hive-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20061024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Orbital Media</developer>
		<publisher>SouthPeak Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shonen Jump's - One Piece.zip</path>
		<name>Shonen Jump's One Piece</name>
		<desc>You can try to grab the greatest treasure of them all, the "one piece," in One Piece: Grand Battle. This pirate action game is based on the TV series One Piece, and it lets you play as Monkey D. Luffy and more than 16 other playable characters. There are six game modes for you to play with either one or two players. You can unlock new characters, costumes, and minigames and collect powerful items as you progress through the game and explore the interactive environments from the TV show.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Shonen Jump's - One Piece-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20050907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SMA4 - Super Mario Bros. 3 (e-reader levels).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Advance 4: Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<desc>THE MARIO BROS. AT THEIR BEST!

The best-selling game of all time has arrived for Game Boy Advance, now with all-new features! Mario’s not alone! This time around, Luigi can get in on the action!

Link up with any Super Mario Advance game for multiplayer Mario Bros. madness! Use wild power-ups like the Super Leaf and the Frog and Tanooki Suits!

EVEN MORE MARIO FUN IS IN THE CARDS! LINK UP AND USE AN E-READER AND SPECIAL CARDS TO ADD CLASSIC AND UPDATED MARIO LEVELS, ALL-NEW LEVELS, AND INCREDIBLY HARD “SUPER” LEVELS, THAT YOU CAN SAVE TO YOUR GAME PAK. THERE ARE ALSO POWER-UP CARDS, DEMO CARDS WITH PRO TECHNIQUES, AND MUCH MORE! (e-Reader and e-Reader cards sold separately.)

BONUS LEVEL CARD AND POWER-UP CARD INCLUDED!</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/SMA4 - Super Mario Bros. 3 (e-reader levels)-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20031021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<desc>Be your favorite Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle and master your ninja skills in their action-packed world. Roam NYC streets, scour underground sewers and fight your way across rooftops on a collision course with The Shredder and his vile pack of foot ninjas. Find scrolls to unlock special attack moves and effects. Interact with characters from the animated television series, such as Splinter and Casey Jones. Don't hide in your shell--be a hero.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20031031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.zip</path>
		<name>TMNT</name>
		<desc>Over the top Ninja Action!

Use acrobatic moves and extreme fighting skills to unite the Turtles and save the City. Use special weapons, such as deadly ninja starts, and unique tag-team moves. Play the famous TMNT characters, each with his own fighting style. Take on the big bosses from the TMNT movie.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/TMNT - Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20070320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok Evolution.zip</path>
		<name>Turok: Evolution</name>
		<desc>The game begins with the seer, Tarkeen, explaining the history of the Lost Lands which had, for years, been fought over by tyrannic warlords.

On earth during the old west, Tal'Set faces off his enemy, Captain Bruckner and succeeds in cutting off his arm, but both of them are sucked into a wormhole. Tal'Set is nearly killed and the people of the River Village, who found him, call upon Tarkeen to heal him. Tarkeen then commands them to bring Tal'Set to him. He is sent into the jungle and kills enemy factions, lizard-like enemies known as the Sleg, that are close to the Village. Tal'Set hooks up with Genn, a pilot from the Village, who will be guiding him to the seer. Along the way, he uses the Pterosaur to evict the Sleg from the jungle and destroy their air ship.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Turok Evolution-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20020826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RFX Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Hominid.zip</path>
		<name>Alien Hominid</name>
		<desc>He's been shot at, shot down, stolen from and probed. It's time to get even.

The game is a side-scrolling shooter in a similar vein to games like Metal Slug, where one hit instantly kills, and can be played simultaneously with one or two players. Players play as the titular hominid who has to fend off waves of secret agents. His main arsenal is a blaster, while players can also melee close-up enemies and use a limited number of grenades. Advanced moves include rolling under shots, jumping on and biting off enemies' heads, temporarily scaring other enemies, and digging underground and dragging enemies down with them.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Alien Hominid-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tuna</developer>
		<publisher>Zoo Digital Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T055300</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game &amp; Watch Gallery 4.zip</path>
		<name>Game &amp; Watch Gallery 4</name>
		<desc>Relive the birth of handheld gaming with over a dozen classic Game &amp; Watch games. Picture-perfect versions reproduce all the fast-paced action of the original games, and new modern versions bring these games into the 21st century with improved graphics, sound, and game play!</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Game &amp; Watch Gallery 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20021028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tose</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170305T033432</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror</name>
		<desc>Once again, Kirby must save the kingdom from evil. But this time he'll need some backup. As Kirby, you can call up one of four alter egos for help during your quest. Each character features new copy abilities that range from arrow-shooting to melee moves. Practice your skills in new side games, such as Crackity Hack and Speed Eaters. In addition to new abilities and subgames, Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror also introduces new multiplayer modes.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kirby &amp; the Amazing Mirror-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flagship</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land.zip</path>
		<name>Kirby: Nightmare in Dreamland</name>
		<desc>When King Dedede steals the Star Rod, it's up to Kirby to recover the fragmented pieces from Triple D's underlings and restore power to the Fountain of Dreams. Kirby: Nightmare in Dream Land is an action-packed side-scrolling adventure chock full of awesome copy abilities and fast-moving gameplay. Kirby may not look tough, but he can float over dangerous obstacles, eat enemy projectiles, and copy his enemies' abilities. You can use these skills in the single-player story mode or multiplayer mode with up to three friends using the Game Boy Advance Link cable.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Kirby - Nightmare in Dream Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa 2 - Dream Champ Tournament.zip</path>
		<name>Klonoa 2: Dream Champ Tournament</name>
		<desc>Floppy-eared hero Klonoa returns in another fast-paced, colorful side-scrolling adventure for the Game Boy Advance. In his latest challenge, Klonoa must race against time and other dream travelers in the Dream Champ Tournament to collect stars, sun and moon stones to become the ultimate Dream Champion. Combining platform, puzzle and adventure elements, Klonoa 2: Dream Champ Tournament is just the adventure fans of the series have been anticipating. Explore the intricate and puzzle-packed worlds where you’ll meet a wide variety of interesting creatures! Solve Fiendishly-Designed Puzzles 

- Use Boxes, Bomb Boxes, Switches, Pressure Switches, Goomis, Springs and Scales in your quest for glory. Hoverboard Races
- Each world contains a fast-paced thrill ride of gem collecting fun! Master your Skills to Win 
- Klonoa must prove his skills against other dream travelers in the Dream Champ Tournament.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Klonoa 2 - Dream Champ Tournament-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa - Empire of Dreams.zip</path>
		<name>Klonoa: Empire of Dreams</name>
		<desc>A grumpy Emperor suffering from insomnia has banned dreaming and imprisoned Klonoa for breaking the law. To prove his courage and win his freedom, Klonoa must defeat the monsters that are creating havoc throughout the empire. Help our hero in his most perilous journey yet and experience the all-new thrills!</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Klonoa - Empire of Dreams-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi Superstar Saga.zip</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Superstar Saga</name>
		<desc>An evil witch has replaced Princess Peach's fair speech with explosives! Mario and Luigi must once again come to her rescue, but this time they employ the help of Bowser, their sworn enemy. Mario and Luigi must learn new moves and combine powers to fight off enemies and move closer to the witch's castle. Guide this unlikely bunch through an abundance of minigames such as Border Jump and Mystery Carts. Combine the powers of Mario and Luigi to pull off special tag-team moves. Immerse yourself in this bright, cartoonish, and humorous world, complete with hit music featured in previous Mario games.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario &amp; Luigi Superstar Saga-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlphaDream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170218T134310</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart - Super Circuit.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Kart: Super Circuit</name>
		<desc>Whoever hands out driver's licenses in the Mushroom Kingdom is about to be in some serious trouble. Classic Mario Kart action is back once again, this time in a colorful, lightning-fast game that you can take anywhere. Mario, Luigi, Peach, Toad, Wario, Yoshi, and Bowser are all tearing up the track, tossing Koopa Shells and laying banana peels along the way. Mario Kart: Super Circuit puts your driving skills to the test on 40 tracks, each littered with wild weapons and obstacles. Four players can compete in Mario Kart: Super Circuit using only one Game Pak. If each player has a copy of the game, bonus features and new modes of play become available.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Kart - Super Circuit-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis - Power Tour.zip</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis: Power Tour</name>
		<desc>Players can test their backhand in this unique role-playing tennis adventure. Train hard at the Royal Tennis Academy to be a champion. Gain experience and improve your skills through lessons and tournaments, and rise to the top of the ranks. Play as Mario, Peach, Waluigi, or Donkey Kong in a slew of wild modes. Advance through the story and unlock even more characters, all with their own power moves. Beat Mario at his own game, then link up with a friend or three for even more frantic fun.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Tennis - Power Tour-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong.zip</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong</name>
		<desc>After years of apparent goodwill, Mario and Donkey Kong are at it again--this time, on Game Boy Advance. Donkey Kong has stolen all the Mini-Mario toys from the Mario Toy Co., and now it's up to Mario to hunt down his longtime nemesis and retrieve the pilfered goods. As Mario, you must race through challenging levels while finding keys and releasing Mini Marios before time runs out. Along the way, you'll master new moves that can help you overcome new puzzles.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario vs. Donkey Kong-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20040524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor - Infiltrator.zip</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor: Infiltrator</name>
		<desc>Medal of Honor Infiltrator puts you in the role of Corporal Jake Murphy, a man who must complete five daring missions to defeat the Axis powers in WWII. From sabotaging enemy resources to capturing key personnel to all-out firefights, you'll need to master a variety of gameplay styles to overcome the enemy. On foot, in a tank, or even in disguise, you must engage opponents on the battlefield with an assortment of WWII-era weapons, including machine guns, grenades, bazookas, and more.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Medal of Honor - Infiltrator-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20031117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Netherock</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Zero.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero</name>
		<desc>It's your mission to help the exiled scientist Ciel discover the source of a new reploid energy! Play as Mega Man's pal Zero, the reploid from the Mega Man X series turned good by the infectious Sigma Virus and 100 years of sleep. Conquer your adversaries and find the energy source... or risk ultimate defeat. It's up to you to defend good from the destructive powers in the universe.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Zero-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20020426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170217T002743</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Zero 2.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 2</name>
		<desc>In Zero's next mission, he falls prey to a trap set by Neo Arcadia's ruthless commander. Planning to trick Zero, he tries to use him to wreak chaos between reploids and humans once again. But, can he succeed?</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Zero 2-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20030502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Zero 3.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 3</name>
		<desc>It's the third chapter in the Mega Man Zero action adventure series for the Game Boy Advance. Featuring a new customization system, you can now equip Zero, with a combination of chips that will affect both his attributes and abilities, allowing you to adapt him to different challenges. Among his other new skills, Zero will now have weapon called the recoil rod. Now be jumps at double his normal height. These new skills will allow our hero to march into Arcadia to defeat the evil Omega single-handedly ... Or will they?</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Zero 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20040423T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Megaman Zero 4.zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero 4</name>
		<desc>The Zero Knuckle... the baddest new tool in Zero's arsenal lets you steal enemies' weapons and use them in battle. Employ this along with countless other cool moves to fight the Neo Arcadian army, defeat the evil Dr. Weil and help the caravan of humans reach the peace and security of Area Zero.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Megaman Zero 4-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20050421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug Advance.zip</path>
		<name>Metal Slug Advance</name>
		<desc>Now you can have all the 2D arcade action of Metal Slug in the palm of your hand, because Metal Slug Advance has arrived on the Game Boy Advance. Through five action-packed missions, you must move out on foot or in slug vehicles across rugged terrain and underwater bases. Your objective is to rescue hostages by destroying enemies and solving strategic puzzles. Completing your missions becomes easier when you collect more than 100 types of E-cards, which enhance your character's abilities.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metal Slug Advance-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Fusion.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid Fusion</name>
		<desc>Samus Aran returns in an all-new Metroid adventure!

While lending mission support on planet SR388, interstellar bounty hunter Samus Aran is attacked by an X parasite, an organism with the ability to mimic the abilities of any creature it infects. Near death, Samus is saved by a vaccine made from the DNA of the last Metroid -- the X parasite's only natural predator. When the X spread to a research station in orbit around SR388, a weakened Samus is forced to exterminate them all ... or die trying.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Fusion-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo Research &amp; Development 1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170216T235134</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid - Zero Mission.zip</path>
		<name>Metroid: Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>The full story of Samus Aran's first mission finally unfolds...

The first Metroid game just scratched the surface of the cataclysmic events on planet Zebes, and at long last the rest of the tale has come to light. Experience the first of Samus's legendary adventures through all-new cut-scenes and action sequences as the bounty hunter races through the deeps toward her showdown with the leader of the Space Pirates. But will the end of Mother Brain really mean the end of the story...?</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid - Zero Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20170216T233340</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster House.zip</path>
		<name>Monster House</name>
		<desc>Oh no! Old man Nebbercracker's house is eating anything and anyone who gets near it, and Halloween is almost here! So grab your Water Blaster, gather up your courage, and get ready to explore the Monster House™ to find out its secrets.

Monster House is an action-adventure game developed by Artificial Mind and Movement and published by THQ. The game is based on the film of the same name.

Although the game was marketed toward the same pre-teen audience as the accompanying film, its gameplay was highly reminiscent of Resident Evil 4; the game was generally higher-quality than many other games based on children's films, and it received high ratings from numerous prominent gaming magazines and websites, including Play magazine and GameZone.

Monster House was met with mixed reviews. Aggregating review websites GameRankings and Metacritic gave the Game Boy Advance version 66.50% and 69/100, the GameCube version 65.13% and 60/100,  the DS version 63.65% and 62/100 and the PlayStation 2 version 60.64% and 59/100.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Monster House-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20060718T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind and Movement</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mother 3.zip</path>
		<name>Mother 3</name>
		<desc>Welcome to the World of Mother 3.

The Nowhere Islands are an idyllic place; the residents of Tazmily Village live peacefully and in harmony with nature and with each other. But this all changes when the mysterious Pigmask Army arrives and proceeds to destroy and corrupt, with force and sly persuasion alike. Lucas and his friends must find out who wants to destroy the tranquility of Nowhere Islands and turn them into a high-tech nightmare.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mother 3-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo, HAL Laboratory | Brownie Brown</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Five-0.zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Five-O</name>
		<desc>Take on the role of Ninja Five-O as he uses all his skill, stealth and magic to rescue hostages and defeat his enemies. Master the art of ninja swords, shuriken throwing stars and ancient ninjitsu magic!

* Kaginawa Wire grappling hook that can be used to hang, fly, jump, climb walls and surprise attack.
* 6 Challenging missions covering 20 levels.
* Crush objects to find hidden Power-Ups and secret items
* Unique enemy boss characters for each level.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ninja Five-0-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia - The Sands of Time.zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time</name>
		<desc>Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is a 3D platformer which focuses on acrobatics and agility. Throughout much of the game, the player must attempt to traverse the palace by running across walls, ascending or descending chasms by jumping back and forth between walls, avoiding traps, climbing structures and jumping from platform to platform, making other types of well-timed leaps, solving puzzles, and using discovered objects to progress.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Prince of Persia - The Sands of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>20031028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - The Minish Cap.zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: The Minish Cap</name>
		<desc>Link returns in an all-new Game Boy Advance adventure. When the sorcerer Vaati turns Princess Zelda to stone, the king of Hyrule sends Link on a quest that takes him to all-new locations. Using the power of a mystical hat called the Minish Cap, Link must travel through a fantastic world rife with new items, puzzles, and bosses. As Link, you can shrink down to either battle large enemies from within or find secret items. You can also unlock items and solve puzzles by fusing together magic relics.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Legend of Zelda, The - The Minish Cap-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lara Croft Tomb Raider - The Prophecy.zip</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: The Prophecy</name>
		<desc>Lara Croft discovers a manuscript which speaks of a mysterious occult magic which will bring desolation on earth in the near future. This prophecy also talks of three legendary stones which are linked with the mentioned devastation. Fascinated, Lara travels around the globe in search of these fabled stones. Along the way she'll meet enemies both human and otherwise and will also have to deal with dark magic of sorts.

Lara is now in a "quasi-3D" overhead environment, as opposed to the 2D-platformer view of the previous handheld (GBC) versions. This view proves helpful while Lara runs, jumps, shimmys, and shoots around. Although there is lack of a save feature, there is a password system which lets you restore back to 'almost' where you left.</desc>
		<image>/home/joe/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - The Prophecy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
